I don't say how are you all this evening
of your time as you create time to
exist as we have said last week of your
time this interaction shall be entitled entitled
tune
matara Christmas
bells as you would say in your language
and we will tell a
Story Katani Matara story of the Essani
world spirit spirit
shakana
tapune world spirit bell Christmas bell
in your language world spirit we have
discussed many times with you that which
you call your Christ consciousness which
has been known by many names upon your
planet to our perspective is the world
spirit that which represents the
collective consciousness of each and
every individual. It is known in many
individual. It is known in many
different various themes, many different
forms of expression and they are all
true. For by definition, the world
spirit is a multiaceted and
multi-dimensional multidirectional
being. You have had the idea of a
scenario. Your world spirit played out
upon your planet in many ways at various
times in your
history. And in our world, we have had
the idea of our world spirit, our
shakana played
out similarly, not identical, but
similarly to
yours. And in this the full story of
this idea, we will relate this evening
of your
time. What might loosely translate if
you wish into an Asani Christmas
story? Now you have had speaking
strictly specifically of the idea of
what you call tri consciousness the idea
of the manifestation in one of the forms
in your physiological forms for
approximately 33 years of your
accounting in the format you call the
one of the ways one of the phases one of
the manifestation of the world spirit in
that way in our
way in our
civilization there was also as we have
said briefly
for a manifestation to some degree
physiologically of the world's spirit.
But only did it last in terms of Calving
3 days rather than 33 years as you
understand I for that was all that was
necessary for the unification and the
awakening and the recognition of our
collective consciousness into one
unified direction. Now the
Now the
idea if you would in that sense give
your participation will occur in the
participation will occur in the
following
format. May I have requested that this
day of your time you bring a bell of
your choice. Do you have them?
choice. Do you have them?
Thank you.
The idea therefore shall be there will
be a few places within the story that
will relate to you where the word
vibration will come up precisely in that
manner. When we say that word vibration [Music]
For a count of
three, every time that word comes up,
allow yourselves to give of that
vibration which will add to the energy
of
unification to the
story. For the count of three, ring your
bell when we say
vibration and then we will continue. It
will happen three
times within the
story. It shall begin as
follows. Our world has had
history not exactly like your own, but
there have been
similarities. And there was a time when
we had arrived at what you would call
the end of the experimentation and the
exploration of the cycle of living in
diversified communities that you would
call most similarly nations upon your
planet. We did not have the rigidity of
the borders that you have. But
nonetheless, we had undertaken many
different experiments and many different
styles of living to determine that which
would represent to us all of what you
would call the best out of each style of
life that could be applied towards the
idea of one direction in the
world with our hearts and our minds and
our souls, our
spirits and our bodies.
We arrived at a point in our
history where the
desire for the unification of our planet
in that way truly manifested in the phys
theological representation of the world
spirit born as you would say into
physicality as a
child over the course of what you would
call 7 month gestation
period. and the
idea upon the rendering the focus of the
world's spirit into that physical
spirit into that physical
manifestation in our
society of Sissonyi flesh as you
say of Cissani mind of Cani
spirit that became for three
days a
threefold experience
As this child was born in our language
shakana, the world's spirit
physicalized, crystallized, focused and
manifested, pinpointed into our physical
dimension, a sleep came upon the entire
planet. Now before this time in our society we
Now before this time in our society we
had the notion that you understand that
sleep that reconnection to the higher
self the realignment through dream
reality of all that you know yourself to
be. And so upon the first day of this
physical manifestation of chakana a
profound sleep came upon the entire
planet all at once and all drifted into
a dream into a
slumber into an energy sea.
And the first day was spent in a unified
world dream. A dream that all of our spirit,
dream. A dream that all of our spirit,
all the energy, all of our
knowingness was
one. And as we merged and blended into
this world dream, Shakana did
vibrate. the
vibration. And all that were asleep in
the dream did feel the energy coursing
through every soul, every spirit in a
ripple around the planet and were
unified in spirit in the dream.
And they dreamed
on through the second day, still asleep
in a world
dream. And as they now experience the
unification of spirit from the highest
levels, there was more focus, more
crystallization as these energies
spiraled downward into more and more
physical materiality.
And the mind in that sense, the emotion
of all the beings upon the planet began
to draw itself together through a
profound gravity. And as they merged not only
gravity. And as they merged not only
their soul but their heart, their mind
and truly perceived all to be existing
within an energy sea. Shakana did
vibrate the second
[Music]
vibration. And it rippled throughout the
very emotional fabric of our
existence and did blend and crystallize
and unify so that we came as one mind,
as one heart.
as one
spirit. And we slept and dreamt unto the
third day the whole
world breathing as one, slumbering as
one, dreaming as
one. And on the third
day, as the energy of
shakana did, they crystallize into the
final form and
form and
manifested in true solidity.
All beings on a society did that feel
the physical intertwinement, the
extension that each and every body is of
everyone else as the fingers of a hand.
else as the fingers of a hand.
Each
body, each feeling physical, each
thought became
interwined and
enraptured and in love did it pulse as
one with all other physical
forms. and that the dream
solidified and the veil of physical and
non-physical reality was
dissolved. Did we find that we were not
only of one soul, not only of one mind,
not only of one heart, but truly of one
body with many
faith. And as this realization dawned
upon all on the third day, Shakara did
vibrate the vibration
[Music] And in a burst of
And in a burst of
light did Shakana render itself back
into energy having accomplished the
crystallization of the entire
planet. And then after that physical
materialization and the rapid ascension
back into
non-physicality did everyone
awake from their dream from their
slum but not back into the world that we
had known but into a new
dream a new
realization a new
understanding that all is
one that all is a dream and the dream is
real. From that day forward as a world
we were awake and awakened by the world
spirit of shakana which is all of us
even as your Christ consciousness and
Buddha nature is all of
you and in awakening and in knowing that
we were always connected to the infinite
to the all that is to the source of
inner light.
Thus from that day
forward did we never physically sleep
again. For we were in the dream
completely alive and alert and always in
the dream always connected and not
needing to break the
idea of projecting into unconsciousness
to make a connection.
to the rest of
ourselves. Your world is awakening as
well at a different pace, but one that
is still beautiful and one still
representative of the soul and the mind,
the heart and the body that you are.
We are overjoyed of the world to be able
to interact at this time of your
awakening with you. To see
replay at a different
pace the recognition and realization
that we have created for ourselves once
again replayed through you to allow us
to see the vast beauty of your
awakening.
We thank you for the
gift. The gift that you have chosen to
share with all of us. The gift that you
have allowed us to choose to share with
you. For this is an
acceleration. The whole idea of what you
call your
Christmas, an acceleration of the
awakening of the Christ consciousness in
each and every one of you.
and the creation of heaven on
earth. Anytime within yourself, within
the tone that you are, within the energy
that you are, within the frequency that
you are, within the
pitch you know yourself to be, that is
your signature
resonance anywhere and anywhere.
Allow yourselves to
unify and be
one by
being the vibration.
[Music] When you perceive the ringing of all the
When you perceive the ringing of all the
various instruments that you have
brought this day of your time, it is one
of the closest analogies we can make for
how we perceive all of
you. You are different frequencies,
different resonances, and that is how we read you.
resonances, and that is how we read you.
We feel you. We hear you in that sense.
And we allow your energy to pass through
us. Even as you may choose to allow our
energy to pass through you so that
together we become one song, one
dream, one
heart. Individuals
always but one
mind. Fashioned out of the
one infinite
unconditional light and love of all that
is.
We thank you for your
participation. We thank you for your
radio and at this time in return for
your
gift. What are the gifts I may
share with you?
[Music]
Good day. and goodbye to you. I'd like
to share a little um kind of ritual I I
did on the s on the eve of the solstice.
All right. Um speak up and be bold so
that all may share. Okay. Can you hear
me now?
Okay. Um so on the eve of the solstice,
I planned like this this walk into the
darkness in the back hills of my house.
So very exciting. Yeah. So my niece and
I went and before we went I knew we were
going by ourselves and we weren't taking
any flashlights or any thing to protect
us like that. So I just got some tobacco
and a little prayer in the tobacco to
just um be gentle with whatever like
fears it reflected to us on this night
of going into the darkness. And so we
went out for the walk and I was kind of
nervous and kind of afraid cuz uh it was
just my niece and I. Usually when I take
hikes back there, I'm with other like
adults and I'm not really afraid. So we
were walking walking and and then it we
came upon this tree and it just felt
like this was the place to bury our our
tobacos that we had kind of prayed and
meditated and made affirmations and and
so at first I thought, well, is this a
tree? And then and then this shooting
star came down like right behind the
tree. And so I just all right, you know,
like I bury our tobacco into this tree.
And the truth is rather curious. It was
um it had like about what
it had. It had
um like five
five main trunks instead of like one
main trunk of humanity on Earth. Five.
Ah. And and so I was just going to like
put the the tobacco in this little in
the embankment in the dirt in the
embankment. And something said no, it'll
go up to the roots. And so I climbed up
on top and I went I went to the roof and
I was feeling around to bury the
tobacco. I could feel the roof of the
tree on the surface of the ground
instead of under, you know, and so I
thought that was kind of curious and and
something to that. And usually I just
stay with the tree to to let it tell me,
you know, whatever it wants to tell me.
But I was kind of afraid and it was
really dark and all right. Okay. And so
anyway, I was ready to turn back at that
point and my niece said, "No, let's go
further." And as soon as she said that,
I knew that there would be something up
on this clearing that I had passed
frequently. And so we decided to go
ahead anyway. And we walked ahead and we
were walking ahead and we talked about
her dog to kind of do this. And we were
kind of a little nervous and a little
afraid and stuff, but we just kept on
making steps further and further into
the darkness. And and then when I got to
that clearing, right when I knew that
something would be there, I saw this car
and all the lights were out and it was
all dark and I like stopped and I
thought, well, maybe this is my friends
that have visited me up there before and
I was going to like go over to the car
and then these like two red lights like
flash like where the driver would be,
but the car was like the headlights
weren't facing us like the front door
was. And so I could see these two lights
like as they were eyeballs, big red
eyeballs. And they couldn't have been
made like by a cigarette or a lighter or
anything like that. And they were just
like went like went on and went off. And
then so I just thought, huh, now wait a
minute. Are these my friends that have
kind of like sent a visitation to me
before up there or or what? and I was
going to take a step further and then
just something in my gut said no, you
know, and so and my niece at that point
at the same time said, "I don't think
they're who you think they are. Let's go
back." And so then we just walked back
and and so I was wondering, so you There
was a definition of, shall we say, a
parameter, which was your perimeter,
your perimeter to the new you, to the
transitional you. It was a symbolic
synchronistic reflection in terms that
involved some individuals on your own
planet unconsciously and also some energies
unconsciously and also some energies
that you were perceiving through a
gateway that they did not necessarily
see in the same way you did to simply
signal the idea of your own
understanding of your own limitations
and the next step that you will be
taking through the next doorway through
the next gate.
Go back into yourself and expand through
yourself. And you will find that all
ideas you would call obstacles and
perimeters and limits and barriers and
borders will be dissolved by going
through the gate of yourself and by
forming that connection to nature as you
instinctively did. And perhaps, shall we
say, for now, most importantly, some new
information will be coming out in what
you call your new year time about the
idea of those roots and the whole idea
of why they were exposed on the surface
in that way. What it means symbolically
to you and your entire society.
There will be information also that will
be revealed in this your coming new year
about certain occurrences that have been
happening upon your planet, certain
interactions that have been going on and
where some of that shall we say comes
from, how it was set up and where some
of that is leading to. But that will be
in your new year. And it will be an
event and an opportunity for
self-discovery within many of you on a
completely different level than we have
undertaken in all the time we have
interacted with you up to this point. It
will be coming very shortly within your
new year time. So that all these
synchronistic signals and energy
recognitions and doorway
recognitions will begin to unfold a more
rapid rate from your
memory. And much of the lies you are now
unaware of about yourselves will come to
the forefront of your consciousness.
Much of the agreements that have been
discussed only in vague terms will now
be able in your new year to become far
more specific. We will in this sense be able
specific. We will in this sense be able
and be allowed to dispense some of this
information. But there will be others as
well, other levels of consciousness that
will endeavor to reflect to you some of
the ideas of how you are intertwined
with other, shall we say, civilizations
in ways that you have not perhaps
perceived yet and perhaps in far more
intertwined methodologies than you have
allowed yourselves to imagine.
We will be discussing all of these
things and we thank you for taking the
first steps at
self-recognition to the direction of the
doorway through which you will realize
and recognize the things we will be
sharing with you because once again they
can only be reflections of what you
already know. But many of you are
beginning now to discover these ideas
about yourself and the full expanse of the
yourself and the full expanse of the
true lives you have all been living when
you blend the physical and the
non-physical reality together.
Can I ask if if um last night this one
dream was connected to that where in the
same kind of embankment that this tree
had been you know in back of our mirror.
Um, I had crossed over it again in the
dream and out from the dirt were these
like little tiny whales and little tiny
dolphins and people were saying like,
"Oh, get away from them." And I said,
"Oh no, I think they're whales and
dolphins." And when I picked them up,
they were like little ones that would
sit in the palm of your hand. And I put
water on them. And when I was digging
the dirt off around them, I uncovered
this skull and then it had a spaceuit
on. And I thought, "Oh my god, is this a
dead astronaut? He's been buried
underneath this dirt or something." But
his body was too small, like to be
human, but his skull was like the size
of a human, but his body was really
little. It has to do with your roots and
your origins. And we will be discussing
much of this for all of you in your
coming new year. Okay. Thank you. Thank
you very much. Thank
you, Michelle. Bashar, would you care to
share who was the uh who what was the
energy that came through at the end of
the last session? It was a blending of
all the preparation for a new level of
energy that is coming up in what you
call your new year time and will be
understood by the name galactic. But it
was a blending of all of us of the
association many different
civilizations softly gently blended in with the
softly gently blended in with the
overall fabric of existence that is
known by the nomenclature the galactic.
It was a preparation and a transition.
Thank you. Also, I was uh uh talking to
the channel uh before starting and we
were both sharing that we both had a
very very lucid
UFO ifo flying you dreams uh last night
connections. Mine was uh observing you
talking to to the channel in a chamber
in on the craft. Any comments? simply
more of the preparation that is being
made for the ability to funnel through
more detailed information into your
society in your coming new year. The
laying down of foundations, shall we
say, synchronistically paralleling the
organization many of you are now doing,
squaring yourselves away in a sense,
clearing out the old ideas and truly
focusing on that which really represents
the new directions you will be taking in
this year, year of conviction and yes,
as some have said, the year of
compassion as well. The idea simply is
that there will be far more clarity in
the direction you will be taking, far
more conviction, far more action, far
more outward interaction as well as
inward interaction. It was simply the
delineation of certain steps that will
be taken. And there is more conscious
recognition now on many different parts
of the dialogues that are going on. When
you are in your dream reality between us
and many of your guides and many other
levels of consciousness, you are
beginning to remember those dialogues
now. They take place far more often than
you remember.
So that assist. Yes. Were you in the
neighborhood? Are you in the
neighborhood? Yes. Near the uh moon
from time to time.
Thank you very much. We thank you.
Sherry, welcome to our celebration,
Bashar. Well, we thank you for the
cocreation of life and light. This is
your violin playing navigator here. All
right. Or navigating violinist,
whichever. I have for you a
statement. Pick up a loose thread on
something you said last month that I
would like to finish off if I can. Weave
it right into the tapestry, if you will.
A proposal, and then I bring to you a
gift vibration. Speak up so that all may
share. The title of this is the page from my
The title of this is the page from my
journal, November 11, 1987. The title is
the broader picture in parenthesis. It
sounds much like the title of a
monologue at the start with you. Maybe
he has something to do with it. I don't
know. I don't know. We shall see. But
November 11th is the date in your
society that translates into my
birthday. Do continue. In 1918 AD, the world
Do continue. In 1918 AD, the world
largely recognized the need for peace as
they declared November 11th to be
remembered at Armist Day. The end of
World War I, the war against the end
wars, World War II, and some 50 or so
other war. The day came to be known in
the United States as Veterans Day,
symbolizing the acknowledgement of man's
inhumity to man and seemingly hopeless.
Two days from now, I can mark the 64th
anniversary of my entrance to this
lifetime. As a female on this planet,
and indeed as a veteran of my many wars
and conflicts, I have come to the
understanding of a broader picture as to
my relationship to self, the cosmos, and
the higher mind for all that is.
attaching no more concerns, anxiety, but
at the same time attaching more and more
self consciousness, cosmic
consciousness, and the condition of the
planet Earth and all that is upon it
within it, above it, and beyond it, in
time or no time, in space or no space. I
now live in love, light in peace. The
creativity, I we enjoy manifest in
multiple dimensions. We send blessings,
encouragement, support and enthusias.
Thank you. Last um month on your
discourse on electronicism and crystals,
we dropped the idea that uh there
traditional solids. Well, this is what I picked up.
solids. Well, this is what I picked up.
I've been looking at how about a
based on the CS. No, no. Spirit in one
sense, but in the sense we have meant
we will give more information on that in
your coming new year as well. Oh, thank
you. Well, I will give back to the
drawing board as well. Oh, I see. Now my
proposal is that I recognize the art for
William teach have been observing you
and my proposal is that at some time
down the road in the future speaking in
our channel there's the time and if you
are willing I would like to share with
you a discourse on teaching methods
because that seems to be what I am
doing. Good. That's agreed. Now I have a
little gift to you that I would like to
present for you here. And if you want to
invite your colleagues, you know,
obviously they are already invited
there. That's right. Um I have an
instrument which we call a violin has
four strings and and I would love to
play an offering for you. All right. We
will change the mic just a moment.
Each and every one of you may remember
that you can utilize this
opportunity to take the vibration you
will be hearing and feel how it
resonates the very chords of your
existence. Make no mistake, as you say in those
Make no mistake, as you say in those
terms, the idea of these vibrations when
you find yourself surrounded by one tone
in this way, one unifying tone and
melody does unify you for you are energy
and you are responsive in that way. And
you do become one being
manifestationally and it does increase
your ability to manifest that which you
desire. Again, remember that these
things now are becoming far less
philosophical and far more material in
your ability to render them in
crystalline form in your reality. So
participate for each and every one of
you are instruments and as one will play
you all play
within. Feel the self that is playing.
Feel the aspect and the facet that you
are. proceed. proceed.
The
melody and his dance [Music] [Music]
[Applause]
spirit. [Music] [Music]
Number six.
[Music] [Applause] [Applause]
[Music]
Heat. Heat.
[Music] Heat. Heat. Heat. Heat. Heat.
[Applause]
[Music] Heat. Heat.
[Music]
[Applause] [Music] [Music]
[Applause]
[Music] Heat. Heat. We thank [Applause] [Applause]
That particular
energy as we perceive the vibrational
tones as they have translated into our
dimension was shall we say channeled by
the individual in your society who wrote
that piece from the vibrational density
you would call the etheric or lower
ostral. It is representative of
crystalline formations of the way energy
patterns itself within what you would
call that etheric or lower astro realm.
We thank you for the ability to perceive
the translation of this vibration from
your dimension to ours.
I wanted to give you a gift even though
I was out of practice. But you all
always give us gifts just by your
willingness to be as fully as you can
who it is you know that you are. We
thank you being who you are. You're
never really out of practice. That
we love you Bashar. Our unconditional
love to you. We thank you.
Hello Bashar. And goodbye to you. Always
a pleasure to be here with you. Ah,
pleasure. Bat, you are there. Thank you.
Um, I just want to share a couple
things. Um, since I talked to you last,
I've I've manifested a wonderful place
to live and I've been moving about five
times in the last year. And uh, I also
manifested some studio time for myself,
a visionary that um, um, is helping me
produce my music. And I almost um I've
realized that I've almost asked for for
things too soon because I'm all over
overwhelmed by all right all of it to to
a certain extent. But well the idea is
not if I may interrupt you for a moment
if you have asked too soon. It is simply
that many of you because you have
created your physical reality to have,
shall we say, a time lag, a time delay,
will realize in your mentality when
things are beginning to manifest within
you. And because of the habitual rituals
you are in and creating the time lag, it
will seem as if the knowing of it and
the asking of it was too soon. But it
did represent the actual timing of the
energy change of when it began to change
in the direction that then allows it to
manifest in your physical reality with
whatever time lag you have in there
based on your belief systems. You
understand? Yes, I do. Um, what I've
noticed has been happening is I I seem
to be very aware of of my power and I'm
Well, thank you. Seems as though I'm
trying to repress it, however. Oh, all
right. Why? I That's what I was hoping
you could show me. Oh, but I am not
asking you why you are attempting to
repress it. I am asking you why it seems
as if you are attempting to repress it.
Um, well, because I have a tendency to
be indulgent. A tendency. A tendency. A
tendency. I am from time to time
extremely indulgent, self-destructive. I
don't know. Because you choose to be.
Um, I guess I guess Oh, there's no
guessing. Is it? And yes, I guess I've made that
Is it? And yes, I guess I've made that
choice. Yes, I've made that choice. You
see, this is the only thing that is the
quote unquote tendency is to forget that
it is a choice. And when you start
looking at it as if it is a choice and
not a tendency, then it starts to occur
less and less often because you are
constantly reminding yourself that
you're in control and that it has been
in fact a choice, not something that is
on, as you say, automatic pilot, right?
But it's not always out of it's not out
of depression or anything. It's out of
excitement. Does not have to be, you
know, um does not have to be out of
depression. Can be out of many things.
Can be out of fear. Can be out of just
testing yourself. can be playing all
sorts of games to get knowledge that you
may need for someone else later on for
all different sorts of reasons.
Maybe that's it. Um I I have a tendency
to it's been it's been such a tendency
to say Yeah.
I have to be so careful with you. You're
really sad. No, no, no. I do not mean to
watch in the sense that you should watch
every single word. I do not mean in that
sense to bind you in your ability to
communicate but simply from time to time
we find that the idea of reflecting back
to you the words you use are a very
precise reflection of how you think.
This is true and therefore you can get
in touch with that you can realize more
consciously what it is you are choosing
to do. Mhm. Well, I'm aware of that. I
um very excited because we love to play
with you when we know you really don't
have that much to understand.
[Music] I do appreciate that.
I do appreciate that.
Um, anyway, I do want to thank you for
giving me the power to manifest my
dream. Oh, but I didn't. You didn't. I
know. Thank you. Thank you for making me
realize it. Allowing me to realize.
Well, thank you very much for allowing
me to do so. So, how do I get rid of my
cold? Are you having a nice rest? No, I'm not
Are you having a nice rest? No, I'm not
resting anymore. You're not resting? Why
not? No, cuz I'm busy. I'm swamped. Oh,
swamped. You like it in the swamp? Yes.
It feels good though. It feels It feels
good though. All right. Many times what
you simply call the cold or the flu in
that sense of lower grade conditions are
simply in that sense processing that is
going on allowing yourself to change
many old ideas and flush them out of
your system. Right? That in a sense is
what you call the purpose of your
American Indian your Native American
sweat lodge. in a sense to sweat those
ideas the old conditions out of you to
translate them into more etheric form so
that you can change them. Mhm.
Understand? So you can purify the cycle
from physical to astral to physical to
astral to physical to astral. The
constant creation of self. Sometimes I
feel like they're a little disconnected.
sometimes like my my physical hasn't
caught up with what I I know I'm capable
of spiritually. I often times feel
really disconnected.
Yeah, that's what having the feeling is
there for to put you in touch with the
fact that if you have a feeling that
means you must have a particular belief
and that's the only way you can get the
reaction that you call a feeling is by
having that belief. The feeling puts you
in touch with the fact you have the
belief so that if you no longer prefer
the belief you can choose something
else. I know I can. It's just staying in
touch with them. But um let me ask you a
question. Yes. Thank you. Why is there
the assumption that it is difficult to
stay in touch with that?
I don't know. For me it seems that way
sometimes better at it. I understand
exactly what you are saying. But
remember we are simply giving you an
opportunity right now to decide that
everything you're saying is nothing but
a definition. Yeah, I'm aware of that.
And that you can change it to whatever
definition you prefer to be right now.
And that's up to you. And I do. Yes.
Doing that. All right. Most of the time.
All right. But that timing is up to you.
You have the ability to do it all the
time. I know. It's up to you. If I get
enough rest, maybe I'll stay square with
it. But thank you very much. We thank
you very much. All perhaps you really
need to know is that there really is no
rush. Even when you are fully connected
and busy on every level, everything
still has a proper place and timing and
everything fits. So you don't have to
rush. You don't have to juggle to keep
everything in place. Relax and act. I
know. And let it be in the place that it
is for that's where it belongs. Even a
cold. Well, yes. Simply sometimes the
idea is that many of you give yourselves
the call either because of the
processing you are doing or to tell
yourself to relax relax to not force
yourself of course. Thank you Bashar.
Well thank you very much.
Merry Christmas Bashar and to you
Bashar I am a college instructor and I
have been grateful for your sharing
since March of this year.
I the teacher in me is excited by the
teacher in you. Oh, thank you. I have
become so excited about the content.
I want to develop a course at the
college I teach at. Well, go right
ahead. And I wonder if you might have some
And I wonder if you might have some
suggestions for course title or course
structure. Well, that's up to you. We
will see what happens in your
imagination first. Maybe later we will
comment perhaps in that sense on what
you have created. But the idea, the
structure, the imagination, the creation
is up to you. The initiation is up to
you. Why I why I uh seem to struggle with the
Why I why I uh seem to struggle with the
idea and I admit it is my own negativity
is that we might say the material is is
not traditional in the sense that I I
have 55 churches in a small town and the
negativity that I introducing to it is
is a concern that I may stir up a
hornets nest and yet I feel such
excitement to do this. Are you being
you? Uh, I think that might be part of the
Uh, I think that might be part of the
problem.
I I tend to be too conservative and I
tend to hold back. And well, now your
case is up to you. You don't have to
label it any particular way or
invalidate it in that sense. Simply, are
you being true to yourself? Yes. All
right. Are you doing what you are doing?
And do you have the desire to do these
things you have said to us through
unconditional love? Are you doing what
you are doing? And do you have the
desire to do these things you have said
to us through unconditional love? And do
you believe to the best of your ability
that you are not really doing something
that would consciously hurt anyone? Uh,
no. I'm I believe I'm acting with
integrity. All right, then go ahead. Any
stirring that happens will be because of
the individuals who have attracted
themselves to know that you are who you
are and will have chosen to be stirred.
I I become aware of the of the struggle
of students not only in education but
the struggle of their life. Okay. And I
become excited that a course like this
could not only help them in their
pursuit of education but help them in
all aspects of their life. And perhaps
it is the greatest course that could be
taught. Well, you have done it before,
you know. Why not simply rely on your
own Atlantean incarnation?
Okay. Well, I'll uh I'll check
that. Allow yourself in a meditative
state to remember how you did it
then. How you reached the very prime
levels of their consciousness. how you
taught for how individuals were taught
in Atalantean times is qualitatively
different than how your systems of
education teach now. Get back in touch
with that idea and see if you can apply
some of that into your present day like
framework. All right. All right. Thank
you. Thank you very much. Think in light
colors by the way. Thank you.
Sherry Shikica to you, Mr. Bashar. Oh,
mister. Yeah. Well, we want to keep this
serious, you know, or serious and robot.
That's supposed to be funny. Forget it.
Forget it. Anyway, I haven't been here
the last few weeks, and I wrote a few
questions down if I might ask them. Oh,
all right.
Well, instead of asking the
questions, [Music]
[Music]
couple now, if you're in with this with
Lincoln, we can get along fine. Now,
instead of asking you the questions, why
don't I just give you the number like 28
and you give me the answer. All right.
28. [Music]
This is a big one. 17 maybe.
If so, what kind? Whatever you would
really like it to be. All right. One
more question.
23. Synchronicity is the key. Excellent.
Excellent. Well, now that you've
answered most of my questions,
uh, this being Christmas and has a lot
to do with little boy named Jesus who's
came from a Jewish family. And without
getting too secular here, the Jews
actually came from the Israelites. And
going a little earlier, they were called
Hebrews or actually Hebrews. And these
Hebrews had a god with no name or Yahw.
And I was wondering if you can give us a
little scenario in this particular area
of our planet at the time when these
particular people
were starting up. Well, how did to some
degree it fits into some of the things
we said we would be able to share with
many of you regarding your history and
this will occur next year of your time.
Next year is 12 months 52 weeks. Uh, can
we bring this down a little closer to
present time within what you call the
first three of your months of the new
year? Much better. Well, Bashara, it's
been a pleasure and you can ring my bell
anytime. We thank you for ringing your
own. Sherry,
Sherry,
goodbye to you. I'd like to ask you
what's been happening at SeaWorld with
the whale. All right. With um Yes. As we
understand um the idea first has to do
once again with the recognition that
what you call the orca is the samurai or
the sorcerer of your world of the sea in
that sense and any individual that do
not approach that particular
consciousness with absolute blended
integrity may find themselves out of
sync with that particular being and a
wind up creating a great deal of
friction or physiological interaction
that can be in some cases
detrimental. The idea simply is that
those beings function as a polarity
mirror, black and white, and that
individuals must approach them with
absolute integrity in order to ride the
current of their thoughts, in order to
blend with the current of their energy.
Okay? You understand? Yeah. Um I heard I
was I earlier heard a conversation
someone said that a friend of ours asked
another um being what they were what was
happening and they said they were trying
to tell the trainers and the people that
they wanted to leave and they needed
more freedom but they wouldn't come back
just they do require the freedom of the
sea. Yeah. And the idea is that the idea
of confinement is to some degree an
expression of lack of
integrity. But the idea also is that
many stations, many interaction stations
are now being created upon your planet
to allow these beings to interact with
you in their natural environment. They
will come back in that sense if you do
set up these stations. That is one of
the messages to some degree. Not that
some of them are not willing to exist in
what you call captivity form. If you are
also willing to learn on your behalf
what they have to say in a sense because
of the mismatch of frequencies then came
the idea of the type of interaction you
are describing that was
injurious to individuals of your species
because it is showing that there is not
enough room for the interaction and that
the interaction is not being allowed to
be natural and is not being allowed to
be in two direction.
Okay. Thank you very much. Does this
assist you? Yes, it does. Thank you,
Mash. Thank you. Share it.
Good evening, Mashar. Good day to you.
Okay. My question um I would like you to
help me with help me synthesize a theme
that has been a part of my life.
Synthesize. I'm at a point where things
where I think are coming together, but
it's real confusing. Oh. All right.
Well, do remember that the confusion is
part of the process of coming together.
Yes. Okay. And speak up so that all may
share. And it has something to do with
the star of David. All right. And the
star in Bethlehem. Okay. Now, my my I
myself belong to the Catholic religion.
And I dedicated my life to 10 years to
religious institution. Came to a point
where all that did not make any sense.
The total system and I and I left it.
And basically when I left it, I rolled
in at a wasteland. No belief at all
belief. Oh, a limbo state. Yeah. And it
was such total chaos.
How exciting. Yeah, it was great. Okay.
And uh how bold of you. Yeah. Well,
anyway, it didn't feel bold, but and
then I came to a point where I don't
know, something made sense because
although I I identified very much with
the stranger in Albert Kimu's book, his
disconnection with life, I certainly
didn't want to go and on a sunny day
kill my mother. That part I did not
associate with. Your mother would
appreciate. Yeah. Right.
But at the same
time I I I also saw that you know there
were other people like me who were were
in this chaos. Yes. And did not have any
belief systems or were not aware of
them. And yet we were very very human to
each other. We didn't really understand
where that was coming from. We didn't
really have any any ulterior motive
other than that we really wanted to be
that way. Well, okay. And then it come
from the heart. Right. Uh yes. Anyway,
it felt right. And so then I progressed
and I came across another kind of well
at least it opened my eyes a little bit
more. Yes. And at least I I'm able to
tolerate people who mention the word God
or God and things like that. One of my
difficulties have always been Jesus
Christ. Yes. And I've been able to
accept that a little bit better when I
see him as an evolved
uh being on our planet and a lot of good
that came through him. All right. Do
remember that by definition the Christ
consciousness is anything you define it
to be and they are all valid right
that's a lot more acceptable to me and
so what happened is uh on my search here
I came across a book called the secret
places of the lion and this book did
make a lot of sense to me in many ways
because it did deal with uh some
chronological things that I felt
difficulties with one of the very minor
names that came up was the name Melis
Yes. Whom I for some reason associate
and this is not I don't know why I do
this but I associated with one of the
wise men who came to Bethlehem. In this
book this man talks about Melchisedc who
was mentioned in Genesis and the Psalms
as Jesus was well you know how I go
there was
Melisedc incarnated. And it didn't ring
right to me but yet there's a real
connection there. Bethlehem and that's
what I I'm here to to ask because
Mechisedc makes more sense to me than
Christ and I would like I understand
because Mechisedc is in the ancient
language the remembrance of the world
spirit of the world itself called
Maldank which destroyed itself and did
thus incarnate upon your planet and
become intertwined as a part of the
earth's world spirit now known as the
Christ consciousness.
Okay, understand it is the blending of
two world consciousnesses into one. The
absorption and intertwining of that
idea. One from one reference point, one
from another reference point. Now they
are, shall we say, a hybrid. They are
something different, a third principle.
Melchisedc represents another direction
of incarnation, another direction of
arrival upon your planet to which you
simply have a stronger connection than
what might be called the original energy
of the planet
Earth. In other words, the individuals
who usually label themselves as being
those that have wandered in a sense have
been wandering far longer and farther
than they think.
It involved many other star systems as
well. But from certain star systems,
there were, shall we say, incarnational
migration to another planet in your
solar system that was known in those
times of Malbec. And upon the
destruction of that world, the entire
world spirit did begin to incarnate and
project its incarnations upon the
earth's plague to work out the idea of
the negativity they had set up.
Mechisedc in that sense is the
recognition of the ancient wisdom, the
ancient balance to some degree of that
world that it seeks to recover and
discover within itself once again and
allow to come to terms in a blended
sense with the world spirit of earth as
well so that you become more than the
sum of your heart. All are valid. All
approaches are true. It is simply that
still in this limbo state of your
transformational age, many of you will
still recognize one particular pathway
as having perhaps a little bit more
apricot energy for you than another
pathway because there is still
differentiation. In time, within what
you call perhaps the next decade or two,
maximum five decades, all of these
particular paths will be
undifferentiated. It will be understood to be the one
It will be understood to be the one
energy that your world simply is at that
point. And the labels will not matter
nor will they be used anymore. They will
simply be recognized as the collective
consciousness of all of you. That is
your particular aspect of the infinite
creation. But for now, that are still
remnants of the path that have been
taken because many of you are now
rediscovering what those paths
originally were to begin with. And once
again, some of this detailed information
about the original path that created the
world you now understand and where these
paths might be leading will be some of
the detailed information we will be
discussing again within the coming new
year of your time. Does that assist you
sufficiently? Yes. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for waking up from
one dream into another.
Sure. Greetings. And good day to you.
I've been so static lately that
sometimes I can't hardly breathe.
All right. And I wanted to share the
reason with you and everybody and then
ask you a quick question about a friend.
Oh, all right. Um, by January 1st, I
will have quit three part-time jobs and
I decided I don't prefer to live in LA
anymore. So, I'm going to take off and
head to the Southwest and live somewhere
there. I don't know where. Oh, all
right. How fun is you? So, it's pretty
exciting. Yes. Bringing your three
trinary parts together into one hole.
That's funny because there's three
places I'm considering. Colorado,
Arizona, and New Mexico. Oh, right. So,
um, it's like jumping off a cliff and I
feel like I'm going to fly. Yes. In a
sense. That's really great because last year at
That's really great because last year at
this time I was real depressed and I
told you about it in a private
channeling and said that I got upset one
day when I was in Panga Canyon standing
on a big rock because I knew if I
decided to jump off I wouldn't fly
because I didn't believe I could fly.
Yes. So now it's like it's a different
way of jumping off the cliff. Very good.
Okay. So I want to thank you because you
did this to me a great deal and I'm I'm
learning to trust and in a positive way
in a positive way. Remember all of you
always trust infinitely always. Just a
matter of whether you trust in negative
or positive. You always use the same
mechanism of trust to create the reality
you experience. So it's not that you're
willing to trust just that you are now
choosing to trust in a positive
direction instead of a negative one.
Right? Um, I have a friend in Ohio who's been
Um, I have a friend in Ohio who's been
ill for a long time. Oh, hi. Ho. All
right. It looks like she's creating more
It looks like she's creating more
disease. And I sent her the tape of the
channeling at San Jose State University.
Name Carol Kiggley.
Three bits of information delivered by
three different
friends is coming to your
friend. This can assist her or it
cannot. But she will be given three new
mirrors to look at, three faces, three
new books in a sense to read, three new
ideas, three facets of the persona. She
can decide she can be or not. These are
coming already from guys, from friends,
from environment and
experience. We can comment on the fact
that we recognize this information is
coming very soon, very soon, very
abruptly and very very strongly. But we
cannot interfere beyond that. Uh-huh.
Okay. But she is going to get the three
opportunities. It is up to her to decide
what to do with the information.
But within what you
call no later than the next month, all
three will have manifested in her
consciousness.
We thank you. Great. Thank you. One
suggestion that can come from
us. This may tie into past life
symbology, but it may also ignite
something within.
You may suggest that she simply look to
the horns of the
moon and focus on the vibration called
Isis. Isis. Yes. And see what that
Isis. Yes. And see what that
does. All right. Yes. And the sands of
time are
within. That phrase, the sands of time
are within. Can you repeat that? The sands
within. Can you repeat that? The sands
of time are within. Well, thank you very
much. You may repeat it to her as well.
I will. Well, thank you. Thank you,
Vish. I love you. Our love to you as
well. Thank you,
Sherry.
Merry Christmas, Michelle.
Shakama. Uh, I do a lot of physical work
in in the type of work that I do. Uh,
and in the last year I've injured my
back. Three different times. Oh. 1, two,
three. Yes. And uh I' I've been doing a
lot of things to uh build my body up to
where this doesn't happen. All right.
And uh I thought maybe you could uh
suggest some sort of help with
medication. All right. I can suggest
first of all that three times is
sufficient. I'm injuring my back. Okay. It is
I'm injuring my back. Okay. It is
sufficient to have released everything
you need to have released and to now
join together into one idea, one
principle, one thrust, one direction,
all of the energy you know yourself to
be. May I ask you a question? Yes. When
you think of yourself as energy, how do
you picture it? How do you see yourself?
Can you describe the idea to us? Yes. Uh
I see a ball of light but it seems to
uh be contained in what way? Uh
restricted and then it sort of
bursts loose rather than an even
flow. It sort of like when I utilize my
energy. Yes. It kind of uh it's spurt
just doesn't run smoothly. All right.
Can you create in a meditation a vision
of that sphere of light operating
smoothly? Yes. I'll give you a
suggestion. See the
spurts and see them sped up faster and
faster and faster and faster until every
single place on the sphere that a spurt
could ever occur will all seem to be
happening pulsating at exactly the same
time like what you would call an atomic
pile. You understand? Yes, I do. I like
that. See that acceleration blending and
harmonizing and in a sense fusing the
whole idea of yourself into one notion,
one idea that is infinite and eternal
and touches everywhere at
once. See if that is of assistance to
you in your meditation. Very good. I'll
do that. Thank you very much. Thank you.
One at this time each and every one of
you. One deep breath in and in and
[Music]
out. A second deep breath
in and out.
A third deep breath in and in and
out. [Music]
[Music]
Vibration. How refreshing.
[Music] Hello, Bon and good day to you. I had an
Hello, Bon and good day to you. I had an
interesting encounter with a signpost
last week. A signpost? All right. I was
driving down the street in a
neighborhood that I'm not normally
familiar with. Ah, very exciting.
Exploring. What are you in your little
craft? All right. And up ahead was a side
All right. And up ahead was a side
street. And I became very curious as to
what the sign name of the side street
was. All right. And as I approached, I
saw her name was Arurus. Oh.
So I thought, well, this must be telling
me something. And I thought, well,
obviously I must have a connection to
this energy. All right. And what will
you do with this obvious recognition?
Well, I'm sorry, guys. All
All
right. You have and I have reflected it
right back.
How did you feel when you saw the sign?
It took me actually a couple of days to
realize that that was talking about me.
All right, fair enough. Um, when you
made the realization, when you made the
connection, how did you feel? Very
happy. Very happy. Yes. Do you feel that
way now? Yes. You still feel the energy?
Yes. What do you want to do with it?
That's a good
start. The release. All right. First
step. Always the release. The start.
Good start. What
next? Go out in the world. Oh, thank
you. Was it pointing in a particular
direction?
Um, well, it was perpendicular to me. I
guess it was sticking out maybe more to
my left or south. No,
right. How do you feel when you think of
that particular direction on your
planet? Well, from here that would say Mexico,
Well, from here that would say Mexico,
which creates visions of what type of
atmosphere?
I associate that without tracking the
sun. Oh, the sun, star, octurus. All
right, then use that perhaps as a
symbolic guide. Not that you necessarily
have to in specific terms explore all
the detailed ideas of that civilization,
but you might be able to take some,
shall we say, cues or clues from the
essence of the symbology of the golden
light of your sensual thought and the
idea of the golden
vibration that our tourist represents.
Okay? and see what that does. And think
of the
lushess of that climate on your planet.
Okay? Feel Feel
feel the
fertility of that soil of the
greenness, the emerald
greenness and feel yourself growing and
feel yourself absorbing the light of
that gate and see where that leads you. Act
gate and see where that leads you. Act
on it. All right. Okay. You are already
obviously giving yourself all the signs
you need. You're doing just fine. There
is no need to stop the process to ask
what it means when by continuing to live
it, you will see in no uncertain terms.
If you apply yourself in the directions
that excite you the most understand.
Does this help you? Yes, it does. Well,
thank you very much. Thank you. Bright
and shining dreams to you. Yes. To you,
too. Oh, always. having one right now.
[Music]
Happy Shanaka Shash. Well, thank you and
Shakanaka. Shakana Sha to all of you.
The idea Shakanaka simply in that sense
the world spirit Shakasha the exalted
light of light. Thank you. Um I'm afraid
to ask this question. Oh, all right.
Maybe I'll play along and be afraid to
answer it. [Music]
[Music]
That was an answer right there. Thank
you. Maybe the whole thing. Oh, thank
you very much.
Does that satisfy you? Well, I still
sort of
like No. Okay. I do. All right. Okay.
Nine years ago, I was I I was given a
vision and it changed my life and I I
started singing and writing songs. Is
that all right? And then at the same
time, there seems to be this old pain
that is rumbling around in me. Old pain.
All right. It's embarrassing in front of
people anyway. But it's only in front of
reflections of you. Okay. You're just
looking in a mirror and learning about
yourself.
Yeah. Yeah. So, I'm I'm real angry at
myself at this point. Like, all right.
And you can use it in a positive way.
That's all right. Remember that anger is
alignment. It aligns you with what you
know is truth for you. So use it that
way. Okay? Cuz I I really I
Okay? Cuz I I really I
really I want more than anything to live
the vision that's in my heart. And yet
this pain still keep seems to keep
bringing up roadblocks and and sabotage
where everything goes wrong. You know, I
lose both. Oh, everything goes in
unexpected ways. But why label it wrong?
It is always the label that makes it
seem that you are unable to use it when
these things happen in a positive way.
Remember, nothing has built-in meaning.
You give it the meaning you have been
taught to give it. Don't give things
that happen unexpectedly in your life a
negative meaning and they will not
manifest in a negative way. That's just
it. I want to I feel like I it's it's
time to absolutely retrain myself. Are
there any steps or information that I or
anyone else could have to actually take
steps to not go on the old patterns I
was taught or brought up with? You can
rely on your imagination to provide
those. I could provide you with any
number of ideas, but you'll always allow
them to be adapted by your imagination.
Anyway, your imagination has the ability
to give you whatever methodology will
work best for you. That is why it is
keyed to you. Your vibration, your
imagination, that's why it's your
imagination. In your own meditations,
you can simply ask your imagination what
will work best for you to allow you to
transform these ideas and it will give
you the process that will work best for
you. You can do that the idea of the
music of the tonality can center you can
balance you can blend you in that sense
as well. You understand? Mhm. But also
perhaps here is a suggestion from us
just as you observed that we did when
you said these old pains. I said old
pains. Take each and every one of these
Take each and every one of these
definitions and personalize them. Act
them out on a stage of your own
creation. Be all the characters. Be old
K. Hi, I'm Old
Page. Be whatever other definitions you
have created within your play, within
your scenario. Be all the characters and
act it out and dialogue with each and
every one of them within yourself. And
see in that dialogue that you will write
how you can in a sense come to
definitional terms so that the different
actors will know when it is their turn
to leave the stage to transform into the
audience and to leave the one individual
you prefer to be left on the stage
acting in the manner you prefer to by
having learned what you need to learn in
all that the other characters have to
tell you and teach you. You can do that.
Wow, that's incredible.
Quite credible.
It's very interesting because someone
just came to me who's been coming to my
shows and saying he wants to write
a my story of how I like my life story
told him that I felt I wasn't ready. But
it was a signal for that idea. Yes,
exactly. Now all of a sudden what he
said makes sense. Thank you very
much. Um, let us get one little person. All
Um, let us get one little person. All
right. See if it will fit in here.
[Music]
See, I only trust my imagination cuz I
saw Oh, of course you do. Remember once
again, you all always trust. Your
imagination has brought you everything
you've experienced thus far. How can you
not trust it? It will always create what
is your strongest belief, your strongest
definition. You don't even have to worry
about it. That's automatic. Your
imagination always works and will always
work in the direction you choose it to
work in. Well, why does why does this
being always choose to to work in old
pain and sadness? It doesn't. You do.
But you can ask it. If you then create
it to seem to be another individual, you
can ask it in the play in your
meditation. Okay? and it will tell you
and then you'll understand how you can
integrate that within yourself. Remember
in becoming the individual you desire to
be it isn't at the expense of these
other aspects it is at the integration
of them. So once that being created to
be separate from you on the stage in the
play has given you the reason for its
existence then you can take that reason
back inside of you. So it no longer has
a reason or a need to manifest in an
exteriorized separatized and segregated
way. Then there will be no effect from
that character in your life because you
will have reabsorbed it. Understand?
Yes. Doesn't it sound exciting? Yes. All
right then, curtain go up.
Thank you. We thank you for allowing us
to share the idea of this co-creation
with you. And thank you. And the what I
was wondering is I haven't been here in
many months and yet I felt last week I I
felt this I felt like he's saying come
you know talk to Daryl Lincoln come sing
at at next week and then I saw I saw the
channel the next day and asked him and
he said yes it could be possible that my
I felt like I was I felt the
communication. Well yes it is the
synchronicity of the connection all of
you have. Yeah. Remember that each and
every one of you, though you seem to be
separate, are all reflections of each
other and are all playing different
parts in the overall play. I like that
everything fits and everything works
flawlessly. Thank you. Oh, thank you very much. We
Thank you. Oh, thank you very much. We
always know that when we see one of your
plays, we will always
applaud. Very masterfully done. It is.
Thank you very much. I love you. Enjoy
your play. Our love to you as well.
Thank you. Remember that you are also
each and every one of you worth loving.
Thank you. Thank you. Sharing Uncle
Boo and the
M. Thank you.
Uh I was sharing a question and sharing
is I brought uh crystals I need little
bags and I think if everybody gets one
there's enough for everybody to have
one. No. What? From uh from love to
love. Well, thank you for your
sharing and for your love. Thank you.
Oh, I enjoy it. My question is um I read
in I'm pretty sure I read in the most
prestigious magazine. Um it was about uh
the I think it was the one about the
dolphins and the extra communicated that
I read about the whales something about
the word the whales and the word wheel
and that the whales have given the
wheels to the people to help us on our
whatever that we're doing. Anyway, not
in the literal sense. The idea is simply
a notion that the sitation life forms on
your planet complete the other half of
the cycle of soul that you are. And the
cyclical nature of that understanding of
togetherness can give you an analogy of
your physical wheel. But it's simply
that they are imparting to you that they
are the other part of the cycle that
they belong in your cycle. Understand?
Yeah. Well, that was my confusion cuz
the second part of that was that I read
that the Mayans had discovered the wheel
and they didn't they chose not to use
it. They use it in their toys because
they knew it would roll the earth flat
to use the wheel. Yes. And then I was
wondering well now why would the wheels
have given it to us? They did not
directly use the water either. No,
but so that's what I was wondering
about. Are you wondering now? So the
whale Laura just like clarifying the
connection between the whale and the
wheel. The idea simply is that your
humanity interprets the idea of cycles
of motion as a wheel. What you call the
wheel of life. They gave you an
understanding with their telepathic
transmissions that they are a part of
your cycle that you are one world that
you are a wheel of life.
Any solar system, any planetary
civilization in a sense can be
considered to be a gear or a wheel
within the overall universe. It is
simply that the water
sens together creates the whole wheel.
They are the other side of the wheel
that you are. Okay. Understand? Yes.
Well, thank you very much. I have a
quick synchronous sharing there. What?
uh little verse I read in a beautiful
book called Voices of Our Ancestors. It
says uh medicine wheel mandala at near
clear mind that the sacred boots be
removed in this time. Yes, it shall be.
I got circled. Thank you. Thank you very
much.
I be sure you
I have a question about a secret you
have that I've been curious about for
some time and that's about spontaneity.
Spontaneity? Yes. This is no secret.
Well, it seems like a secret to me
because I see when I try to be
spontaneous, I run into a lot of
problems. Well, of course, because you
cannot try to be spontaneous by
definition.
The idea always sends back to what we
have shared with you about doing the
thing that you are most excited about
doing. Spontaneity will come as a
natural result. You will simply know how
to act in what way to act when you need
to know it. If you are really doing the
thing at any given moment that you
really love to do. Spontaneity is a part
of the package.
Does that make sense? It does make
sense. I guess I just don't understand
why you haven't changed your mind yet.
If if I were to do something like what
you're doing, yes, every Thursday night
at 8:00, you know, channel through Daryl
Anka, etc., etc., I would be really into
it for probably 2 or 3 months. I would
be so excited about it and I would I
would my whole life would revolve around
it, right? And then I would get turned
on by something else. Yeah. And I would
be off on another trip. But I always am
as well.
Remember, in the idea of living in the
moment, quote unquote, every time I do
this is the first time I've ever done
it. Literally, as far as I'm concerned,
now wait a minute. You're still here at
8:00 every Thursday. It isn't 8:00 to
me. That's your time frame. Well, how
can I do the same trip and by living in
the moment and truly understanding that
every single moment you call a moment of
time is literally a new moment and isn't
really connected to any other moment
except in the sense that it quote
unquote occupies the same place that the
last moment did. But it isn't the same
moment nor is it really a direct
continuation. Continuity is your
illusion. Every time we do this with
you, it is totally new for the first
time. It is simply that we live that
much in the moment. Everything is really
that new to us. In the same way before
your society unteaches you in the same
way that you as children live in the
moment and are fascinated with
everything because you see everything as
if you are seeing it for the first time
which you are which a child knows it is.
Understand? So it would be the same
thing as if a child would see an
opportunity every Thursday night at 8:00
to do this thing. If you wish to put it
that way, but the child does not see it
as an opportunity every Thursday night
at 8:00. They just happen to notice that
they notice an opportunity. They act on
it. I see. It does not matter where or
when it is. It is simply the expression
of who and what they are. They have not
yet keyed into as specifically as many
of you have the notion of linear time.
They are simply acting in the moment
with whatever is there that represents
the vibration that they know they are.
And so it is always new. Always new.
Understand that when you see a
flower and every day you approach that
flower, you are always always
approaching it from a slightly different
direction, a slightly different time.
Therefore, it is never really the same
flower, is it? Because we're not the
same people.
Correct. So when you understand that
every moment is absolutely new, brother,
then you really no longer need to
express yourself that way. You simply
start expressing yourself in whatever
way is most representative of who and
what you are, which is what I will do.
When the energy itself
shifts, we can translate this idea into
your linear time saying, "Well, it will
last such and such for so long." But the
idea is not really how we experience it.
We simply go with the flow. And we know
that when the flow changes direction, it
is representative of the collective
energy that you and we are together in
this interaction. And we simply follow
it. We simply act on it. It is not that
we actually plan it out, time it out.
All right. This channeling is going to
take 3,287
3,287
Thursdays. We do not approach it that
way. We simply live in the moment. And
in a sense, in a sense, as a
civilization, we are now gaining the
ability to actually experience every
single one of the channeling we have
done with you as one
interaction. Simply in a sense,
approached from a different point of
view simultaneously. Is this making any
simultaneously. Is this making any
sense? A little. A little. You're saying
that you're beginning to experience all
time is now. Yes. Because we are moving
into the idea from what you call
physical to non-physical. Our reality is
almost completely blended as one idea.
Understand? Okay. I think it's going to
take a while for it to sink in. If you
think so. But that's how you create more time
so. But that's how you create more time
with that definition. Here's to you. For
the time you will experience will all be
worth experiencing and we'll all be
beautiful. And the sooner you allow what you do
And the sooner you allow what you do
create to be worth experiencing, the
less of it you will perceive.
Paradoxically enough. Understand?
enough. Understand?
Could you wait a minute for the one? No.
One more time for the first time. Thank
you. When you allow whatever time you do
When you allow whatever time you do
create for yourself to
experience to be experienced in full
joy, then paradoxically, you will
actually experience less of
it. Because when you live in the moment,
you don't create as much time
because you're not always waiting for
something else. Correct?
Only the waiting for something else
create the time that happens in between
because you then create the notion of
here happening more
quickly. You understand?
This is great. Does that help you? It
does help me. Well, thank you very much.
Do understand each and every one of you
from one particular point of view point
of view I shall now choose is actually
always spontaneous even when you create
hesitation the spontaneous
creation understand yes I do so the idea
is to simply look at everything in your
life as a spontaneous creation if that's
what you desire and then you will start
to see everything being redefined in
that way and you will see the result of
that attitude in the action
that you perform. Understand? Um I don't
understand the last thing that you said.
In other words, if you see hesitation as
simply one more way to experience
spontaneity, then that attitude seeing
even the idea of planning and hesitation
as a spontaneous creation in the moment
will actually allow you to manifest in
physical terms the idea in a truly more
physicalized spontaneous manner.
The attitude of how you look at things,
in other words, will determine the way
your life unfolds and the way the
opportunities come to you and the way
you will act on them in a more
spontaneous fashion. Does this make
sense? I think so. Uh this might help to
explain how sometimes we create feelings
of being stuck. Yes. Oh yes. Yes. Yes.
It is only because of the definitions
that you give to the circumstance.
Because you are saying this means things
are in stasis, not moving. When you see
this, that's what it means. It means
you're stuck. It means you're not moving
ahead. Instead of having the attitude
that what is happening is a part of the
process, not an interruption in it. And
you dive right into it to find out what
part of the process it is. Soon as you
dive into it, you're in the middle of
experiencing it. and therefore it goes
right through you very quickly and
before you know it you're through it.
So if you think you're feeling stuck,
you just do the next thing. You're
really not stuck. Correct.
Explore the ideas of your definitions of
stuck. Remember that anything you call a
block is not actually a block unless you
treat it like one. Unless you treat it
as if it's something to go around
instead of something to go
through. Discover that what a block
usually is is simply information that
you really need to know that comes in an
unexpected package that you may not
recognize on the surface, but that
doesn't mean it doesn't belong in your
life. Dive into it. Unwrap it. Is the
time for unwrapping presents in your
world. So when something comes you think
is a block, find out what you would have
to believe in order to experience it
that way. Dive in and find out what
information it is bringing you. Absorb
the information and the idea you have
called the block will unfold as a
direction as a path in a very obvious
and clearsighted way. Understand? Yes. I
think this must be the real meaning of
the statement this two shall pass in a
sense. Yes. Because everything in that
sense though real is transitory because
it is all the product of your
imagination. Physical reality is only
what you dream it to be. What you
imagine it to be what you define it to
be. That's all. But that's the reality
of it. Does that help? It does. Well,
thank you very much for being so
spontaneous in this interaction.
Well, I was I couldn't make up my mind
till the very last minute which question
to ask. I always have at least a dozen.
Keep the whole blanket. Thanks for shar.
Bye-bye.
Hello, Mr. Ambassador. Hello, Mr.
Diplomat. Greetings and salutations. Andrew, you
Greetings and salutations. Andrew, you
are well. Thank you.
Um, I don't have a joke tonight.