All
right, I'll say how are you all this
evening of your time as you create time
to exist.
Allow us to begin this interaction this
evening of your time with the
entitlement karmic
template assistant. [Laughter]
Now while the aforementioned visual aid
is being prepared, allow us to reiterate
some of the ideas we have discussed with
you briefly to lay down a foundation for
the reason for this graphic. Do not show
it to them
yet. The idea first and foremost is that
we have discussed karma. The idea you
call karma and we have discussed the
idea that karma is completely
self-imposed by you upon yourself.
There is no outside exteriorized
judgment against you. Karma is simply
representative of a momentum of an idea
that you wish to play out in any
particular physiological lifetime that
may have connections to what you call
other physiological lifetimes you have
lived or will live.
The idea also is that we have discussed
that time even though it is real while
you are in it is nonetheless your
projection your
illusion. It is a concept that exists
within creation obviously since you live
within it. But it is your
self-created idea, self-created
definition so that you can experience
the idea of a physiological reality
because one of the definitions of
physiological reality is the concept
spacetime. Those limitations, those
definitions create your ability to exist
as a physicalized being. But we have
also talked about that because time is
an illusion, all the different lives you
have ever lived or will ever live in any
dimension of experience all exist in a
sense now
simultaneously. They all have their own
reality. They are all a part of the you,
the whole you, the total you that you
are. But in choosing to experience a
fragment of your consciousness in a
linear fashion, then you relegate that
portion of your consciousness so to
speak to experience that totality in a
stepbystep linear fashion one after
another rather than all at once which is
the perspective of the non-physical
consciousness that you also are which
you colloally refer to as the oversoul.
The oversoul in that sense can be viewed
as we have discussed many times as the
projectionist and the lines can be
viewed as the film strip as you call it.
Each frame on the film representing
perhaps a different life or a different
moment in one life. Now to the portion
of the film that exists within the film
itself from frame to frame. It only
knows the frame it is in at any given
moment. Has what you call a memory of
frames that have gone by. And in that
sense only a dim understanding of
projections or predictions of the frame
coming up based on past continuity. But
the projectionist sees the whole film
all at once and knows that all the
frames exist right now from beginning to
end as you say and only the characters
on the film are isolated to the
particular frame in which they exist
until the next frame creates the
illusion of movement and change and
continuation and momentum. This is a
similar analogy to physical reality.
Continuity is simply your projection,
your illusion. In that sense, your rate
of flow of transformation of creating a
series of different nows in a different
format, in a different shape, even from
what you call a movement here to here
may actually be the creation of many
millions of different realities in
between to create the illusion of
continuous movement from one point to
another. No one really moves anywhere.
No one really goes anywhere. motion in
that sense is completely a true
illusion. The idea is that you simply
recreate the reality over and over and
over again discontinuously now now now
now to create the idea the sensation of
physical reality that defines its
coordinates by space and time.
Now the
idea also is that we have discussed that
you since you exist only now only in the
present experientially actually create the past
experientially actually create the past
as well as the future from the
present because now is the only time in
which you actually ever really exist.
The idea of memory, whether it be
something in your particular present
life in the past or whether it be the
idea and notion of a particular past
life in the
linear let us say film of your
existence. All of that memory is still
created in the present. When you create
memory, you are not actually in a sense
thinking in the past. You are thinking
of an idea called the past but you are
creating that memory in the present. All
creation takes place in the present
always. It is always to put it very
simply now and it is never any other
time but now. That is the only
experiential time that exists.
Now this visual aid can show to some
degree by a mechanical
analogy how the idea of the
simultaneousness of all your lives can
be interpreted in a linear fashion in
the physical reality you are used to
experiencing. But
remember this is simply an analogy for
this particular visual aid is in a sense
simply a two dimensional
presentation of a
threedimensional representation of a
representation of a
fourthdimensional
concept of an infinitely
interdimensional structure.
So while many different degrees of
dimensionality are removed from this
particular mechanical visual aid, it
will serve to get across the basic idea
of the
mechanism. Are you ready?
Do you want me to show?
Yes. Very good.
Now what you will first observe is
simply a representation
of either now you can take this either
way many different
lives each one represented by hexagonal
format of six arrows pointing in six
directions leading to every other
hexagonal arrow pattern. So each of
those can be a life. Each of those can
be a different version of you in a
different dimension. Past, present,
future, alternate reality. Call it what
you will. It does not matter. It is a
holographic representation of the
simultaneous existence of every single
probable reality and possible way that
you can exist and do exist on every
dimension there is to exist upon. It is
referred to as a holographic matrix.
Holographic in the sense that every
point in that sense in one sense is
equal to every other point. From any
point you can proceed in any direction
and in a sense all points connect up to
all other points. In other words each
spot contains the information of the
whole and basically is a microcosm of
the whole. Now this represents the view
that your non-physical oversoul has when
it looks at all the different lives that
you have simultaneously going on. It
simply looks and says all right 1934
199200 all these ideas are all
simultaneous to the oversoul. They are
all extensions of the oversoul.
simultaneous extensions in much the same
way that your fingers are simultaneous
extensions of your hand. Each finger has
independence in a sense and represents a
different idea, but they all lead back
to the hand are all part of one
idea. Now, if you will apply or hold up
the karmic overlay template, what you
can see is a symbol, a strip that
contains a particular idea. This is the
representation of physical reality.
Linear spacetime with arrows moving only
in one
direction. The central arrow represents
your idea of now. The two arrows in that
sense on what you would call your left
represent past and the two on what you
would call your right represent the
future. In this indication is simply
indicated past negative 1, past negative
-2, future positive one, future
positive2 to indicate different either
moments in one life or different
lifetimes. You can take it either way.
This chart can be used to represent
whole lives or moments within one life.
You follow along so far? Amen. Now if
you overlay the idea of the karmic template
overlay the idea of the karmic template
upon the holographic matrix, you will
understand more precisely that karma is
simply literally pattern recognition.
That is all it is. It is a pattern
overlay that you decide represents the
present life you are living.
You thus by overlaying that particular
format or pattern or template upon the
present idea you now decide to be
determine with that overlay what
connections you have in the past and
what connections you have in the future.
For it illuminates a particular set of
arrows in other simultaneous existence,
both now that allows you to call it the
past and simultaneous existence that now
allows you to call it the future.
Because you are looking through the
filter of the overlay, you now only see
these simultaneous lifetimes in a linear
fashion. Before, now, after. because
that is the definition of physical
reality and the definition of the karmic
overlay. It is a pattern that you impose
upon yourself. Now this is why in having
chosen that particular pattern you can
see mechanically that you have
determined which simultaneous other
lives will be represented as past lives
and future lives to this life you are
creating. angle the karmic
angle the karmic
template. Now you can say that this is
perhaps another idea, another lifestyle,
another personality that you chose to
be. Understand how being that other
personality still allows there to be the
bleedth through of the holographic
matrix to create still the illusion of a
temporal momentum.
But now you have a different set of past
lives, a different set of future lives.
And the new person that you are
literally determines the fact that you
will then relate to a completely
different past, a completely different
future. So the idea of having this life
now and then assuming that perhaps you
die and
reincarnate doesn't necessarily mean
that the life you're having now will
literally be directly connected to the
next life you have. You can actually
diversify very radically by altering the
idea sufficiently so that the next
person you are will actually have a
different past life than the one you're
living now.
understand the mechanics and simply see
that the lineage always follows suit.
And also if you take this as an analogy
for even the moments in one life, then
the change in direction can represent
changes in the patterns or ideas that
you are being at any given moment. And
you can see that by a change in the
pattern, you change the feedback all the
way back and all the way forward and
create literally within one life a
different past, a different future for
the vibrational frequency you have
dialed yourself to at this particular
moment. And also it shows you how in the
present what you call the center
point small changes in direction create
large changes in the past and large
changes in the future because you can
see the sweep of the arc is a mechanical
analogy that a small divergence of
pattern in the present will compound
itself both in the future and in the
past to create large variations. You
understand the angle of incidence?
The idea therefore is to recognize that
you do not have to create
overwhelmingly obvious changes in your
present to create overwhelmingly obvious
changes in your past and your future. A
small divergence in any direction in any
frequency in your present will manifest
as a widely different idea or outcome in
what you call the future and a widely
different idea and outcome in what you
call the past. Because as you understand
past you have based your experience on
what will happen on what has happened.
This is the illusion you have created.
So simply understand that if you change
yourself even minutely in the present
and that small change creates a great
divergence in the outcome in your future
then it by definition there must be a
large divergence in your past to have
initiated the type of foundation that
would create such a large divergence in
your future. You understand?
The idea simply is to recognize that you
are multi-dimensional,
multi-dimensional,
multi-directional and any subtle change
you make within any one life or any
change you make from life to life will
connect you to a whole other series of
incidents and events that have to do
with the life you are living at the
present. So when we talk about the idea
of what your past lives were, that does
not necessarily mean that in the next
life you have, if you have one, that you
will have the same lineage. And it does
not necessarily mean that the quote
unquote past life you were has the same
future life that you consider yourself
to be. They branch out
multi-dimensionally, holographically in
all dimensions at once. And you can take
any route, any path, and they will all
be real, all directly connected to you.
Whatever idea you are being at the
moment, determines utterly any other
ideas that are capable of being
perceived as being connected to you now,
whether they are in what you call the
past or the future. You are the dial,
and the dial for your reality is always
in the present with you. It is never in
the past. It is never in the future. It
may in your terms affect what you call
the past and affect what you call the
future. But that control and that
malleability is with you in the present.
You all follow along. Does this
mechanical analogy illuminate some of
the ideas for you that we have
discussed? Thank you. We can go into this perhaps
Thank you. We can go into this perhaps
further at another time or perhaps
according to anything you might
specifically wish to apply to this idea,
but for now it will do and it will sink
into your consciousness on whatever
level it needs to. Thank you very much,
assistant. And at this timing, in exchange for your
And at this timing, in exchange for your
willingness to allow us to share with
you the reflections of the ideas that
you all are, we will ask you now how may
I serve you?
Hello, Bishar. Hello. I'd like some more
information on the pink Amazon River
dolphins. All right.
Um, I've been drawn to them and how do
they differ from the ocean dolphins or
how are they dissimilar?
They are in a sense an aspect obviously
of the overall dolphin consciousness a
segment of the other alien if I may
species upon your planet aside from
humans which all citations are in that
sense. They to some degree have a
similar relationship to what you call
your typical ocean
dolphins as what you call your Native
American culture has to the mainstream
of your human society. They are in that
sense the dimensional wanderers. They
are more instinctively based. All
dolphins are in a sense. But certain
types of oceanic dolphins do have a
capacity for what you would call reason
that is similar to your way of thinking.
Whereas the idea of the Amazon dolphins
are far more let us say
original to your planet in that sense.
They are far more naturally attached,
far more instinctively attached and can
wander far more readily through
different dimensions and gateways. They
are not so strongly completely attached
to the present level of what you call
your humanity as are the ocean dolphins.
They are connected to many archetypal
segments of your overall human
consciousness and therefore can be very
conducive in quote unquote reflecting
and symbolizing and luring you into
associations with your let us say old
ways your natural ways and the ways you
are now learning to be to reconnect
with. They are very primal in that sense
very clear in that sense but almost
entirely instinctive.
You follow me? Yes. So it can form a
reconnection for many of you to that
pulse of the earth. Whereas the oceanic
dolphins, although they are connected to
that, will appeal more to the idea of
your dream realities within reason
within the mentality band. Whereas the
Amazon dolphins will make connections
within the emotional bands and the
etheric bands. You follow me? Yes. Does
that assist you? Yes, it does. And would
the pink ones fall into the same
category of what? that you were talking
the differences the pink ones are what
we were referring to. Oh okay. Okay. So
if they entice you and they attract you
then that is simply archetypally
representative of a certain portion of
your consciousness that you are
integrating within yourself. Now attract
yourself to them in whatever way shape
or form your imagination so desires. If
you wish to go and play with them by all
means do so. But remember they are in a
very way magical. And in that sense, not
that anything else is not, but they are
more prone to the idea of intuition. And
therefore, you may find that if you go
and attach yourself to that particular
symbol, you may find yourself wandering
in and out of dimensional gates that you
will not necessarily be able to use your
reason to understand, but which you can
feel with your heart. You follow me?
Yes. They are very similar to the idea
of the vibration of rose quartz, the
heart energy directly.
Uh-huh. Okay. Thank you. Thank you very
much. Sharing.
Hello, Bashar. And to you. I was here
last week for the first time and I had a
friend with me and we both put our names
in line and we're leftovers, but he
couldn't be here tonight. So, I'm going
to ask his leftover question also.
Just a couple of months ago, he lost his
father. All right. And I've been doing a
lot of reading uh in the area of
theosophy. And I am interested. We've talked about
And I am interested. We've talked about
the ideas I've come across he and I and
in theosophy they say that the soul goes
to a kind of blissful rest uh within a
certain period of time a short period of
time after it dies. In a sense it will
depend upon the belief systems that were
most strong at the point of death.
Uhhuh. Okay. So I think he's interested
to know if his father is really at peace
if there's any illumination you could
give in that area.
I mean maybe not specifically his
father. Not that you're necessarily in
touch with that spirit, but generally is
that the idea first of all is to
recognize once again that whatever the
individual's strongest belief system was
at the point of death will usually be
what they experience at that moment
because then you become a thought form
in a world of thought form and there is
no longer the time lag in the creation
of a thought into a thing. So the idea
first of all is that whatever they most
strongly expected to see is usually what
they see. And sometimes if they had a
strong expectation of something that
they may find unpleasant then seeing it
may shock them out of having that
particular expectation very quickly. I
would think so. So the idea is to
recognize that there will be individuals
who will always assist that individual
as far as that individual is willing to
be assisted. You recognize that the
state of bliss that you are referring to
is the ability to be willing to
recognize that you utterly on all levels
and particularly very quickly in the
quote unquote non-physical level create
utterly create your reality that you
experience around you based upon the
strongest belief that you have of what
that reality will be. So if an
individual is open enough to understand
that they did not have to expect one
particular experience upon death then
they may be willing to receive the
assistance from other individuals to
show them that they can really
experience anything they want and in
that sense that is bliss. You follow me?
Yes I I think I do. One moment.
Once again, repeat time frame of death.
May 5th,
1987. His name was Albert Fineberg.
Immediate impression is that there
are perhaps three but one very strong
individual that they have been
associated before in many other lives.
what might have been referred to as a
very strong
strong
feminine energy that preceded
them that is willing to share of her if
I may experience. I say if I may because
a soul is no longer in that sense
strictly male or female but will present
herself to him as female because it will
be the vibration he will be most
familiar with upon arriving in that area
that vibration and this female will have
begun to present different ideas. It is
our perception that this individual is
in your terms catching on rather
rapidly. He was a smart man. The idea also is
He was a smart man. The idea also is
that it is completely utterly up to each
and every one of you to decide what you
wish to do from that point forward.
Whether or not in your terms to
reincarnate, although of course from
some of those higher points of view, you
understand that it is not reincarnation
but simply a different focus of
simultaneous existence. But the decision
has not yet been made. One
moment. There seems to be some strong
consideration of expression of musical
aptitudes that may or may not be
explored by this
individual either within what you call a
reincarnation or in assistance as for a
while performing as a spirit guide for
those that may in your terms still be
physically alive. All right. Perhaps
most strongly the sun.
Oh, you understand? Yes. Yes.
Our immediate perception, but this can
always change because time in that sense
is fluid and there is no solid future to
predict is that the individual may
choose to explore right now some of
these ideas for approximately what you
would call the next two years before
making a strong decision. The individual
being Albert.
So they may be in contact through dream
by functioning as a spirit guide for
approximately two years while they
develop their own understanding of what
it is he would like to do. You follow
me? Yes. In other words, he will serve
an apprenticeship of being of service
and in so serving will give himself more
understanding of the desires he has to
express himself either within another
incarnation or to simply project himself
to other dimensions of reality. All
right. And your question, my question, if we
And your question, my question, if we
take evolution as a fact, at least our
present understanding is that evolution
is the probability. Yes. Although your
present understanding of what you call
evolution is somewhat incomplete. I'm
I'm sure. But if as much as we know
right now, evolution is and we started
as pure physical amieba, bacteria, etc.,
and then grew from there, at what point
did the spirit join the physical entity?
Thank you. First of all, recognize that
all consciousness in a sense is spirit
and all physical reality is
consciousness and is spirit. So physical
reality is in a sense spirit in physical
terms. But we understand what you mean.
The idea is a blending of the two ideas
you are now dealing with in your society
that you call evolution and creationism.
Because the idea was that there was in
your terms physiological evolution up to
a certain
point between what you would call six
and three million of your years ago. And
then your overall collective
consciousness combined as one idea
projected itself reincarnationally to
the vibration of your earth at that
time. Saw in the evolutionary patterns
upon your planet a suitable host
representation for your consciousness.
And then mutations were directed by your
consciousness to allow that
physiological form to become able to
connect to your consciousness to carry
your consciousness into physical reality
in this particular vibratory
frequency. You follow me? Yes, I do. So
between about 3 and 6 million years ago,
this happened as all right. As you count
time generally. Yeah. The idea simply is
that a suitable vehicle was observed and
was mutated to become even more suitable
and then you began to project your
consciousness into it and in a sense
quote unquote not meaning that you are
imprisoned within it but in a sense
locked yourself into association with
that physiological form. Now many
changes have taken place since that time
as well and some of these changes are
the product of interaction with what you
now colloquially call extraterrestrial
species as well. All right. I thank you
very much. Thank you very much. All
right. Shutting.
Hi. Hi.
Um, recently I I had something occur and
uh I did something not within my
integrity and I felt really terrible.
Oh. All right. So, you did two things
outside of integrity. The first thing
and then feeling guilty about it.
That's the Catholic way.
All right.
And that's what I wanted to speak to you
about. All right. There there are two
things. One is I I said, "Well, when I
did something that's just for lack of
saying integrity all over again, when I
did something bad, I said
I said um all of a sudden I felt like
everything that I'd ever done that was
good and every time I just felt light
and like life was wonderful, I felt like
it was a lie." All right. And I thought
and I was going, "God, where is this
coming from? What you
couldn't be me?" Yes. And um so then I
looked back and and I saw that when I
first started finding out about the
Catholic religion and baby Jesus and all
that stuff, right? Well, I wanted to be
a saint, but finding out that I I felt a
saint had to be pure at heart, which I
realized very quickly I wasn't.
So, well, I do mean little rotten
things, stuff like that. All right. And
um God, this is you can be a mean little
rotten saint. Thank you. Thank you.
[Music]
Maybe you can get your halo in
installments.
Well, that was the other thing I was
going to talk to you about. The way to
get pure at heart once you're not pure
at heart, the way to get there via
Catholicism, which I haven't been for a
long time. I didn't even know I had all
this stuff still there, um, was uh, you
suffer. you you crucify yourself very
much like Christ did. We understand the
analogy, but remember that the idea of
the Christ consciousness acting out that
particular idea of suffering was for the
point that neither of any of you from
that point forward had to do the same
idea. So what do we do now? It is up to
you. You see the idea now is that it is
completely your option because in what
you call the enactment of the
crucifixion was played out all of the
culmination of your need to suffer. And
now if you choose to suffer, it is
completely your choice.
So do you prefer it? I just prefer not
to do anything outside my integrity. All
right. Doesn't always happen that way.
You can create it to be that way if you
wish. Yeah. I mean, I'm working on it,
but I still tend to go back to if I do
something that's not within my integrity
to, you know, do something against
myself. All right. All right. Mayor
Kulpa, what the idea simply is to remember that
what the idea simply is to remember that
if you do recognize that you have done
something outside of your integrity and
you no longer prefer to do that, well,
first of all, in a sense, you do in fact
only add to the lack of integrity by
berating yourself for it rather than
simply using it as a positive reflection
that now you know something you no
longer prefer to do. It's kind of
godlike. Well, you are, you know. Mhm.
The idea simply is to recognize that if
you do something outside of integrity
and it gives you the opportunity to
recognize you no longer wish to do that,
then the recognition in and of itself is
all the absolving you need.
Understand? I understand. Therefore, if
you simply know, to put it very simply,
that you are always doing the best you
know how to do at any given moment and
that you are always to the best of your
knowledge acting within integrity, then
should you discover that for some reason
you haven't been, then allow yourself to
be in your terms rejoiceful that the
path you took allowed you to see it so
that you could take the opportunity to
recognize what you no longer prefer to
do. And then you will understand that in
having allowed yourself to see what you
were doing was an act outside of
integrity that in the overall sense you
must have been acting within integrity
to have given yourself an opportunity to
see that you were acting outside of it.
I got it. Thank you. It can be that
simple. Yes, I agree. I I just got real
confused there for a few days. I was
like, "All right, some of you enjoy
that. It's fun."
But remember that confusion is a limbo
state to give you time to assess other
probable realities that you may prefer
over the one you are living. Yes. And I
couldn't come up with another one. So
that's why I was here. Uh the other
thing I wanted to share with you um
which while I was exploring this same
idea, I was looking at the idea of like
saints, they're holy. If you say so.
Well, here's what I realized. I mean for
me anyway the way that I created at this
point is the idea was not to be wholly
hol it was to be w thank you
very astute well you're welcome and
remember in that sense and in no way
shape or form is this meant derogatorily
to your species but saints were human
too thank you thank you
thank you thank you
[Applause]
Jenny thank you for applauding
yourselves. You deserve it. Hi Bashar,
my friend. I I would like to share a
dream I had. All right. Speak up so all
can hear and ask a question. All right.
I don't haven't dreamt much in my life
that I realized you had done and the
about a week ago I had a very vivid
dream like living in it. Yes. As I am
now. Yes. I was on this spaceship that
I've been hearing about. I didn't see
anything. I just knew I was on a
spaceship. Many of you are in your dream
states. And I didn't see any objects.
And I began to wonder who I was going to
talk to or how I was going to talk to
them. And it came to me in just a
knowing way telepathically.
Yay. And I was just knew I was there.
And I all of a sudden had in my hands
three objects.
a tape which was bigger than our tapes,
a disc which is thicker than our
discs, and what they told me was a
hologram. Nice. In a case, a glass case.
I don't know what was in it, but it more
of the same as on the tape and on the
disc. Well, it answered questions. I
just knew this. It came to me. It
created things and if it got in the
wrong hands, it disappeared.
I the idea simply is a recognition that
anything that is not of the vibration of
that information, it is simply
unfindable, invisible.
I see. Yet it is all recorded within you
in a very crystalline way. That is what
those things represented is the
information and the knowingness that is
always recorded in you. Anytime you are
of a particular frequency, a particular
vibration, you always contain all the
information you need to be who you need
to be at that moment. Always. I see.
The dream continued or it was an
additional dream. All right. Where my
wife had a meeting in Long Beach and I
was worried about her driving and all of
a sudden I knew a spaceship was going to
take her there, which it did. I didn't
see the spaceship at that point. I
worried whether they would pick her up
and instantly I was in Long Beach
watching her being retrieved. Yes. As we
have said, when you are dreaming, you
are in the dream realm, the dream
reality. You may call it the astral or
ether atheric realm. And the thought is
instantly the thing. Well, I I didn't
see much of this except these three
objects and the spaceship, but I just
had a knowing. I knew this. I just knew.
Dice. Now, the question that I wanted to ask
Now, the question that I wanted to ask
was, uh, we have a a Down syndrome boy
in the family that we love very dearly.
All right. And he's been with us for
just short of 20 years, but we wanted to
find if you could give us
an the purpose of our sharing with him
and him sharing with us in our family.
This individual is very strongly
connected to the extraterrestrial source
of your
dreams and is interacting on a level let
us say above what you are used to
interacting upon in your dream reality.
Next time you have such a dream, look
up literally into a higher frequency and
you will recognize him there. For he is
projecting into many different
dimensions of experience and has created
a type of limitation and focus in the
physical life to actually push him into
those realms much faster to allow him to
maintain his connection to a realm that
is more familiar to him than your earth
dimension is. And he has attached
himself in that way to you to be of
representative and reflective
significance and assistance to allow you
to explore the dimensions and the realms
that have to do with who you desire to
be in your life. You are a triad, the
three of you in that way and have been
many times before. It has been a very
strong teacher in the past in many
different ways, especially in what you
would call adalantean times. Individuals
many times will take upon themselves
certain afflictions or restrictions to
push themselves in certain dimensional
directions that they would otherwise
perhaps not move in if they had more
freedom in physical
reality. His needs and his services are
such that he has to project into the
dream dimension to be of best assistance
and so he has given himself a symbol to
direct him where he needs to be. There
can be as we perceive the energy now a
very strong and profound change that may
occur in what you call approximately the
23rd year for 23 will be one of the symbols
year for 23 will be one of the symbols
representative of the interconnectedness
of the holographic matrix what you call
synchronicity in life and many new ideas
may explode upon the scene and that
individual may choose to explode in
another direction altogether
interdimensionally. Mhm. But for now, in
what you call the triad of years that
remain, allow yourself to realize there
will be high degrees of acceleration in
your dream reality if you wish from this
point forward. And that some of them are
being directed by that individual very
strongly. For they are a very strong
spirit and very clear, very clear and
very loosely connected to physical
reality. I see.
Next time, think of an equilateral
triangle and look up to the apex and see
what you see.
I will. Well, thank you. Thank you.
Pleasant dreams. Thank you.
Shutting dear Bashar, your introduction
fit right into my scenario
I was going to give you today.
It's interesting. Well, there was good
news and there was bad news. Uh the good
news was as a child I knew I had lived
before. The bad news was I had no one to
talk to about it. Now you do. Yes.
Things have changed. Nice. Okay. Anyway,
uh when I was about 6 years old, I was
little kid. I was very able mentally,
physically, me um emotionally. And I was
sent to a camp for the summer and we
were down there was a river and we were
was at the beach
and I don't know if you know what the
mill on the floss is or not but it's a
wheel that goes around into the water
and it pulls out one hell of an undertoe
and there was a fence quite some
distance away from it which naturally we
were told not even to get near to and
further down the beach is where we did
our swimming. All right. As this, excuse
the expression, young boy that I was, I
got not only close to that fence, th I
went under the fence and through it. And
the next thing I know, I was caught in
this whirlpool undertoe and I was being
drowned and going down, down, down. And
I says, "No way. This is not going to
happen to me." How exciting. Or some
words to that effect. Nice. And the next
thing I knew, my head was popping out of
the water way on the other side, the
safe side. And our counselor's lifeguard
grabs me and starts balling me out for
being so close to the fence. Guys, no
way could I explain to him not only was
I not close to the fence, I was on the
other side being dragged down. And
that's when I kind of put this whole
experience aside cuz I really couldn't
communicate about it until many, many,
many years later. When I teleported once
again, guys, it is something becoming
far more common in your society now. But
when I teleported that time, it brought
the recall of having done this when I
was a six-year-old boy. Nice. The only
thing I recall, as I said, looking back
prior to me even being 6 years old, it
was amazing some of the abilities and
the awarenesses I had. Not really. It is
natural in your children. Well, it was
except after I did this teleporting and
putting on the forgetter. Nice. My tone
level, emotions, my abilities dropped.
Yes. uh my Scientological years I thought
uh my Scientological years I thought
maybe well it was just emotion dropping
but listening to you this
past year I came across and especially
what you're discussing today my
particular view is I shifted from one
reality to another to another a
different world so forth you all do that
many times a day
many times a day I kind of like the old
one I this this this one was a little
harder to live with than the old one
before I really it had to be absolutely
representative of the vibration that you
were. Okay.
Absolutely. Now you can change that
vibration again and pop into whatever
world you wish.
I think I'll do it with the younger
body. But it was very interesting. This
was what I was going to mention today
and you came up with your scenario and
thank you. Well, thank you very much for
allowing us to reflect the crystallin
multiaceted consciousness that all of
you are discovering yourselves to be.
You are all very loosely connected.
loosely very loosely. Thank you again.
Thank you.
Shooting. Hello Bashar. Strawberry.
Bashar. I realize that for some time
you've been reflecting to us the what
works for you and your density. Nice.
And I realize that you've been doing
this because we have chosen to transcend
from what we consider to be our density
closer to an approximation of what yours
is. ice. But I have been getting the
feeling lately that you are not
um articulately aware of the mastery of
limitation that we have achieved perhaps
and that there are um although we have a
a philosophical draw by painting where
we want to go and where we are there
seem to be some intricacies that are not
workable from simply taking the point of
view of what works for you. At least
this is my feeling here. All right, fair
enough. Okay. And uh one of these intricacies
Okay. And uh one of these intricacies
seems to be um what Humber defined as a
stimulus response mechanism. Now I know
you from a consciousness level you're
saying that this occurs simply very fast
and is not within our conscious level of
awareness and it probably has the same
karmic patterns of the of the type you
were portraying to some degree. Yes. But
I think the key ice is workability. Yes.
Always you know what works for the
individual. Yes. And you've given us the
tool of imagination to define what works
for us individually. Yes.
And
uh I'm getting the feeling that
um we need to match frequencies a little
bit more in terms of what works some of
these intricacies.
But more along the direction, the
concept is to come up with more
workability in terms in my own personal
case in terms Oh, I love that. That's
beautiful. Are you giving yourself a
homework assignment? That's very nice.
Yeah, I got all your telepathic.
Yes, that's very nice. I'm sorry. Sorry,
I just got a whole telepathic message.
It translates into more spirit of play,
develops more workability. Thank you
very much. Thank you. Good to talk to
you again. And you shooting.
you shooting.
Good evening, Bash to you. Good day.
Thank you. I would like to share an
experience with you that I had with
extraterrestrials. In June, I went to Grand Junction and I
In June, I went to Grand Junction and I
was visiting some friends who I'm
involved with in a meditation group. I
was staying in a home uh at the base
of the Grand Junction Monument. The
first evening that I was there, I got
into bed and I was lying there in bed
and all of a sudden the bedroom door
started swinging open and closed against
the carpet. About this time, I was just
looking in kind of an amazement and I
rolled over towards the other side of
the room and looked out the window and
there were two lights that shot
horizontally across the sky, went over
the cliff formation and the next I
couldn't see what happened. Then the
next thing I heard was a loud rumble.
Then two lights came out from the side
of the cliff and they were bouncing
around for about a half hour and I was
just like mesmerized by the whole event.
All right. And I went to sleep and this
happened for five nights. All five
nights that I was there. Nice. The
second night instead of seeing two light
shoot out, I saw one light. And um since
then when I returned home in on July
4th, I was looking out my bedroom window
and I was watching the fireworks across
the valley. Hi. And my little dog was in
the room with me and she started barking
out the other window and I went to look
to see what it was and I saw another
light appear and it was very bright and
then all of a sudden it disappeared and
then it was back and disappeared and did
this about seven times and then it was
gone again. So what I would like is if
you have some insight or understanding
for me what this is in regards to. How
does it allow you to feel? Uh, and what
do you wish to do with that feeling?
Are you inspired to do something in
particular? I'm not quite sure. I feel very um just
I'm not quite sure. I feel very um just
relaxed
and calm and
uh and in calm and in
relaxation, what can't you do?
Think, analyze. All
right. But what can you do? Um, explore,
explore, anything. Anything. Right.
Now, what do you wish to do?
Um, and where do you wish to do it?
Do you wish to remain in your present
area? Is there somewhere else you wish
to go more strongly?
Uh, I'm not quite sure. Um, all right.
I I do wish to be in service to people
and in what way?
Um, in actually in learning um I am very
interested in learning several different
um subjects and I'm very um interested
in passing it to other people. What have
you learned about fear?
That it's limiting. All
right. Can you assist individuals to
unlearn fear?
Yes. Do you believe you have unlearned fear?
Do you believe you have unlearned fear?
At times. All
right. Enough so that you can assist
other individuals to unlearn theirs
while you continue to unlearn yours.
Yes. And once again, in what way do you
And once again, in what way do you
specifically wish to be of
service? For what you are in that sense
recognizing are identifications with
individuals you have made agreements
with. That is what the lights
represent. And the dog represents
service.
I see. In what way do you wish to be of
service? In what way do you wish to
fulfill the agreements you have
made? How far? Or how fast do you wish
to go?
I guess as fast as I allow myself. Which
is now? All
right. In what way? Um, what excites
you? I had a feeling this question would come
I had a feeling this question would come
up.
Um, then you are aware of the
conversations and communication that
went on during those interactions. Yeah,
I guess I am. Yes, you are. So, what
excites you? And when will you do it?
I don't seem to have answers right here.
Um, do you know what excites you at all?
do you know what excites you at all?
Sometimes I'm really not sure. All
right. That's true.
That's true.
I I seem to um go from one direction to
the next. I'm not staying in one certain
area and working with that. It's my mind
is always thinking about what's next and
what else is there to do. What else is
there to learn? All right. And um but
everything you will ever learn and
everything you will ever do will be done
in the present.
Correct. So one of the ideas you were
being told and shared within those
conversations and connections was to
remain in the present and you will get
wherever you want to go the quickest
because it all happens here not out
there. Nothing happens in the future. It
happens in the present.
Okay? There is nowhere to get to that is
any more rewarding than where you
are. It will be different. you will
expand and you will grow. But if at any
given moment you are willing to simply
be completely in the moment with
whatever you are
experiencing then all the information
all the opportunities and all the
ability to act upon the opportunities
will be yours in the present if you
remain in the present.
That's true. This is the gist of the
energy as you say that was being sent to
you. The awakening of that realization
within you, the commitments in a sense that you
you, the commitments in a sense that you
have chosen to make. The agreements you
have chosen to fulfill and the
identifications with those portions of
yourself that you have simply as a
member of your species segregated in the
past and can now integrate in the
present. You are as fast as one of those
You are as fast as one of those
lights in every way, shape, and form. In
a sense, you are one of those lights in
more ways than one.
Mhm. And you were reflecting something
back to
yourself from in a sense your own
future.
Thank you. Well, thank you. I had
nothing to do with it.
Now, does that serve you? Yes, it does.
Remember simply that the idea of what
excites you the most does not
necessarily have to be something other
than what you are capable of doing right
now. For everything else in that sense
is
pointless. And if you simply are excited
about what you are doing right now, you
will generate all the ability you need
to be able to do anything else that will
excite you that will come along.
Understand? Fits perfect. Thank you very
much. Thank you.
Nightlight. Night lights. Night
lights. Night lights. Think night
lights. That is the vibration that can
allow you to
connect very strongly in your dream
reality. Nightlights. Yes.
Uh, I know you communicate with uh
telepathically, but on on earth we
communicate many ways. One of them I saw
yesterday was via t-shirts. I I saw a
Bashar quote on a t-shirt that was uh
something like you get you don't get peace by
like you get you don't get peace by
hating war. You get peace by loving
peace, guys. And I was dwelling on that
today. It seems like with all our
limitations on this planet, this is
knowledge that we now have on our planet
that apparently the positive energy and
the plleadenss when they were trying to
stop the negative energy and the Orion
didn't have cuz they put their attention
on the negative energy instead of on
their positive energy.
Guys, now you are blending. That is the
whole idea of the transformation upon
your planet. You are the fulcrum to
blend and balance the idea of those
energies and allow it to move in a
positive direction. Mhm. Anyway, the question I
direction. Mhm. Anyway, the question I
wanted to ask was I'm curious if your
this individual signature vibration is
it always the same no matter what
density he's on or does it change when
he changes density? It changes but there
will always be the signature pattern
that will be recognizable. I see. Thank
you. Thank
you. Sharing
Bashar. Hello. Hello. Going to Sedona
for the convergence. I hope you'll see
you there. Have a good time. Why do you
need to hope?
Okay, I'll see you there. Boon Canyon.
Maybe. Okay. My my qu my question.
Yes. Recently I have been um uh
listening to some tapes and doing some
studying on the subject of immortality
and um the regression of aging as we
know it on this planet at this point
and it's come to my attention that the
thymus plays a very large role the
thymus gland plays a very large role in
this and also that uh the thymus in a
large part your entire endocrine system
does. Yes. Okay. Um, well, my question
dealing with the thymus is that with
most of us, as science tells us now, the
thymus gland uh goes to sleep around
puberty and doesn't really wake up
again. And it's No, no, it just changes
jobs. Oh, really? Yes. Oh, can you tell
me about that? It begins to secrete
other kinds of chemical compounds which
dissolve themselves so thoroughly, you
have not even discovered where they are
coming from yet. Even though some of you
are aware that they exist, you simply do
not know what is manufacturing them
because you think that that particular
gland has shut down, but it hasn't. Oh,
and some of them have to do with some of
the changes that you go through. You
mean aging changes to some degree? Yes.
And therefore recognize that when you
get in touch with living in the moment
and get in touch with the idea of
subsisting off of more of the energy as
you accelerate your vibrational
frequency, you will begin to recognize
that these patterns can become
selective. Certain ones will cease,
certain ones will stop, certain ones
will continue, certain ones will expand.
And in this way you can recognize that
it is the regulatory system in general
though it is connected to other glands
in your body and other hormonal
secretions as well. But that the thymus
along with what you call the pituitary
will begin to regulate a type of dance
of
balance to assess what your thought
patterns, your attitudes, your
behavioral beliefs are all about and to
inject the appropriate chemical hormones
to represent what you believe most
strongly is the pattern of electrical
activity within your body that
represents your self-awareness, your
self-image. I see. So my thought on that would would
I see. So my thought on that would would
be that um taking and paying in
meditation a lot of attention and
putting a light for instance maybe as a
as a symbol on the area of the thymus
and and then maybe as you're saying
connecting it with the pituitary would
that be a helpful meditation one way
that will work for some people. It will
not work for everyone. Uhhuh. I see.
Just as any idea that you might call any
treatment for any disease will usually
not work for everyone.
Okay. Thank you very But if that is what
you are attracted to, then experiment
with it. We perceive that you will
probably make many changes in it, but
for now experiment with that. It will
lead you to a further understanding of
your glandular system. Uhhuh. And the
thymus is like right behind the heart,
right? Is that what I
In this area inward. Yes. Upper upper
upper. Okay. Thank you very much,
Bashar. Thank you.
Ching. How you doing, dude? Just fine,
buddy. Life is rad.
Um, say Bashar, you know, I know that a
lot of people invite you down to uh
visit them and uh you usually refer to
the timing and I'm not going to invite
you down before the timing, but when the
timing is uh propitious, uh, come by my
place. We'll crack open a couple beers,
catch a Star Trek uh episode, maybe pick
up a couple of chicks, you know, have
some fun.
He does this, you know.
Because he likes to have fun. Yes.
And so do we. Yes.
However, as we understand some of the
references you have made, there are a
few suggestions that we could
suggestions that we could
make to allow the starship you are
referring to to travel more like a ship
we are familiar with. The starship um
Enterprise you mean? Yes. Go ahead.
Well, recognize the idea that it does
not really in your terms take any time
to get anywhere.
Right now, the only way such a ship
could exist is if, in your terms, the
drive flickered on and
off, allowing them to go just a small
amount of space at a time. Mhm. So that
it would create the illusion of the need
for long distance traveling even at what
you would call a rate higher than light,
so to speak, which doesn't literally
occur. Yeah. So, you're saying their
warp drives are uh somewhat warped in
the actual
uh concept of space travel. You may say
that. Yeah,
I'll be sure to mention that to them
next time I talk to them. All right. Uh
my question relates to your earlier uh
discussion about the blending of the
idea of create creationism and um
evolution. Evolution. Yes. And I'm
wondering how the process that we
created on this planet for ourselves
compares to processes that other
civilizations have created on their own
planets such as well yours or any other
um ours is similar, not identical but
similar. Although there are some that we
have come across that are widely
divergent such
as such as the
idea of what may be called remote
control evolution. There is a society we are
evolution. There is a society we are
familiar with that allow the idea of a
form of puppeteering to occur if you
wish in the evolutionary chain as they
observed it while not quote unquote
attached to the physical form and in a
sense truly played out the entire
evolutionary process while observing it
from above. Yeah, that is one way.
So the evolutionary process, how far
does the evolutionary process take the
development of the physical being or
physical uh manifestation? It can take
it all the way from what you call first
density into non-physicality. It depends
upon the drive, the needs, the reasons,
the impetus, the directions. You follow
me? Yes. So I guess my question was more
along the lines of uh prior to the uh
assumption of a sensient consciousness
um where does where does the
evolution at what point in the
evolutionary process does the sensient
consciousness take over if you will in
the framework that you are referring to
that we may call most common colloquial
between us it will be when
The neuronic mass capable of sustaining
and representing consciousness in mentality
representing consciousness in mentality
format has reached
approximately 6 to 700 cubic
centimeters. Oh yeah, that makes a lot
of sense.
Okay. Do you understand? You're talking
about the size of the brain, the volume
of the brain. Okay. How about although
not all beings would be representational
of what you would call a brain format,
there can be other modalities that still
represent the necessary amount of mass
but do not contain it in the format you
would recognize as a brain. Okay. Some
of them will contain it throughout the
entire structure of the body. Such as an
earthworm has a rudimentary brain which
extends along the length similar to that
idea. Yes. Okay. Well, how about
relating it in terms of u our evolution
um with respect to various evolutionary
steps? We've got uh labels such as
chroman or chromagnon
um
neanderthol uh
pithicanthroperectus things like that.
Where would
that where would the assumption of the
consciousness occur within that frame?
It can still vary but it will require as
our perception understands it a minimum
of approximately 900 cubic centimeters.
The average will be around what you
would call 1,200. See I don't know how
to relate the volume of the brain to the
the stages that I just listed. Can you
help me there? Yours is approximately
1150.
Thank you. Hey I am speaking in general
of all of you.
Yeah. Okay. Okay. So you're saying um
the assumption is what' you say 9,000
900 900 I mean okay and uh which
promagnon as you understand that
approximately was 1320
that's bigger I for different
reasons different expressions in
different ways what you call
analysis has in your terms reduced the
need for some poor ions of activity
within the brain which which activities
is it really the intuitive ones. Okay.
So um the crow magnet had a more
intuitive yes
existence. Is it relatively common then
for this process of evolution and the
assumption of the consciousness uh
within civilization is that a relatively
common within this universal frame of
dimension? Yes. But there are many
others. Yeah. Does this assist you? It
does it. Thank you. Thank you very much.
Sharing.
Hello, dear friend. And to you. Good
day. Butterfly here. Ace. Yes. Do you
like your mountain top? Oh, I just got
back about two days ago and uh four
months of about
95% I can't say seclusion because as you
know I have communicated with you quite
often and your energy bashar. We thank
you for your love letters.
Uh, it's been four months of probably
more changes than I've had in my entire
life. Thank you. And I appreciate all
the help that you've given as far as the
vortex and the energies and the things
that you said would occur. Um, one of
the things I want to talk to you about
was I've heard your tapes every day and
I suggest everybody in the room, please
do not go out without tapes. You hear
them later. I've heard them two to three
times now. Now, now and I keep thinking,
where was I when I heard it the first
time? Exactly where you needed to be.
Right. But on the the one thing that I wanted
But on the the one thing that I wanted
to share with you is I wanted you to
name the community. I I didn't want to
be like I wanted you too. Now this is
sort of indirect but I didn't want to
tell you I didn't think you would
actually come out and give me a name to
the Well, it's your job. I know what you
did anyway. All right. On a tape three
days ago, I got him on this one. Three days
ago, I got him on this one. Three days
ago, I kept putting it out and you
wouldn't answer. And here on a tape, one
lady asked a question about a word and
you gave more definition to it. And the
minute you said it, I knew that was the
name of the mountaintop community. And
the word is Eliatar. Mount Eliatar. And
I've got not sure my pronunciation. Your
description on it was we just all sat
there with goosebumps and tears and what
have you. So, are you referring to a
word in our ancient remnant language?
That's what I Yes. Ilia. Ilia. And could
you spell it please?
If you wish, it can translate into your
phonetics as I l L I
A K. Apostrophe A R. That's what I Woo.
It means experience. Yes. I've got the
words I I took your definitions down on
it, but it actually literally means what
you see in the mirror. Yes. The mirror
reflection. You see, mirror image. So
that is Mount Eliaakar. Iliaakar.
Iliaakar. Somebody remembers. Okay.
You may if you wish. Okay. Simply use
your own translation if you wish. That's
no no but it just it felt right because
of the of the idea on it. And I just
wanted also one moment one moment
perhaps as a preference if you wish. It
can simply be
Elie. I L L I E Ele. It will in
annotated form mean the same thing.
I think that'd be easier. Elely. Yes.
Mount Elie. Not Elely. That's it. That's
it. See, you did name it. Mirror
Mountain. Mirror Mountain.
Okay. That's it. And like I said, the
four months the changes have been uh
unusual. We'll find you. Um you had
mentioned before to research Plleades as
you know. And my first question I wasn't
going to ask. I keep I've said yes and
no all the way up here and I'm going to
ask you I think yes I am. You said to
research the Pleaides landing and it
would be you sent me to the person that
does Plleades and you said it would be a
second landing there and he said don't
say too much about it. The government
has tendencies to have some corrections
on it and then when you said on one tape
you are the government I decided to hell
with it. I'll just come out and talk
about it as I feel it's necessary. All
right. And we have had some very strong
energy as you know dice. I mean it's
been hovering right over and it's the
most it it got exciting and now it's
like well will you get down here and
start talking is sort of where we're
feeling at this point and it feels very
natural. It doesn't feel unusual. One
suggestion for all of you to remember
with anything and you can apply it in
whatever way shape or form it makes most
sense to you to remember this for this
might occur and this will be something
you may be able to use if and when it
does occur. Anytime an energy that you
have focused on might seem to be
dissipating, remember it does not
necessarily mean it is dissipating if
you do not feel it as strongly. It may
only mean you are acclimating to it.
Oh yeah, you simply have a tendency to
measure thing in terms of the
differences that you are used to seeing
between different ideas rather than
recognizing that something does not have
to be represented as going away. If you
are simply getting used to it and
actually getting used to it means it's
coming closer because you are being more
equal to the vibration and as you become
absolutely equal to it it will in a
sense seem to have vanished externally
because it will be completely internal.
[Music] Okay. Thank you. All
Okay. Thank you. All
right. Uh, and and the question I've
gone back and forth on
uh, okay, come
on. You said to to research the
physiological face to face confront with
the Billy Meyers, which u, there's been
a situation connected with me and I've
got some friends that have pointed out
their viewpoint of Sime
and I've got goosebumps right now and my
stomach's rumbling and there is a
connection. I've had such strong
judgment on her and I people
mispronounce the name and I'd instantly
jump all over him. Why? I that's what I
wanted. I think I know but I want your
viewpoint.
Is there a there is some kind of a
connection? I know that because it's
just it's an instant I I don't know. No,
you are tapping into the general
consciousness stream. Yes. Why is so
judgmental of her? I mean it's just it's
so it's not sane and I see myself doing
it and jumping in conclusions and all
right you are picking up on some of the
vibrations that are also associated with
the way some of the information has been
filtered or translated into your
society. It is that negative polarity
filtration translation that you are also
picking up on because the energy has to
include both. Simply don't focus on the
negative and you will not feel it coming
through you in a judgmental way. Right?
because that's about the only major
judgmental thing that I cover very
strongly. Let me put it this way very
very colloquially. Do not necessarily
take me absolutely literally but this
may suffice to illustrate what you are
doing. Some of the connections that you
yourself have unconsciously
realized have allowed you by being
connected to your earth plane as well to
see how some of the information that the
plleadenss have presented upon your
society has translated sometimes into a
negative form. And the reason you are so
judgmental is because you are looking at
how some of this has translated
negatively and all you're doing is
looking at the pleadians and going, "How
could you let that happen?"
But it's not up to them. It's up to you.
It's up to us. It's up to us. Yes. You
will always translate the information in
the way that represents what you are
most strongly all about at any given
moment. They can do nothing about that.
Okay. It's your planet. They're they're
here to help. I realize that. Oh, yes.
They're here to aid. But they cannot
force you to understand the information
they deliver in the way they originally
deliver it. They have to let you
interpret it in the way that you choose
to interpret it as a society. That okay
that's also why at this time to some
degree there is a
small pullback on the part of all the
pullback on the part of all the
civilizations to some degree that are in
contact with your planet to let you
assess the information you already have
and see what direction you choose to
allow it to take you.
Yes. Because that will determine whether
or not you give us the ability to
continue to interact with you on certain
levels. Plain and simple.
Plain and simple.
Yes, it's that does. No, it makes a lot
more sense. But we we are really working
on a fourth density viewpoint for the
community. All right. Don't have to work
too hard. Remember, no, it's just
happening. It really I've never seen it.
You say the synchronicity has been
occurring and we're going to accelerate.
I want you to know we have a sign made
up of Bashar Boulevard. Is that okay?
It's true. In the sense simply that the
word we have chosen to represent
ourselves is one of the words in the
languages of your planet. You obviously
may use it as you wish, but it does not
have to be a direct reference to us,
which in a sense it isn't. For remember
that in one of your native Arabic
languages, the word Bashar, which I have
chosen to represent myself by, simply
means messenger.
And that is what you all are. Yes. So
use it in that way with that spirit.
Okay. Now, because we've been on this
thing, you mentioned the vortex again
come up several weeks ago and you said
the vort the main vortex had an Orion,
one of the most ancient tunnel back
connected to the Orion times. And we
were kind of curious is that because is
that exude the service to self energy or
because to some degree it is also partly
responsible for allowing you to begin to
learn to blend and balance the
polarities we have discussed. And if you
simply connect into the negative
vibration, you will find yourself being
very judgmental. If you don't, you
won't. But it is there very clearly
representative. And you can choose
either way. And the way you choose will
instantly transform into the type of
effects you create. That's what's been
happening because I've never seen myself
so judgmental in my life. It comes
flaring up and we've been very dramatic
about I see new people coming in and you
hear judgment, judgment, judgment,
judgment and it's becoming we're making
a game out of it now. All right. Very
good. That can turn it around into
positive light. Putting it in the now
and dramatizing it and it just
disappears. Balance blend. Remember
remember if you are calling it mirror
mountain then all the images you see are
reflections of yourselves.
Thank you very much. One just one last
one. This is four to see you. Very
brief. Very brief. You do not need to
ask these things. That's true. That's
true. But you mentioned something about
two things on pain because I'm still
working through but it's I know it's
okay. But you you said something all
pain is judgment. And you mentioned
another thing about it is resistance.
Resistance. But then you mentioned on
another tape the idea that pain is when
your your your met your metaphysical
self frequency is quite different than
your body frequency and it's going
through a painful change over
resistance. In other words, the idea of
creating there to be a difference
between your body frequency and what you
call your spirit frequency when there
really doesn't have to be a difference.
In creating a difference, you create
friction because you are creating the
idea that your body frequency is somehow
lower than your spiritual one. And when
you put together a slower and a faster
frequency, you get friction which
creates pain through resistance.
Okay, that makes sense. Remember your
body is your spirit in physical
terms. Remember your consciousness is
not in your body. Your body is in your
consciousness. Oh, there it is. Yes. Fly away, little
Oh, there it is. Yes. Fly away, little
butterfly. Oh, you're beautiful. Well,
as you know, you'll be up. You've been
there. And everybody is welcome. If
anybody wants to leave their names,
everybody here is welcome to Mount Mir
Mountain or Mount Eli. Elie. Mount Elie.
Is it done? You may find out during your
break time which is coming up shortly.
Thank you so much, sweetheart. Thank
you. Love to you unconditionally.
Shing. Good evening, Bashar. And to you. I
Good evening, Bashar. And to you. I
haven't talked to you in a long time,
but I've been around and uh it's about
time I I'm sorry. I'm going to ask a
personal question. I need to do that.
But I'm about to make a change uh in my
occupation. More of an addition. Well,
yeah. No. All right. Yeah. No, I sort of
seesaw back and forth on that. So,
seesaw. All right. I thought I'd like
some of your input on what you might
perceive ahead for me on that. Why are
you mumbling? Am I mumbling? I don't
know why I'm mumbling. Are you not
certain of the things that you say
excite you? That's right. Do you not
trust them? Do you not trust that they
can support you? That's it. That's it.
Exactly. But do you not understand the
contradiction in definitions? That which
excites you by definition must support
you or it wouldn't excite you because
excitement represents the vibration of
the path you chose to
be. It therefore shows you by being
exciting that it will allow you to do it
effortlessly and allow you to do it as
abundantly as you need to. Otherwise,
you'd be excited by something else.
Well, I'm sort of in the position of the
young lady who was up here earlier of
having a little trouble sorting out
where the excitement is.
Well, what do you want to do? Keep it
simple. Keep it simple. What is the most
exciting thing you can be doing that you
are capable of doing at this moment?
What Daryl's doing. All right.
But I I I find it difficult to picture
me in that. Why? I don't know why. I
haven't figured out why. All right.
Let's use that imagination, shall we?
Yes. No. Maybe. Uh maybe.
All right. I will not force you. I will
wait.
I I guess that I I have considerations
about what other people think and I I
have trouble seeing it fitting into my
family and personal other um ties that I
have. But the you you define yourself to
be right now, the uncertain you, will of
course only be able to project an
uncertain relationship with everyone
else. The second you define yourself as
the certain you, then you will project a
certain idea of all your relationships,
a definitive one. I do understand that
and I can see how that fits me.
But still I I vacasillate so on this and
I um all right but can you understand
that perhaps for you the vacasillation
is a part of the process and that
through this so-called vacasillation or
oscillation you will then touch like a
pendulum on all the things you need to
touch on so that you can bit by bit as
you accelerate into the center add and
integrate all these things to vibrate in
the center of yourself by having first
touched on all sides. That has occurred
to me. Yes. Well, then trust that that
having occurred to you allows you to
know you are instinctively in touch with
the fact that the process you're going
through perhaps for now is exactly the
process you need. Well, it might. So,
the second you relax that what you are
going through is exactly what you need
to go through paradoxically in relaxing
you will allow the process to speed up
and you won't need to go through as much
of it. That would be nice. Could you It
is nice. It is nice. Could you just sort
of give me a little look into the First
you must answer the original question.
Yes. No. Maybe. Shall we use that
imagination or not? Well, that's what
it's for. I guess we should use it. All
right. No guessing. Yes. No. Maybe. We
should use it. Yes. Thank
you. Imagine. Simply play with us for
now. Imagine yourself doing it. Just
doing it. Picture it for now. Even if it
is only for you a game. All right. Okay.
Just picture yourself doing it.
Now you have already stated on one level
that you may hold yourself back because
of the fear of what other people will
think. Yes. Yes. All right. What do you
care? Well, it's a pattern I've had this life.
Well, it's a pattern I've had this life.
All right. Do you
understand that you cannot prove
anything to anyone anyway? I do
understand it. All right.
Then realize that no matter what another
individual chooses to believe about you,
it is simply representative of their
belief. The idea is that every belief is
valid. And if you are willing to do what
you say excites you, then in a sense
what you are also willing to say is that
you are
unconditionally loving. And if you are
unconditionally loving, then it will not
matter what anyone else says. you will
love them nonetheless for the point of
view they choose to be relative to who
you are. And in a sense in another
individual giving you their point of
view, if it doesn't vibrate with your
frequency, then they have done you a
service by pointing out to you in ever
strengthening formats the ideas you are
not which strengthens the idea you are.
Okay. Understand? Yeah. So, even
individuals who in your terms will
rebuke you and attack you and judge you
are giving you an opportunity to
recognize that they may simply be
expressing a high degree of polarity to
allow you to more strongly define the
vibration you are. All right? You can
look at it that way. You see, we are
ever the
optimist because we know for us it works
and it always works and it never doesn't
work because that's our reality and
that's our belief. So no matter what
anyone chooses to say about you, you
understand that your life is yours. And
if you know you are functioning to the
best of your ability within your
integrity, then perhaps also some of
these other people might from time to
time point out to you where they believe
you might be functioning outside of your
integrity and you have an opportunity to
examine what they are saying and agree
with them or not. So it always can also
be looked at as a feedback
self-regulating self-checking system to
have other people around you give you
their opinion on what you are doing. But
that doesn't mean that they have the
right to determine for you what is
correct and what is not. Understand?
Yes. You can use them as a
self-regulating system. I see your point
of view. You may say, I understand it.
Thank you for giving me the loving
opportunity of examining that. I find I
a agree with you or b disagree with you.
Thank you very much. Have a good
day. Plain and simple. Remember, all
realities are real. All truths are true.
And really nothing we say is going to
make a bit of difference to you until
you decide that what you prefer is what
you really prefer. Act on it and then
that is the only thing that will make a
difference. That decision. Mhm. We can
provide you with our experience and our
atmosphere to perhaps allow it to be
more conducive and literally conductive
for you to choose what you prefer.
That's what I'm after. But that's all we
can provide and that's all we are
providing right now. Right? simply that
it always does work and that you can
learn to trust it. And I guarantee 100%
the more you trust it, the more that
type of reality you will experience and
you will experience no other.
I understand.
Now dream the dream you prefer to dream
and then live that dream. Your physical
reality is only a dream. And you do not
have to convince anyone else of that.
You do not have to convince anyone
else. That's not the point. The point is
to fully be
whoever you are in this life to the best
of the ability you have determined. You
can be that
you. That's it. That is all that it
takes to fulfill completely the idea of
all the agreements you have
made and to
absolutely shine as a reflection of
infinite creation. You have that right. You
creation. You have that right. You
deserve to be who you desire to be. All
of
you, you have that right. No one can
tell you any different. It is up to you.
And if you wish to be who you wish to
be, then fair is fair. You must allow
everyone else to be who they wish to be.
Even if who they wish to be is
absolutely polar to you. For only in
allowing them to be who they wish to be
will you fully allow yourself to be who
you are. And in being who you are fully
do you then only give them the best
opportunity to see what idea you are.
And only by fully allowing them to see
what idea you are. Do you even give them
an opportunity to change their mind if
they wish to
understand? I do understand. and I'm
working on that and haven't achieved it
fully yet. Now, here's another, as you
say, catch.
Remember this and do not be so hard on
yourselves. Whatever you have achieved
right now is a full and absolute
completely perfect idea in exactly the
way you need to achieve it right now.
You do not have to measure yourself
against what you will be. Yes, you will
change. Yes, you will grow. Yes, you
will expand. But what you are right now is an
expand. But what you are right now is an
absolutely perfect representation of
whatever it is you are right now. So,
you have achieved this perfection, have
you not? That's right. All you will be
doing by changing is creating another
perfection and another perfection and
another perfection.
Understand? I like that. Thank you very
much. Thank you. At this timing, you may
all take a short break. We will resume
contact in approximately 15 of your
minutes. How's it [Applause] [Applause]
going? All
right. Okay. Before we
continue, an idea that we have heard
expressed from time to time in your
civilization from some of the more
seriousminded of
you. Not that we are in any way, shape
or form offering the
idea of proof at this timing of who we
are. For that is not the
idea. It is the idea to remain
unobtrusive to share with you the
information. So the ideas are what you
will focus on and not who is delivering
them. But some individuals have
expressed in their thoughts the
idea that interactions between your
civilization and members of another
civilization perhaps should be a little
more [Laughter]
[Laughter]
dignified. All right.
I can be just as somber as any of
you. However, nobody said that what you
call extraterrestrials didn't know how to
extraterrestrials didn't know how to
play. And you will find in all reality
that it is through play and through
laughter that you will create the
closest bond with
us. Just as with the dolphins upon your
planet, they know how to play.
And they can be very loving guides to
teach you all how to play in whatever
way, shape or form you desire to. And to. And
so
recognize that in the majority of these
interactions, even
when you are perhaps perceiving from us
a somber attitude, a straightforward
delivery of information.
We are always
laughing and many times we will simply
tailor the way the information comes
because we perceive you feel you need to
hear it that way to allow it to sound
believable and so you will not think
that we are laughing at
you. Never are we doing that. We cherish
you. We enjoy you immensely.
And so we thank you for being such a
source of
joy. And so on that
note, let us play. Shing.
Good evening. How are you? Unto you.
Perfect. And you? Very good. Thank you.
My question. No, your question. My
question as as our question, our answer
is about about 3 weeks ago, I was
involved in a channeling session and we
were talking about Orion and experiences
maybe I've had there and on play this as
well. I and some healing abilities that
maybe I possessed at the time and then
the entity said Bashar wanted to talk to
me. So now I ask you, thank you. What
would you like to say? Thank you.
simply a reflection to each and every
one of you that recognize your
connection to the particular frequency
you call Plleadian and Orion which are
the polarity aspects of each other.
Blending them backwards, if you wish, a
linear representation into the systems
you call
LRA many many of your years ago before
what you may call the split into Orion
and Plleadian. The idea is to simply
Plleadian. The idea is to simply
recognize that it is our particular
agreement or there is a particularity
within the agreement we have made to be
of service to your plan at this time to
reflect and represent some of the
original choices and agreements that
were made specifically within the Orion
systems. For we are geared, if you will,
to allowing the idea of the original
Orion energy, some of which may have
been steeped in negativity, to find its
fulcrum, to find its balance within the
understanding of the triad structure of
all creation, the polarity. And the
third point of balance that allows there
to be transformation and change.
The whole idea in this blending and this
balancing is to simply truly very simply
always understand that the second you do
with integrity the thing that excites
you the
most then you will be allowing for the
strongest blending of the polarities to
take place within you.
Now we have found from time to time that
the idea also of certain systems that
have been created upon your planet and
very strongly specifically the one that
is referred to as
Scientology will have been in a sense a
system created by Orions for Orions to
allow them to assimilate to the idea of
the Earth vibration in ways that were
similar to the way they assimilated and
understood the Orion original vibrations
to be. This does not mean that other
individuals who have other connections
cannot use that system or have not used
it. But it simply was originally created
and much of the idea of analysis upon
your planet stems from some of the idea
of the original Orion filtering.
Therefore, to some degree, the way in
which many individuals perceive the
concept you call science in and of
itself upon your planet stems to some
degree as a trickle down effect from
some original Orion
vibration. the
analysis, the idea of the high focus of
awareness in what you might call an
analytical nature. The idea simply that we wish to
nature. The idea simply that we wish to
share and simply recognize that our
service automatically attracts is the
opportunity to reflect back to each and
every individual that is dealing with
that particular connection
that the control is always within you.
as to some degree you have already
discovered for yourself. Simply the
attraction at this point and the drawing
together functions as a reflection of
something that is now after the fact.
Something that functions as a reflection
of things you have already begun to
integrate. just so that we can function
as a marker, if you will, for
individuals to allow them to know they
are keeping the agreements they have
made and can continue to accelerate
those agreements by doing what excites
them with integrity.
You follow me? Yes. Maybe you uh are
going to be answering the question that
my is for tonight. Uh it deals with a
dream I had maybe about three or four
months ago. All right. when I was uh
encountered by family that the devil was
going to possess me and they possessed
them already and I woke up and as I woke
up I took a sip of water lit a cigarette
and before me behold an 8-ft etheric be
very old stepped out of thin air what is
it who is it is it me in a sense yes but
the idea is to also recognize that what
you typically call or typify as the
devil is simply the negative polarity of
the combined consciousness of your
entire race, of your entire world. And
therefore, you gave yourself the
opportunity to recognize there really is
no strong distinction between the dream
reality and the physical reality. They
are representations, different
representations of the same reality. And
so that gave you an opportunity to see
the manifestation of that hereto for
ethereal form projection of that aspect
of your consciousness. an opportunity to
see the polarity in active manifestation
to recognize that you call those things
forth out of the immaterial into the
material solely based on the vibration
and the attitude and the beliefs that
you are at any given moment. So it was
an opportunity to see the polarity idea
to see how those dream realities bridge
into physical reality and how physical
reality is but an extension of the
dream. So in a sense yes it was you but
also it was an archetypal representation
of the collective portion of your
consciousness that represents that idea
that ancient belief a very very ancient
and old belief sometimes can be
expressed as the negative form of the
dragon. Sometimes can be expressed as
the positive form of the dragon. It is
the ancient almost the most ancient
symbol your planet has to represent the
combined collective consciousness in
either polarity expression on your
planet. Does that serve you very well?
Thank you very much. Thank you very
much. Exciting dreams to you
sharing. Good evening Bashar and to you.
I am very excited about the harmonic
convergence and I plan to be in Hawaii.
All right. any of us who are planning
being different places. Um, I want to
thank you for everything you've said
this evening and particularly your
introduction and what you just said
about playfulness and laughter. That
strikes a deep chord within me. Oh,
thank you for allowing me to play your
tune.
It's my pleasure.
Um I was just speaking to uh the entity
friend um several weeks ago about the
idea of levitation. Nice. And I said it
had occurred to me that uh seriousness
and somberness have to do with gravity.
And a lot of mass and weight whereas
laughter and levity have to do with very
light very uplifting isn't it?
Absolutely. Thanks. And I find myself
flying in my dreams quite often. Yes.
And enjoying it so much. Yes. And the
minute I find myself flying, I know I'm
dreaming. Yes. And I've taken to saying,
"Oh, I'm dreaming." And and I'll say,
"Um, lucid dreaming." Yes. Now, will all
of you do me a favor? All of you. All at
once. You do not have to, but you may
find it fun. Repeat after
me. Oh.
Oh, right now right now I am dreaming. I
am dreaming. Thank you.
[Music] It is very literal. Very literal. Right
It is very literal. Very literal. Right
now you are all dreaming the physical
reality dream. And the whole idea as
many of you are discovering is to learn
to wake up in that dream to create it to
be whatever dream you prefer it to be
because it is only a dream. Yes. One of
my favorite things that Bob Dylan said
once was, I'll let you be in my dream if
I can be in yours.
So I want to thank you and everyone here
for being in my dream. Thank you.
Thank you.
One moment. Yes.
[Laughter]
Though we cannot share much at this time
to simply let you know what the
connection was, the individual you have
mentioned by the name of
Robert will have some interesting
accelerations within the next seven of
your years.
Robert Dylan.
Robert. Oh, sorry.
For the individual, as we recognize, it
already has a profound effect upon your
planet. Absolutely. And in this way,
recognize there will now be within the
next 3 years an acceleration and four
years after that, a very different
approach. A very different approach. A
very different
approach. as we perceive the energy now
and to some degree interconnectedness
with more things in a different way.
Thank you. Thank you Bashar for opening
the door so that we may have perceived
that portion of the momentum of your
planet. Who's speaking?
It is as you recognize I but with an
overtone connection for now. That will do.
All right. Yes. Thank you. Very
perceptive. Thank you so much. I've felt
very strong connections with that that
energy being and the viewpoints that
have been shared. Some of it will have
very strong connotations with regard to
the dolphin consciousness.
I love it. Dream, dream, dream, dream. I
can already wait. See you at the
harmonic convergence. Thank you.
Shooting.
Good evening and to you good day. Thank
you. Uh in the spirit of everinccreasing
play and learning, I we seem to have
moved most recently away from what could
be seen by some as a polarization to the
negative side of nuclear war. As in our
perception, you have as of approximately
10 of your years ago already decided
that you will not annihilate yourselves
by that means.
This is simply a reflection of a
decision you have all made
unconsciously, collectively and which is
now leaking into your conscious
awareness that is as we perceive your
energy now. So my question would be then when
now. So my question would be then when
will the old forms that supported that
kind of activity worldwide as a
planetary consciousness cease to make
way and make way for new forms most
abruptly within what you call the next
15 of your years most absolutely within
the next 30 as we read your energy now
in what way will that be a manifestation
of what you brought here tonight as the
matrix the matrix for the planet say for
instance guys will the idea one of The
ideas behind what you call this harmonic
convergence as the fulcrum point between
an old reality and a new reality, an old
vibration and a new vibration is to
recognize that as you each individually
become the pattern for the reality you
wish to experience. Then bit by bit each
and every one of you add to the overall
energy of your world's ability to become
that world as you have envisioned it.
And it will accelerate in that
direction. And you will begin to see the
blending and harmonics occur between
what is now distinct and segregated
levels of your society sociologically,
economically, politically. All these
things will begin to blend as each and
every one of you realize that you are
your governments and begin to act
accordingly. Thank you. Thank you. It is
your world. Shooting.
Good evening. I'm to you. Good day. Hi.
The last time we were talking about or I
was talking about
uh and we got into the area of
multiple existences on the planet Earth
and sociological engineering
ice and I'm aware of a bit of the
sociological engineering to me suggests
an
organized system of data and application
somewhat. Yes. Although it is on our end
somewhat spontaneous, organized in its inherent
spontaneous, organized in its inherent
idea, but not so much completely
pre-planned. Yes, but it all but
apparently that seems uh in opposition
to the concept of we're each our own
path. No, no, no. Slightly. Not really.
We do not mean there to be a
contradiction, as you understand that
term. simply that our sociological
engineering has to do with attracting
ourselves to the vibrations that are
already creating themselves to be most
conducive to interaction with us. Okay.
So, one of the basic principles to me is
the fact that we are creating our own
experience, our own existence. Yes.
Could you share some other basic
principles upon which the engineering is
based? Like vibration attracts like vibration.
plain and simple on that
level. Also, the fact that there are
multiple realities and therefore that
like vibration will actually create and
coalesce the one reality that is
representative of whatever collective
vibrations are most representative of
our vibration and that is the one we
will interact with. Social engineering
in that sense may be a misnomer. The
idea can be perhaps more aptly or
precisely defined as simply attraction.
The principles of attraction that will
gather together the gravitational
attraction metaphysically speaking,
energy speaking that will gravitate
together all the different fragments
that are vibrating at the same rate to
create in a sense project themselves
into the universe that represents that
particular reality. Social engineering
is simply more of a gathering of like
vibration. rather than a forcing or a directing
rather than a forcing or a directing
into a particular modality. It is the
supplying of an atmosphere that is
literally conductive to attract those
elements that are similar or desire to
be similar to gather unto ourselves as a
seed as a nucleus all in that way that
desires to be of similar vibrational
realities to instill within each and
every one of those gathered their own
sense of being a seed and a nucleus. In
other words, self-empowering them so
that then it can be a holographic matrix
that supports every element within it
equally. Not by focusing around one
particular center such as ourselves, but
by creating an infinite number of
centers within the whole idea around
which all realities will then interlock
and rotate. Is this making some sense?
So, so you're attracting a similar Yes.
It is the idea that has been colloially
referred to in your planetary mythology
as harvesting.
It is simply that we radiate at a
particular frequency and gather the idea
of any individuals that radiate a
similar frequency, reflect that frequency back
frequency, reflect that frequency back
to them, show it to them as their own
frequency so that each can function as a
similar radiator and a similar
attractant to strengthen the cohesive
glue of that reality and allow it to
coalesce and manifest. Okay. But there's
also some presumption of uh change. Yes,
of course. All things
change, but many changes can still occur
within an overall signature vibration, a
reality vibration. There is much room,
much leeway in any particular reality
for many divergences within that
reality. That is what enriches any
reality is the diversity within it. That
is what allows it to be holographic,
holographically reflective. It is homogeneousness
reflective. It is homogeneousness
through diversity.
So what is the purpose of the gathering?
Because simply it is the representation
of like attracts like. The only purpose
that it needs to have is that it is
simply that we are being true to who we
are and individuals that we attract into
our reality are being true to who they
are. That is the whole purpose to it is
to simply create the reality that we
perceive ourselves to be and to do it
and share it with as many other
individuals that desire the similar
reality. That is the purpose. The
purpose is to create because we are all
you and I
creators because we are you and I
creation itself. We do not need any
other purpose other than the fact that
that's what we
are. We are simply being true to
ourselves. That is the purpose.
Does that explain it? I'll have to work
on it for a while. Oh, all right. What
is it about it that seems to be
difficult or unclear? I don't. It's a matter of
or unclear? I don't. It's a matter of
absorption.
All right. And absorb away.
Thank you for your sharing. Thank you.
And the expression of the vibration that
you have chosen to represent the idea
you are most aligned with at this
moment. Thank you.
Shutting. Hi. Hi.
Um, I've always uh
Hello. Okay. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hi.
Hi.
I I've always uh hallucinated a lot,
which means I see things that other
people don't. And I don't Oh, really?
And um recently it's gotten my way and
I've started taking medication to reduce
the hallucinations. Why? Uh because
everyone thinks I'm crazy. So it is a
relative thing. You know there was
another problem. Everyone is crazy in
their own way. There I know I am crazy
in my own way. That I agree. But um
there was a problem is it got to the
point where I couldn't work. All right.
do things that it takes to survive in
this world. Things you think it takes to
survive. Yeah. Tell me, how can I make a
lot of money without having to work? No.
Uh well, the idea is to do what you love
to do and then it will not seem like
work, right? I know that. But how how
can I um integrate these hallucinations?
Like I'm taking drugs now that I don't
really want to keep taking. All right.
Can you define or describe any of the
so-called hallucinations? Um, well,
first of all, do you understand what a
hallucination is? Well, uh, sometimes
when I'm having them, I I know it's a
hallucination and sometimes I don't. Do
you know what a hallucination is? Yes, I
do. It means other people don't see it.
What is it?
Um, well,
it's I don't know. They're different
things. Oh, thank you. Different things.
It is, however, one particular thing.
All hallucinations are one particular
thing. They are all realities, right?
Well, real realities. Recently, I've
been having just minor things like u
spatial distortions where it looks feels
like I'm looking down a tunnel and the
floor is on the ceiling. Yes. And um
when I look at um it seems like I can
see things microscopically. Yes. As in a
closeup all the time. And uh when people
talk, it sounds like they're screaming.
All right. All the time. All right.
which really is disturbing.
really is disturbing.
All right. Loud. Yes.
And then um also uh I I think now this
people have called paranoia that I hear
what people are thinking. To some degree
you can. Yeah. You are simply very
strongly empathic. Uhhuh. Very strongly
empathic. Do you understand what that
means? No. No. Then why did you say
uh-huh? Well, I know empathy means to empath
Well, I know empathy means to empath
emphasize. And what does empathize mean?
Uh to care a lot about the other person.
You're on the right track. But that's
the mechanism that activates it. But
what is empathy? Empathy is a feeling.
It is a complete
identification with someone else so that
you create the same patterns within
yourself perhaps sometimes in an
amplified form. Mhm. Do you understand
what we have said? Uh yes. What about
you know when I hallucinate say a big
party or something like that? What about
it? Is that the same? That's not
empathizing. That's just it can be it
can be empathy. It can be in other words
identification with other whole
realities that are shared by groups of
consciousness. Now you can learn to tone
it down to a comfortable level if you
are willing to understand the first
principle above and beyond anything. The
first principle being that you are
choosing to create that reality for your
own reasons. You must own it before you
can transform it in any way, shape or
form. You follow me? Yes. So, do you
understand that there is a reason for
why you are creating it? And do you
understand that you are creating that
reality? I don't understand the reason
why I'm creating it. Do you understand
that you are creating it? Uh, I could
see that I might be. Yes. Do you
understand that you are? I do not mean
to be insistent nor force a belief
system upon you. But the idea is once
again that you cannot change it if you
do not own it.
You must understand that everything you
experience in your reality is your
projection, is your creation in the way
you're experiencing it. This does not
mean that there are not things going on
in other realities that you are not
sensitive to. But in order to experience
it in your reality, you have to create
your version of it in your universal
reality or you can't experience
it. Understand? Uh no. All right. Let's
say for a moment that each and every one
of you is distinct your own universal
reality. In order for someone to share with you
In order for someone to share with you
an idea that they have, in order for you
to experience a similar reality to them,
you have to tell empathically agree to
experience it so that each of you can
create the similar idea in your
perceptible experiential reality. If
someone as you say is not willing to
telepathically share that with you, they
will not experience an idea that you
have chosen to experience and hence as
you say they do not see what you see
because they simply have not agreed to
share that idea with you perhaps simply
because it has nothing to do with the
particular reality they prefer. Every
single person on your planet to some
degree shares a common reality. To some
degree that common reality is not there
without you. You are agreeing to
experience any degree of commonality.
You are experiencing. You are agreeing
to play a certain game. Now some of you
in this transformational age especially
because you are allowing yourself to be
more sensitive to different realities
are becoming a little bit unstuck from
the massag agreed upon reality and are
willing to explore a few more probable
realities in a very different sensorial
way. This is what you are going through.
You are loosening up the idea from
attaching or focusing to one particular
agreed upon reality and expanding your
senses to be able to perceive different
vibrational frequencies on what might be
called the telepathic level. The level
that most individuals do not allow at
this moment to manifest into
physicalized reality. But nonetheless,
you are sensitized to thoughts, ideas,
wishes, desires and so forth that other
individuals sometimes fears that other
individuals and groups of individuals
may be playing out in the dream reality
as probable realities they may manifest
but to you they are becoming real
because you are beginning to bridge the
gap between non-physical and physical
reality. You are beginning to live
literally in the dream reality as one
reality and not two realities. So you
are seeing less and less distinction
between the non-physical reality and the
physical reality. You are seeing them
blend. Many strong individuals in that
way have allowed themselves to do this.
One of the most famous among you as you
understand it was the being you call
Nicola Tesla. And that is how this
individual invented many of the things
they did. By learning that the
hallucinations they were seeing were
real realities, understanding that they
were creating those and then defining
and describing them as they desired to
see them so that they could then
manifest them at their own rate to their
own preference without in your terms
simply allowing it to be a random and
wild talent. you have that wild talent,
that sensitivity to the non-physical
realm because the non-physical is no
less real than the physical. It is
simply that it is easy for you to
experience the solidity of dreams.
Whereas most individuals still relegate
them to a non-physical realm and so are
unaffected generally by them. But you
are highly empathic. You are highly
allowable in that sense. You are highly
open to
manifestation. Remember also this, the
reason you are connecting in that way to
so many other realities is because when
you blend the dream reality and the
physical reality, you begin to really
really understand that each and every
other quote unquote individual in
reality is simply you in another version
in another form of expression. So of
course you are intimately intertwined
because every other person is you in
another mode of expression. So of course
you can identify with all of them feel
the same things that all of them do.
Now what it takes is simply a
recognition and a definition and a
sitting down and a meditation of the
particular vibrational frequency you
prefer to represent a convenient idea of
your persona. And as you define what
your persona is, you are not going to
shut out all the other ideas because you
really don't want to. But you will allow
the other ideas to manifest in your
reality at a rate that will still allow
you and a level that will still allow
you to express the persona you desire to
be at the rate you desire to express it
without feeling overwhelmed and out of
control. The only reason you feel out of
control is because you have been taught
to believe that thing can be
overwhelming and out of control. And it
is only that viewpoint that seems to
create that lack of control in your
life. You don't need that viewpoint. You
can redefine the personality that you
are. And you can redefine that
personality to no longer contain the
definition that you can be out of
control. No matter what you connect
into, no matter what your senses
receive, you can know that you a must be
receiving these things on a level you
can handle really intrinsically
fundamentally or you wouldn't be able to
receive them at all. And therefore
knowing you can handle the way it is
coming paradoxically will allow you the
conscious control over the reality so
that you will then create it to be in
the format you believe consciously is
representative of the way you desire to
handle it. Is any of this sinking in? Uh
yes. All right. Also understand we are
communicating with you on many more
levels than just the auditory vibration
you are hearing. We are speaking to you
on fundamental empathic levels. You are
getting this message to some degree.
What we are now doing, if you wish to be
let in on it, is that we are directing a
very strong electromagnetic current in
your direction that will only intersect
and only interact with vibrations of
like kind wherever you desire them to
intersect and interact to allow you to
become as you already are beginning to
be, superconductive, but not in a way you
superconductive, but not in a way you
cannot handle. Not in a way that panics
your ego structure. If you allow your
ego structure to blend and balance in
that superconductivity, I shall actually say
superconductivity, I shall actually say
hyperonductivity because
hyperonductivity is the ability to
transmit that energy in more than one
direction at the same time. Then you can
blend and balance and solidify
communication between yourself on all
levels. That communication between
yourself on all levels will let you know
you have the power to adjust any of the
dials and any of the knobs of your
reality to whatever level you think you
can tolerate. A lot of this information is
tolerate. A lot of this information is
going to come out in what you
colloquially call your dream reality.
Some of it may come out in your physical
reality since you are more willing than
most to allow your physical reality to
be representative of your dream. But let
it come out and understand that the
level first of all a a a pay attention.
a the level it comes out on in the way
it comes out first. Let it be all right.
Let it be all right. All right. If it's
uncomfortable, fine. We understand it.
It doesn't have to remain. But at first,
let it be all right because you created
it that way. And paradoxically, as soon
as you acknowledge that you chose to
create it that way, you will usually
find that the level will change
instantly. As soon as you acknowledge
that the way it came was all right and
don't invalidate it, don't push against
it. Don't resist it. Let it flow through
you. Through you. Remember, you are
hyper conductive. It will go through
you. It will not stick. It will go
through you. And as soon as you allow it
through you, you will be able to
modulate it because then you will own
it. And as you own the frequency, you
can play with it all up and down the
scale as you wish to. And you can adjust
it. Oh, that's a little loud. All right,
let's tune it down.
I chose to allow it to be loud. Perhaps
just to get my attention at first.
Perhaps in allowing it to get my
attention, there is something here I
should pay attention to. All right.
Well, I'll tune it down a little bit and
pay attention. The sooner you pay
attention to anything you create in your
reality, the sooner it can manifest in a
form that will allow you to be more
comfortable with it. The only time
things become grading and obnoxious in
your reality is when you are coming from
a belief system in which you say, "I do
not wish to pay attention to this thing.
It has no business in my life.
Let it have a business in your life. And
as soon as you let it in, it's within
your control. And as soon as it's within
your control, turn the dial down. It
will go down.
Understand? Mhm. Yes. Does this assist
you? Yes. I think so.
Allow yourself also to be assisted by
all levels of reality, all levels of
consciousness who wish to assist you. It
is not that you need a lot of help, but
allow yourself to know that you have
assistance, unconditionally loving
assistance that will help you
modulate and relax into the vibrational
flow that you are. For remember what we
said. Something that may seem to be
beyond you. Something that may seem to
be above
you, if you allow yourself to match that
vibration, will seem very typical and
very easy to handle. It is only when you
create there to be a vast difference
between who you think you are and what
you are manifesting in your reality.
That is what creates the friction.
So do not let there be so much of a
difference between what you are
perceiving and what you think of
yourself. You are literally are the
reality you are
experiencing. Your so-called
hallucinations are simply your creative
way of beginning to realize that you
actually are the reality and do not
really exist in a reality.
Okay. our unconditional
our unconditional
love and
light and our congratulations and our
appreciation at your willingness to be
so
bold in your
life, so
artistic, so
blatant. Soften your edges.
Relax into the being that you are.
Sleep comfortably within the idea of
yourself. And you can awaken
refreshed and knowing beyond the shadow
of a doubt that with ease of creation
and effortless joy, you are the creator
of your reality.
pleasant dreams to you. Thank you. Thank
you. [Applause] [Applause]
One other
idea, breathe
slowly, clearly and easily.
Breath itself as a technique can put you
directly in
alignment with all the energy that you
are and all the control that you are
aware of within you. Thank you shedding.
Good day Bish and to you good day. Um
what's been resonating with me is vision
quest. Um,
and I had this experience and I was
talking to this person and it and just
was this strong experience of like
looking straight at me and as if I don't
know just this strong energy coming from
him to me as if he pulled me to his face
and told me in my face that like I would
be doing that or something. All right.
So, what do you wish to do with this?
Um, one I want to know if you're the
creator of your reality and I understand
that in vision quest you put yourself
through maybe physical
um extremes to transcend that or
something like that. It is one way. You
don't have to do it that way, but it's
one way. Yeah. So, I was
wondering why do I why am I going to do
it that way? Why are you going to do it
that way?
going to do it that way. I know. Cuz
Well, why are you going to do it that
way? I don't know. Well, then why do it?
I don't know. Well, then why do it?
Um, why not do it some other way if you
haven't done it that way yet? Which way
do you prefer to do it?
Well, I guess there's a part of me that
prefers to do it that way because One
moment. One moment. One moment. Okay.
Very important what you just said. Did
you all hear? I guess there's a part of
me. You really do not exist in
parts. Any idea you are experiencing at
any given moment, you experience with
the totality of your being. So if that's
not the way you wish to be, do not use
the excuse that a part of you is that
way and therefore the rest of you can't
help it. I don't know. It's a part of me
in there somewhere. I can't find it.
Yeah, that's an excuse. Yeah, it was.
Yeah, it was. It was. You are a whole
being. How does the whole being prefer
to be? The the whole being is pref the
whole being's fine. She wants to to do
that and that's why she's going to do
it. It's as simple as will she do it in
a way that she finds pleasurable or will
she do it in a way she finds painful?
I'll probably do it in a way that I find
pleasurable. I my concern was I didn't
want to go against like sacred ways or
that something like that. And I know
that's crazy because it's not crazy. But
do you understand that the quote unquote
sacred ways involve the very act of
ways involve the very act of
effortlessness itself? That is what is
so sacred about
it. It is a flow. It is not a struggle.
But pinching your skin in four
directions and burying yourself in a
hole sounds like a struggle.
All [Music] [Music]
right, but
[Music] remember individuals have created those
remember individuals have created those
ideas. Not that you have to go through
the same idea, the same ritual, but
individuals have created those ideas to
show that they are so centered that
things you would typically think are a
struggle and painful for them aren't.
That's the whole idea. They have
transcended the idea of giving it a
painful meaning and so they can do
anything they wish even things you think
are painful because to them they aren't.
That's the whole idea. Okay. Do it in
whatever way, shape or form represents
your ability to know it doesn't have to
be painful and you will fulfill the
spirit of the quest.
Okay, understand? I got it. Thank you.
Thanks. setting.
setting.
Hi, my name is Glora. All right, if you
say so.
I would like to share some things with
everyone. And but first of all, I want
to say that I'm just very excited that I
am creating and that you all are
co-creators of tonight. Oh, thank you.
And everything very excited that you
chose to create us in your reality.
Um, and also I'd like to share with
everyone that I went to SeaWorld last
Sunday, Saturday, whatever. Nice.
Whatever. And um, um, I got to pet the
dolphins. Nice. Did they get to pet you?
Yes. Nice.
That was so exciting. Nice. Another
thing I mean, every every day is so
exciting for me right now. It's just me,
too. I tell you, it's like
I tell you, it's like
It is believable. Yes.
And um another thing I like to share is
that about a year from now, four days ago,
about a year from now, four days ago,
I'm going to give birth to um a little
baby girl and I've I have a 20-year-old
one-year-old son and um a 16-year-old
son. And made a lot of agreements,
haven't you? Yes. And this is um the
thing that has excited me the most. And
so now my my dream is is going to come
true. All right. And it's just been a
lot of fun playing with that and playing
with a lot of agreements on this planet
about a 40year-old not having children,
etc. I Anyway, all things are flexible.
That's right.
Um what I was wondering was if you could
share with us
some
um of your perception of what might be
the optimum
optimum
diet for us at this stage right now.
There can be no general diet for
everyone. Well, I do know that because
everyone creates their own reality and
wishes to experience whatever they want
to experience and they're creating that.
So, what does your body consciousness
tell you is correct for you? Well, I
knew you were going to say that. I mean,
you know, it's like how psychic of you.
I I mean, you're right. We all know
everything. Yes. Um, I just thought
maybe you might be able to
already very well aware in general that
some of you are losing urges for certain
things in your dietary supplements. Some
of you are already leaning toward the
idea of what you call vegetable and
fruit, which has long been understood to
be more representative of what you would
call a higher frequency. But there is no
need to force yourself into that
spirituality if your body consciousness
says it is not yet timing.
aware of the type of things that your
body can use to transform into
physiological energy and many of you are
very well aware of the difference
between eating what excites you and
eating what you are anxious about.
Okay, that's a good point because I have
seen many people that
um you know I've seen someone that died
let's say at 60 that that was ate very
well etc and someone that you know died
at well there are many other belief
systems that go into it is not simply
diet okay very good that so um
in other words that individual to put it
very simply not saying this is
specifically the case could have said
well I'll be very healthy up until the
day I
die which might be very soon.
It all depends on how you define the
beliefs within your reality. That
exactly. I'm very perhaps they did not
believe that if it stretched beyond that
they would be able to remain healthy.
Right.
Um then what I'd like to offer then
is and share with everyone is is the
idea that perhaps um
if more people would consider like you
say themselves as a whole unit and and
and feel the vibrations and get in
communication with the food so that you
know that particular food is going to
give them the energy that they have to
break away from patterns or that they
may have so that they be you know
because it is on an individual basis.
Absolutely right. Well, thank you. Thank
you. I love you very much. We love you
all unconditionally. Thank you. Shutting.
Shutting.
Okay. Hi BR. Hi. This is the first time
I've spoken with you in this particular
situation. Right. So, I've listened to a
number of your tapes and I find them
very exciting and I have a lot of fun
with them. All right. Can you all hear?
Okay. Uh anyway, I'm I've listened to a
bunch of your tapes and I've been having
a lot of fun with them and um my life
has been changing quite a bit. Thank you
for changing it. Yes. Um there's there's
one area that um that I'm have some
confusion and uncertainty about. All
right. do share. So, um it has to do
with uh consciousness. Yes. Um let me
just throw out a few thoughts that uh
you've you've mentioned. All right.
Somebody get a bucket. Try to tried to
put them all together.
Uh you you said that we we are all that
is. You've said that we are immortal.
Yes. Just today you said words to the
effect of every person is me or You said
to a lady, every person is you as
another mode. Yes. Uh you've mentioned
things about uh yourself blending your
consciousness with other consciousnesses
and then speaking uh you talk about us
expanding uh uh growing. So what this
all uh makes me wonder about is see I I
right now this moment feel the awareness
that I am aware. It's like I'm alive.
Yes. Not just this personality
construct, but that it's me, you know.
Yes, I am. I am. Yes. And uh I I like
this feeling. Oh, good. And uh I I like
to to have it for a long time. Well,
this is what I'm this what I'm hoping.
But the question Well, see, the question is
the question Well, see, the question is
is that it appears that there's there's
sort of a um a blending of
consciousnesses and uh pretty soon or
maybe we see this one. I'm not too clear
about did we start out as one
consciousness so that we're all now the
same consciousness just looking out of a
different viewpoint. So I'm you and I'm
every the way it's always been. Yes.
This is the way it is. And so that means
that uh even if I blend with another
consciousness, I still have the same
awareness of being aware and I don't
lose anything else. You do not lose your
identity. No, I don't get stirred in
with a bunch of everybody else.
You see the idea is that since it is all
multi-dimensional and all looking at
itself anyway then any blending that
goes on always takes place from the
viewpoint of any particular portion of
the blending. In other words, each and
every one of you will think that all the
blending is happening to you. Oh great.
Oh I see. That is what it means to be
all that is a multi-dimensional
perspective. Each and every perspective
gets to remain its own perspective
just in a different way. So then we have
an oversoul you mentioned that oversoul
is the same consciousness as I feel I am
now and that you are basically now.
Okay. So how oversoul can be simply
called a microcosmic version of all that
is. Uhhuh. So then every once in a while
you mention something about the oversoul
that makes it seem to me as if the
oversoul is more caused than I am. No,
not really. Again, remember that we are
limited by translating our concepts into
your language. Your language does not
always contain the words or the concepts
that will allow us to express ourselves
clearly. Well, like I remember
specifically you mentioned something
about if the oversoul decides you're
going to walk down the hallway,
basically you'll go down it one way or
another. You decide how you'll go, but
you'll go. Yes. Yes. Generally, yes.
There is an exception. Okay. It is
called conscious suicide.
Yeah. Right. I heard another tape about
that or maybe it was today. But but
anyway, that means that the oversoul is
making a decision. But it seems as if I
have less control over that decision.
Not really. In fact, in a sense, you
could say you have more because you do
agree with the decision of yourself as
the oversoul. But you even have the
ability as a physical representation of
the oversoul to add a level to that
agreement that will allow you to forget
you made the decision. It is you that
have made the decision. You are not
truly separating the oversoul from you.
That is your colloquial point of view.
You are the oversoul. Do you have an
oversoul? Everyone does. But again, this
is a convenient analogy. All
consciousness is one. Yes. So then I
could then somehow uh make a point of
connecting together with my oversoul.
And then there's only one consciousness.
Uh so then we don't have this mystery of
what is my oversoul. What what is it?
You know the separation I made that I
don't remember the separation is an
illusion. Okay. So we have when you
recognize there really is no separation.
You have a connection but it is more
than a connection. It can take the form
to make it seem as if you are having a
discussion with an oversoul that is
different from you. Yeah. But that is
simply an illusion as well. You are
simply talking to yourself. Yes. Okay.
So So just like I am right now. Yes. I
see that. I see that. This is great.
Okay. Thank you very much. Thank you very
Thank you very much. Thank you very
much.
At this timing.
Oh
yes. Allow us to remind each and every
one of you that you are already wrapped
up in all the joy you
need. You have yourselves and you have
us. But we are with you in the way that
allows you to be fully who you are.
Share be the ideas that you choose to
be. Remember
action. Being who you desire to be is
the way to have an equal conversation
with us.
Action. We thank you for the sharing
that you have been willing to co-create
with us this day of your time for you
this night.
We thank you. Our unconditional love to
you all. Exciting dream life dream to
you all. And we thank
all. And we thank
you for
sleeping within
us and for allowing us to awaken within
you. Good day.
How'd it go?
Thank you all for being here.
Thank you for being here.
The time is