I'll say how are you all this evening of
your time as you create time to exist
allow us to begin this interaction this
evening of your time with the
entitlement unfoldment of
persona now we have discussed many times
the idea that what you call a persona is
in a sense an artificial construct a
projection of the consciousness the
non-physical consciousness that you are
as an entity as a being
The idea is that persona personality the
person you think yourself to be is
simply a face and interface between your
consciousness and the idea you call
physical reality. Persona is one of the
ways the being you are has of presenting
itself in physiological terms. It is an
artificial construct in the sense that
it can be changed at any given moment by
simply redefining any or all of the aspects
redefining any or all of the aspects
that go into constructing this
personality. Those three aspects which
we have discussed from time to time are
simply beliefs, emotions and thought
patterns. These three things are the
things that construct the personality,
the person you have been taught to think
yourselves to be in your daytoday
existence as a physical being. But it is
only one of the faces that you have, one
of the ways, one of the methods you can
present yourself as an individual, as an
idea, as an entity.
Now let us create a pictorial
analology to illustrate another aspect a
multi-dimensional aspect of the persona
and how it unfolds in the format you
call physical space and time. Let us
assume by
analogy that the beingness the whole
homogeneous one beingness that you are
the consciousness the awareness
selfawareness that you are let's say for
now non-physically speaking can be
analogous to simply a cylinder does not
have to be very long very short cylinder
for now now it is unhomogeneous thing not
now now it is unhomogeneous thing not
made up of parts, not made up of
components or molecules so to speak or
atoms. It is one homogeneous substance,
one cell, one
idea. Now physical
reality in a sense is the product of a
certain frequency of energy. This
frequency that is created
is called by you the electromagnetic
spectrum. All of it. Even though there
are many frequencies within it, it is
within a particular range that
represents what you call physiological
reality. And out of that electromagnetic
field, all physiological material is
solidified or
crystallized, if you will.
This electromagnetic vibration of the
prime energy operates as many of you
have discovered on your own in vortex
patterns, spiral patterns, circular
cyclical patterns of expressing that
energy. That is the format, the
matrix, the framework of physiological
reality, the spiral pattern. So now you
have this homogeneous cylinder of
yourself and now you have the desire let
us say to project yourself into the
matrix of physiological
reality. All
right? You have this cylinder and let us
say there is a
screen and this screen is the edge of
your physiological reality. Now you're
going to push the cylinder into physical
reality and the screen is made up of
spiral patterns that for the analogy
would be like unto very thin cutting
wires. So as you push the cylinder into
the screen, you turn the cylinder
screen, you turn the cylinder
into something and similar to what you
have called a rolled up carpet or your
jelly roll in a sense. A spiral pattern
has been cut all the way through the
cylinder. Therefore, it can now begin to
unravel itself in time and space. It
contains all of the basic ideas of the
whole cylinder. But the whole thing is
cylinder. But the whole thing is
experienced not all at once but in its
unraveling. The length of the unraveling
is the length duration of what you call
the lifespan. Cylinders can be very large,
lifespan. Cylinders can be very large,
can be very small, can be very long,
very tight. Any different idea you
choose to be in any given lifetime will
determine the basic construction of the
homogeneous cylinder that represents the
overall direction of that life. And then
it will unfold unroll itself throughout
the structure of space and time which
are relegated to physical reality only.
Therefore, recognize what this means. As
you unfold your physical life in your
terminologies, as you grow from a child
to an adult, that is actually simply the
carpet unwinding. You are seeing different
unwinding. You are seeing different
aspects from moment to moment of the
whole cylinder that was there to begin
with that determined what this life
ought to be in general terms. So a
child, the child that you were, so to
speak, was simply one moment on that
role and the next moment another place
on that role. And as it continues to
unwind and unravel as it leads into what
you call
adulthood, you then are simply
experiencing in linear fashion all the
different faces, all the different
ideas, all the different expressions and
explorations of what the cylinder you
were to begin with was before the
physical life playing itself out in
linear terms. One moment after the next. Then
terms. One moment after the next. Then
in what you call physiological death,
you wrap yourself up again and become
homogeneous. Change the idea so to speak
of what you now wish to be. And if you
decide to push yourself back into
physical reality and unroll as another
life from another direction, another
point of view. Because you can see the
cylinder in a sense is perhaps more
properly analogous to a sphere. And you
can cut a cylinder in it in any
direction. In taking the direction of
the cylinder out of the sphere you are,
you determine what life and the
differences that that life shall
be. Now again we are speaking in linear
fashion. All of these cylinders, all of
these unravelings all exist now all
simultaneously. You only experience it linearly from the
You only experience it linearly from the
physical point of view because that is
the definition of physical reality. Time
and space. Things have to take time and
occupy space. You cannot have one
without the other so to speak. That is
why your own physicists, your own
scientists recognize that space and time
are simply different aspects of the same
one idea. And that is why now in your
physics you do not really refer to it
just as time just as space but as
spacetime as one thing one thing because
if you have space the concept of space
you have you must have time if you have
time you must have space in which to
play it out. So the idea however is that
all these unravelings go on
simultaneously in a way that you have
called again because of your linear
format parallel worlds. Parallel
unravelings. All the personas you have
ever been are now or will ever be are
all unraveling simultaneously in
different directions at
once. This is your collective being. All
the unravelings together is your
collective beingness, your totality, the idea, the
beingness, your totality, the idea, the
expression of the infinite that you are.
Now you can unwind yourself rapidly. You
can take your
time. It is up to you. How you unravel
yourself is up to
you. The discovery of the things you
contain as the persona you created
yourself to be is your discovery. is
your treasure is your joy to see what is
wrapped up within yourself as you
unfold. Many times in our interactions
with you from time to time where
appropriate we may be able to see you
edge on and in the folds see certain
things that may be coming up for you
that you have created for yourself to
experience later on when you get to that
particular unfolding level. But
sometimes sharing with you some of the
things that we can perceive would
perhaps inhibit your unfoldment. And so
we reserve our point of view and our
perspective on some of those ideas so as
not to spoil your treasure and spoil
your surprises of
self-discovery. Always you have
determined the surprises and the markers
and the signposts you will set for
yourself upon your
unfoldment. And always we know that the
discovery of these markers leads to
great ecstatic revelatory leaps of
self-awareness. And that's what your
life is all about. discovering more and
more of who and what you are by
unraveling and unfolding the idea you
chose to be before that life at your own
pace in your own
way. Mostly our civilizations and other
beings and other levels of consciousness
are now communicating with you in this
way to simply remind you that you have
the capability to unfold yourself at
whatever rate you wish and that the
unfoldment in and of
itself is what you want to experience.
It is not a matter of kicking the carpet
quickly just to get to certain things
that are trapped within the carpet. and
ignoring the unrolling action itself.
The unrolling action itself is a part of
what you wanted to experience. And this
is only another way of reminding you to
live in the moment. Every inch as you
say, every cimeter as you say, every
micron as you say that your carpet
unfolds is an experience unto itself.
Because every moment is a dimension unto
itself that stretches infinitely in all
directions. This is the holographic
nature of reality. Every
point. Every point contains the whole.
Every line stretches to infinity. Every
plane to infinity. Every cube to
infinity. You are infinite beings.
infinitely unfolding in infinite
directions within the infinite you that
you are. You are going in many directions at
are. You are going in many directions at
once. All directions at once. This is
your nature of self-discovery. This is
what it means to be a part of the
infinite all that is the infinite
awareness. The infinite one homogeneous
being of
creation. You are selfrevelatory.
That's how you were designed to be
self-revelatory. You are all mirrors for
yourselves and for each other to
discover all that you can be, all that
you can choose to be, all that you can
enjoy being. You are a hall of mirrors. The
being. You are a hall of mirrors. The
universe is a hall of mirrors.
Everything you see is your own
reflection in one form or another to
give you the opportunity to discover
what you prefer to be, how you prefer to
act, what you prefer to manifest.
manifest.
Persona, even the idea of persona in
physical terms is not the limited thing
that many of you have been taught to
think that it is. Well, you're stuck in
this rut. That's it. That's all you have
to deal with. Many of you have said this
is who you are. Oh, you can't change
that. You always do change it. Always,
always, always. You see, the thing of it
is is that many of you are so steeped in
the idea of space and time in the past
and the future that even when you change
it, you don't know you've changed it
because you have so completely changed
the present many times that you change
your past, you change your future, you
change your entire timeline history and
nothing seems different to you because
it all seems to fit the present you have
created yourself to be. So many times
you don't know you have changed
drastically all the way up and down the
timeline because everything fits.
Nothing seems out of
place until
now. Some of you are beginning now
because of your increased sensitivity to
be aware of the fact that you are
changing relative to all the other you
have been could be or are
now. This is the limbo state of the
persona that we have discussed with many
of you many times that makes you feel as
if you are as you say in neutral gear
floating in the midst of a collection of
probable directions and probable reality
not necessarily knowing which one to
take or which ones to take or in what
direction to move or act. This is in a
sense not a new state of being but it is
new in the sense of how many of you are
beginning to recognize that this state
exists and it is a natural
thing. Many of you have become very
worried about experiencing this state.
You say oh no I'm becoming
disoriented. Yes you are. And that's the
whole purpose to become
disoriented to old ideas, old use, old
personas you no longer need to be, no
longer prefer to be. You say, "Oh, now
I'm becoming
confused." Yes, you are. As we have
said, confused, fused with more of
yourself. I'm becoming
depressed. I don't know what to
do. Depression once again is only
meditation that is judged to be negative
by you. It is actually compression where
you pull yourself together into the very
center of your being and examine all the
things you prefer to be and then expand
as the new persona having restructured
and redefined yourself in a new
direction. That's why when you come out
of your depressions, you really feel
like new people. You are new people.
Even though you may think you look the
same, you are a new person literally
because once again the persona is
constantly unfolding and it is
constantly changing. It is an artificial construct.
construct.
So everything you will hear from most
consciousnesses of our nature will be
aimed at reminding you that you have the
tools to be whatever persona you wish to
be and to be whatever life you wish to
be is represented by the persona you
choose to
be. Always the clearest definition of the
Always the clearest definition of the
persona you create yourself to be will
determine the life you live. Always
because your physical reality is only
the product of what you define it to be.
It always has been, is now, and always
will
be. All of you have that ability because
all of you are a part of the infinite.
And what you are learning to do is not
lose your individuality but at the same
time as you strengthen your
individuality glean a true feeling
perception of the individual. All of you
are together because you are together an
individual. And with our world together,
your world and our world is while we are
individuals, an individual, a larger
individual. And with other worlds
together, we are a larger
individual that will go on
forever. There is no end to it. No end.
end.
Infinity means just that. The infinite
is without end and without beginning. It
is infinite in all directions. Direction
simply being your nomenclature. How you
see things in linear space and linear
time. Your personas now are dissolving
their old barriers, their old
definitions and expanding accordingly.
And that is why we are capable and any
level of consciousness now is capable of
interacting with you in this
way. We remind you that just as once
again everything is a mirror. We are a
mirror for you for all that you can
choose to be in your own way. Not saying
you have to do it the way we have done
it. I remind you once again our motto.
Do not believe anything I say just
because I said it. Believe it because
you feel that it is true for you.
because it works for
you. All the
ways that you can discover for life to
work for you are all true, are all real,
are all valid, are all accurate, are all
powerful. Infinity is just that. All the
different ways together as
one. At this timing, we thank you for
cocreating this interaction with us.
once again for choosing to be
ambassadors, representatives of your society and
representatives of your society and
allowing us to represent our respective
societies. In return for the gift of
your sharing, I ask you now, how may I
be allowed to serve each and every one
of you? Good evening, Bashar. And to
you, good day.
Uh you were just talking about the
spiral of life unwinding. Yes. Through
time. As time. As time. Yes. Uh what
would happen
if a person had his spiral or I guess
you could call it even a helix perhaps?
Yes. Yes. Yes. In three-dimensional
terms. Yes. A helix. Yes. So he had his
time planned out so to speak, so to
speak. Timing planned out. Yes. And then
he died. Yes. And did not return to what
you might call the spiritual plane,
but regained another body. Yes. And
continued on on a on a on another life.
Yes. And
so this is quite typical especially on
your world. Because of the cycle of
world. Because of the cycle of
forgetfulness that many of you have
created so long ago about the fact that
you can have a choice to go where you
want to go after physical death. Many of
you have created an automatic return
cycle. That is what you have called
karma. This automatic return cycle is
now what you are, I shall assume,
beginning to be aware is your creation
and can be broken simply by your
awareness that it is your creation. That
you can actually go wherever and
whenever you want to.
And what I'm referring to is that there
is a
uh starting to be known a perceived
cycle in which someone dies and their
spirit goes into some kind of a white
light. Yes. And goes into like a Yes.
These are what you might call lower
astral realms. Lower astral non-physical
quasifysical vibratory states of
existence. very close to physical
reality but just slightly higher in
frequency. Understand? The idea simply
is is that they do enter the spiritual
realm but there is a layering that you
have created in this spiritual realm
around your world that makes it so that
the lower layers will contain the
automatic return cycle and the higher
layers will not. Okay. But what happens
if someone doesn't even enter those
layers and then well they have to enter
them somewhat. If you become
non-physical at all then in your
terminology you are in one of the
non-physical layers. Now they do not
have to recognize they are
there. Understand? Yes. If they do not
recognize that they are there, it may in
your terms of perception take them a
long time for them to realize that they
can be anywhere they wish to be. There
will be individuals who will at least in
your terms make an attempt to remind
them of this to assist them. These are
what you call guides. And there are some
guides that are specifically crossover
guides to aid and assist individuals who
have in your terms physically died and
are in your terms disoriented about
where and when they are. The idea
throughout your history of what you have
called, more often than not, hauntings
or ghosts in that sense, are simply
individuals who many times do not even
know they have died and are still
attempting to live their physical lives,
not understanding and being confused
about why they cannot affect physical
reality in the same way they used to or
creating an illusion in a sense, a
hallucination for themselves that makes
it appear as if they are still affecting
physical reality when they're not.
individuals, crossover guides on either
the non-physical or the physical side
can send love and light and assurance
and reassurance to them to help orient
them and wake them up, open their eyes
to see where they are and allow them to
know they have conscious choice and
conscious ability to go where and when
they need to go. That was the original
purpose of what has become in your
society the idea of an exorcist.
It is a spirit psychologist in a sense
to allow individuals who have died to
know they have died that is all right to
go on with their lives on another level
if they wish
to understand. Yes. Is this clarifying
the idea you wished to discuss? Yes.
More than I thought it would. All right.
Well, thank you very much for your
sharing. Thank you. Shunning.
Shunning.
Yo. Oh, and good day to you.
Thank you. How are you? Uh, Mr.
Ambassador. Oh. Ah, perfect. How are
you, Mr. Diplomat?
Well, in uh new age terms, perfect. Oh,
thank you. In old age terms, lousy. Oh,
all right. Nice of you to represent both
sides of the issue. A true diplomat. Yes, thank
Yes, thank
you. I I'm actually just kidding. I have
been exploring um abundance again and
I've noticed that um I've identified two
areas of abundance. Oh, number one, I
have a lot of credit
and a lot and a lot of debt. Oh, all
right. Abundance of that.
What I um came up here to talk about was
a letter that I wrote to the president
uh on October 22nd and president of the
United States. All right. And got a
reply not from him but uh from the
National Archives. Oh, all right. And
they say that um the only reference we
found among our records to in our
custody to Snowbird is a January 11th,
1955 US Air Force memorandum on exercise
Snowbird. Snowbird being the the name of the
Snowbird being the the name of the
project that you identified anyway. Yes.
Relating to um extraterrestrial uh an
extraterrestrial crash on the planet in
1947. No. No. Snowbird refers to what
you call contact and communication and
dialogue between your world and other
worlds. Okay. Anyway, what they are
calling it uh exercise snowbird provides
for joint training of the employment of
army and air force units under arctic
conditions. They've enclosed a couple of
flyers and stuff like that. And yes, one
of them
says at the end of it, it says,
"Periodically, it is erroneously stated
that the remains of extraterrestrial
visitors are or have been stored at
Wright Patterson Air Force Base. There
are not now nor ever have been any
extraterrestrial visitors or equipment
on Wright Patterson Air Force Base. All
right. So yes, either they
are either they have identified Wright
either they have identified Wright
Patterson and that's not where they're
being kept and they've used this. Not
anymore. No. Okay. Well, see what I'm
wondering is it is they are are they
being ignorant at this point or are they
being um covert? Are they are they not
telling us the truth?
Most of the individuals who are
responsible for responding to your
letters do not know.
Okay. However, the original directives
for their response come from individuals
who do and in that sense they are being
covert. The individuals who in your
terms simply carry out the orders do not
know. Okay. Do you have a suggestion for
getting to the people who would know who
would uh best utilize my encouragement
to release the information?
You may, if you wish, perhaps involve
yourself with some of the individuals
who have already in your terms been
successful at acquiring from your
government documents that in that sense
do reinforce the existence of many of
our not our society specifically, but
our the association of world craft upon
your planet. Associate yourself with
individuals who have created
publications of that nature and perhaps
involve yourself in their organizations
because to some degree they are already
very well organized at accessing this
information from your government. Yeah.
So you can join them if you wish. That's
an idea. Add your voice to theirs. You
see one of the things that your
government has been taught to believe in
is numbers.
Yes, that's true.
So if you continue to act as isolated
individuals they can afford to not
listen. If you start becoming one voice
as many individuals then they will have
to because you will be saying that you
are your government and just as equal a
voice as you have created them to be.
Yeah. And again the whole thing is
unfolding within the timing. Oh okay.
Remember that to some degree, again, the
idea of what you may call mass
revelation of some of this information
upon your planet now would not
necessarily sit too well with the
majority of members upon your
planet. But it is leaking out at
whatever rate. It can be speeded up, but
it is still leaking out at whatever rate
represents the overall mass consensus
reality's ability to absorb the
information in a way that will not allow
your planet to feel as if it has been
undermined. in a sense by the sudden
appearance of other civilizations that
your society may still take to be so
much more advanced than you that you in
seeing the comparison that some of you
might inevitably make between yourselves
and us would give up trying. Understand?
Yes. Sure. Um I'd like to ask a related
question. I see it as related because it
relates to our government. All right. I
just read a briefly, excuse me, a
briefing on Soviet scalar
electromagnetic weapons. Yes. And this
briefing indicated that uh the Soviets
have developed the scalar
electromagnetic technology to a very
relatively refined extent. Yes. And we
in this country at least our government
is totally ignorant of it. Well, not
ignorant. No, but you are concentrating
on other things.
You have a wide selection of weapons of
destruction. Yeah, I know. Now, the idea
to some degree has already been realized
by individuals working with what you
call the scalar wave technology that it
cannot be used to its full potential.
Otherwise, the total disruption of your
entire structure of your planet would be
at stake because of the uh sun earth uh
earth moon and moon sun electromagnetic
u mostly simply because of the earth's
own crystallin structure. The scalar
wave technology would in a sense break
it aunder at certain pitches. Mhm. This
to some degree is more analogous to the
type of technology that was utilized by
the world we have referred to called
Maldbec which destroyed itself. Oh,
understand. It was not in your terms
nuclear. It was more the idea of
vibratory wave technology that has the
ability to truly disassemble a planet.
Okay. Well, according to this briefing,
the Soviets have developed this
technology to a point where they can
defend themselves against our missiles.
Now, I'm not particularly into the
weapons or anything, but it is not very
well directed at this time. And again,
they understand that they cannot really
use it to its full potential, for it can
in your terms get out of hand and wreak
more havoc even upon them than it would
do to the incoming missile. Was that
responsible for the accident at
Chernobyl? No. Okay. Was it responsible for the
No. Okay. Was it responsible for the
destruction of the Challenger? No. Okay.
This briefing seemed to think that it
was, but uh No, you're saying not. Okay.
Uh was it responsible for some of the
space some of the missile shot failures?
Some earlier ideas much earlier on in
your program were the early
experimentations with some of that
technology. I will not get any more
detail than that. Okay. when I when I
was asking for uh you know if there was
responsible I was talking about the
Soviets using them against I understand
what you were saying. Very good. Thank
you. By the way, I want to thank myself
for all the affection that you've been
to me. Oh,
[Applause]
hi Bashar. And to you good day. Um I'm a
little nervous because this is the first
time I've talked to you in person. Well,
this is the first time I have talked to
you and I'm overjoyed.
Okay, you be overjoyed and I'll try to
reflect that. Oh, all right. Go right
ahead. Do remember we have talked about
the fact that anxiety and excitement are
the same energy. One experience through
doubt and one experience through trust.
Understand? Mhm. So, let your
nervousness transform into the positive
side of excitement. That's all you're
really feeling is your own energy
expanding. Okay. Do continue and do share. Everyone
Okay. Do continue and do share. Everyone
is a gift and everything you have to
share is valid. Thank you.
Um my question is is there any
information or insight you might like to
share with me? We do not work that way.
Oh, you must initiate the opening of the
door by sharing the idea that excites
you the most. When you make your
statements of conviction more strongly
than you make your questions, then we
are allowed to perceive more about your
energy. If you simply ask us to tell you
what we see in that sense, then you
yourself are not necessarily putting out
the reflection, putting out the energy
that we can reflect back to you. The
idea we always do when you ask us if
there is anything we would see about you
and share with you would be to turn it
back to you in the form of the question
that we usually ask everyone. Are you
doing in your life the thing that
excites you the most or not?
I think so. You think so? You don't
know? Well, so far I think it's the most
exciting thing. All right. Is there
anything else you could imagine doing
that would be more exciting than what
you're doing now?
Yeah. Such as traveling or traveling.
All right. Going on vacations a lot for
any particular purpose.
Just to enjoy it. All
right. What service, what expression of
creativity does it excite you to create
on your planet? What outward expression
of creativity?
Um, God, I didn't think this was going
to be so hard.
Doesn't have to be. Does nothing excite
you in the sense of sitting out there
and I Pardon me. Does nothing excite you
in the sense of creativity? Yeah. I'm
just not sure what where to direct it. I
I don't know. Um I mean, I feel a lot of
energy inside. I just don't know how to
put it out there. All right. I don't
know which direction. All right. All
right. Well, this is what we are
discussing. The direction is always most
strongly represented by the thing that
excites you the most. That's why it
excites you the most. The idea of
excitement is the signal of the thing
that represents the direction in which
to put your energy. That's what
excitement is for. That's what it tells
you. Understand? Mhm. So, when you have
allowed yourself to glean the things
that are most exciting to you at any
given moment, then act upon the
opportunities that in your estimation
best represent your ability to move in
the direction of what excites you the
most. And that will be the fulfillment
of that direction. Okay, this excites me
a lot. I mean, reading about all this
metaphysical and trying to learn that is
absorbing. What about reflecting?
You're not a one-way mirror. Well, I'm
not sure how I can reflect this. What
excites you the most in terms of
creative output?
Is there something that would represent
a creative expression that would excite
you to
do? Do you want to share the information
you are learning about? Yes. In what way
would excite you the most to do so?
I don't know. It's it's all kind of new
to me. So, I'm not really sure what ways
are available. Then you don't have to be
in such a hurry. If it's really that new
to you and right now you are in what can
be called absorption mode, then continue
to absorb and allow yourself to be
attracted to whatever information works
best for you. There is nothing in that
sense that you have to do at any
particular time. The idea is to simply
recognize that when the timing is
appropriate for you to be able to
express in a creative output modality
what it is that you are best at, then an
opportunity will automatically be
dropped in your lap. That will be the
opportunity that absolutely represents
what will allow you to express yourself
in the fullest possible way. If no such
opportunities are making themselves
obvious right now, then continue to
absorb and learn what you need to learn
to be who it is you wish to be and enjoy
that. Remember also that when we talk
about doing what excites you the most,
we are talking about moment to moment to
moment. You don't necessarily at every
given moment need an absolute curriculum
in order to know that you are living in
the present, living in the moment and
doing what excites you the most at any
given moment with integrity.
Allow yourself to absorb. If it is new
to you in a sense, then absorb it in
whatever way is most joyous for you. If
at any moment it strikes you to express
it in some way of sharing, do so.
Express it in whatever way is your
creative modality. Do so. That will then
be your service. That will be your
reflection. That will be your feedback
to those around you. So that they will
then see by your example who you are,
what ideas you have to share, what
perspectives you have to share with
them. So they can see through you. Yet
one more way that the infinite has of
expressing itself within the creation
that it is. This whole idea does not
have a real time track affixed to it. is
spontaneous play, spontaneous allowance, spontaneous
play, spontaneous allowance, spontaneous
expression of joy, ecstasy, excitement,
creativity. Does this sound good to you?
Mhm. Can you relax in the modality you are in
Can you relax in the modality you are in
without necessarily wondering if you
should be doing something else? Yes.
That really is in that sense nothing to
say except what we have said. If
opportunities need to be in your life to
allow you to express yourself, they will
be there. Everything works
automatically. You do not have to try to
do anything except the things that
represent who you are not. Those are the
only things you really have to try to
do. The things that you are
not. The things you really are will come
into your life and the opportunities to
do them will come into your life
automatically, effortlessly, joyously, with
effortlessly, joyously, with
excitement. It'll be an obvious path to
take, an obvious direction when it
comes. You won't even think twice about
it necessarily. You'll just move because
it excites you to do so. And that will
lure you into the circumstances to give
you the capabilities that you need to
express yourself as you have chosen to
express yourself in being of service on
your planet at this time.
Understand? Yes. Is this of assistance
to you? Yes. Does it
sufficiently respond to your query? Yes. Yes.
Maybe.
Well, would you rather that I simply
told you go here, do this, and No, I was
just hoping you could um Oh, hoping.
Yes. Yeah. Which implies doubt. I would
have liked. Yes. Is that better? Um if
if there was a little bit of something
that you would have been willing to
share with me that wouldn't unravel my
carpet too quickly,
but just a little I don't know. I don't
know. I guess I was just All right. All
right. All right.
One moment.
First we access what you may
colloquially call clearance to do so.
This we will do from one of your own
guides. Oh, I do have them then. Of
course. Thank you. Thank you. Everybody
does. Now, one of the suggestions which may
Now, one of the suggestions which may
come symbolically, but you see that's
the way the guides speak is to hold in
your hand a copper bowl.
If you were holding in your hand a small
copper bowl, what would you like to fill
it with?
Well, water. Is that a question? Well,
it's the first it's the first thing that
came to my water. All right.
Water. And then what would you like to
do with it? Probably drink it. All
right. And what do you imagine would
happen?
It would be cool. and
refreshing. And would it have any other
effect upon your psyche?
I'm calming, I guess. Lead you to do
anything else?
You still have the bowl, you know.
Anything else you wish to do with it?
Well, if there were other people around
me, I'd probably share it. In what way?
I'd pass it around. Pass it around. Oh.
I didn't know I wasn't by myself.
Okay. And what would happen after you
passed it around?
Would they drink from it as well? Yes.
Uh-huh. And how would it allow them to
feel
refreshed and calm? And And how would
you feel about them in seeing them do
this?
Good. I I'd feel I'd feel like we shared
something that that I don't know. Yes,
you do. Be nice. Yes, you do. Know it
would be nice. I feel close with them.
You'd feel close. All right. You'd begin
to identify with them. Yes. Mhm. Begin
to share in intimate ways with them.
Yes. Mhm. Intimacy. Yes. Intimacy.
Yes. Intimacy.
Okay. Yes.
The copper bowl and the water therein to
some degree is a symbol of intimacy in
certain ways. Experiment with this if
you wish and see how much further you
get with that
idea. Pay especially attention to your
dream conversations with your
guides in creating this symbol for
yourself. And I will give you one word.
One word which is
allow
oracle. That is what we can share. See
what comes of that. Okay. And have a
good time. Thank you. Thank you very
much. Shannon.
Hello Bashar. And do you good? Um I have
the great fortune of doing something
that excites me very much. All right.
Um, recently I've been um sort of
personalizing it to the point where uh
I'm responsible for um all of the
creativity. I I'm a songwriter and a
singer. And recently I've I've had a lot
of opportunities
to share my music um and try to get it
out and what um and get it out. Thank
you. Um, but it's not I guess it's not
as important to me as the actual
writing. I guess the the actual writing
of it and performing it is what excites
me the bo the most. So I have a problem.
A problem how I have a challenge. All
right. Um of doing business with it. I I
have a tendency not to return phone
calls thinking that I'm sure that person
is a choice. It's a choice. Yes. But I
it I think it stems from just the
feeling that um um I I almost know
intuitively whether it's going to be a
waste of time. Take me away from the
creative process. Well, take me away
from the creative process. It's not
possible. Okay. Why would you assume
that it is? Why have within you the
definition that that particular scenario
only contains the type of circumstances
that would remove you from your creative
process? Why not create a definition
where that particular methodology of
getting your music out there would only
come to you in the way that would still
allow you to remain completely attached
to your creative process? Why not define
it to come to you in the way that will
allow you to do that rather than
assuming that it can only come to you in
the ways that would remove you from that
creative process? Why do you have that
definition? Well, I guess because I
don't feel that the business aspect is
very creative. Oh,
it's just the way I feel. It is just as
creative as anything. Now, you may not
prefer to manifest it in your life in
the way other individuals have, but that
does not mean there is not a way that
fits who you
are. That is always the key for all of
you in any endeavor in terms of
expanding and expressing yourself. There
is always a method in any category that
fits the way you
are. There are no extraneous creations.
There are no unfulfilled creations.
There are no incomplete kits.
everything you are. If somehow what you
are gives you an indication that you can
expand yourself in certain ways that
other individuals can receive what you
have to share in certain ways, then take
it for granted that there must be there
must be a methodology that represents
the methodology that will allow you the
easiest conduit to place yourself out
there in full sight and sound without
that conduit being a taxation on the
things that excite you the most in the
giving.
Why? That what gives you
joy would need to
attract another aspect of that idea that
would not be able to give you as much
joy or expand the joy you already have.
Why assume that the joy you have can
only be funneled to other individuals
along pathways that would restrict what
you are? I feel that I that restriction.
Well, yes, you feel it because you
believe in it. Yeah, but that's simply
the definitions you have been taught.
You have had it drumed into you over and
over and over again. This is the way
business is. Get used to it, kid.
You have to, as you say, eat or be
eaten. I know. I guess I I just I feel so so
I know. I guess I I just I feel so so
much more comfortable sort of on an
artistic level and I I understand what
you maybe there's a vision visionary
person out there that can handle that
end of it for me. But you are missing
the point. Attracting that person can be
your way of getting yourself out there.
That's all we're saying. No matter what
form it takes, there is a conduit for
you to express yourself to the fullest
of the capacity you want to. in a way
that will allow you not to feel
hindered. Be that another person or a
methodology, doesn't matter. Attract
whatever is there that will key into
your pattern because you can because it's
pattern because you can because it's
there for you. For every single person
who acts, there is a stage for every
single person. As long as you understand what
person. As long as you understand what
you are is valid for what it is, then
you can attract the appropriate stage or
circumstances to allow you to be
represented in your purest possible
form. Right? Nothing has to limit nor
restrict your expression of what gives
you joy. Well, see, I feel that the
expression is there and that is what
excites me the most. It's it's not
dropping the tape off your expression.
Um well I've become aware recently that
just the mere fact um that I have
created a song um I I feel like I
channel when I write. Well yes yes yes
yes that's what channeling is and I feel
that it has entered the consciousness
just by the mere fact that I've created
it. Yes. So now you can be excited
simply about the doing of it in that
way. You know, it does not have to in
your terms go any farther, but we have
simply perceived within you some sort of
a desire on some level that it should.
Well, I Yeah, I want it to affect some
change, you know. Oh, all right. Then
assume once again that if you simply
continue to be who you really know you
are and fully express yourself, you can
then by retransating the definition of
business attract to yourself whatever
conduit or path will allow you to put
out there your creativity and create
that impact. Do not assume that it has
to come in ways that restrict you. Well,
it's just very difficult weeding through
all the people that stop stop. What you
have just said is not a law of the
universe. It is another definition.
You're right. It's very difficult to
weed through all these people. You have
been taught that phrase. You see, this
is what you call your catch 22. Many of
you think, well, I don't do it because
of this. It's for this reason that I
don't do that. And then, well, all
right. I see that I don't have to think
this way anymore. And I see I don't have
to think this way anymore. But now
because of this reason over here, it's
hard to stop thinking that way. And
because of that reason, it's hard to
stop thinking that way and that reason
this way and that reason. You'll never
run out of reasons if you keep creating
them. All right? So I have to get
excited about meeting uh whoever it
might be that you don't even necessarily
have to worry about the details. You do
not have to come up with the way it will
happen. The details are always
subordinate to your strongest intention.
As long as you are fully excited about
being the you you prefer to be, and just
know beyond a shadow of a doubt that if
one of the things about being the most
exciting you you can be is the fact that
you will have an impact upon your
society, you will automatically attract
whether you consciously are aware of how
or not, the circumstances and
individuals necessary to allow you to
create that impact. You don't have to
know what the details are. Yeah, I feel
that. I feel it's it's on its way. Yes.
All you have to do is get out of your
own way by ceasing to impose upon
yourselves definitions of a physical
reality that have nothing to do with who
you say you want to be. Okay, I'll
monitor my
definitions. Um, one, don't try too
hard. I won't. Do remember one other
thing. This ties into the idea of
persona that we were discussing earlier
in this interaction. And we thank you
for allowing us to bring this point up.
Now in your interaction, many of you
think what you call your physical
senses is what lets your reality
in. No, your physical senses is what
keeps most of it
out. Your physical senses are not in a
sense perceivers as much as they are
filters. Understand? Yes. So the only things you
Understand? Yes. So the only things you
will see at any time will be what you
believe most strongly is the most likely
thing you will see. That's it. Your
physical senses will act as automatic
filters to represent your strongest
beliefs and will give you only your
strongest beliefs and definitions. They
are filters not perceivers. They keep
most of reality out.
It's frightening. No, very freeing.
Okay. Because then you can choose what
you will perceive and know beyond a
shadow of a doubt that's what you'll
get. Because what you have determined is
the clearest definition will be what you
get and nothing else will interfere with
it. Understand? Mhm. Just because I'm
saying that it's a filter doesn't mean
that's a negative connotation. Did you
think it was? Well, I guess I did. Well,
thank you. Another opportunity to
discover within yourself how you choose
to label things. And that has a lot to
do with how you experience life. It's
true. Remember, none of these
situations, no situation has built-in
meaning. No situation means anything.
They are neutral, empty, devoid of
meaning. The meaning you automatically
give them through what you have been
taught to give them is the effect they
have in your life. No more, no
less. Does this help you? Very much so.
Thank you. Well, thank you for singing
your song to us. You're welcome. Sharing
Hi, how you doing? Perfect. And you?
Good day. Good day. Great. I have a
question on um healing. Healing. All
right. Um uh yeah, I I know we just you
just sort of talked about how there
really isn't any purpose in methods that
it's the intention that gets you there.
Well, there are methods, but the
intention in that sense will always
attract the opportunities to allow you
to express the methods that are most
conducive for the intention you are.
Okay, great. Then I have a question on a
a method for myself. Yes. On um doing
absent healing. Absent healing. Yes.
Um because one of my cats was was
injured in a car accident. What? And I
just want to know if there's any
specific method that I could use that
would be best to um allow Have you used
your imagination to come up with a
method? That is what your imagination is
for first of all to give you all the
methodologies that work best for you.
Have you used your imagination to
imagine a method you could use? I've
used a lot of methods. That's why I'm
wondering if there's one that would be
better than another.
These methods that you have
used, what did you feel about them? Were
you using them out of desperation or
inspiration?
H both. I think one or the other. Okay.
Not both at the same time. Okay.
When you use them out of inspiration,
you will get the result you need. When
you use them out of desperation, you are
grabbing at straws, as you say. Okay.
Understand? Yes. Let your imagination
inspire you.
Okay. Um, how can I channel the most
energy that I can possibly channel to do
healing? Is there is there any um is
there anything you can tell? and loving
as unconditionally as you can. Okay.
Now allow yourself also for do
understand animal consciousness is
always a reflection and a guide for all
of you. Many of them are willing to put
themselves in circumstances that will
put you squarely face to face with the
thing you actually need to understand
about yourself.
So in dealing with your
cat, what comes up within you about
yourself? Does it allow you to face the
idea of your own healing abilities? Does
it allow you to face the idea of what
you say you really want to be and do?
Does it really put you in touch with
more of the definitions you have created
yourself to be? And does it allow you to
change those definitions in ways that
you prefer to? Does it put you through
your paces? Yes, very much. Then in a
sense that's what it's for. Whatever you
are discovering about yourself in the
interaction between you and your animal
friend is what that particular situation
was created for because the animals do
love unconditionally. You could learn that
unconditionally. You could learn that
from
them. You understand? Yes. Now that does
not mean that they have to injure
themselves many times to prove a point.
But the idea simply is that because of
the way your world still is, sometimes
that's the quickest way. They in a sense
know ultimately they are really in no
danger. They know they are infinite
consciousness. They know that physical
reality is simply one aspect of the
total consciousness that they are. They
do not really have a hard dividing line
in most cases between the idea of
physical reality and non-physical
reality. So they can be more willing to
express in certain ways ideas even if it
seems to cause them physical harm that
will actually serve you in the quickest
way. The sooner you learn what you need
to learn about yourself in the
interaction, the sooner they in a sense
no longer need to exhibit that idea and
they will be healed. In a sense, that's
one of the quickest ways to heal them.
Learn why you are present in that
interaction. What that type of
expression or gesture on their part
shows you about yourself. what it puts
you in touch with within yourself.
Integrate that information, learn from
it, become more expanded. They will no
longer need to reflect that idea to you.
They will be healed. Great. Understand?
Yes. Thank you very much. Remember that
your cat is the symbol of the bridge
between physical and non-physical
reality. Understand? Yes. Thank you. Well, thank
Understand? Yes. Thank you. Well, thank
you very
much, Shannon.
Bashar, welcome. And you as well. Good
day. Um, this is this formal channeling
is uh very new to me. Um, formal. Well,
this this setting is very I'm sure I
have channeled before with other beings
and people. All of you channel in many
ways, but I'm I've never been aware of
it. Um, my life has been very fulfilled and
Um, my life has been very fulfilled and
since I was a child. Yes. Oh, thank you.
And I still am. Yeah. Thank you. But
something concerns me. Um, I have always
been intrigued and fascinated with the
physical part of the earth with
meteorology and geology changes. Nice.
And since I was a child, I monitored and
watched as much as I could see and tried
to place pieces together to see if there
was any
um puzzle that was being put together
with a a change on the planet. Oh yes.
Um hand in hand with your consciousness
changes. Changes occur upon your
planetary sphere both in the ground and
in the air and in the energy. Hand in
hand with the changes in your planetary
sphere both in the ground and in the
weather and in the energy are changes in
your consciousness. They are handinand
with each other manifestations of the
one idea. All of you are together. They
are interrelated, interconnected,
inseparable. Okay. So this would explain
and I've read this also with with the
higher consciousness that we're all
seeking um and the changes that are
happening so quickly as we seem to
perceive them. Yes. now because we are
perceiving the changes now. Yes. And let
me simply remind each and every one of
you that all of these changes can be
experienced either in a negative or a
positive way depending upon how you
approach the changes within yourself.
Correct. What puzzles me is I am seeing
more and more and for some reason I
there's an inner feeling for me um that
in the next year of our time uh that
we're going to see some drastic physical
cataclysmic changes here and there there
may be some spontaneous representations
of this. It is nowhere near as
widespread as it would have been had
these changes occurred approximately 30
to 50 of your years ago. You have
already done much to alleviate many of
these ideas and many of the notions of
the degree of the change you are feeling
doesn't mean that it has to be
experienced in physical terms. It can be
a shift within your consciousness. It
will be a physical change but it does
not have to be a destruction to be a
destructurization. Correct? Remember that every thought you
Correct? Remember that every thought you
have literally changes you physically.
But that doesn't mean you have to
experience the change in what you would
call an abrupt destructive way. You will
change physically. The vibratory
frequency of your planet will ascend,
will accelerate in many different ways.
This in and of itself will cause many
physiological changes, but they do not
necessarily have to come in ways that
are destructive. There may be isolated
places around your planet that will not
be able to create the transformation in
any other way. But some of these areas
will act in your terms as safety valves.
And many of them do not have to happen
in areas that in your terms are highly
populated. Understand? Yes. One of the
strongest changes will be the
electromagnetic field of your planet
itself. And this can create many changes
within the consciousness and within the
crystallin form of your earth. Yes,
there will be a few. But individuals who
are not on the frequency of needing to
experience the idea catastrophically
even if they are in those loces will not
be negatively affected.
Understand? I understand. Thank you. Oh,
thank you very much. And thank you for
your sensitivity. Shutting.
Shutting.
Hello. Oh, and good day to you. Um, my
name is Kathy and all right. Um, my
question is
my question is um throughout my life
people have always called me Mary. All
right. And it's people that that are
familiar with me that that I'm
acquainted with. And I just I'm curious
as to well maybe I I do think that
perhaps it's from a past life
experience. There are some associations
but that is not the only one. Uhhuh.
Some of it has to do with the fact that
in dream states, you're actually very
helpful to many people and they know you
in the dream guide state as Mary because
Mary is more representative of your
whole energy, not just the person you
are physically now. Understand? Yes. So,
they're simply calling you by your dream
name. I see. Does this help? Well, yes.
Thank you. Well, thank you very much, Shannon.
Shannon.
Hello Bashar. Oh, and to you good day.
Thank you. One moment if you please.
Certainly. By the way, all of you are
very busy in your dream lives. Very
busy. You are learning many things. You
are being of assistance to many
individuals. You're having
conversations, so to
speak. Even though you might not have
mouths, as you understand
it, but you are all very interactive.
And many of you already in many
different ways function as guides and
reflections for other individuals being
of assistance being loving being caring
and compassionate in that way. Thank
you. Yes.
Um a few weeks ago I had an experience.
It was um while I was working with the
healer, right? And the experience as I
sensed it was that a being came into me,
but it was me. Yes. But it was a me that
I felt hadn't ever been in this body. I
understand. It was in a sense that is
correct. Okay.
Okay.
I felt that it was a being that I've
been told is an alien spirit guide of
mine, so to speak. Another aspect of the
same oversoul of which you are a part.
Similar, not exactly the same way,
similar to the relationship. I am to the
physical channel. We are extensions of
the same oversoul. I am to some degree
the channel's future self to use your
classic terminology.
So in that sense I have never been quote
unquote as myself the body of the
physical channel. Although now that I am
linking and identifying with the idea I
call the body of the physical channel
one of my past
lives. Understand? So this would be a
future self of mine. I it felt so much
like me that it became kind of
schizophrenic. I felt like I was talking
to myself. Well, you were and you still
are right
now because you are the in a sense the
only one in your immediate reality and
you are co-creating all the reflections
of us including me that you interact
with. So in a sense what you're doing is
talking to yourself right now. The idea
simply is that it is mostly
representative of other connections you
have in other areas and other
dimensions. But it is also
representative of the future you you
will be on your planet. the you you are
turning into using the other idea as a
guide as a reference in again the same
way that the physical channel before you
is using my consciousness as a reference
to become more of his version of me to
have his own future self on your planet
even while I am his future self in
another dimension remember what we talked about
dimension remember what we talked about
of being multi-dimensional beings right
yes so in a sense you are familiarizing
and in a sense to some degree
refamiliarizing yourself with another
aspect of your own consciousness that
exists in another dimensional plane. And
you are feeding that information, that
contact through yourself, as we perceive
you anyway, to allow yourself to
construct the you you prefer to be in
your immediate future
reality. You are creating a multiple
reflection of who it is you desire to be
from. Many different points of view.
Many different reference beams are going
into the creation of the you you prefer
to be.
Is this making any sense to you? Yes,
very much. When I have this experience
again as I expect to or in a sense
you're having it right now. Okay. Do not
feel that you must experience it in
exactly the same way all the time.
Remember sometimes when many of you
think, "Oh, I have this wonderful
experience. I wish I could feel it
again." Mhm. It is not that it has gone
anywhere. It's that you have acclimated.
So you don't notice it as much. Yeah.
Okay. And then you get something else
that represents yet a higher level and
you acclimate to that and then you don't
notice it as much because now you're
used to it. So you are actually
experiencing it to some degree right
now. Mhm. The fear that I experienced as
as that sort of wore off and even kind
of insanity that I felt. Very typical on
your planet.
Um I'm not being condescending. Okay. It
simply is that because so many of you
have been brought up to have repressed
and suppressed portions of your
consciousness. When you start to
reintegrate yourself as a whole being,
all those things that you have
suppressed must by definition come to
the forefront and be dealt with and be
integrated. All you're doing is
discovering more and more and more of
you. As we have said, two things.
Nothing nothing there is nothing you
could ever discover about yourself that
cannot be applied in a positive way. So
you do not have to buy into the fear.
The fear is only there to point out
things that you have been taught to
ignore. The fear makes it so that you
can no longer ignore it. It grabs your
attention. It grabbed me. All right. Oh, yes.
It grabbed me. All right. Oh, yes.
Because you see, you have as a society
not been taught to live in the moment in
joy. So, if the only way you can live in
the moment is through fear, that's how
you'll do it until you get the hang of
it. I see. So the more the more I can
let go of the fear then the more joy it
will be. There is absolutely nothing
within the circumstance itself that is
inherently fearinducing. Only your definition of
fearinducing. Only your definition of
what you think or have been taught to
think the circumstance is all about is
what generates the fear. Only your
definition of it. The second suggestion
we would give to you, share with you and
all of you is simply once again another
motto. Put in what you may call a
rhyming form. So in your terms, it's
perhaps a little more fun to remember.
Let it through. It's only you
understand. Yes. Thank you. Help you
very much. Well, thank you for your joy
and your self-discovery. Thank you,
Shannon. Hello, Bushar. Onto you. Goodbye. Uh,
Hello, Bushar. Onto you. Goodbye. Uh,
first of all, I'd like to thank you for
that peace clock idea. That's really
great. Well, thank you for cocreating it
with us. Tick tock. I sent it out in my
Christmas cards and I would recommend
that you, if you haven't sent your cards
out yet, you might include a little
thing like that in. It's a easy way to
get it out. There will be provided for
you next week of your time actual as you
say literature that also can be dispersed to
literature that also can be dispersed to
your society.
Um couple of quick technical questions
right um people
people ask me a lot of questions about
the magnetic beds and one of the things
is how can we measure that 7.5 pulse
that you refer to the bed has is the
same as the earth. Do we have machines
that we like to some degree you do? Yes.
Some of your electromagnetic devices are
sensitive enough to pick it up. There
are however many ways to do this. You
can set up what is called a sympathetic
quote unquote vibrational tool. If you
can create in a sense a device
preferably of a hollow, fragile,
delicately balanced nature such as a
sealed tube or a sphere. And you can
impose upon that device the 7 and 1/2
cycle per second vibration by flowing a
current to it in that way and creating
it to vibrate in that way. Then in and
of itself it can be created to vibrating
at that pace be sensitive to all other
vibrations of that pitch and it can be
created to act in certain ways if it is
perhaps balanced to move as a compass
needle would move in certain ways to
align itself with that particular
frequency. You can create a device that
is sensitive to that pitch by giving it
that pitch itself so that it only
identifies with that pitch and will do
something either create a resonance or a
tone or a motion that will indicate to
you when something is also of the same
frequency. Understand? But it must be a
very delicately balanced and fragile
idea. Okay. Thank you. Made out of
conductive material.
The other uh thing that you mentioned
one time was these gigantic uh magnetic
imaging devices that they uh scan people
with. Yes. Can also be used as healing
devices but they don't know about that
yet. Yes. And I have a friend whose wife
is undergoing a number of treatments u
and measuring things and I was wondering
is there some uh something we can say to
the doctors or something that would make
them Well, I'll leave that up to you.
Well, I cannot force anyone to buy into
a belief they simply do not want to buy
into. Well, however, in the line of a
suggestion, yes, however, you can
perhaps suggest, oh, you know, I read
somewhere, I don't know
where, about the magnetic and electrical
conductivity of the body, and I saw
there were some experiments being done
by very reputable doctors and
scientists that showed how the body is
somewhat like a battery and how magnetic
field And electrical fields, especially
those that seem to resonate at the
frequency of the natural frequency of
the earth, seem to have some well sort
of, shall we say, balancing or conducive
balancing state to the body to allow the
body to perhaps or well maybe heal a
little bit faster than it normally
would. You know anything about this,
[Music] doctor? Maybe that way, but I'll leave
doctor? Maybe that way, but I'll leave
it up to your imagination. Perhaps you
can do your own research and find some
of the individuals that are already
working in that way. Perhaps you can
work with them. Perhaps you can attract
into your reality an individual that is
already sensitive to these ideas. Or
perhaps you can simply allow yourself to
know that everything is working out
according to your own timing and trust
it and act upon your instincts but in
ways that does not violate anyone else's
belief system. I'll leave that up to
you. But there are many ways you can
educate yourself with some of the
research that is being done upon your
planet and bring that up if you wish
specific references.
Okay, thank you very much. There is to
some degree, although we will not touch upon
degree, although we will not touch upon
this in exactly the same way literature
that exists in what you would call book
form that can set you in a certain
direction. There is one book we are
aware of called body
electric refer to that. There are many
other works as well. I didn't realize
there was anything that covered these
machines cuz they're they're so new. It
does not cover the machine. It covers
the principles that can then later be
adapted to the machine.
By the way, the discovery of the
electromagnetic pulse of any planet can
be found by simple formula. If you will
take what you call the circumference of
any planet in your terms now in miles
and you will divide that in terms of
those miles divided into what you call
your speed of light. You will then get a
result that is representative of the
cycles per second of the electromagnetic
field of the planet. Understand? Yes.
Good. Oh, thank you very much.
At this timing, you may all take a short
break. We will resume contact in
approximately 10 to 15 of your minutes. [Applause] How's it Those are continue.
are continue.
Hello and to you. Good day. Good day to
you, too.
I really don't have uh many questions.
All right. Uh, but I have a few
curiosities uh about you. Oh, what? Um,
I already asked you about if you slept
or not. Yeah, I know. I already know
that. So, but I wanted to ask you uh
what do you eat at this point in our
history? Nothing. We subsist mostly on
the idea of the intake of direct
electromagnetic energy since we are now
in our evolutionary transformation going
from physicality to non-physicality very
shortly. There used to be a time when we
did, in your terms, consume substances
similar to your own in many ways and
evolved in a sense to a time when we did
not require that much physiological
substance except very simple forms of
veitation. And then we evolved to a
point where our mass mentality created a
particular type of vegetation that would
be analogous to a crossbreed idea to
something what you would call either
corn or limema bean in nature. It was
not natural to the planet but it grew
naturally out of the energy of the
atmosphere of our combined mentality and
now as a civilization we no longer have
any need to even consume that for
sustenance. H okay.
Um you mentioned that uh well I know
that we all have guides. Yes. Okay. Um
and are we all guides to each other?
Yes. Um in our conscious state as well
as our dream state. Yes. Okay. Do you
have guides? In a sense, yes. Although
we do not necessarily carry on the same
kind of relationship with ours as you do
right now with yours, since we are more
consciously aware of their interaction
with us. It is simply that we have more
of a direct communication rather than an
unconscious one. But we do recognize there are many
one. But we do recognize there are many
levels of consciousness that are far
more accelerated and
expanded than our consciousness is. And
we can refer to them in a sense and key
off of them in a sense as reflections of
our own future directions and in that
sense use them as guides. We simply now
are more conscious about our
interactions with them because we are
more willing to be equal to
them. I see. And
um could you um expand on uh what the
definition of a guide would be uh here
for us now? our guides. Someone who
reflects to you the ideas that are most
representative of the vibrational
frequency you are or chose to be.
Understand? Yes, I do. Someone who
reminds you of who you are, right? Well,
we all remind each other who we are.
That's why you're all guides to each
other. That's right. Okay. Now the
relationship we have with our guides no
matter what their dimensional plane is
more akin to the type of relationship
you have with each other in your own
plane of existence.
Understand? Yes I do. Um I've been asked
a question to ask you um about during uh
the month of June I think it's 13th June
13th through the 22nd there's going to
be an alignment of the planets uh in our
solar system.
Um, are you aware of this alignment to
some degree though it will not
necessarily be as much of one as many of
you may think.
I see. So, um, there will not be any
great impact on the earth's vibration.
To some degree there will be but do
understand these ideas of planetary
alignment are more representative of the
state your consciousness already is in
rather than having a direct effect upon
your consciousness. I see. So our our
consciousness is creating this
alignment. Well, in a sense, yes. The
timing, the cycles that you have
patterned out within your collective
consciousness are responsible for the
timing of anything you observe in your
physiological universe that reflects
back to you those cycles and patterns
that are embedded within your
consciousness. Okay? So, everything we
actually know right now, we are
creating, right? Yes. So, we're creating
you right now, basically, right? You are
creating your version of me. I am
creating my version of you. That's
great. Yes. All right. Thank you very
much. Well, thank you very much.
Remember, as each and every one of you
become more aligned to more of yourself,
that is what has the greatest impact,
though it may be symbolized from time to
time in the seemingly exteriorized
cycles of your universe.
Thank you. Thank you, Sharing. Yes,
Bashar. uh a mutual friend of ours uh
David Lane who's a composer uh who's you
who heard you recently in uh Colorado
composed a piece of music that he'd like
you to hear and share with everyone. He
entitled it Living Light and we're going
to play it for you right now. Just a
couple minutes of it. All right. [Music] [Music]
Oh my god. god.
Yeah. Heat. [Laughter] Hello. Heat.
Heat. Heat. Heat. [Music]
Oh, heat, heat. [Music] [Music]
Oh, heat,
heat. Heat. Heat. [Music] Hallelujah. Oh yeah. Oh. [Music]
Oh, hallelujah.
[Music]
Well, thank you.
Thank you. By the
By the
way, as has been announced, we will hold
an
interaction upon what you call your
Christmas Eve
night. And on that night, we will
entitle that interaction Christmas
bells. All of you who desire to attend that
All of you who desire to attend that
night, bring, if you would, a bell of
your choice, one that really strikes a
chord within you, and we will have some
fun. How about the How about crystal balls? I
How about the How about crystal balls? I
just got one. Any type of bell will do.
That is a type of bell. Thank you. Yes,
Bishar. I have a a brief question. bowl,
right? Uh the bowl that I got is from
the information I have is made uh
different from the other bowls that I've
seen, it had it is made from crushed
real quartz crystal. Yes. And would that
affect the tone as you see it? Would
there be any difference in the vibratory
exchange? Different from what? From the
other ones which are made from
siliconized sand as I understand them.
There will obviously be to some degree a
slight difference, but it may only be in
the specifics, not the overall general
specifics, not the overall general
tonality. The basic theme will be the
same, but there may be some specific
keys that will be turned in one that are
not turned in another and vice versa as
you say. Very good. Thank you. Thank you
very much. Shedding.
Hi Bashar. How you doing? Oh, good day
to you. Um, I've been through quite a
process the past week and I was
wondering if you could comment on it
from your point of view and perspective.
May I ask a question? Sure. Oh, thank
you. Are you acting upon opportunities
that come into your life?
Uh, not all of them. No, I'm not. Um,
good question. Well, thank you. U, but I
intend to capitalize on all of them at
this point.
All right.
Simply you are reorganizing,
reassessing, recalibrating the idea of what
recalibrating the idea of what
physiological life can be. Allowing
yourself to see in clearer and clearer
approach different avenues now that can
be taken and how each of those different
avenues can interrelate to each other in
the doing of your life in the acting through
doing of your life in the acting through
of your life and in the being of service
and physical way for other individuals
and then receiving the abundance
necessary in the reflection of the doing
of that service. You are
recategorizing your idea of who and what
you are as a
persona. Allow yourself to begin as you
have said to more fully act upon the
opportunities that are coming to be of
service in various ways that can support
you in that sense. Mhm. Okay. Does this
assist you? Yes, it does. And could you
comment? I keep getting the phrase uh
second phase Andromeda activity. And
what does that mean? Can you shed some
light? Remember that the idea of
Andromeda consciousness is that which
represents in the local quote unquote
group of galactic consciousness is that
which is the overall and not meant in a
ruling way but the overall organizing
energy. It is that which is the conduit
through which flows all the
communications of all of what you would
call the nearby galactic consciousness.
says therefore you are tapping into that
because you are representing in your own
life the whole idea of organizing things
in a way that will actually serve best
all the individuals you come in contact
with and then can serve you best. It is
a facilitation energy in a sense. You
follow me? I see. A networking energy in
a sense. You follow me? Definitely. Does
that help you? It does. They seem to say
uh as far as all the different
extraterrestrial groups that are active
down here that if you step back and look
at them more holographically you get a
better picture in a sense. Yes. Because
then you are also included in the
picture but in your own terms and
there's more balance there. Yes. Okay.
Because we are all intertwined in that
way. And remember that regardless of the
individuals we are we can only come to
you through your consciousness your
dimensional frequency. So we are
inexurably a part of your consciousness
even as you are a part of ours because
that's the only way we can experience
each other is through each other. Mhm.
Have you been communicating with uh the
plleadian named Ta lately?
Off and on. Is he okay? Yes.
Okay. At least the aspect we are
communicating with is fine. All right.
That's all I need to know. Now one thing
we will share at this
time. Now not meaning that each and
every one of these is in your
terminology members of what you would
call the association in the way we refer
to other worlds, other civilizations.
Some of them
are. But the idea simply to delineate
your immediate shall we say
neighborhood will be as follows.
within what you call
approximately 12 of your light years
surrounding you in a spherical
manner. The closest civilizations to you
are in your neighboring system of what
you call Alpha
Centauri in what has been termed
Barnard's star and we have discussed
this many times.
In the system of Sirius and we have
discussed this many
times. In the system you call epsilon
Eidani in the system you call epsilon
Indi and in the system you call to
cityi. These are the closest
civilizations to you within what you may
call a 12 lightyear radius.
Now there is consciousness associated
also with the star system you have
labeled wolf
359 but it is of a nature that we will
not go into now.
Thank you very much. Thank you.
We will expand on some of these ideas
later. [Music] [Music]
Sharing
good day Bashar and to you good day. I
have enjoyed so much the entering into
the imagination more and expanding it.
Well, thank you very much.
And I'm and I'm wondering about
uh
about when it goes into fantasizing or
now there can be sometimes what you may
call a fine line between the idea of
what you would call quote unquote
pragmatic imagination and fantasy. It is
all real on some level. The things that
you would more often than not, however,
call fantasy are simply those realities
your imagination is in touch with that
may not have what you would call
immediate application in your physical
dimension. That is simply a matter of
degree as well. For now, in your
transformational age, many more things
can actually apply now that you are
opening up your definitions of what your
reality is to begin with. So there is
not as clear-cut a definition anymore
between the idea of imagination you
manifest physically and imagination that
has to do with other realities that are
not applicable in your world. Many more
realities are now becoming applicable on
your level as well.
However, generally speaking, you will
find that the imagination that is
representative of the realities that can
be applicable in your world will be
represented by circumstances and
opportunities that will be most
automatically attracted into your life
to act upon. The imagination that is in
touch with reality that is not
immediately applicable will not attract
opportunities for you to be able to do
anything about it. Understand? Yes.
Nothing will manifest as an opportunity
physiologically that will give you a
chance to manifest it simply because it
does not have immediate application in
your physical reality. So the
opportunities that come in your
life are indicative of the levels of
your imagination that are immediately
manifestable and the levels of
imagination that are immediately
manifestable will always attract
opportunities through which you can
manifest them if what you are imagining
represents what excites you the most.
Understand? Yes. Does that assist you?
Yes. So you can look to the action
reaction feedback mechanism of your
physical reality itself to show you what
is most immediately applicable. Now
sometimes you may get a sense that
something that right now seems like
fantasy in the extreme somehow feels
very much more real. And what you may be
getting is that somewhere down the road
as you say the circumstances you are
attracting to yourself now may make it
more conducive for what is now a fantasy
to be manifestable some point later on
in your life.
Understand? Yes. But you don't have to
worry about it. Nor do you have to
really in that sense focus on it until
an opportunity actually presents itself
to you that you can physically act upon.
So know it is there if it feels real to
you. Use it as a strong guiding point,
but act upon the things that are
immediately in your reality because only
doing that is what's going to get you
there anyway. Yes. Does that help? Very
clear. Thank you. Thank you very much,
Shannon. Hello Bashar Strawberry.
Good day to you. Good day to you. And we
see the sun shining brightly on your
strawberry patch. Yes. Yes, it is doing
well, isn't it? Yes. All the little
seeds have sprouted very nicely. Yeah.
It is very green and beginning to be
very lush and sweet. I love it. Yeah,
it's been very delightful. things have
been expanding in many areas. Yes. And
thank you for watering the park. Oh,
it's a pleasure.
Chap. I know that traditionally
um you are of the mind or of the spirit
by which you say that most of what we
receive from you is a reflection of
ourselves and that you're constantly
validating our own self-empowerment and
creativity and that is delightful and
appreciated. Well, thank you.
However, at this time, I would like to
extend to
you what a delight it is to have you as
a friend. Oh, we thank you. And to
extend to you
um a real heartfelt thanks for sharing
with us all that you have shared and for
taking on the role that you personally
have chosen to take on. I thank you and
remind you that I have only done it out
of joy. I know. and it's been our joy
too. So, but I wanted to thank you as a
personal friend. Well, I love you too.
Okay. And now um since I am very rapidly
transcending out of uh what has been
traditionally called by you the third
density. And just for a little
nostalgia's sake, I thought maybe we
would take a look back at the solidity
of that old density
and and uh you know look from a more
exterior viewpoint at some of the uh
ways in which our culture traditionally
uh chooses to create upsets and
difficulties in their lives. Trip down
memory lane. trip down memory as it
were. Right. As as it were. Yes. As it
were. Right. And I noticed that possibly
one could sum up what individuals would
call upsetting incidents or incidents
that they choose to to judge as
upsetting guys in maybe one of three
following categories. one one
consciously uh reaches for something
that they do not get or they reach to
have something and uh get something else
or they seem to have to have something
that they don't want. And these three
areas manifest uh large and small in all
of our consciousness. Such as we have a
conscious uh idea that we would like to have
uh idea that we would like to have
ourselves move down the freeway at uh
rapid speeds and find ourselves
presented with an abundance of uh
nonmovement. Yes. And out of that you know of course
Yes. And out of that you know of course
we have the choice to uh assign various
meanings and enjoy the abundance of it
all. Yes. And then we have the choice to
be really peeved at what's going on.
Yes. Which is the more traditional
choice of course in third in third
density on yours planet. Yeah. And our
planet being nostalgic about it about it
all. Yes. Those were those were
fascinating days.
Long time ago. Long time ago. Yes.
Galaxy far away. Far far away.
Yeah. Yeah. Don't do you you know the part I
Yeah. Don't do you you know the part I
liked you know do you remember how how
you used to suggest to us that what we
would do is to find ourselves in this
situation and add new meaning to it. Oh
yes. Wasn't that interesting approach
still is rather Yeah. Yeah.
And uh but I like the concept of going
back to the essence of changing the
momentum that brought us into those
circumstances in the first place. Oh,
isn't that you know that was But do you
not see that that is one and the same
thing as giving it new meaning. For when
you give it new meaning, it changes.
Uh yes. Yes, I do see that. All right.
Yes. Just checking. Oh.
[Music] So anyway, I thought that was a nice
So anyway, I thought that was a nice
little excursion down memor memory lane
and it was very fascinating that the
planet and the culture went through
those things. Oh yes. And quite a
museum. Quite fascinating.
And I'm sure it's added to many
fascinating and fun stories that you got
to exchange with other civilizations on. All right.
All right.
No lack of tales here. No. No.
Yeah.
Yeah. Has the association created a
mastery of limitation library of some
sort? Yeah. Hall of Fame. Hall of Fame.
I thought
so. We did it really well, didn't we?
Yes. You did spectacular. Yes. Thank you.
You did spectacular. Yes. Thank you.
Well, I just stellar performances. Oh,
wonderful. Wonderful. Well, that that
pretty much concludes this excursion and
uh as you see now, I simply share things
with you. There aren't really any
questions to ask since we now all know
the answers to all of these sorts of
things that or at least know you have
the ability to discover them, right? And
uh so I hope you enjoy the the few
remnants of our old density as they pass
through your consciousness. And I shall
savor every little bit.
Great. We thank you. Thank you my
friend. Good night
Shming. Good day Bashar. And good night
to you, Bashar. Last week in a city
called Golf Springs, Florida, there was
a sighting that was seen by a lot of
people. Uh bell-shaped
craft. Yeah. More bells. And it was on
the news one time from what I understand
and then never to be seen again. Could
you comment on that uh sighting last
week at all? Did you have a good time
hearing about it? Yes, I did. And what
did it awaken within you?
More interaction. More interaction. All
right. Again, everything is
representative of timing that is
apppropo for forming
identifications to shall we say check
the level of your consciousness.
You understand? Yes. Just checking the
dials, seeing how much receptivity there
is and then measuring the amount of
static that remains.
going away and coming back later for
another check, seeing if things are more
receptive. That is generally the purpose
of these excursions that are brief. Just
checking in, huh? Just checking. Okay.
Seeing how much more receptivity there
is as opposed to static.
Thank you. Also, could you talk about um
the idea of sandanda a bit, please?
or simply that there are many
expressions of the overall collective
consciousness of your planet expressing
itself in many of the different cultures
that you have created yourself to be.
And you will find that for each and
every belief system in each and every
culture the combined collective
consciousness of your world will have
found a way to express itself to
represent itself to symbolize itself
archetypally to that particular culture.
So that each will
know that each facet contains one of the
aspects, one of the sparks of light of
the total whole. That was simply one of
the ways is one of the ways will be one
of the ways for the collective
consciousness of your entire society to
have expressed
itself. Understand? Yes and no. Yes and
no. Right. In what way do you know?
Well, for a long time my understanding
of son was that son was the new name for
the Christ and then recently well knew
in the last 40 years or so 50 as my
understanding. Okay, just my
understanding. All right. And then um
recently I've heard that the idea of
sandanda is more of a group
consciousness or um rather than an
individual rather than like the Christ.
But what did I
say? It was representative of collective
consciousness in any particular cultural
format. And it is also an aspect of the
combined consciousness of your entire
planet which is the Christ consciousness
or sand or Buddha nature or great
spirit or many different ideas that you
may call it.
I got it. Thank you. Thank you
Shannon. Hi Pasha. And to you good day. Thank
Hi Pasha. And to you good day. Thank
you. Um at this moment I'm feeling
wonderfully ecstatically joyous and full
of bliss. Oh well, thank you very much.
And um actually this vibration seemed to
happen since I've been in this room this
evening. Well, thank you for creating
it. Well, um you know, I'm sure it's a
intermingling of all of our vibrations.
Oh, yes, that too. But the only way you
can experience it is by creating it for
yourself in your own reality. by taking
your cue from others that may be
radiating that frequency and matching it
in your own reality. You don't have to
accept that Q. You don't have to feel
it. Just because we are radiating it and
all together are manifesting the idea of
that vibration doesn't mean you have to
meet it. Mhm. But you have. So, thank
you. Yeah, I have because I prefer to be
this way. Oh, yes. Me, too. It wasn't
how right. It's it's the only way to be.
Um, well, no, but the way I prefer to
be. Okay.
as far as I'm concerned. Oh, all right.
Um, this wasn't how I planned to start
the conversation. Um, Oh, good. But I
changed my mind. Um, thank you. Just
recently, in fact, most of my life, I've
chosen to live on the edge. Yes. And
many of you, very creative spot to be. I
know. And it's God, it's real tough, but
boy, do you learn your lessons fast.
Yes. And um but it doesn't have to be
tough in the negative sense. I know.
Well, this was the last time I decided
this was the last time that I will ever
go through Trial by Fire again. Oh,
thank you very much. However, Oh, yes. I
changed Okay. I changed my mind again. All
Okay. I changed my mind again. All
right. I changed my mind when I just
before I first interacted with you. Yes.
However, the physical
manifestation kept on spinning in the
negative. It's like it didn't change
with my mental. It just got worse and
worse and worse. Do I have a particular
definition for this physiological
manifestation? Yeah, monetarily um
monetarily. Yeah. monetarily and and
physical material manifestations. Yes.
Um which were created from
allowing myself to be taken advantage
of. I'm I happen to be a a very
vulnerable, emotionally sensitive
person, which I looked on as negative
because I allowed other people to make
me believe that was negative and I now
choose to see it as a positive. Oh,
thank you. However, yes,
what is happening right now is that the
physical situation got to where last
week I had to give up my apartment and
have people taking me to court, small
claims courting, exciting and detectives
looking for me and
um um I'm living I don't have a home
anymore. I'm living like a gypsy. I have
my clothes in my in my car. I've been in
fact, you know, I decided this month to
diligently look for like a regular job
in order to a job I didn't prefer in
order to get myself out of this
situation as fast as I could. Did you
change your mind about that? Yes, as of
today. Because nobody would give me a
regular job. They won't. That's because
you're not a regular person. I know. And
you don't want to be. I know. I know.
And um it's like what job would you
like? Okay. I know exactly what I want.
Oh, do share. Do share.
I want to work as a regular in soap
operas. Oh, I've already worked in soap
operas. I've already worked in um you
know just a good general
um cross-section of everything to do
with the entertainment
movie everything you know just about
except for you know there's one category
I haven't but that's okay I'm not going
to name that
so you want to act yeah and I want to do
it in soap opers it I that would be the
most exciting way you could imagine to
express yourself okay yes I I have a lot
of emotion I tend to be really
excessively negative and positive and
it's like I've been experienced all this
anger towards these people that have
taken advantage of me, you know, and
it's like I get up every morning and I'm
living with this woman that, you know,
she was one of the people that helped to
take thousands and thousands of dollars
from me with my permission this year.
And it's like I'm being forced to live
with her right now. And it's like I'm
having to control my anger because is
she with you in your automobile?
Thought you said you were living in your
car.
I'm living I'm living in my car pretty
much. That's my meditation centering
space. But I have I use her place as a
crash pad. Crash? Yeah. [Music]
[Music]
Because would you prefer to make a soft
landing? Well, um, now I now I would. All right.
Well, um, now I now I would. All right.
May I ask you a question? Sure. Thank
you very much. Have you acted upon all
the opportunities that exist for you to
be able to express yourself in the way
you say you wish to? Have you talked
with the individuals who may be
connected to that idea? Well, something
happened this week. Oh, all right. That
really inspired me. Oh, I was looking
for to get a regular job as a
receptionist in a law office cuz that
pays the I've experienced in that and
that I could make the most money
quickly, you know, so I could get my own
apartment. Then I was going to go into
the acting. But what happened was I
ended up co coincidentally
up co coincidentally
getting a job with Triad artist as a
receptionist. Oh, Triad. Oh,
how much we love Triad.
Yeah. And um I was sitting there
answering the phones and going crazy and
trying to be normal. And why? Because I
needed to make some money quick. I had
Oh, you're saying the only way to have
abundance is to be normal. Well, I was
experimenting. Oh, thank you.
Okay. Because no, you know, cuz I
nothing was working. I didn't want to
lose my apartment. I I didn't want them
to take my car away, you know. I I don't
want to live under a tree. That's too
much. What a nice place to live. I know.
But the tree thinks so. Okay. It would
be cold, you know, and that's a bit too
much. Okay. And um anyway what happened
was that all these people to do with
that all these people to do with
entertainment started coming in like
actors and actresses and some of them
were you know their egos were like
really obnoxious some of them some were
really nice and it was like I looked at
this and I thought well god I have a
choice I would rather be doing that than
doing this you know. Yes. And and and so
did you start acting in the way you wish
to act to be one of those people? Seeing
in both of them both polarities the
opportunity to decide what about being
one of those people you prefer to be and
what you don't prefer to be. Well, it
wasn't until today that I made up my
mind. Oh, all right. And it's cleared up
your definition.
The the only thing that I'm creating as
a dilemma is because I really don't like
my living situation. I'm living
sometimes at my boyfriend's which that
that's fine but I don't like living with
this woman because I have all this
anger. Then where am I going to live? I
can't live with my boyfriend all the
time. Why do you not in that sense trust
that there is a place for you? Because I
don't know where it is. I mean, you
know, my brother, as soon as you start
acting like the person you want to be,
you will understand. As soon as you start
will understand. As soon as you start
acting like the person you say you want
to be, you will attract the things that
belong to that person.
Okay. Is this making sense? Yeah, it is.
Except Except you don't trust that much.
I do trust, but I don't know. Well, what
do you mean? Should I get up tomorrow
and just go to the casting people and
and give them a my picture and resume a
job tomorrow? Why not? Um, you know, and
I'll have enough money to get an
apartment tomorrow. Maybe you might, if
you need that, if you really need that,
if that is really the path of least
resistance that will help support the
person you say you want to be. And if
you are that person, then that's what
will happen. Whatever will be the path
of least resistance to support you will
be what happens as soon as you start
being the person you say you want to be.
automatically, instantly. What's the
word you have? Miraculously,
which is not a miracle at all. Miracles
are not out of the ordinary. In fact,
miracles are the normal state of things
when you allow them to be so. Mhm. Why
can't it happen that quickly? Is there
some law of the universe that says it
can't happen that way? No. No. You'll
have to create the expectation that it
must happen that way. And so, if you
don't see it happen exactly that way,
you'll think you have failed. But be the
person you really want to be and act
like the person you really want to be.
And then whatever is the path of least
resistance that will be the most
abundantly supported of you will come
into your life. The opportunity will be
there. You'll recognize it. You'll act
on it. Act upon the thing that excites
you the most when it comes in out of all
the opportunities that you will be able
to do. It will be represented whether it
seems connected or not of the thing that
will support you the best. Okay. So the
fact that I have interviews for regular
jobs with law offices again tomorrow and
I will that excite you. No, not at all.
I believe you. Okay.
Then it is our suggestion not that we
will ever tell you what to do. But if it
really doesn't excite you, it's our
suggestion that if you in that sense
involve yourself in those interactions,
you will be choosing to make the things
you really want take longer. Okay?
Because you will be spending your energy
in the direction that you don't want to.
So just throw it away and and just trust
transform it. Okay? Do the things you
really prefer. Act like the person now
that you say you want to be if you were
the person you want to be. Would you be
doing things differently than what
you're doing now? Would you be acting
differently? Would you be approaching
people differently? Would there be
people you would approach that you're
not approaching now simply because you
don't think you're that person yet?
Approach them. Be the person you want to
be. Approach them. you know you're going
to be approaching them with integrity.
You don't have to worry about the idea
of not having integrity. If you know
you're doing it with integrity, approach
them. Don't be afraid to. You'll get the
response that will steer you where you
need to be steered. Mhm. Automatically.
Mhm. Flow into it. Flow into the person
you want to be. Be that person. You will
have the life style of that person. Mhm.
You cannot have the lifestyle of the
person you want to be if you're not
being that person in all the ways that
you can. How do I get rid of this anger?
The anger is that I have towards only
towards yourself. I know it's towards
myself too. Then understand what natural
anger is for. Natural anger in the first
stages is an alignment energy. You are
seeing something around you that you
know you're not. You automatically
experience the rush of energy alignment
that allows you to know quite clearly
what you actually are as compared to
what you are not. There is no reason to
judge or invalidate them. They have
shown you what you are not. Thank them.
Thank you for allowing me to see through
you what I do not prefer in my life.
Thank you for allowing me therefore to
have a clearer idea of what I do prefer.
I love you. I love you. Goodbye.
You understand? I feel I saying I hate
you. I hate you. Goodbye. Then you only
hate yourself and you slow yourself
down. I know. Okay. Do you really
believe that by them showing you what
they have shown you that they have
actually turned you more clearly onto
the path of who you are? Yes, I do. Why
would you hate them for that? Yeah, I
know. It is a service. It is a service.
And do not forget you attracted them.
Yeah, I know. Well,
then the saying I hate you. I hate you
is saying I don't work. I don't
function. I don't work. I don't believe
in myself. I don't trust myself. That's
when you start putting your anger and
projecting it outward as hate. Yeah.
Because all you're doing when you scream
at them is screaming to yourself, I
don't believe in me. Yeah. They are
giving you a very clear opportunity to
understand that that's the belief you
had. And now you can change it because they
And now you can change it because they
are showing you clearly what you do not
prefer so that you can now choose more
clearly what you do. All you have to do
is say thank you very much. See you
later. Okay. And get on with being the
person you really want to be. That will
bring you what you need instantly. Yeah.
All right. Okay. Thank you. Well, thank
you very much. What a soap opera that
was. And thank you very much for all your
And thank you very much for all your
interactions. I've been using all of
your tapes as self-hypnosis and playing
them over and over again in my car. And
look what's happened. It's great. We
thank you for allowing us to reflect to
you the full measure of love each and
every one of you is. And at this timing,
we reflect that to all of you to thank
each and every one of you for the
co-creation of this interaction which
has given us unbridled joy and unlimited
ecstasy. We thank you for allowing us to
feel you, to share with you, and to
dream beings as lovely as yourselves in
our reality. Remember,
remember who and what you
are and
be who you know yourselves to be. It is
up to
you. We thank you and bid you a fond and
loving good day and good night. [Applause]
Let it go. Thanks, girl.