All right, I'll say how are you all this
evening of your time as you create time
to exit.
Allow us to begin this evening of your
time with the
understanding that we are now in our
interactions with you expanding in many
ways but also at the same time. It is
now the perfect timing to begin a sort
of pulling back. A type of
unplugging title
unplugging. In this way, allow us to
remind each and every one of you that
the facets and phases that we are now
moving into in terms of our interaction
with you will be more and more
conducive to creating the type of
atmosphere in which you yourselves now
are being given by us the strongest
opportunity to realize that you have the
answers that you need and you have all
the tools that you need to create the
realities that you desire. higher. And
so in this way, you will now find from
this point forward that our
conversations with you on many different
levels will be to some degree a little
bit more, as you say,
casual. In this sense, we will not
necessarily guide and delineate every
single turn of phrase that you use. We
will in this timing allow you to
recognize the primary functions, of your
own speech, of your own attitudes, of
your own perspectives, of your own
points of view. To allow you to begin to
truly listen to yourselves in this way
to now reflect to you our belief in your
self empowerment. It is because of this
empowerment. It is because of this
timing also that we are going to be
sharing and interacting with you in what
you call the workshops coming up to
bequeath in this way and to share the
idea of a kit of tools of simple primary
tools that will allow you to know that
at any place and any time you have all
the tools necessary. Should you feel out
of balance, should you feel any
negativity to realign yourselves
instantly, easily, effortlessly, for
this is what life is all about, allowing
it to be an effortless unfoldment of
creation. Therefore forward our dialogues with you
Therefore forward our dialogues with you
will take a lighter tone, more of an
equal tone, more of a conversational
tone in that sense, so that we can truly
begin to reflect to you the equality we
feel you exist in with us. Not so much
will we put forth the idea or energy
that you require our existence or
interaction for you do not need us in
that sense. We simply will continue to remind
sense. We simply will continue to remind
you on every level that you are the
creators of your reality.
But now, bit by bit, day by day, we will
function more simply as the ambassador
of our world and allow you truly to
begin to function as the ambassadors of
your as day by day, bit by bit, we come
closer and closer to the opportunity for
your civilization to begin to interact
with all the other civilizations of the
association on equal terms. This day is
approaching. This timing is appropriate
and therefore now we'll begin a little
bit more of a weaning if you will to
allow you to know you are standing on
your own two feet with regard to these
interactions and that you do not need in
any way, shape or form to hold any
consciousness that is communicating
through any of you with undue awe or
elevate them above and beyond
yourselves. For all consciousness
expresses itself differently. There may
be consciousness that at this time may
express itself in more expanded way. But
in no way, shape or form does that ever
mean that they are any greater than you,
any better than you. We love you dearly.
And at this timing, we will now begin to
express the love that we have always
shared with you in terms of reflecting
to you that we know that you can create
the world you desire to create and we
will begin to treat you
accordingly. You all follow along.
Therefore, allow us to begin with a
little bit of a sharing of an
idea of once again allowing yourself to
live in the moment. We have discussed
with you several times the idea that
what you call your persona, your
personality is in it an artificial
construct of your
consciousness. And thus any new idea you
create yourself to be will literally
create a different persona, different
personality, a different aspect of the
overall multiple persona that you are
will come to the forefront and that will
be the person you will be being to
express a specific idea that your
consciousness may be desirous of playing
out at that time.
In this way, holographically speaking,
recognize that every time you change the
personality that you are, every time you
do that, you literally are in that
moment a different person.
And as a different
person, whatever idea or notion of
whatever kind of past was necessary to
have created the person you are in that
given moment. The person you have
changed into will actually be the past
you then have because you are creating
the past from the present as well as
creating the future from the present.
All things are created from the present.
Therefore, if you wish to look at it
this way by analogy, recognize that you
know there are many different types of
incidents, many different ways you could
have looked at the many incidents in
your past. On days you choose to be, let us
past. On days you choose to be, let us
say, sad, you might recall a certain
incident in a melancholy way. But on
another day you choose to be happy, you
might recall the same incident or
different aspects of the same incident
that will reflect your joy and ecstasy
on that particular
day. And so you can see just by even
that analogy that you have an
opportunity even through attitude to
determine what type of events, what
style, what meaning, what flavor, what
atmosphere of events have occurred in
your past depending upon who you choose
to be in the present. You as a happy
individual will basically act as if you
have had a happy past. You as a sad
have had a sad path and will focus on
all the
sadness. Now recognize it even goes a
step beyond this idea and this is one of
the things you are learning to
understand by living in the moment.
The persona, the personality that you
allow yourself to be at any given
moment literally, yes, literally creates the
literally, yes, literally creates the
type of real past that goes hand in hand
with being the type of past that would
have created that persona. You are being
in that present.
The other past, perhaps the past you
used to be as another individual, as
another persona, now has been relegated
more to the idea you call the potential
state and is not indicative now of your
linear time track. You have switched
stations. You are now listening to a
different program. And when you switch
that dial in the present, it realigns
the program up and down the entire time
track literally. So that when you are
functioning, when you decide, when you
choose to function as a happy individual
in the present, you will allow anything
that you may wish to call your past that
got you to that point to only contain
the scenarios and events that would be
conducive to the creation of the person
you are now choosing to be. We are
speaking literally.
So allow yourself to recognize their
follower. that there really is no longer
a reason, unless of course for your own
good reasons, you decide to hang on to
this idea. But there really is no reason
why you should now assume from this
point forward that anything that you
have perceived has happened in your
so-called past has to have any negative
control over anything you desire to be
in the present because the dial is with
you in the present. And when you choose
to switch that dial in the present, that
is what will determine the past. You
have had
it. The present is not a result of the
past. The past is a result of the
present. Allow yourself to begin to
awaken to the malleability, flexibility,
and commandment that you have in
creating the conscious decisions in your
life. Now that will make a difference
along the entire idea of a time
frame with this at this
time towards the idea of sharing. Allow
us to simply ask how now may we serve
you? Sharing.
Good evening, Bishar. And to you. It's
been a long time. I really appreciate
all you've done for me. We thank you for
every interaction you have been willing
to cocreate with us.
Uh my friend uh Steve and myself were
going to get back to work on our device
that you inspired.
It was not so much our inspiration. It
has existed in many ways upon your own
world from the inspiration of many
individuals of your own society. But we
understand to what you are referring
well for us specifically of course.
Uh we want to test it without the shell
and we're wondering one will that cause
us any harm? Not really. Okay. When we
approach the uh excuse me resonant
frequency of the revolutions that we
mentioned uh do we need to be how close
a tolerance do we need to have?
Very precise within 1%.
At least. So, our instruments need to be
pretty tight. Nice.
Um, there's a shape on the edge. We were
talking about having a seven degree edge
all the way around. Will that disperse
the charge properly? Yes. Okay. What
else?
We're using insulated copper wire this
also. Very good. Yeah, the poles. It's
okay. Do they have to be 58 diameter
poles? 78. We're using 78. We have the
20 coils going around and we're using
7/8 steel uh actually iron wrapped with
coil copper coils. The more windings you
have, the more effective it will be.
Okay. The diameter of the hole doesn't
make that much difference.
Below a certain point, above a certain
point, not really. You are within the
tolerance range for the size of the
device you are creating. Because I got a
good idea,
but you may find that many, many more
windings may be necessary.
Why? What? Why are we limited?
The idea of the effect, part of it is
created by the amount of conductive
mass. Can we um Now, you suggested using a
Can we um Now, you suggested using a
quarter inch disc. Why can't we use a/2
inch disc or a 1 in disc? Would that
increase the effect?
To some degree, but you do not have to
increase it that way. We are also
specifically speaking of the windings
themselves. Okay? like increasing them
by a factor of two or three over what we
talked about before. At least three, if
not five, if not 10. Then we need to
make a a a larger disc and space them
out and make a much larger device
perhaps. Yeah, that's down the line. We
can still achieve the effect. Yeah, I do
too. To some degree to some degree. But
again, many of the
parameters may still need much
experimentation. And again, there is
information that you can incorporate
that does exist that you will be made
aware of. Of course, as you know, we're
waiting for it. Okay. Okay. Thank you.
Thank you very much, Bashar. Enjoy it.
We will. I have
a Would you mind? A lot of people are
wondering what you're talking about.
Just could you briefly, very briefly
give a description of what it is? Well,
six months, eight months ago, Bashar had
Okay. Six or eight months ago, Bashar
had suggested to us how we might
uh say do experiments that would
simulate the anti-gravity effects of
flying saucers. And so he gave us some
very basic uh methods of experimentation
including a rotating copper disc inside
of a series of uh copper coils. All
right, producing a ever burgeoning
magnetic effect. uh more or less
duplicating the work of a guy named John
Surl in England who's now deceased who a
foundation in England has taken over his
work now and are soon to make public
their results and whatnot. We're trying
to do what we can here uh in the
meantime. We've had one effort not
successful but we're ready to give it
another shot. So
good. [Applause] [Applause]
So
hello Bashar. Hello. Um, the other
device, I don't know what to call it.
The crystal sphere with the uh pole, the
1/8 inch pole with the uh Fibonacci grid
going around it. Oh, the the generator.
It's called a generator. Pardon me.
Okay. The the Fibonacci the um center
pole is approximately 8 inch diameter.
And then um at perpendicular every 90°
you have the other uh the other four
holes with the wire coming out. Yes. Now
are there two wires coming out of each?
Yes. Hole. Yes. One on top of the other
or
two wires from each spiral. Not
necessarily from each hole. Two holes
for one spiral. two holes for the
opposite spiral. Uhhuh. Okay. Just
double Fibonacci. Okay.
No, there's been a misunderstanding here
between the way we're interpreting it.
So, there's there's four holes, one wire
coming out of each hole. One Fibonacci
grid going clockwise, one Fibonacci grid
going counterclockwise. Yes. And two
wires from each going through the holes
to the central spire.
Two wires from
each. Okay. Well, two two wires going
counterclockwise.
No, there aren't two wires coming out of
each hole.
There's the holes that are going um 90°.
Yes. Perpendicular. Every 90° there's
one hole. It's approximately 32nd in
diameter. And you put a 30 second one
132 wire in there. Yes. And then you go
counterclockwise with the Fibonacci
spiral. And then you go 90° to another
one. No matter which way you go, it will
be the opposite Fibonacci. Correct.
Sprint. And then the one that's 180 from
the first one where we started would be
uh the same the same as the one before,
right? Yes.
Okay. Does that assist you? Oh, thank
you. Thank you, Sherry.
Good evening, Bashar. M. I was at
breakfast this morning with two men and
in the middle of it. Yeah. I was at uh
with the microphone for the audience as
well. The microphone. I was at breakfast
this morning with two men and in the
middle of it began to shake. One of them
was former editor of National News
Magazine. The other is a very creative
money man out of Texas. Um one of whom I
already knew. Could you talk to me about
your feeling, your perception of that
shaking and what was going on? Not
visibly, but inside me very strongly.
To some degree, you have had connections
in dream realities with these
individuals before, conversations,
dialogues, arrangements,
agreements. Some of what you were
perceiving was your inner awareness of
connections that were forming, things,
paths being pushed into momentum, being
set up, being initiated, being
accelerated. in a sense a feeling of doorways
in a sense a feeling of doorways
opening.
You follow me? Absolutely. Now, some of
this may still within you to some degree
lightly be being interpreted in old ways
of anxiety, but it is also the same idea
as we have said as the energy of
excitement. It is like having switched on a certain
It is like having switched on a certain
sensitivity to the vibration that now
you can use as a scanner to decide and
determine at any given moment what
opportunities that are presented to you
do carry the most excitement for you and
to simply trust the ones that do carry
the most excitement and to realize that
those that don't are not necessarily
going to be indicative of the most
effortless path. You follow me? Mhm.
Does that assist you? That does the the
shaking felt like two things or both
among many. One that it could be a kind
of breakthrough as you're suggesting
suggesting anticipation, recognition and
desire. But also it felt that I could
shake myself out of myself. That could
be a breakthrough it feels like to me in
the way you're suggesting. Or it could
be a desire so strong to be outside of
myself as not to
be as not to be totally centered. It is
all right. We understand that it can be
both in that way. And you may be now
feeling the expansiveness of yourself
which for a while may seem to be outside
of yourself simply because you're not
used to thinking of yourself as capable
of containing that. But you will grow to
fit it. Well, I I know that they were
drawn there because of my own business
vision. Uh so that it was mutual and
they knew that too. Can you talk a
little bit about one of them Jack Crosby
my connection to him? Is he in fact a
valued financial advisor is the
connection other than
that has functioned that way for some
individuals possible that can function
that way for you. There are other
connections that you may discover along
the way as well.
Some of which may surprise you.
One I think I already know. One is a
personal connection I believe. All
right. Uh but in terms of a business
relationship with him, let it form
naturally not push it. Let him come. In
fact, he came to me this time. Simply
act upon whatever opportunities present
themselves to you without pushing. And
whatever opportunities you are capable
of acting upon that represent the
opportunities that carry the highest
degree of excitement for you. Mhm. That
will always be your guide. Excitement is
always your infallible guide. What
excites you is indicative of the path
you are. Otherwise, it wouldn't excite
you. Understood. Understood. And one
last part of that, there is since Jack
is from Texas and and that karma is not
finished. Is there a larger karma of
mine involved in Texas? It excites me.
So that's to some degree. Yes. But not
so much the idea of karma as anything
negative or
retributionoriented but simply the
continuation of some momentum. You have
to some degree still I'll say roots
there. Mhm. That can be activated on or
just appreciated in general. Our
perception is that you will take care of
business on that level while you are
taking care of business on another
level. It will be automatically cleaned
up as you say. Mhm. And is Jack feeling
whole and healthy towards me at this
point? Basically, although there are some
Basically, although there are some
uncertainties within that individual, as
an activation of a doorway within any
individual within a gathering activates
doorways within all. Understood. There
may be some settling that needs to take
place. Mhm. But that's up to him. As for
himself as Thank you very much. Thank
you. Happy trails.
Sure. Hello. Hello. Um, I've been
experiencing a rebirth, a
transformation, uh, what I would call a synthesis of the
uh, what I would call a synthesis of the
masculine and feminine within me. Oh,
how exciting. It is appropriately the
timing for it since this is the
transformational aid. Well, it's it's on
me. Yes, it's in you. Yes. Yes, it's in
me. Um, and I'm feeling very much the
emergence emergence of my feminine
nature. And I want to know what insights
you may be able to give me in how to
stay clearly on this path. How to
quicken the growth perhaps and
specifically how those insights might
relate to two areas which I have in the
past felt a block and I now want to move
through. One being G getting work
consistently as an actress and the other
a body transformation having to do with
shedding 60 pounds that has become
obsolete. All right. The answer to each
and every one of those phases is the
same answer. Do what excites you the
most. When you do what excites you, then
you do not wait around to
do. You follow me. Mass is energy.
Energy is mass and when you are not
using the energy of your excitement,
when you are not doing with that energy,
it stays and converts into mass because
you are waiting to do instead of doing.
When you do, you will lose waiting.
You follow me? Yes, I do.
It is the ability to trust that what
does excite you the most in life is what
will work most effortlessly for you and
will attract you into whatever
circumstances and situations are
necessary for you to be supported in
that endeavor that excites you the most.
Excitement is really the only sign that
you need and it is the sign and signal
that will bring you everything you truly
desire. Excitement is your physical translation
Excitement is your physical translation
of the vibratory energy that represents
the path you chose to be. Excitement is
the sign that comes with the situation
that lets you know that this is the most
effortless situation you could possibly
undertake at any given moment. At any
given moment, whether you think
outwardly in outward appearance, whether
you think a situation seems to be
something that is connected to you, if
it is exciting to you, it is a part of
your path. Because only the things that
excite you the most are indicative of
the path you chose to be. Even though
outwardly in appearance, it may not seem
to be connected with what you think you
want to do. M if there is something in
life that excites you very strongly but
you do in all honesty not see a way that
you are capable of creating that right
now then all you need to do to become
capable of creating it is to act upon
whatever you are capable of acting on
that does come with excitement.
Any opportunity that presents itself to
you that is the most exciting thing out
of all the opportunities you are capable
of acting on will always lead you into
whatever opportunities you are excited
about that at that moment you may not
have been capable of acting upon. Even
though it may not seem connected, it is
the excitement that lets you know it is
connected because excitement is a thread
that leads to all other excitement.
So when a situation comes along and it
is exciting to you, the most exciting
one out of all the things you could be
doing at that moment, do it because it
will lead you in
unexpected coincidental synchronistic ways into the
coincidental synchronistic ways into the
other thing you want to be doing. You
see, when you activate a desire, you
radiate messages all around you. those
messengers from you go out and they pull
in automatically the things that will
get you to where you want to go most
quickly. Now, the only reason that many
of you allow it to take so long is
because when the messenger brings you a
methodology that will be the path of
least resistance and the quickest way to
get there, you refuse to believe it has
anything to do with the thing you think
you want to do. because logically and
analytically you don't see the
connection. But that's not the point.
Knowing that there is a connection is in
here. The excitement is what lets you
know. The feeling is what lets you know
there is a connection.
You follow me? Yes. Does that assist
you? Yes, it does. Thank you. Thank you
very much,
Shelly. Hello. Hello. That was a very good
Hello. Hello. That was a very good
dissertation earlier. It almost answered
my question. My
my almost which is real interesting. The
things I've been thinking about lately,
you've been talking quite a bit about um
all is becoming synchronicity and there
is no accident that any individual that
is attracted to the vibration of our
being and that we are attracted to your
vibration again is not an accident. To
some degree, this is already an
indication that we at least on some
levels think alike.
That's very interesting.
Um, well, thank
you. Um, I have a question. I have, um,
I've done a lot of meditation into my
past. All right. And have gone back
many, many, many, many, many years. Many
many many, many, many, many, many years.
Right. Uh there's one area though that that
Uh there's one area though that that
kind of bothers me. I'm kind of hung up
on it. Oh, between uh 1754
and 17 uh 79.
Pretty precise. I'm trying to be as
precise as possible. All right. I was
involved somewhat with the Revolutionary
War and there was uh there was two
forces at work here, both one positive,
one negative. I don't know if you've
ever discussed this on any tapes before,
but I haven't heard it. And I was
wondering if you could fill me in. I've
got very sparse. There's some uh big
blockage there on u on on my track. I
can't quite pull some of that up. And
most most of my track is real easy to
pull up. I see. Why do you imagine there
might be what you call a block in that
particular area? Because uh I have a
feeling I was on the negative side and
I'm not willing to face some of the
possibilities. Oh. All right. May I ask
you a question? Right. Well, thank you.
At this time, what would be so negative
about having been on the negative side?
Nothing. All
right. Do realize, of course, that even
what many of you in your society call
the positive side still use negative
methodologies. Very true. All right.
Very true. All right.
Do you feel in this way that perhaps you
might think less of yourself if you
believed that you might have betrayed
someone close to you? You're very
clever. Um, that's an unfair question.
You did not mean it to me. No, I'm not.
I I I merely I don't feel bad about any
of the instances at all. I'm just trying
to clarify some of the if you could push
me in certain directions. We are nudging
gently. I noticed.
Now understand, however, of course, that
primarily from our point of view, you
have all you need to know in the present
to live the present life you are living
without having to delve into the idea of
the past. Not that we are invalidating
it. Right. Right. Many times we are
reluctant to push people through the
idea of past recognition because many
ways, many times in your society, many
of you have created a habit of becoming
stuck on those past lives rather than
simply knowing that you are at your own
command in the present regardless of
anything you truly have ever done. right
now. Do you like to eat? Absolutely. How
much? Lots. Lot. All
right. Mhm.
If you thought If you
thought that you would have to curtail
anything that to you might represent the
symbol of your
abundance, do you think you would react
to that?
Curtail abundance. If you thought that
something might happen that you believed
would affect your ability to be as
abundant as you want to be, how do you
think you would react to that? I would
probably be very angry. Why? Because I
enjoy abundance. I enjoy freedom. I see.
Freedom create so forth. Oh, freedom.
All right. Right.
Do you know that you do create your own
reality? Absolutely. All right. Then now
you know that there is no way that
anything could actually curtail your
abundance if you do not decide to create
the illusion that your abundance is
being curtailed. Yes.
Yes. All right. You did not know that
then. That's true. And in this way, our
perception for now, at
least the information that we perceive
will be of best benefit to you for now.
Mhm. delivered in this way is to perhaps
simply recognize that there was at least
in your mind then a
threat from seemingly
outside from someone you knew that if
they were to maintain their
integrity perhaps you felt would have
jeopardized your position of comfort.
Yeah. and in this way perhaps reacted
out of
integrity to allow them in your terms to
come to harm so that you would safeguard
what you felt to be your comfort. Mhm. A
betrayal of sorts in that sense.
Now, we also perceive that you have
worked through many ideas with this
individual in many different lifetimes
since then as well. Can I ask a question
here? Maybe.
Uh, was this individual Ben
Franklin or was it the other guy? This
connected to Ben Franklin.
I don't know his name. All right. All
right. Let us simply for now say that you are
Let us simply for now say that you are
connected to the
consciousness that you colloially refer
to in your society as
Franklin. Not that you are now dealing
specifically with one particular
embodiment for that embodiment so to
speak. Well, there was more than one
embodiment of the same energy, right?
And in a sense there still is even more
so now than there
was. Let us say there were political
ramifications that came back to you that
allowed you to feel as if you were in
control but in control through lack of
integrity, right? Rather than in true
control, right? Which was kind of
painful. Yes. Um, that leads to the
second question about abundance. Yes.
Which I've been thinking quite a bit
about lately, but it deals with music
and creativity in general. I feel like
there's a definite lack of abundance in
that area. Every time I approach I have
several instruments and used to write uh
prolifically or wrote a lot, not that
prolifically, I guess, but um but now
it's very hard for me to uh there's a
barrier there that I can't seem to push
through. It's hard for me. It feels like
I'm starting something that's going to
be painful. Oh, all right. All
right. Many of the things in life that
you consider barriers, of course, are
not truly barriers, but simply signs
pointing in an unexpected direction or
perhaps a direction you are reluctant to
move in. And that's the only thing that
makes it seem as if it is a barrier. The
sign is very clear and the path is truly
very clear. Any foggess, any cloudiness,
any resistance is simply the lack of
willingness to believe that you will be
all right. Be all right. You will for you
right. Be all right. You will for you
are in control of your
life. Let me remind you now, and let me
remind you on many different
levels. There is really nothing at this
point you could ever possibly discover
about yourself that you would not now be
willing to add to yourself in a positive
way. So there really is nothing to fear
about what you will find out about
yourself in going forth on these paths
that are truly very clearly marked but
which you may be reluctant to walk upon
because of the ingrained belief that you
might find something that would allow
you to devalue yourself. as you devalued
yourself back
then that really cannot happen anymore.
So, uh I still haven't learned the
lesson from the 1700s. Well, yes, in a
way you have. And this is what we are
saying is that if you are willing to
simply walk as if you are free, the
things you will discover will allow you
to know you really have worked most of
it out. I see.
Now, a suggestion perhaps that you may
be able to pick up on and allow. Now,
some great release and emotionality may
come with it. But let us remind you that
you deserve to do this. No one will
begrudge you the freedom and the release
you may experience from this exercise.
All right? No one except you perhaps,
but you're going to not have to do this.
Okay? Pick up what you call a
f. Do follow me. Absolutely. All right.
And play upon
it anything that represents the feeling
of freedom to
you. Grant yourself the permission to
rejoin the
ranks of those that knew they were
building an idea of freedom, peace, and
harmony. They will let you back in. All
All
right. I will sign your own Declaration
of Independence.
All right. All right.
Thank you very much. And pleasant dream
communications this night of your time.
Okay. Thank you. for a door has opened
and you will be once again able to
communicate in your assembly hall.
Good. Thank you. Thank you. Hi Bart. Hi Bart.
Hi.
A couple questions or a couple areas I'd
like to have you give me some insight.
All right. we will reflect your
knowledge back to you. Thank
you. It
helps. Um the definition of abundance is
being able to do the definition of
abundance is being able to do what you
need to do when you need to do it.
Thanks. Okay, that is one definition.
Oh, more. Well, it is our definition.
Okay. It is the one representative of
our vibration. That's why we gave you
that one. Okay.
Now, are needs and wants the same? Not
necessarily. Okay. What is the
difference? They can be different in the
sense that your negative ego may think
that it needs something and then may
want it for its own reasons. But that is
not necessarily representative of what
you may as a being truly need to fulfill
the overall idea that you chose to
fulfill in being born into this life.
You can create the idea of
wants from the idea of buying into belief
from the idea of buying into belief
systems about what you think you need as
a
being. And it may be gratifying on
certain levels, but it may not truly
serve you in a positive
way. Sometimes your needs and wants can
coincide. When you add the ingredient of
trust, they usually will.
Without trust, then there is the
opportunity to experience a great
dichotomy between true need and what you
may think you want.
You follow me? Yes. Does that assist
you? Yes. Okay. U probably somewhat along the
Yes. Okay. U probably somewhat along the
same line. Um you talked about
expectancy and expectations. And as I
understand it and it seems and it works
for me is expectancy is a a broader
scope and it's dealing with trusting.
Yes. Expectancy is simply knowing that a
certain idea, a certain vibration is
true for you and representative of your
basic reality. An
expectation many times is a specific
structure that you assume the
manifestation must occur in or you will
invalidate it as the result of your
desire. Okay. Now in working with some of the
Okay. Now in working with some of the
Lazarus materials in consciously
creating what you want or need okay what
you desire desire um he seems to guide
you guide a person toward details or it
seems more like expectations and then I
guess well not really and Lazarus points
that out as well. The idea is not that
you cannot use specifics as your model
to put that into activation. It is
simply that there may be circumstances
that some of the levels of your
consciousness are not aware of that may
represent a path of resistance that is
even less resistant than the one you
have pictured. And so to simply insist
necessarily that the picture you have is
the way it must manifest when something
else that might occur to bring you what
you want may manifest more easily in
another way to insist that it must occur
the way you have pictured it might
actually be fighting your own best
interests. But the idea also behind the
exercises that Lazarus has put forth on
that tape is to be very very clearly
aware with very clear
honesty as to what your beliefs are and
why. This is most important. Why you
want what you say you want. When you are
truly clear about why you want what you
say you want, then you are operating on
a level where what you picture more
often than not will be precisely in
every detail what you
get. Because you will be being honest
about why you really want that. And you
will truly come to the determination
that if you do finally decide that this
is something you really do want, it will
be made with thorough honesty and
integrity and you will not be fooling
yourself in that way. You follow me?
Yes. Does that assist you? Yes. Along
the same line, Shati Guan in her
creative visualization again speaks I
guess as I'm trying to think about it
the same way Lazar says with the same
principles apply there. Oh yes, in many
ways all we are saying and as Lazarus
has said is that if you do the exercise
and you have a specific
visualization and it does not come to
pass exactly as the way you have
visualized it. The idea is to not spend
time chastising yourself and heaping
guilt upon yourself but to simply go
back to the tools and see if you have
actually used them in a clear way. Okay,
you follow me? Yes. Thank you. Does that
assist you? Yes, it does. Thank you very
much. Sure.
Hello, Bashar. Hello. Um, I have
Well, I don't know how to explain it,
but my grandparents both died very
suddenly. Oh, right. And I was wondering
um if my grandmother is trying to tell
me something cuz I've been seeing her a
lot. That is communication. Now, in a
sense, they are not trying. They are
telling you. Yeah. The idea is to
recognize that communication from those
levels always will permeate to you and
you will feel that love. All you need to
do is to simply relax, open up, send
your love in return, your unconditional
love and in whatever way, shape or form
you truly need to understand the
communication, you will understand it.
Many times that doesn't mean you will
have analytical understanding as if you
are listening to an actual verbal
conversation. Sometimes what they are
communicating will actually play itself
out in the circumstances that unfold in
your physical day-to-day life. You
follow me? Yes. Simply know that you are
in communication. Do not create the
struggle that you think they are trying
and that you are trying to receive it.
Allow yourself to know that the
communication is received and that your
communications are received. Allow
yourself to let those communications and
the results of those communications
manifest in your life. For now, the idea
generally speaking of anyone who
precedes you into the non-physical
reality that has loved you in that way,
they will function to some degree as a
guide for you. But do remember that they
are also learning many things themselves
and in this way cannot necessarily hang
around and have long involved
communications with you. They are very
busy. But they will send you their love
always. They will send you their love.
If you send them your love
unconditionally, that will open the path
for them to use that energy in whatever
way will assist them to accelerate most
quickly. And it will also open the path
for you to receive whatever information
coming from them. You need to simply let
it manifest in whatever way is
representative of the way you will get
the most benefit out of it. You do not
necessarily have to have an absolutely
conscious aware communication, dialogue,
conversation with them to know that
communication is there. You follow me?
Yes. Does that assist you? Yes. Pleasant
dream. Um I have another question
though. Um, I have this little girl that
I babysit and um, I feel very very close
to her and I wasn't sure if she was from
a past lifetime. Yes. And uh, it's and
it's really weird for me cuz I weird.
Yeah. Cuz I don't understand. Well, that is
Cuz I don't understand. Well, that is
all right. That is all right. The idea
is not even necessarily that you really
have to have an analytical understanding
of all of these metaphysical things.
The idea to primarily understand is to
trust your instinct with regard to how
it allows you to relate to the person.
And however it is you feel most
comfortable relating to the person, that
action, your willingness to simply carry
through that action and relate to them
how it feels you need to will allow your
lives to unfold in the way that you have
agreed to have them unfold. You will
learn everything you need to learn about
each other at the appropriate timing.
You have interacted many times and you
have interact whether you have an
analytical understanding of it or not.
Trust your feelings. Trust your
instincts. Use your integrity. And that
is really fundamentally all you will
ever need any of you to allow your life
to unfold in the way you have agreed
with all the individuals you interact
with to have it unfold. We follow. Yes.
Thank you very much. Thank you very
much. This
child may be
able in time to remind you
specifically of certain relationships
you have had and also to remind you
specifically of certain agreements that
you have made with yourself about this
life as well. But they may come in
symbolic ways, methods of actions that
the child will perform that may simply
spark something within you.
When that
occurs, you may also find yourself
thinking of the grandparents you have
discussed as well because they also to
some degree their energy plays a part in
the sparking of that awareness within
you. You are surrounded by loving
guides. You are a guide yourself for
them in many ways. Let your life unfold
as naturally as a flower.
You will be just
fine. Enjoy the relationships you have
attracted into your
life for you will learn much and you
will enjoy much.
And thank you. Yeah,
this is about sleeping. Sleeping. Yes.
Okay. Um I was finding that um I wasn't
sleeping during the night. So then
during the the days after that I would
be doing all my things during the day
and I'd feel tired and uncomfortable.
Yes. And then I thought, okay, well
that's fine. I'll just not sleep and
then eventually I'll be so tired I'll
sleep. However, I found that um I would
sleep during the day and not during the
night. Nice. And that is your natural
biological cycle. All of you do you know
that? Yes. Okay. I asked you this
before. So, so finally I got so tired I
said okay what I really want to do what
excites me the most is just sleeping so
I can feel refreshed. And so I just okay
let my let my body decide when it wanted to
my let my body decide when it wanted to
sleep which is during the day. Yes. And
so I feel that I want to create a cycle
of sleep during the night so that I can
so that I can participate in my
agreements with other people during the
day. Why? Because
why not create individuals in your life
that you make agreements with to
participate with at night?
Well, I don't know. I have I haven't
found a whole lot of businesses that are
open after 5:00 in the afternoon. What
about your own?
Right. Well, yes. Well, I don't know.
There's just a lot of different aspects
of society that would be hard to
recreate for myself after 5 p.m. If you
say so. Um, not if you find enough of
your cohorts who are all sitting awake
at night wondering what to
[Music] do. Also,
do. Also,
also don't forget your entire planet is
not asleep at the same time.
There are many people wide awake when
you are. Well, I understand. But if I
want to create sleeping during the
night, why can't I do that? I mean,
well, you can do it. But it may be in
direct opposition with the things you
truly want to do in life.
You see again the idea is that if you
are expanding in a natural way then
anything that goes along with that it is
actually more representative of a
natural cycle will start occurring to
allow you to be your more natural self
and being your more natural self is what
will allow you to do truly do the things
you really want to do in
life. So the cycle you are getting is
indicative of what will allow you to
begin to be your more natural self and
do the things that truly move you, truly
excite you. And again recognize that as
soon as you quote unquote give into your
natural cycle, you will not necessarily
need as much sleep during the day as you
may think. You follow me? Okay. So it seems
think. You follow me? Okay. So it seems
like to accept that is natural is okay.
What about creating a cycle when I
choose to sleep creating that reality
for myself so that if I want to sleep
well you can do that but again the point
is is that if you are simply being
insistent that you want to sleep at a
certain time for reasons that have
nothing to do with other things that you
say you really want to do well the
majority of where your energy is will
win out if it is more important to you
and more desires to you to do certain
things and to do those things requires
that your sleep schedule change, then
you are going to be in a sense fighting
yourself to insist that your sleep
schedule doesn't change. And that is
what may tire you out
truly because you are fighting your
belief in your own natural ecstasy and
your own natural timing.
The natural cycle that your entire world
is moving into is more the natural
biological cycle of being asleep between
what you call 2 to 4 in the afternoon
and being awake between what you call 2
to 4 in the morning. That is your
natural biological
cycle. And when you know that more and
more individuals function that way, then
you won't be alone in the morning.
Do you not recognize that there are
individuals that have already begun in
your society to create many different
things that used to only take place
during the day that now also take place
during the night? Perhaps you have
simply not research the fact that there
are avenues of outlets at all hours in
many different ways.
All right. And also once again do
remember that generally speaking if you
will fall into step with your natural
cycle you may find that you will not
require any more than about three of
your hours during the afternoon anyway
for for total sleep. Yes. Maybe if you
wish, another hour later on in seemingly
the appropriate time frame. But the idea
is to not force yourself to be asleep
when your body says it is
awake. That is what will frustrate you
beyond anything.
I
agree. Okay. So the body consciousness
wins over my desire to create. No, no,
no, no, no.
your desire to create what you really
want. You see, you may not be allowing
yourself to be consciously aware of the
total idea you really truly desire. Your
body consciousness is actually going in
step with what you truly as a being
desire. The only thing that's putting up
a fuss is your negative ego.
Okay? Because I'm judging that natural
pattern. Okay? Yes. Recognize also, of
course, that the only reason you need
sleep is to form the connections between
your so-called physical consciousness
and your higher consciousness that you
usually do not allow yourselves to
exhibit in your typical waking state.
The more you do what is representative
of what you are all about, the more
connection you will have between your
physical consciousness and your higher
consciousness in your typical waking
state, the less sleep you will need
because that connection will always be
there. You will be literally living your
You will be literally living your
dreams. So you will not need to sleep to
physically inactivate yourself in order
to set up the dream patterns that you
will then live out in physical reality.
You'll be creating and living them at
the same time
spontaneously. The connection will not
have been broken. You will be asleep so
to speak dreaming so to speak in
conversation with your higher
consciousness and you will be living and
aware and awake at the same time.
Okay, that makes sense. So
relax in general. Relax. I have another
very quick question. Um this is
regarding the um the use of cocaine.
What? Sort of in general. And you
mentioned once before that that um the
acceleration that a lot of people are
feeling in generalating um there is a
correlation between the substance that
you refer to as cocaine in the sense
that yes when individuals in your
society feel the acceleration going on
but still believe that power is outside
of them in the symbols with which they
surround themselves. Then they will seek
to emulate and match the feeling within
themselves by relying on what they
believe to be the power of an outside
symbol. That is the root of all
dependency and addiction is not
understanding that the socalled
substance is not what is really creating
the effect. You are creating the effect
and in this way you can modulate it in
any which way you please.
That's it why that's sort of become a
big thing to some degree. Yes. But once
individuals know that the power to
create their reality is within them and
not in the symbols around them, then
they simply will no longer have a need
to remove their power from themselves
and place it in a substance in that way
that also contains as an idea many of
the ideas that they hold about
themselves negatively as well. Because
many individuals still have a belief
that that degree of acceleration is
something which they can't handle and
must burn them out.
And that's why they attract themselves
to a symbol that will give that effect.
They do not believe they can handle it.
They do not believe they're in control.
They do not believe they can contain
their own power. And so they represent
that negative belief about themselves by
choosing a representative substance that
will create the effect that reflects
their belief in their lack of power. You
follow me? Yes, I do. Thank you. Thank
you Shannon
for sure. Yay. First off, I'd really
like to thank you for the meditation
last Thursday night because it was
really most beautiful. Thank you for
your co-creator.
Uh question.
I've been reading the book The Keys of
Enoch Enoch. Enoch and asked for some
guidance and helping me to understand
more of the information. All right. and
went to bed that night and woke up the
next morning. Had a dream that there was
a lot of people lined up uh around
alongside a big buildings like a block
couple blocks long. All right. Can you
enlighten me what was going on there?
What that symbol was about? Well, in a
sense, it is out of perception that you
went to a particular level or plane in
your dream reality that represents
storehouse of knowledge. What you
generally call causal plane or aashic
records in that way. You are in a quasi
plane or reality of that type. Looking
upon those so-called edififices as
storehouses of knowledge, the pinnacles
of knowledge in that way. When you woke
up, you gave them a dream
interpretation, a physical reality
interpretation. You symbolized them as
the buildings you are familiar with in
that sense. Not that they literally
looked that way, nor were that way, but
the effect, what they represented to you
was clothed in a symbol that would
represent the idea of that storehouse of
knowledge. You follow me? Yes. So, you
went to the right place.
You can do that again anytime you wish.
All of you can. Thank you very much. Oh,
thank you. Do remember, however, that
that place is inside of you as well and
not truly any great distance away.
Thank you. Thank you.
Hello, Bashure. Strawberry.
Do you grow any strawberries on?
No. But we should plant some. All right.
Michelle, I ran across a friend the uh
other day who told of a story of a lady
who was in a flying class in
transcendental meditation.
And I remember you mentioned a little
bit about that. I got all excited about
flying. I like flying. And could you
reflect for me a little bit of the um
technology or methods or knowhow by
which they pull that out?
pull wa flying flying around.
We have discussed the understanding that
it takes belief.
Mhm. Or if you don't believe that the
beliefs control it, then perhaps you
will not fly.
However, if it is truly something that
you'll really, really find
exciting, all you really need to do is
know that you have activated your
desire, put it out in the universe, and
that perhaps when you know it is safe to
be taken off
guard, then the universe will meet up on
you.
and lift you up, uplift
you. But the idea is that it in a sense
must find you uplifted on all the other
levels you possibly can be
first. You follow me? To some degree,
simply do what excites you. Put the
excitement out there for that specific
manifestation. And then when you are
going about your business being
uplifted, you will then allow the
universe to uplift you in all other ways
as well. Understood. You are still
sourcing the universe doing this, right?
Of course. Of course. Of course. Good.
One more
question. Great
laughers. One more question, Bishop. All
right. Uh, what excites you lately?
Everything. Everything. Everything I do.
interactions with you. Knowing that you
are beginning to all know you create
your own realities. This excites me a
lot. Knowing that we will be interacting
more and more with you in different
ways, seeing all the transformations
that take place within the universe, the
multiveres. This all excites me. And you
know what else excites me? What else?
the thought that one day I'm going to
hold you to your offer of planting
strawberries on my world.
You got it, baby. I will reserve a
little pack.
That's neat. I I'll be there. We'll do
it together. Thank you very much. Thank
you. Shout it.
Shout it.
Hi, how are you? Perfect. I'm you very
well, thank you. Fine, I'm um I'm
looking for an actress who's about 60
pounds overweight, and I was wondering
if you knew of anybody. Well, well, that
I could
uh use. Um I'm becoming artistic
director of the theater this weekend.
Yes. And I'm here to do two things. The
first is to make the announcement that
I'm in need
of services. Actors, technicians, anyone
who has a desire to get involved with
the theater whose focus will be to
assist everyone to expand within
themselves and help in the
transformation in some way. Very
exciting. Very exciting. Thank you for
availing yourself on that point of the
synchronicity of the individual's
presence. Thank you. And um boy, there's
so much going on. Girls, there is.
I'm not sleeping at all because I am so
excited I can't turn off. You are
dreaming. That is why you are not
sleeping. [Music]
[Music]
Um it's it's remarkable. I have um a
couple of questions. What? The first
is is my
vision with um Antonio and the vision I
see connected to Daryl.
Now you know we cannot spill the beans.
No no I don't want you to open my
surprise. All right.
But that is the right that feels to be
the right path. do it. If it feels
correct to you, act on it. If for any
reason it needs to change, you'll know
that and feel it, too. I know. I know.
Um, I was wondering if you could help us
with a name for the company. We have
been brainstorming for a couple of
weeks. We've been letting it sit. We've
been dreaming. We've been thinking.
We've been
asking. And
uh nothing
has arisen yet and we we're waiting for
it because we're ready to move and this
is the thing that is holding us up and
there may be a reason for that too. I
mean holding you up not in this physical
sense but I mean in a practical way
there are things that need to be taken
care of that we're not attending to
because of that need. I see what a
wonderment
I just wondered if you had any
suggestions. I've asked my
mother. I've asked all of my friends. I
thought I I just gave you one. What? A
wonderment. Wonder. Wonder. I don't like
it. All right.
Didn't say you would.
I was hoping you'd come up with
something. Oh, did I disappoint you?
All the great and wonderful Bashar did
not come up with a name.
No other suggestions. I'll think on that
one. I'll let it sit for the way I've
let the others sit. All right. No.
No.
You kind to call yourself dreamers if
you wish.
Um, Dreamers Incorporated.
I like
that. Okay. Thank you. Um, I'll think
about that.
We know you will. And we know that
whatever you come up with since it is
your project will be perfect. Thank you.
Uh, by the way, yeah,
will be some assistance with this idea
in your dream state tonight. Oh, good.
Thank you. Great. I have to go. You
won't be thanking me. You will be
thanking yourself and someone else.
Okay. Um I want to know in a very a more
practical way if Oh, I'm sorry.
If um the conversations that I have
nightly are in a very practical way
being heard.
As we have just
said, you will have another conversation
this night of your time and you will be
thanking yourself. No, that's not what I
want to know though. On this end, you
were describing the woman, a young girl
who was up before about the feeling and
the permeation of the communication. I
want to know on the other end, yes, is
it being received in that same way or is
it on a very more specific practical
level? Well, practical might not be the
Well, practical might not be the
appropriate word for it, but you have a
go
between. You will be speaking with that
go between again
tonight. That go between allows the
communication to be felt and now and
then specifically understood.
Although not in every case is it
understood as to what the source of that
information is.
No, I'm not clear about the source. Um,
you you me I know I I I'm clear about
that. I'm clear about my higher
channeling myself all the time.
um when I I just wondered if it was more
specific because I see generally I mean
I I I get into these lists you know and
they're unnecessary I'm sure but um I
wanted to know if people on entity being
the other end heard it in a way that
we're not hearing it on this end the way
maybe feeling how it was being received
in a physical sense in the physical
sense it is being received as certain
types of manifestations that are
occurring in the physical reality
Sometimes the individuals are aware of
why the manifestation occurred and
sometimes they are not consciously aware
okay of what the source is.
Okay, which is you. It is being
received. It will be received and it
will make itself known in many different
ways. It will fall into whatever holes
it needs to and take the shape of the
hole it needs to to fit. whether that
fitting has anything to do necessarily
in all cases with the individuals doing
the receiving in terms of knowing where
and when it came from in your practical
terms is not always the case. Sometimes
it is
sometimes but not always
since there are so many differences
between the two ends
in terms of how information is
interpreted. That's exactly what I'm
curious about is the interpretation of
the case. They are receiving it as
specifically as they need to, but there
isn't always a way to make that
translation into your terminology to
make it seem specific to you. It may
seem very general to you, but in their
terms, it may be extremely specific
because that's the type of reality in
which they exist. Okay? You follow me?
Yeah. We do not mean to be in your terms vague
We do not mean to be in your terms vague
about this, but the idea for now
requires more communication in your own
dream states and is simply in this way
that we are not the main facilitator of
this dialogue. Okay, that's helpful.
Thank you. I I'm just interested in that
mechanism. Very intriguing to me, this
mechanism of communication. It's
something I want to incorporate in in
the work on all levels. Well, perhaps
once again do remember
That consciousness is not in the body.
Your body is in your consciousness. Yes,
I do. That is in a sense the
mechanism because all things are right
here, right now. And in a sense,
therefore, not meaning to be flippant,
all you are doing is talking to
yourself. I know that's what's so interesting
I know that's what's so interesting
about it. That's the mechanism. Okay.
Okay.
Um, Russia. I've been having a lot of
images about Russia, a lot of things of
skirts and violins and I'm I have a very
strong feeling that's growing in me
that's being drawn towards Russia. Yes.
Um, there are many things you can do
within your plays endeavors and things
like that as you say that can also be
taken to the heart of their land as
well because they will be
receiving an old friend.
What period? Some 17th. Was Antonio
there with me? Now and then
very passionately.
Very artistically, quite poetically.
Yes. Not a coincidence, of course. Well,
yes, it is a coincidence. It is not an
accident. Yeah.
Thank you. Thank you very much, Bashar.
Hello, Bashar. Hello. Yeah. I have a
question. Uh I was involved in um let's
say a collision between two cars two
days ago. It was at a very high rate of
speed. That's and uh number one, I was
happy just to walk away from it. Oh,
right. Um but I know there are no such
thing as accidents and then we create
our own reality. Oh, right. In that
process, what occurs in our reality are
beliefs. And I haven't been able
narrowed down what specifically what
police were
were
resulting in the accident and so forth.
Yeah. Collision. Do you believe that if
you do begin in life to accelerate as
fast as you truly desire to that you
will be suddenly stopped?
One more time.
Was that too fast?
Do you believe
that if you accelerate as quickly as you
desire to in the things that you desire
to accelerate in in life that there is
something that might stop you from going
as fast as you want to go.
That you might have a mishap if you go
Yeah, there could be some things around
that. Well, you can work with
that. Anything else? Yeah.
Um, is there anything else there or just
that? How is the other person? Fine.
Fine. Um, real quickly on excitement,
Um, real quickly on excitement,
impulses, how do those align with
excitement? It will depend again upon
your willingness to understand whether
the impulse comes from your integrity or
an expression of lack of integrity. Is
the impulse something you are moving to
or running from?
That will allow you to determine how it
is aligned with excitement or whether it
is an expression of anxiety. But in a
sense, both of them need to be explored.
Yes. Allow yourself to simply be honest
within the communication of yourself in
that way and to truly understand whether
you are doing the things you are doing
in life because you are running from
something you fear to face or whether
you are truly going towards something
that is representative of the vibration
that you are.
Uh real quickly back on my first
question that what was strange about the
night before I had a dream that I was in
an accident. All right. And uh you do
plan everything out in your dream
reality so to speak.
But not everything happens out
literally. Not always. And sometimes it
gives you the opportunity to recognize
that it does not have to play itself out
in physical reality if you have played
it out in the dream reality and
extracted from it what you needed to
learn. Yeah. Just seems cheap enough.
Now this may give you an opportunity
obviously as well since you both as you
say walked away from it to understand
that your dream reality and your
physical reality are the same thing. It
may be an opportunity for that
reflection as
well. You follow me? Yeah. And to know
therefore that you truly are in control
and that what seemed like an accident
was truly set up. Yeah.
So that you could let us say in a very
graphic but safe way completely
understand that you create your reality
from your dream
levels. Now that you know that if you
are willing to know that you will not
necessarily have to create in your terms
such a radical demonstration of that at
least not in negative ways.
Although again this is not necessarily
negative if you are looking at it from
the positive point of view that you now
are squarely in touch with your
creativity and controllability.
Appreciate we appreciate your
willingness to be that bold. Thank you.
We thank you. At this timing, you may
all take a short break and we will
resume contact.
All right, I'll say shouting
Bashar. Hey, December last year, you
mentioned to me that in February or
March of this year, there would be a lot
of Plleadian activity, which has
definitely been happening.
this month. Uh it's been real intense,
but I feel a lot of your energy in there
along with several other groups. More
and more and more of the civilizations
within the association are now able to
impart their energy. As a matter of
fact, more and more of the encounters of
the sightings, as you say, of our
spacecraft will be
association craft rather than those that
are specifically representative of any
particular frequency or civilization.
All will be blended in that way so that
you can begin to learn to identify with
the energy of a collective. You follow
me? Yes, I do. And and that's what's
been happening. Also, there seems to be
a lot of activity in Washington going
on. Can you comment on that with regards
to the extraterrestrial communications?
Not so much at this time other than to
say there are now the opportunities for
many individuals in many levels of what
you might call political and scientific
communities to begin to understand that
there has always been much information
they have not been made privy to and
they are now beginning to inquire as to
what that information is and will begin
to be of assistance in as you say
pulling that information out and
bringing it to the surface. Some of this
is beginning to accelerate within the
circles that formerly were keeping much
of this information suppressed. It is
now beginning to open up a little bit
more by minds within those associations
that are now becoming curious to the
point where they are willing to
understand there is something there and
willing to take their curiosity to the
point where they will reveal some of the
information that has been suppressed.
Okay. Thank you very much. Thank you.
Shing. Greetings and light. Bashar unto you.
Greetings and light. Bashar unto you.
Um, a week ago, Wednesday evening, about
3:00 in the morning, when I always get
my information, I awakened and my the
palms of my hands and the soles of my
feet were on white fire. The heat was
not, it was very intense. It was not
uncomfortable. And I received the
message, follow your birth path. Between
between then and now, it's I don't know
what it is.
You don't know what it is? No, I don't
know what my birth path is. And don't
give me excitement because I'm a kid and
everything excites me. All right.
Could you set shed some light on it if
you will?
We are. Close your
Close your
eyes right
now and take three deep
breaths. And as you do
so, recall. Recall that feeling. Recall
that image. Recall that
light. Recall. Let it create now in your
Recall. Let it create now in your
imagination images.
images that you may call times past.
Images that you may call times yet to
come. Some of them may seem ancient and
at the same time some of them may seem
what you call futuristic.
Are you doing this so far? Mhm. Um, when
I was a child, I was four years old and
I lived in Pennsylvania and I sat under
a pine tree and I wondered why the hell
I was here and I didn't want to be
here. And then I knew I had to be here.
And when I was
13, the vessel that I am and I became
one with, the white energy came upon me
and I tried to refuse it and I had no
choice about that either.
And then when I was 23, the spiritual
transcendence. Is it possible that I'm fighting that to
Is it possible that I'm fighting that to
some degree? Yes. And that I'm ready for
it now. Oh yes. You have always been
ready for any experience you have had or
you would not have been able to have
those experiences. Well, what am I
supposed to do with it?
Now, first of all, what do you want to
do with it? I have four things I'd like
to do with it. Name them. Um when I
start seminars next month. All right. Um
what else? I have really been creative
in my music. All right. Um tonal
vibration and what that tonal vibration
can do to assist other
individuals will play a very important
part of your birth path. What else? I've
always been teaching. I mean it's
something that people are always coming
to me for assistance. Nice. Um I do it
also through artwork. All right. And
color vibration plays a strong part as
well. Yeah. And last evening when I was
doing my meditation and I took a little
trip the the being that I saw was very
the the being that I saw was very
comfortable. Yeah. But it was a
blackness and the features were in blue
and I just couldn't hold on to it long
enough. It is all right for
now. You are in a sense a gate. You are
yourself a
processor. You are in that sense a
gatekeeper and you can process many
individuals through it into the
transformation. That is the general
understanding of your birth path. There
can be many specific endeavors that will
represent it and some of them you have
mentioned but in
general you are the keeper of a circle
the circle is a hole in the fabric of
one dimension that leads to another.
Many individuals through your love and
individuals through your love and
willingness and assistance can be
allowed to step through that gate and go
on to find their own light and their own
love. In that
way, the darkness and the blue image to
some extent had to do with some of the
vibrations of our civilization, some of
the vibrations of a past connection. And
it also had to do with a recognition and
a direct communication with the
mentality, the collective
electrotheromagnetic mentality
consciousness of the planet earth upon
which you are now serving and also
functioned in a sense as your
mentor that which gives you the
reflection of your ability as a
gatekeeper. It is the symbol, the archetypal symbol
It is the symbol, the archetypal symbol
of a mental gatekeeper in many ways and
allows you to know to some degree to
what shall we say colloquially club you
belong. I get it. Thank you very much. Well,
I get it. Thank you very much. Well,
thank you very much.
Sure. Hi, Bashar. Hi.
Uh last week I asked you for a word for
my higher self or guide and you said to
do it myself. Yes. And uh so many words
and I did and uh the word was buzz. All
right. And uh I was trying to go well how do I
And uh I was trying to go well how do I
know I just didn't make this up? Well
you did in a way make it up. Well I gave
myself lots of reinforcing. Uh, I kept
hearing airplanes like five times.
Very good. I was like, uh, what what
else do you want? May I point something
out to you before we continue? Of
course. Oh, thank you very
much. Your imagination is that which
allows you to know that the realities
you desire are real and you do make them
up. But making them up does not mean
they are not
real. This definition has caused some
consternation in your life. The
dichotomy as to whether it is real or
not just because you imagined it. Your
imagination does create the reality you
experience. Well, that was the other
part of it because pretty soon I was
getting all these words and symbols and
I realized, well, I'm going to make a
big list if I start all the words and
signs from my higherelves and my guides.
So, I realized that everything was
communication. Yes, you do not
necessarily have to compile a list of
buzzwords. But you can take the whole concept, the
But you can take the whole concept, the
whole communication and simply trust
that whatever you focus on at any given
moment will be the reality you
experience will be the reflections that
you get. And you can do this add
infinitum as you say. You have an
infinite number of perspectives. And so
any one of those perspectives that you
choose to activate will always call
forth the details that go with that
particular perspective in infinite ways.
It is simply letting you know that the
dial is free. You can turn it any way
you want. Stop it anywhere you want. And
when you stop it where you choose to,
that will be the program you pick up.
Okay. I two uh symbols that I would like
to ask you about uh the archetypal
symbology. The letter Z and uh spiders.
Spiders. The letter Z.
I like spiders. It seems like a power
animal for me. Of course.
Now understand again that to some degree
and perhaps specifically in this case,
the spider represents the connection to
everything, the synchronicity, because
it is at the center of a web and the web
radiates out and connects to all
reality. Again, it is a reinforcement of
the idea that you are the center of your
own creation and that your web extends
infinitely in all directions. You follow
me? Yes.
The Z in a
sense has to do with the
symbol of nomenclature has to do with
the symbol of naming things to some
extent in your reality. This is somewhat
esoteric because it represents a facet
and an aspect that has not really been
used very much in your society for quite
a while. But it connects into ancient
remnant ideas of you. And it also
connects into an idea of a future
self. That is what the basic Z idea
represents. A connection for you to a
future self. Yeah, I do feel uh when you
told the young lady to make a letter M,
I I go, I should make a letter Z because
I feel like it's one of those what you
call lures. Yikes.
I remember when I was younger, but not
so young. I had a little doll that I
named Z and then uh came up a couple of
times already since then. The symbol
that has not been used for a while is
now being used again. You represented
your instinctive understanding of what
you would encounter in the future then
and you gave an appropriate symbol to
the reflection of that doll, that idea.
Now, in a sense, the doll is calling
you. Your childhood is calling you. Your
Your childhood is calling you. Your
future is calling you.
Thank you. Oh, thank you for
creating that connection so
lovingly, so
thoroughly, so immediately.
Quick sh Good evening, Bashar. And to
you, good day. Um, my life is going
through a lot of changes, of course,
which is exciting. are for the court.
Uh, and um, I got a question for you.
Um, for me,
I shall take very good care of it. Put
it on the sale.
Okay. I've got a question to you. Um um
I've left a job that was security for me
and I'm moving my company out of the
city and I'm moving on March 15th and I
was wondering if you could tell me very
strong transformational date your March
15th what you call the eyides of March
very strong gateway with regard to all
things and particularly in your society
things that have to do with what you
call economic structures.
Sounds good. Now the idea is that you
did not give up something that was
representative of security. You are now
by becoming more fluid truly becoming
more stable and therefore more
secure. You follow me? Yes. Does this
assist you? Uh yes it does. Thank you
very much. I have another question. All
right. Um about two months ago, I experienced
Um about two months ago, I experienced
uh an event that happened three weeks
later. Okay. Uh but it was a very
trivial daily event and nothing is
trivial. I was wondering if you could
give me
any I don't understand why I because all
time is fluid. I understand that but I I
understand why I experienced this
particular event and I've never had it.
What happened? Yeah.
Um, I experienced opening my uh checking
receipts from the bank. And seeing a
check that I had written to somebody, I
didn't know his last name. And when I
got the check back, I noticed he hadn't
put his last name on the check. And I
turned it over and saw his endorsement
on the check. And I told somebody about
that. And then three weeks later, it
actually happened. I actually did get
the check.
And I just don't understand why that
particular event I would remember when
I've never had any kind of because it
has to do again with the financial door
you are walking through the economic
door. You are focused on events that
show you that economics can be
open-ended and not so
structured. Okay. You created in a sense
a clear and conscious manifestation of
what typically is called deja vu. Mhm.
If you had not quote unquote consciously
remembered that you had dreamed it when
you got the check, you would have still
had the dja vu feeling. Right. If I had
not spoken to somebody about it, I would
have thought it was deja vu. There you
go. You are giving yourself the
understanding of the fluidity of the
future and the past and the present and
allowing the basis of your abundance to
be flexible in many ways.
Okay, I've got one more question for
you. All right. Um, I'll put it on the
shelf next to the other. Okay.
Uh, person before me was mentioning UFO
activity around Washington. I was
wondering if it was possible if the
association might possibly take our
president to observe him. [Laughter]
[Laughter]
We do not have to take anyone anywhere
to observe them.
But it would help us a
lot. Not
really. The idea once again is for each
and every one of you to remember the
following thing. You are your
governments. You they are what you are.
You they are what you are.
[Laughter]
[Music]
They are created out of the lack of
willingness to take responsibility for
your fears in your own life. And when
you are willing to take back
responsibility for your fears, when you
are willing to communicate with them,
not accusatory, attacking, but
unconditionally loving ways, you will
then open the lines of communication
between this self and that self. And
there will be free communication and the
government so to speak will begin to be
able to be allowed to serve rather than
rule you. You follow me? Yes. Thank you very
you. You follow me? Yes. Thank you very
much for anything you care to do in that
direction. Thank you. For that
willingness is what will
assist in the formation of relations
between your world and others.
You mean we until we have a global
government that serves us properly that
we that we run we're not going to have
basically more or less not that it has
to be absolutely in the final stage it
will be in but the idea is that more and
more expression of the willingness to
recognize that you are a global entity
will make it easier for you to be able
to act and interact with other global
entities. It is as simple as that.
Whatever vibration you are on will
attract other vibrations of like kind.
Will we be able to maintain our cultural
diversity and have a global global
system of government? Well, as a matter
of fact, though it may seem paradoxical
to you, you will strengthen your
diversity because the idea of any unity
that you create upon your world or
anywhere, unity is the result of the
granting of equality and validity to the
diversity within your society.
It is utter allowance of all forms of
existence knowing that they can inter
mesh so that you can extract from them
the different benefits of the different
points of view. That's what enriches you
and creates you to be
strong. Not becoming the idea so much of
homogeneous though that is also one
expression. But you know that you think
of yourself as a person with many
different personality parts. Yes. Mhm.
Well, you know that you are strongest as
a whole person when each and every one
of those personality parts is granted
equality, are you not? Yes. Then it is
through the granting of equality to all
the diversity in your cultures that will
allow you to truly function as a unified
whole. Does that make sense to you? Very much
Does that make sense to you? Very much
so. Well, thank you very much. Thank
you. Sure.
Good day, Bashar. And to you, good day.
Thank you. I have come across something
that I think is very very interesting.
Oh wow. Douche. Okay. I have it in my
left hand. It has been called a cosmic
egg. And I was told that about seven
years ago several hundred of them were
found in the ground in Rome, Georgia.
And I meditated with it for 33 seconds
with M. And as I did so, my voice my the
tonal of the M went five times lower
than my normal tone that I use for M.
They are centering stones, balancing
stones, deepening stones. They connect
you to the earth. They connect you to
the sky, to all the heavens and all the
dimensions. They are centering stones.
Thank you. They are in a sense, if you
wish to be poetic, the gems of your
consciousness. The earth giving birth to the gems of
The earth giving birth to the gems of
your consciousness. They are
seeds. Truly, they are
seeds which if you plant in the fertile
soil of your heart will grow and
blossom. Oh,
wonderful. Thank you. Uh, one more
question. Um Boris says hello to all of you and
Um Boris says hello to all of you and
Bashar. He is in Florida now playing
with the dolphins. Nice. And uh last
evening he said uh stood in a grid of
all of these eggs and also with crystals
has taken grids to place on the
dolphins. Is he having fun with them?
And the dolphins are they enjoying the
grids? Yes. Also, these seeds are
representative of some of the ideas we
have discussed wherein in the past the
dolphins would scour the bottom of the
ocean and retrieve some of these ideas
bringing them to the surface for your
use. Oh, thank you so very much. Well,
thank you. Thanks. Sure.
Good evening. Good day. Um, I would like
to know what the key is to cellular
rejuvenation and what activates that
living in the now. Okay, completely
utterly because you see time is your
creation. And when you live in the now,
well, let's back
up. You know what you say happens to
time when you're having fun. Yes. Yes.
You say you don't notice it. You say
time flies. You don't pay attention.
Hours go by, seems like minutes. You
follow me? Yes. Well, the secret of the
matter is is that when you are living in
the moment and to you experientially it
really feels as if only a few minutes
has gone by, your body really has only
aged a few minutes. Aha. So living in
the now, doing what you enjoy doing
right now, then you don't create as much
time to
experience. You live in an eternal now
moment and therefore you become timeless
and ageless. H
another way that we have discussed this
idea is to recognize that it's living in
the now is a very childlike quality
spontaneity as you say. Now your
society is one that thinks that this
spontaneity is only relegated to a
childlike frame of reference. And the
two times you are allowed to be
childlike in your lives are when you are
very young and when you are very
old. And so if you are willing to be
childlike now then you won't have to age
for it to be all right for you to be
childlike again. Ah great.
That is the primary fundamental
methodology. Now, there may be many
representational tools
that you will use to represent your
willingness to let it be all right to
stop the idea of aging. Mhm. Any and all
of these can work because they are
external symbols of your permission to
live in the moment. But you can also
render it right down to the very act of
simply living in the moment. And then
you will not necessarily need what might
be a metaphysical or medical symbol for
the idea that you are willing to simply
allow yourself to live in the moment
and be excited. That's all it takes.
Right? I got it. That's wonderful. That
energy is the energy of the flow of
creation. And when you know you live in
the moment, then you are constantly
recreating yourself every single moment
over and over and over again. And you
are always
new. That's why it's
called recreation.
recreation.
Recreation. You are recreating yourself
a new every moment. You never age. You
are always at zero zero zero. You follow
me? Yes. Does that assist you? Yes.
Thank you. Thank you very much for
playing with us. My pleasure. And ours
as well. I have one more question. All
right. There is a voice, a singing voice
that uh will come through me rarely. And
when it does, it sounds like an angel.
Yes. Angelic. Yes. In a sense, it is
archetypal angelic. Someone that heard
it said it sounded like a mermaid. And I
would like to know how I can be in touch
with that voice more all the time.
Actually, remember when many of you were little
remember when many of you were little
and you
created imaginary friends?
You can do it that way if you wish.
You can play in your
sandbox and you can have an
imaginary friend that represents this
energy so that bit by bit you can get
used to the idea of the many different
ways it can manifest itself through you
for in many ways it is but aspects also
of your own higher being your own soul
self.
Thank you. One moment. Yes,
you can also simply
sing. You can also play with the idea of
notes, tones, the ones that move you,
the ones that strike chords within you
can put you into the state wherein you
can then return an echoing vibration and
it will center you in that way. That is
another way. Play in your
way. Play in your
imagination. It is the sandbox of your
soul. All right. Yes. Thank you very much.
All right. Yes. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Sharing. Hello. Hello.
Hello. Hello.
Um, my question is I need assistance in
putting together my theater and my
family. How I can do both. Putting
together your theater and your family.
Yeah, they both excite me and yet I find
because of both of them I end up not
doing good at either one of them. All
right. All right. What makes you think
they cannot mesh?
Um, what beliefs do you have about both
that makes it seem as if to have both
they are interferive rather than
enhancing to each other?
When I'm doing one, I'm not doing the
other. So, so I feel like something's
being taken away from that when I should
not something else. Not really. Not
really. There really are no shoulds. You
know, you may be attempting to try to be
responsible for other individuals when
you cannot really be. You can be
responsible to them, but you cannot be
responsible for them. All you really
need is a little more trust that the way
circumstances unfold in your life is the
way that is indicative of how everything
will automatically take care of itself.
Okay. I guess that's what my real
question is is I have real strong
calling and I know that I have work to
do and it's real clear from childhood
and I keep feeling like oh am I being
lazy am I not doing it because right now
I'm with my family you are simply
assuming again that one precludes the
other what we are saying is that when
you do follow what truly excites you
what represents the path you are then
all the circumstances that really need
to be in your life to allow you to be
that will be in your life. You will have
what assistance you need in whatever way
you need to have it to allow you to take
care of whatever you have created. It
will all fit if you let it fit. So just
relax and be you are only trying to
juggle something that is one thing. You
are breaking it into two things and
that's why you have to juggle it. It is
one event. the theater family, the
family theater, it is one event. If you
make it two separate events, then of
course, as long as you say it's a
polarity, as long as you say it's a
dichotomy, then both of your hands are
going to be full.
Okay, another question. Um, I've been
having like feeling to do something with
drums. I'm not real a musician or
anything like that. And I wonder if
that's that may simply be an indication
of your timing of the idea that you do
not have to follow society's standards
and that you can move to a different
beat. Oh, okay. You you decide the
rhythm. You decide the rhythm. All
right. Whatever rhythm is correct for
you, you decide it. Okay. You are all
drummers in that sense.
And am I going to have one more baby?
I'm thinking about getting st I mean
fixing myself and feeling there might be
another it is possible there seems to be
an agreement the idea will basically as
we perceive it depend upon your
willingness to relax a little more to
make space for
it when you know you do contain all of
this and that none of this is truly
beyond you there will be more than
enough room for all of the family that you have
room for all of the family that you have
agreed to interact as.
All right. Trust, trust, trust.
Relax. Enjoy.
Thank you. Thank you very
much. And pleasant dreams to you.
Sharing. Greetings from planet Earth,
Bashar. Oh, thank you very much. Just
greetings from Esasani.
Humanoid joke. Just kidding. Um, three
questions. Uh, Bashar. Number one.
Number one is um we like things in
threes. Yes. Uh, one is a question in
regards to past lives and future lives.
Um, if the benefit is in living in the
present and in the now, um, what is the
advantage of learning about past lives?
That is up to the individual. It may be
able to be of assistance to them in many
ways. The advantages will be inherent in
the perspectives of the individual. All
we are saying is that you still at the
same time do have all the information
you need to know to live the life you
are living now regardless of whether you
go delving into the so-called past or
future or not.
But if you feel so inclined, then
obviously you have set yourself up in
that way and by all means follow your
instincts. So it's possible then to
foresee future lives. Of course. How
does one do that?
What do you imagine right now might be
something you would do if you had a
future life?
Um, it'd be more playful and involved in
the uh communicative arts. In what way?
Performing. All right. If you wish to,
you can be that future human now. Yeah,
that's I am. All right.
Yeah. Okay. Um, that's how one goes
about it by performing it. Okay.
it by performing it. Okay.
Uh thank you. You're welcome. Um number
two. Two. Um in regards to I I have a
desire to uh get in touch with my higher
self and guides. And this is the same as
number one.
Yeah. Okay. Well,
um please understand something very
basic again. Not that you cannot manifest it
again. Not that you cannot manifest it
in this way, but it is not really always
what you desire to manifest
communication between your higher self
and your guides in a typical
conversational way. Communication with
your guides and your higher self is
always going on. The way it most often
manifests in your life is in the events
that unfold in your life.
It evolves as action in your life. So
just living the action that occurs in
your life is carrying through the
dialogue with your guides and your
higher self.
Well, I'm wishing to activate that in my
meditation though. Is there can you give
me a meditation or some tools to use in
regards to uh opening up those channels
so I'm I'm more aware. All right, let's
use your imagination right now. How do
you imagine if you were to be able to
hear as you say with your ears your
higher self how would it he she sound?
Well, it would be more in the head. It
would be more as a thought or an
instinct in the past. All right. Would
you hear words? Yes. All right. Would
there be a particular quality to the
voice? It would be pleasant and resonant. All
It would be pleasant and resonant. All
right. If you were to imagine right now
that you say right now from you, the you
you are here, hello higher
self, what would it say? And how would
it sound? If I were to say that? Yes. If
you were to say hello higher self, how
would it respond? How do you imagine it
would respond? Okay. So, I'm speaking as
the higher self now. Is that what you're
saying? Or am I I am asking you a
question that you are hesitating to
answer. Yes, indeed.
How would it respond if you said hello
higher self? Hello and welcome home.
Thank you very much. What was so
difficult about
[Laughter] that? Now, here's the real question.
that? Now, here's the real question.
Here is the crux and the fulcrum of the
entire matter. And this is the strongest
clue we can give
you. If you are willing to believe it is
that simple, you will be in touch all
the time. If you are willing to believe that
time. If you are willing to believe that
was real and it was that simple to do,
you will be in touch all the
time. Now, that is a question for you to
answer in your own good timing. Am I
willing to believe that was real? Am I
willing to believe it was that easy to
do? Are are they one and the same? The
Are are they one and the same? The
higher self and guides or are they
separate? Can be one and the same. Can
be separate. What's the difference?
And why does there need to be a
difference? That's another question.
Okay. How about simply only a
suggestion, not telling you what to do.
How about simply that whatever seems to
work, that's the
communication. Whatever feels like it's
working. Whatever feels easy, whatever
sounds like, yes, that sounded like my
higher self. Recognize that voice
anywhere.
Whatever answer comes most easily to
you, whatever your first inclinations
and instincts and intuitions are, very
often, the first thing that pops into
your mind when you think of something,
when you think of a question, the first
thing that usually pops into your mind
is usually the communication from the
higher self. But it is so quick and so
simple and many times so
obvious you don't believe
it because you as a society have been
taught to believe it can't be that easy.
That can't be right. That was too easy.
You follow me? Mhm. All you need to do
is begin to relax and pay more attention
to the first thing that truly pops into
your head rather than an almost
automatic response that you have in your
society of invalidating that so quickly
you may not even know you had the
thought and then analyzing what should
be the real thought.
What if what if it's a blank space
though that comes up?
Let it be. Yeah, let it be blank. That's
the whole point. It will not remain so
for long. Paradoxically, the more
willing you are to let it be blank, the
more quickly it will be
filled. But let it come. If you do not
seem to get anything in the moment, take
a few more steps in life. Maybe you are
simply not in line with the
communication yet. Maybe you're not
right at the timing wherein the
communication will be focused in a way
that you need to hear it. It is there,
but it may be out of focus. Turn the
dial a little until you bring it in more
clearly by simply taking a few more
steps in
life. You follow me? Yes. Thank you. Oh,
thank you very much. Just a a quickie on
the third one. Hey, quickie. that um tools
um tools
uh on this sphere of existence such as
astrology, tarot and crystal balls,
things like that. Not crystals
specifically. We understand. But those
are those legitimate forms of
communication? Why not? They are
products of your imagination like
anything else. If it works for you, yes.
If it doesn't work for you, don't use
it. Okay. Anything of that nature is simply
Okay. Anything of that nature is simply
a trigger to allow you to work along the
lines of least resistance according to
whatever your belief systems are that
you have bought into. That is all they
are. They are mirrors. They are
triggers. They are in a sense tricks.
Not meaning that in a derogatory way.
They are ways of tricking yourself into
being the sensitive expanded psychic
knowing being that you are.
You see, since you are a society that
has developed yourself to place your
power outside of yourself, well, at
least you have been creative and clever
enough to create some symbols outside
yourself that will at least trick you
back into using your
power. So, of course, they work in that
sense because the one you are attracted
into using is the one that indicates the
state of being you are at at that
moment. And that symbol represents the
way you will allow yourself to be
connected to express yourself
as your higher self. Not talk with
express yourself as your higher self.
And that's the final clue. Understanding
that the idea is not a dialogue between
separate things, a dialogue with. It is
a dialogue as because on that level all
things are
one. You follow me? You just lost me on
that last thing that you said. Clarify
that it is in the universe a reality
that there are what you perceive to be
separate consciousnesses. At the same
time any consciousness physical and
non-physical that you are talking
with, you are talking
as you are one and the same. You are
speaking to yourself because you create
your own reality. And whether you are
interacting with someone else or not,
the actual thing you are interacting
with is your version of them that you
created out of what you are made of.
You follow me.
I'll have to listen to the tape again. A
lot of information so be clear when I
listen. You are energy. You follow me.
Mhm. You create all your physical
appearing reality out of the energy you
are. Once again, remember consciousness
is not in the body. Your body is in your
consciousness. Everything you see is
you. It is made of the being you are.
are. So even if you are interacting with
other consciousnesses, the way you
choose to perceive them is by creating a
replica of them out of your
consciousness to interact with. Because
you are your own universe.
Does that clarify it to some extent?
Yes. Thank you. Well, thank you very
much. Thank you. Happy trails to you as
well. Sure.
Sure.
Good evening. Good day.
I'm amazed that I'm here and I don't
know where to begin quite. That is all
right. Are you having good time? No. Oh, why
Are you having good time? No. Oh, why
not?
Well, most of my life I've been
a dynamic, active, creative, and potent
or powerful individual. All right. Why
the difference now?
That's what I need to know. Since
1982, I became very ill and totally
incapacitated for almost a year. All
right. I regained my health but
uh could
not get back my work going again and
then I
But which work is that? And are you sure
that that work is still something you
really want to do? Yes. Are you
sure? Is that what excites you in life
above and beyond anything else?
Modified somewhat, but the same basic
work. Yes. All right. What is that work?
I've been for almost 17 years a psychic,
counselor, healer, those kinds of things. All
healer, those kinds of things. All
right. Now, in what way do you wish to
continue to express that energy?
I don't know. That's the problem. I
can't seem to generate any energy. I I
would like to go over a couple of things
that happened first because I it's like
a series of events that I can't seem to
shake myself loose from. All right.
After recovery from the illness, I was
What was in your terms the illness?
Well, it was a viral form of rheumatoid
arthritis that destroyed all the muscle
in my body and I for a year I
couldn't walk. I couldn't brush my
teeth, feed myself, clothe, do anything
of that nature at all. Right.
Um I again recovered from that except a
few very minor side effects. All right.
But about the time I began to get back
on my feet from that u attempting to
help another individual, I
was arrested, criminal charges filed,
convicted, even spent 40 months in
prison. My life has not been able to get
back together since that time.
Um, no matter what I've tried to do as
far as working again, I can't seem
to focus my energy. I can't seem to
sustain anything. All right. Has
resulted in in the last few months in literally
in in the last few months in literally
destroying a relationship that
is been the most meaningful thing of my
life. All
right. And I don't know where to go and
what to do. Thank
you. Now, may I ask you a question? Yes.
When you were doing your
work, what was your attitude about it?
Why were you doing what you were
doing? In terms of being of assistance
to
others, how did you look upon your work?
How did you define it?
I felt that I
was fortunate that I had a capacity to
help. I was always fulfilled and satisfied
I was always fulfilled and satisfied
with what I did for myself. Uh but I was
very successful in helping those people
because I was interested and cared. All
right. Do you All
All
right. Do you feel at any time that you
were assisting other individuals at what
you may or may not have believed to be
the expense of your own
life? Were there things that you wanted
to do that you didn't do because you
were helping
others? Or do you feel that what you
were doing was truly what you wanted to
do? There were there were times when I
didn't do things that I was doing, but
it was
feelings and needs for your own life
now in a much more complete way than I
have been before. All right. Only very
recently. All right. But you do
understand that you do create your
reality and that everything does occur
for a reason. Yes. Yes. And you do
understand that in many ways after the
incidents you are describing that you
have learned certain things, extracted
certain things from these scenarios and
you are in a sense on the
men. You understand you are on the men.
uh I I feel that uh in some ways but I
am still I'm not certain all right what
I have learned and what I all right
there is yet to learn about why all of
these events
that is all right
now many times you do understand that as
we have been discussing if you do keep
living eventually you will understand
the reason for every event in your
Yes. All
right. With that knowledge, you can
begin to set yourself at ease to some
degree if you are
willing. If you are willing to not
necessarily make it a completely
paramount thing, not that you cannot
know, but to not make it a
completely important thing to have an
absolute analytical awareness of why
these things happened yet. You will
know. You will
know. The idea also to some
degree is that there are many different
avenues in your world for centering
yourself. And a bit of traveling on your
part now that you perhaps are capable of
doing so might be an order just for
you. Just for you.
You will be being of assistance to other
individuals along the way. And at the
same time, you can pick up on
techniques, ideas that will later allow you to be of
ideas that will later allow you to be of
assistance to other individuals as well.
One of our perceptions at this point,
however, is to begin to relax into the
idea that you can travel now to many
lands and that you can attract yourself
to individuals who can teach you many
different ideas about expression of
energy on all
level. And that with the incorporation
of some of this and some of these new
techniques and
understandings, you may be able to
completely rebuild the idea of the
personality that you are. You are no
longer the same person that you were
before the disease in that way. And what
may be confusing you to some extent is
that a portion of you still thinks that
you are and a portion of you is still
attempting to do things in the same way
the old person used to. It is time for
you to learn what it is to be the new
person you have created yourself to be.
For you literally are not the same
person. I I realize that part of the
problem is that I have always known
anything and everything I ever needed to
know. Yes. And I cannot seem to
know where to find my All right. But you
see what we are saying is whatever this
condition seems like to you, it only
seems that way because you are making a
comparison between what it is and what
it used to be. All right? If you are
willing to trust that whatever way it is
manifesting itself now is representative
of the way you need to know it.
Now you will begin to lock in new
perspectives that will show you bit by
bit that you still know every bit as
much as you always
knew. Simply it is time to begin to
express it in a different way.
Is the travel uh essential because I
have limitations for two years yet I
cannot travel.
Very limited. All right. Whatever travel
you can do within those limitations for
the next two of your orbits will
suffice. After that it will expand
accordingly. Now perhaps one suggestion, one
Now perhaps one suggestion, one
area. Are you at this time in your terms
allowed so to speak by the scenario you
have created to travel to the areas you
would call Arizona and New Mexico?
Yes. All
right. We will
suggest, not tell you, but
suggest that you may be able to drink
deeply from a different well and
re-energize and reenter and
recristallize and reinvigorate some of
your cellular
being. if you perhaps will partake of
some of the
ceremonies and some of the interactions
of what you call the Native American
cultures in those
areas perhaps specifically the
hope. This is our primary
suggestion. In many ways, you are a
phoenix rising from the
ashes. And this symbol has strong
meaning in that
culture. They may be able to assist you
in recognizing the new
persona, the new birth you are going
through. may be of some assistance in
reconnecting, reggrounding you to the
earth along a new
line. That will assist you in rebuilding
your strength. For it will assist you in
remembering, not teaching you anything
new, but simply remembering in a
different way that you are an extension
of the
earth and that therefore its unlimited
power is yours to feel. begin the
begin the
sojourn. Many things will change and
transform. And we would also
recommend slow and easy breathing but
deep knowing that the atmosphere you are
breathing is
electromagnetically charged and that each and every cell bit
charged and that each and every cell bit
by bit will drink its share, drink its
fill until you are a completely
recristallized being but again you will
be a different being.
We simply suggest once
more that it is not about making
comparisons between what you are and
what you used to be, but learning that
whatever way these ideas are manifesting
now, they are representative of the new
foundations of a new perspective of a
new person and that nothing will ever
really seem the same. You will not
recapture the past identically. You will
create a new present that will allow you
to do many of the same things, but they
will be differently expressed because
you are a different person in a very
significant way. All you need to do is find that you
way. All you need to do is find that you
center with that you and some of the
sojouring we are perceiving can assist
you in
that. It might be mirrored in the
stones. It might be mirrored in the sky.
It might be mirrored in the animal life
around you, but begin to
you, but begin to
move, wander, walk, learn, travel. You
are in many ways a wanderer, and it will
assist you in remembering that that
represents your freedom, and that
represents your willingness to be of
assistance in many changing modes.
All of the time before in a sense was an
apprenticeship, a preparation for
something that can be expressed now on
magnitudes far greater. But it will
require a complete rewiring of all your
belief systems in many different ways.
That is what you will begin and what you
have begun this night of your time. We
thank you for allowing us to be a part
of it. Thank you. Our love to you, our
energy to you. Thank you. Enjoy your
travels. Many are with you. You are not
alone. Thank
you. There will be in your terms but a
few moments remaining for this
interaction this evening of your
time. Continue.
Hi Bashar. Hi.
Um, something happened about a week ago
where someone called and started telling
me about a job and I didn't even really
hear what they said because I got so
excited it, you know, it felt like
firecrackers going off in my chest. And
so I said, "Great, just give me the
number." Everything came together. I
wrote a bio, had the interview, and I
just felt it was my job. Nice. So, I was
real happy about it. And uh, they called
this morning and told me they hired
someone else. Nice. So, I was kind of
going, "Huh, I wonder how that
happened." Very simply, obviously, at
this point, the whole reason for the
excitement was in a sense to get you to
move, to get you to know you could
respond that
quickly. It is not so much that you
needed the job specifically, but the
idea and the scenario was created to get
you up off
well, to get you on your feet.
to get you hopping, to get you jumping,
and to instill within you a certain
vibration that is now still scanning for
something else that is coming in. It put
you in the right frequency so that you
would be able to see something else
coming along. It got you into the right
frame of mind. Do you follow me? I see.
Enjoy. Stay at that level. Continue to
enjoy. take it for granted that again
the way it happened was for a
reason and that that portion of the
event is all you needed and it will lead
to something else but it put you in the
right frequency. You follow me? I do. All
frequency. You follow me? I do. All
right. Thanks a lot. Thank you very
much.
At this timing, allow us to extend once
again to each and every one of you
individually and
collectively our utmost appreciation in
allowing us the pleasure of your
company. We thank you for your
willingness to share and create the same
dreams. We thank you for sharing your
hearts.
exciting dream lives to you
all. A fond and loving good day.
How'd it go? [Applause]