I don't see how are you all this evening
of your time as you create time to
exist. Allow us to begin this interaction, this
Allow us to begin this interaction, this
evening of your time with the reminder
that we have entitled this week's
interaction the
sound. It will come this time in a way
that is a little bit different in the
form of what you call a story. Are you
all in the mood for a story? All right.
Now, a portion of this story will
involve a very brief amount of what you
call audience
participation. I will let you know when
the timing is appropriate for that. All
right. Oh, thank you.
And so before we
begin, snuggle
up or snuggle
down. Allow yourselves to become very
comfortable and
relax and
recognize that we will of course be
communicating with you on many different
levels throughout this interaction.
But for now, simply enjoy the
idea of the
sound. It begins with a
being no particular place, no particular
time, perhaps much like one of
yourselves, perhaps not similar
enough. And this bee one day
heard heard a story a story that
said there
is a sound that can be
found and when
discovered can alter the very existence
the very fabric of space and time. Well,
this excited the being a
lot and so the being decided to set out
in search of this special sound, this
magical sound, whatever it is. The being
did not know, but would search anyway
because the being was sure that when the
sound happened, the being would know,
would recognize it.
So off the being
went, thinking perhaps first to itself,
well, let me see. Let me think. Let me
feel. A sound. A sound. A magical sound.
Where do you suppose such a sound would
come from? As the being was
from? As the being was
walking, ran into another
being who happened to have a friend
along as well. And they said, "Well,
good day. Where are you off to? I am in
search of the sound. The sound. The
magical sound most profound when
discovered will change the course of
space and time and alter all of the
universe. Oh
my. There is such a sound, they said. I
have heard it so
said. May we search with you for that
sounds most exciting. By all means, I
would enjoy the company. So now there
were three. You know how we love
three. You know how we love
threes. And so the three set off in
search of the sound, the mysterious,
mystical, magical sound. And they
discussed among themselves as they
went, "Where do you suppose such a sound
would be?" One of them said, "Well, you
know, there are many sounds that animals
make. Do you suppose it might be one of
those sounds?" And so they went into
their forests and their jungle and
listen to all the sounds that the
different animals might make. And they
spent a lovely
day peering into bushes and under rocks
and in caves, climbing tall trees and
forging broad streams, lying in the
grass, listening to the small sounds,
and the large sounds and the sweet
sounds and some that were a little bit
scary. But that's all right, for they
contained much power. And they thought,
well, perhaps in one of those is the
mystical power that unlocks space and
time and changes everything. And they
listened and they copied and mimicked
all the sounds they heard that day in
the jungle in the
forest. And they got very good at
sounding like animals.
But none of the sounds, even though it
allowed them to enjoy themselves and
enjoy nature. None of the sounds seemed
to strike that cord. None of the sounds
to them carried what they at least
expected or thought the sound ought to
be. And so they discussed once again
among themselves. Where do you suppose this
themselves. Where do you suppose this
sound could be? We have listened to
every animal that there is. both large and
animal that there is. both large and
small, both fast and slow. In the air,
on the land, in the water, we have
copied all the sounds they could make,
and yet we have not found that special
sound. What do you suppose it could be?
They discussed among themselves, sitting
in a
meadow, and another of them said, "Well,
do you suppose the sound might be in
another land? There are many different
cultures, and different cultures might
make different
sounds. Maybe we ought to travel to far
distant lands to discover sounds we have
never heard in our lives." And so they
traveled around their world. And
wherever they went, they were met with
most exotic sounds, fascinating,
vibrant, different sounds, different
types of
speech that any individual might make.
And while they found it most educational
and most fascinating and did excel in
many different types of
communication, they still did not find
that sound that one special mystical
magical sound. Most elusive, they said, most
sound. Most elusive, they said, most
puzzling. And they returned to their own
land and did ponder once
again. Do you suppose there really is no
such sound? Oh, there must be. They said
there must be. Why? Why? Why would
someone have created that idea if it
were not something they really felt,
something they had discovered once upon
a time for themselves? The idea in our
imaginations must exist. All we need to
do is call it forth somehow, somewhere,
somewhere. That sound, it must exist. I
know it is within our hearts. I know it
is within our minds. But where where
will we find it so that we may
experience it? With our ears, with our
beings. Where where where is that sound
that changes so much?
The third one said,
"Well, do you suppose the sound itself
might be in the things of nature itself
around the very structure of the
physical reality? There are many
different substances in nature and they
all in a sense make different sounds. Do
you suppose it might be one of those?"
And so they scoured the countryside,
picking up different kinds of rocks and
banging them together and scraping
against trees and splashing in water and
of various liquids and swishing things
around in the
air. And they experimented all the next
day long, making every sort of ringing
and gonging and clanging and clapping
and banging and slapping and smacking
sound that they
could. And by the end of that day, they
were very
[Music] tired and also to some degree a little
tired and also to some degree a little
bit
dejected. We have explored all the
sounds animals might make. We have
visited all the cultures in our
world. We have tried and tested all the
substances that nature has to offer. We
have not discovered that most mystical,
magical, elusive sound.
elusive sound.
And so they sat down back in their
meadow and they pondered and they
pondered and they
pondered and none of them could come up
with another
suggestion. And so as they
sat all at
once, all at the same
time, here's where your part comes in.
They all took in a very deep
breath and all at once let out this
sound. Oh my. Oh my. Let's do that
[Applause]
again. Oh my. Oh my.
Once more to be sure. [Music]
[Music]
That's it. That's it. That's it. They
cried. The sound we have been searching
for far and wide. It is the sound that
alters the very perception of things. It
is the release, the flow of energy. It
is in that sense the willingness to
allow wherever you are and whenever to
be the place, the time, the sound. It is
within us. They discovered it is the
release, the
rush. It is the floating
gentility. It is the trust. The trust
that is the sound that changes all
things that alters space and rewrites
time. Everything in the world, the very
structure of the rocks look different
when you release and
be who you are, when and where. The
sigh. The sigh. The sound of the taking
of responsibility. The sound of the
acceptance of the time in which you
exist. The sigh. The sound of being
comfortable with who you
are. The sound of
relaxing into
yourself. We have found it. We have
found it. We have found it. They sang
and sang and were filled with much
joy and they
did from that day
forward. Anytime they felt that they had
created a situation that was a little
bit too far, a little bit too slow, a
little bit too fast, a little bit too
close. They did remember the sound that changes [Applause]
[Applause]
everything and breathed it in and
breathed it through and breathed it out
again. And we're whole and centered and
fresh and
alive. And all it takes is one little side. the
beginning. We thank you for allowing us
to share this little
tale, little
perspective, little
dream. We thank you for your cocreation
in this
way. We do remind
you that this is the season for
stories. And as we have said, next week
of your time, we will share with you
because of your
season our version of a ghost story. At this
At this
timing, in exchange for the gift of the
consciousness that you share with us, in
exchange for the willingness to function
as representatives of your society and
allowing me to function as a
representative of the respective
societies of the association of worlds.
I will ask you now, how may I serve you?
Hi, Bashar. And good day to you. I have
a story for you. Oh, all right. Um, I
wanted to talk about something that
happened to my mother a couple of years
before she died. All right. Um, mother
had a real fascination with space beings
and the idea of space visitation. All
right. And she collected books like
chariots of the gods and gods from outer
space and all the books that were
popular years ago on oh landing sites on
the earth, possible landing sites and
historical connections and all that.
Well, she was dying of cancer when this
happened. guys. And she was up in her
room. My sister was living nearby. I
wasn't living there, but she she told
this to me later. Um, she got a knock on
the door one morning and she hated to be
disturbed because she wasn't well in the
mornings, but she went down to the door
anyway. And she said that there was a
man standing there who had the most
wonderful eyes that she had ever seen.
And that for some reason, just seeing
those eyes, she felt totally relaxed and
totally good at that moment. to be
sitting by a stranger, you know, and not
a stranger, but go on. But you know what
I mean. Thanks. And he said to her, he
said, "I understand you are a reader."
And she said, "Yes, I am." And he said,
"Well, I have a book for you." And so he
gave her this book. And uh he they said
a few more words and then he left. And
my mother read the book and she was so
excited about it that she called my
sister up. I was living actually in a
foreign country at the time and she
called my sister up and she was
exclaiming about the book and said,
"You've got to read the book and when I
finish it and when you come down I'll
give it to you to read." And so my
mother read the book and when my sister
arrived about a week or so later. Um the
book had disappeared and they couldn't
find it anywhere in the house and she
never did find it. And um what I was
curious about
is could you with me about that? What
did that mean? Was mother somehow
connected or was she just ready for an
an experience to know a little bit more
than most? And and it was in that sense
the final pieces she needed to put into
place to create the passage from your
world to
another to know that she is as everyone
is connected to all different levels.
And in that sense, the book allowed her
to finalize her passage to put into
place the conduit and the tunnel through
which she would travel in that sense to
let her know that always no matter where
you go, there are friends waiting to
greet you.
And did that
um um connection that space connection
was it about beings that are considered
like space beings or was this just uh
transformational information? There was
both within and more.
That's very interesting. And when we
what I'm curious about too is when we
were in the mountains when we were
little kids, we used to spend the
summers up in Idaho. Mother lived in a
very rural town in Idaho in the
mountains. And um I was curious to know
if we'd had any connection like
visitations at that time. There were
some identifications through telepathic
contact. Yes. But let me ask you a
question if I may. Yes, please. What is
your physiological age as you count
time? 45. One moment.
As we read the energy now on or about
the time you would call
approximately the reversal of your age
in numbers now
54. There will be a very strong
opportunity to receive in a very
specific way some of the same
information she received.
And is that connected to her too? Is
that because tangentially? Yeah. Because
I remember in the private session you
told me she's one of my guides. Yes.
Tangentially. Thank you very much. Well, thank you.
Thank you very much. Well, thank you.
Shooting from a particular angle, not
directly connected but on the side.
Hey, hello
Bashar. Uh, I wanted to thank you.
You've said a lot of times to follow
your excitement and you'll get
everything you need and Oh, I have said
that. Yeah. Oh, all right. Thank you for
reminding me.
And uh I
was afraid that if I did my painting all
the time, I spent a lot of time by
myself. And I put myself totally into that in
And I put myself totally into that in
the last couple of weeks and just kept
painting, kept going places alone. I
felt closed off from almost everybody I
know whenever I try and get in touch
with people. I didn't connect with them
at all. And really wonderful things
ended up happening from that because I
found that wherever I went, I had
whatever I needed in the form of
companionship and friends. Yes. Which
was kind of what you just said to her.
Um I I'd go way far away from here and
I'd have a feeling like I wish I had
somebody to talk to at dinner or
something. and all of a sudden I'd meet
somebody that I knew and it's just
happened one thing after another. Yes.
The ecstatic explosion of synchronicity.
That's the way life works. When you let
it work that way, everything is
connected to everything else. And when
you proceed with that attitude and that
focus, you cannot help but see
occurrence after occurrence of what you
call co- incidents, not accidents,
co-incidence crop up over and over and
over again in your life. Because when
you are a particular
vibration, you allow all other things of
that vibration to come to the surface
and to make themselves known.
We thank you very much for your boldness
and your willingness to have the
conviction to reflect to yourself who
and what you desire to be. You will
always be supported in that action.
Thank you. I I really believe that now
and I know it's really true. Thank you.
You see that is why we always tell all
of you we cannot prove it to you. You
must prove it to yourselves. But we can
guarantee it will always work. That's
all we can do. Guarantee it
100%. But we can't prove it to you. You
have to do the proving yourself by
taking the steps. But it will always
work. Well, after I was going through all
Well, after I was going through all
those experiences, when I came here last
week after uh we were done, a man came
up to me and he was from New Zealand and
he had asked you a question about
electromagnetic energy and I talked with
him and his friend and he felt very
strongly that there was something like
that he should talk with me about and we
talked a little bit and we kind of had a
feeling maybe it was some kind of
Japanese um path life kind of thing or something,
um path life kind of thing or something,
but we weren't real sure. So, I wanted
to ask you if there was any if you would
know what that was. All we can tell you
is to some degree, yes, but that's all
we can tell you. It is up to you to
discover some of these things, not up to
us to outline the entire idea. We do not
want to unwrap your presence for you.
Well, is there any particular thing that
I should do or um What does your
imagination excite you to do?
Is there any particular thing you would
like to do that stands out more than any
other with regard to this idea of
awakening within yourself those
vibrations that will allow the
information you require to come in? What
is your imagination suggested that you
could do? Well, the only thing I thought
of because he went back to New Zealand
was to write to him. Write him a letter.
Anything else?
I have a suggestion. Yes, you can write
yourself one, too.
Send it off to your higher self and
receive the reply in your dreams or in
your physical life.
Okay. All right. Thank you. Just a
suggestion. You can invent whatever way you wish.
You can invent whatever way you wish.
The whole idea is to understand that you
can be in communication with yourself if
you simply initiate it like you
initiated everything else. Okay?
Understand? Yes. Use whatever
methodology your imagination comes up
with that excites you the most. The
excitement vibration is what is
important and will put you on the
appropriate level to understand all you
need to understand. Okay, I got it.
Sounds like fun. Yes. Yes. Yes. Thank
you. So go and ring some bells.
Thank you Bashar. Hello and good day.
Good day. How are you? I'm perfect. And
you? I am perfect. Thank you. Okay. I
have a I would like to share something
and in connection with that I would like
to ask a question more right um few
months ago just after the intensives.
Hey uh Steve asked who would like to
facilitate some of the intensives on
tapes and I was very excited about it
and some of us got together and uh uh it
kind of dragged out and dragged out and
then a few weeks ago to get my feet wet
I had a small group of people very small
about four people and I did some of the
tapes and that was very exciting. Oh
very good. It's wonderful. What took you
so long?
Well, I what took me so long was that I
had a workshop scheduled with with Steve
and then somehow I got cold feet and
Steve was on a trip and anyway cold feet
and on a trip. All right.
And uh now uh I have we have one
scheduled for November 5 and 6 and there
seems to be very little response and I'm
wondering whether you can give us some
awareness insight. Is that the wrong
timing? Is it the wrong format? Is it
something that we should do differently?
I'm not sure what's happening. Well, all
we can suggest at this time is to not
necessarily expect that the response
must come a very long time prior to the
time you have announced you will do it.
The response can be immediate almost to
the moment of the time you will do it.
It does not necessarily have to give you
that much forewarning because the more
you all live in the moment, the more
spontaneous your interactions and
gatherings will become. So what you're
saying it's still appropriate to do that
with our excitement. If you believe that
that time is appropriate for you and you
are really excited about that timing
then simply radiate it put it out and
attract whatever you do attract. Okay.
Is up to you. Thank you. Well thank you
very much for being so bold. Thank you.
Shooting.
Good evening Bashar to you. Good night.
I haven't seen you since Hawaii to speak
to you. So, I'd like to say aloha newi
kako. All right. Thank you. I also have
a suggestion for the sound. Yes. How
about the sound of silence and spell it
s i g h. Oh, thank you.
How very sweet is the sound you make.
Thank you. I want to share with you
something that happened a couple of
weeks ago. Share with all. Speak up. Be
bold. I'll try. Don't try. Okay, you can
do it. Okay. Um, several weeks ago, I
had a dream in which I entered a
structure. And inside the structure was a large
And inside the structure was a large
pond. And then I realized it wasn't a
structure really. It was made of
boulders and rocks. All right. And that
the pond was larger than I had first
perceived. There was a a large boulder
in the middle of it. All right. And as I
stood there watching, I saw two boulders
being lifted simultaneously. And they
were tied to the same rope, but they
were so immense that I didn't see how
one rope could hold them both. And one
was large and the other was small. And
as I watched, the boulders were heaved
over into the
center of the crater and they sunk
against the cone that was sticking up
and they bounced and bounced all the way
down. And there was no crane and no
perceptible way of this being having
just tossed them out into the center of
the crater. And as I watched them going
down, I looked into the water and it was
so clear. It was so clear. You could see
everything. And I thought, I would love to get into
And I thought, I would love to get into
that water and feel it around me. And
did you? No. Oh, why not? Well, I'll
explain. Oh, all right.
As I heard the boulders bumping down the
side of the mountain, I realized that
the pond was much deeper than I had
originally perceived.
And as the boulders fell through space,
they were being transformed and honed
and they were um becoming less boulders
and more some other type of material.
And as they got toward the bottom of the
pond, they were utterly transformed from
boulders into crystallin objects much as
a plain piece of glass is transformed
into into the ocean tumbling. Okay,
guys. I wanted to enter this water and go down
I wanted to enter this water and go down
there and see more closely what it
was, but I kind of had the feeling that
if I did, Yes. I wouldn't want to come
back. The wall, right?
And then I realized that it was not
actually water that I was looking into.
It was liquid crystal. Very good. And
that I was not on the edge of a crater.
I was on the edge of a universe. Yes.
And I was gazing down
into another time and another place.
Yes. Did it feel exciting? H. It's still
Did it feel exciting? H. It's still
exciting. No. All right. What do you
wish to do with this perception of
energy? The same thing that I wanted to
do in Hawaii when you had me bang on the
Quan statue. No. I want to go there, but
I didn't want to go there by myself cuz
I had a feeling I might not want to come
back. You're not alone. All right. The
city has crystal
buildings and the atmosphere and the
beings there are familiar. Yes. And I
see uh
uh
my home. All right. And I feel at home
there. All right. You are also at home
where you are. Oh yes. But it was a very
strange feeling and I can
see Oh, I can see things now I didn't
see then. All right. You are perceiving
right through the gate
into an aspect of what you would call a
type of causal
plane. It is a direct view into one of
what we as a civilization have begun to
research that we call the quasiplanar
realities. Because of your particular bent, because
Because of your particular bent, because
of your particular perspective, what you
did is
blend two
symbologies that
are different aspects, different
representations of the same
energy. In your Hawaii area, the energy
is referred to as
kahuna. In your American Indian area, it
is referred to as katina. Yes. It is the
same energy. Yes. And now I do not mean
to be flippant. This is simply being
used to explain in the most practical
way. Oh, so to speak, in the way you
will understand most quickly what you
were viewing to some degree was another
dimensional energy reality that you
interpreted to some degree as a town, as
a city.
It was in a
sense on the outskirts, if you will, of
what could be called capacina
town. Energy beings of light and pure
consciousness that are in and of
themselves the very
fabric that create the dividing line
between all the different universes that
you perceive as different universes.
Within creation, you looked into the
very crystallin substance that gives
form to all the different universes you
would call physically material. The
crystallin pool of energy symbolized in
your dream in that way. The very
essence of the primal energy out of
which all material reality is solidified
or
crystallized. Understand?
I'm you are looking into the raw astral
state of your collective consciousness.
The template city, the template world
you all inhabit in a sense all the time
and from which you channel the energy
that solidifies your experience of
yourself as a physical
reality. Understand?
I'm processing. All right, let me put it
in another way. I do not mean the
terminology literally as the way these
words in your society used to mean, but
it may explain the idea a little
bit. You saw the dream version of your
entire world. the collective mass dream version
world. the collective mass dream version
of your world out of which each of you
individually choose the life patterns
and styles you will with your beliefs,
emotions and thoughts crystallize into
physical materiality. Oh, understand
that explains something. You are in the
raw plastic state of consciousness. Yes.
Out of which you crystallize everything
you call physical.
Does that clarify to some degree? Yes,
it does. And it also clarifies something
else. While I was there in this place,
um I recognized my spiritual partner.
That's and I know that we are here this
time to accomplish certain soul
commitments that we have made to this
time. And I had the feeling that as you
had told me in Hawaii rather than coming
from a very ancient ancient
culture that brought a particular tone,
a particular sound to this planet rather
than going back to that ancient
historical culture that this was future
because to some degree it looked to me
as if it were in the future rather than
in the past. Yes. And the reason,
another reason I shared it with you in
that way was to allow you to remember
that the whole idea is not to quote
unquote recapture what you believe was
in your past, but to create what you
desire representative of the idea of the
past in the present
now. Understand? Yes. That that
vibration is the world as you can create
the world to be now.
Does that serve you? Oh, it serves all
of us. Bashar. Well, well, thank you. I
thank you. Thank you for your
co-creation. I do. And I thank you for
my nickname. I used pine trees this
time, but you'll excuse me for that. You
know who I am. Thank you very much.
Well, thank you. Shedding.
Hi, Bashar. And to you, good day. Good
day. Um, I put my name in just sort of
as a lark. A lark? But I thought it'd be
fun to talk to you. I haven't talked to
you for a while. There is one thing that
I have um thought about in the last few
days. Uh a lot of one thing in a few
days. All right.
Lots of things. But one thing that I
thought I'd like to discuss with you or
see what you have to say about that. A
lot of times you will say to people uh
once you have recognized something as a
habit, it's not a habit anymore. Yes.
And I for one have one habit which I
dislike quite a bit. All right. Which is
very bad which I've known was a habit
for for years. All right. Why do you
keep doing it then? I don't know. Uh I
don't I have quotes tried many different
um techniques to not to do it anymore.
Oh. All right. And I keep doing it. Oh.
All right. And I know it's a habit there
and and I still do it. All right. So I
don't really agree with you that Oh,
thank you. Once once you recognize
something as a habit, it's not a habit
anymore. Could you recognize the full
statement we have made? Okay. Once you
recognize it is a habit, it is no longer
a habit. And you can then recognize you
do not have to keep doing it
unless you either keep choosing to do it
or use it as an excuse to continue to do
it or do not really believe you have the
capability of stopping it. That is the
full statement. Okay.
So, do you, if I may ask, really believe
you have the capability of redefining
yourself to become the person that does
not contain that habit? Well, I yeah,
that's one technique I tried. Uh, let me
tell you what it is and I'm not at all
proud of it. I don't like it at all, but
I have found that sometimes when I talk
about it, especially in a big crowd, uh,
that does reverse things sometimes. Then
this may be your technique now. Uh
anyway, the habit is that I wake up uh I
sleep like an hour and a half, two hours
at a time. Then I wake up and I smoke.
Yes. And then I go back to sleep and I
wake up and I smoke. Yeah. And um so I
smoke throughout the night which is
terrible. Do you enjoy it? Well, yeah. That's Yes,
Do you enjoy it? Well, yeah. That's Yes,
I do. All right. Why? I don't know.
Well, you don't? No. I'm sure it's
because it's it's a physiological
addiction. Well, one moment. One moment.
Don't be too sure.
Why do you enjoy it if you do? Because
it's a habit. Not necessarily. Part of
part of it is that um I I often do it
halfconsciously. I just wake up and I
don't think the way I do the way I think
during the day. Oh, right. And so, and
if in that
state you automatically smoke, what does
it do for you?
I guess it fulfills some kind of need
that my body has, you know, for nicotine
and then I go back to sleep. All right.
But let's not think about it for now
physiologically. What does the act
itself do for you
atmospherewise, as you say?
I never thought about that. Well, think
about it now.
Um, what kind of mood does it create?
What kind of mood does it help to
reinforce, to
perpetuate? Is it one of
contemplation? Does the smoke to some
degree symbolize your very
thoughts? H does it seem to be your way
of meditating?
Maybe. Maybe if it that is what it does for
Maybe if it that is what it does for
you, it may in your terminology not be
as negative as you think. Maybe not for
you. Remember, every individual is different.
Remember, every individual is different.
And certain things that may even be
generally negative within the consensus
reality does not necessarily have to be
negative for everyone depending on how
you use it. Many individuals can
transform what may be negative to the
general population into something that
has no negative effect on them.
How are your lungs?
Uh well, surprisingly good considering
for so many years. Surprisingly good.
All right. Then maybe it simply doesn't
right. Then maybe it simply doesn't
affect you that way because you don't
buy into it that way. And maybe that's
why it's all right for you to continue
to do something that actually is
representative of your way of meditating
and not necessarily has to be thought of
as a negative habit. What about that?
Well, that's that's possible except that
I do fall asleep with cigarettes in my
hands and I burn my night and burn
myself. Then perhaps just a slight
variation of the
idea is all that is really necessary
more than an absolute transformation of
it. Perhaps allow yourself to simply put
the cigarette out first. I've thought
about that. The idea is perhaps that if
you do have a different attitude about
it, you may allow yourself to be a
little more conscious and conscientious
of exactly how you are using it and will
allow the timing and your awareness of
what you need to do with it to be done
in a more natural way. For if you are
coming from the point of view that it is
something you shouldn't be doing, then
you may not be paying attention to the
natural timing of it. and the natural
timing of it may give you in no
uncertain terms the absolute signal as
to when to put it out. Uh-huh. For you,
it may be an extension of something you
have done in the past, smoking the peace
pipe. Yeah, we've talked about that once
before. Mhm. So, if you can use it in a
similar fashion, it can be an act of
meditation. It can, as many of you say,
be your version of prayer because that
is what the smoke from the American
Indian peace pipe represents. Prayer
spirit. Interesting. So look at it that
way and see if that makes a difference.
Yeah. You know, something just just
happened. Now I've noticed many times
when we talk that that I do get things
at different levels without realizing it
or or I realize it later that night or
something like that. And I just a few
minutes ago just got I just felt it. It
was very nice. Thank you. And also
remember one other thing we have talked
about regarding symbols and physical
ideas and
action. When you allow a symbol to serve
the purpose you actually have designed
it to serve. When you give it the
definition, when you recognize the
definition you actually have given it,
that's when you may not need it any
longer. and then it will transform. In
continuing to apply the assumption that
it automatically must be negative just
because of the way it looks on the
surface, you have not allowed yourself
to recognize perhaps what the real
definition and purpose of that
particular act was and therefore could
not allow it to change because you had
not identified it for what it was to
begin with. Understand? Yes, I do. Thank
you very very much. Thank you very much.
See if that makes a difference. Thank
you. It will. Bye-bye. Thank you.
shutting.
Hello, Mr. Ambasso Matt.
Hello, Mr. Ambassadorable.
Thank you very much. I I was wondering
if you would um pick up on the reverse
and call me Mr. Diploor.
Another variation.
A very deep probing incisive question
for you tonight. Oh, all right. Surgical
precision about to take place.
Do you have any money writing on the
World Series? No.
No.
Actually, I don't really have a a big
question or anything, but I I have been
fascinated by um the perturbations in
our um status quo. All right. Status
quo. Yes. Our earthquake a month ago or
so. And um and then your economy quake.
Yes. Yes. Exactly.
And um everything is being shaken up.
Yeah. I was really
fascin Oh, just another major economic
upheaval. [Applause] [Applause]
[Music]
Just another symbol rearranging itself
again. Yeah. And I got the feeling of people
Yeah. And I got the feeling of people
were going, "Hey, we can have these
large perturbations without the sky
falling in, so to speak." And oh, now we
can relax because it's not going to
happen disastrously again. Very good.
Yeah. So, uh I think this is the year
for that, isn't you? You said something
like that, didn't you? Yes. what you
call your 87 has been in many ways the
convergence and the year of
manifestation and recognition. Your year
of 88 if we can apply any label to it at
all could be the year of conviction.
Yeah. As a result of seeing these
perturbations.
Oh. Oh. Conviction. Oh.
As a result of seeing these
perturbations not be disastrous. Yes.
Yeah. Okay. Thank you. Any any um quote
unquote prediction for Halloween in
terms of um a perturbation in some other
area? Just the story that we have to share
Just the story that we have to share
next week of your time. Oh, that's going
to be that might sh
an Apache gold crystal sphere that came
to me. I had it for two weeks and then I
manifested it being lost. Oh, all right.
Okay. um a pink purple lavender leitomite
um a pink purple lavender leitomite
quartz something else and it also
something else. Yeah, I don't know what
it's called. Pink pink something. A pink
something. Yes. All right. And the third
and uh
turquoise zony mountain lion fetish.
Yes. And so Okay. So, the first two came
to me and then they both like have been
lost or they're not lost. They know
where they are. Okay.
[Music] All right. Okay. I don't know. Did you
All right. Okay. I don't know. Did you
discover about yourself when you had
them in your physical possession? What
did they in that sense reflect to you?
[Music] Um, well, each one something kind of
Um, well, each one something kind of
different. Yes, of course. Okay. The
power. Power. Your own power. Yes. Yeah.
And so, okay. Do you need them to
continue to reflect the power or can you
use it now without the triggers? Okay.
That's this other thing that's coming up
with me now. I last like week or seven
days I've been
[Music] like I didn't quite catch that.
like I didn't quite catch that.
That's just what it's it's felt like.
Like
just just this growling
just and I've been having these when I
meditate. Very interesting sound.
Very interesting sound.
Yeah. And that's that's why when you
when you said that when you were talking
it was this a little before about animal
sounds and sounds and that's just been
what's been happening to me. How does it
feel? It feels like like I want to
just like climb on walls and and
just like that and it's just I like that
and I need to do that. I can't sometimes
just want to,
you know, and right now it's like I'm
embarrassed.
It was a wonderful performance. [Music]
[Music]
Now, now that energy, that
energy, to what use do you wish to put
that
energy besides the growling?
Um, it'll be put in in in my
performances and my theater somehow. Um,
all right. And I'm sure it'll it'll come
when I start when it when it'll when
it's time to come or something. Yes.
Yes. Absolutely.
And so and so. Okay. Okay. So So I was
laying in in the bathtub also and
Okay. Just a reminder. Yeah. To all of
you, one of the strongest meditation
boos you have.
Your bathtub andor your shower. How many
times have you been inspired within
them? Yeah. Yes. Okay. So, I was laying in the
Yeah. Yes. Okay. So, I was laying in the
bathtub and and then that's when and I
had, you know, this this this green mal
mold mold detectite something. I can
never pronounce these names for these
crystals on my
Yeah. Okay. on my on my brow here. And
then in a quartz on my like around my
heart around my solar plexus. Okay. And
then in the meditation, that's when like
I I saw my my arms become like these
paws. And first I I I my body like went
to this angle and I got the picture of
this mountain lion laying on this big
rock. And then I I felt her and then I
looked and my hands just like started
going in like this paw shape and I could
feel from my shoulders to my arms the
hands and and the way it felt as a lion
and everything. And and then and that's
when I started like just doing these
growls and and all this stuff. And then
since half of my ears were underneath
the water when I would make these like I
would take these sides like we were
doing going and underneath the water there's
going and underneath the water there's
like these different levels like you'll
hear the uh and then behind like about
two or three I'm talking about like from
a feeling level I got this image this
real pure sound like Abraham's bowls
that I had that go
[Music] And so and so and so you have found a
And so and so and so you have found a
way to very powerfully center and
energize yourself. Okay. Yes. Okay.
Oh, really? Okay. Okay. All right. But
see, I I guess I'm trying to get there.
There's something that's coming with
this with the fetish. Okay. I got lost.
I was driving down the street. I got
lost. And I knew there was a reason I
got lost. I looked up. There was this
this Indian museum. And I went inside
and I had had a dream about an object
like a few months ago and it was this
side of this profound in the dream. I
couldn't identify it. I didn't know what
the heck it was until I went in there
and I and I saw it and I just like just
you know okay so so so what what is
this? I mean well okay I know what it is. What
I mean well okay I know what it is. What
is it? It's just a power symbol. It is
you connecting into many more aspects of
your being. Both what you would call
path life, spirit guides, your own
center of power, the place from which
you can come to do anything and
everything you want to do. You're
identifying with the power of your
natural self even as the animals do.
Even as you did when you connected in
other lives to the American Indian
culture that knows that still that can
connect into that level of nature into
the very fundamental primal cord of
existence and from that center of being
can transform and create anything you
desire. That's what you have discovered.
Now use it in whatever way you want to.
Okay? Do what excites you the most. You
are in that sense unstoppable.
Yeah, I know. I just ask this one more
thing. Vincent, are you okay?
The other Okay. So, I've been talking to
the these trees lately and and they
really they really, you know, they talk
and I and I can feel how like I'll let
it go so far where it's like
comfortable. I still think I have some
kind of mental control over it. And then
and then I'll let myself go to a point
where I'll feel like like my body
doesn't feel it feels disformed and and
I could actually like I could feel
myself crossing over a barrier or
something like into this like
natural. You are all these things. All
of you. You are all these things.
Physical reality is made of your
consciousness. You are all these things.
They are you. They are aspects of you,
reflections of you. Why should you not
feel like
them? You can be and are anything you
wish. You will always be centered in
whatever your intention is. You will
never lose yourself. Okay? You will
always know your identity. It is only a
misconception on the part of what you
have been trained to think that the more
you blend with the infinite, the more
your individuality suffers. And that's
not so. It's just the opposite. The
stronger an individual you become, the
more you discover
yourself in all those things.
Understand? Yeah. Does that help you?
Yeah. So flow with it and use it as the
individual you choose to be. You are
never out of control. Even if you create
the scenario that makes it seem as if
you are, you're still controlling that,
so play and enjoy and express and
create. That's what you're there to do,
right? So have fun. Thanks. Thank you.
One moment within what you call the next
moment within what you call the next
three days. Let's say the next three
dream times.
See what doors you have opened within
this interaction and see what else comes
that will accelerate you into an
unexpected direction. [Music]
[Music]
Sharing. Hello Bushar. And who you good
there? I wondered if you could tell me um when
I wondered if you could tell me um when
that special someone will come into my
life. Do you mean that special someone
or that special someone or what about
that one? Any other? What about the one
right there? The special soulmate.
Special soulmate.
Are you aware of some of the things we
have already discussed about this idea?
I'm not sure. All right. Do you
understand what our definition of a
soulmate is? I don't know. This is my
first time here. All right. Mine too.
In that sense,
recognize every relationship, I will be
brief, every
relationship serves a purpose, is there
for a reason on the fundamental level
because you are always learning what you
need to learn about
yourself in any relationship and are
being of service to the other individual
in that relationship to allow them to
learn what they need to learn about
themselves to grow and change. Every
relationship is a relationship with a
soulmate on the fundamental sense of the
word. Understand so far? Yes.
Now we know what you often mean in your
society by the idea of a soulmate and
that does exist. However, more often
than not, we have discovered that in
your society the attitude will usually
be as follows. That if only you could
discover your soulmate, then everything
would be just wonderful. But not until
then. Your physical reality is the product of
Your physical reality is the product of
your strongest definitions and your
strongest beliefs. If you believe you
are incomplete without that person, you
will usually wind up only attracting
someone to reflect your belief in your
own incompleteness. When you know you are
incompleteness. When you know you are
complete unto yourself that you will not
change and grow. But as you are, you are
still a whole idea and your first
relationship is to yourself and with the
infinite. When you act in that manner
and radiate that frequency, that's when
you give off the vibration that gives
someone else in your life that you may
have made an agreement with to come into
your life to reflect back to you as an
equal the vibration you are already
putting out. If you already shine as the
out. If you already shine as the
brightest light you can, then someone on
the same level as a mirror as all of you
are to each other can reflect that light
back to you. The brightest light that
can be reflected back to you can only be
as bright as the light you are.
Understand? I understand that is what
you typically call the soulmate. And it
can exist in your reality. It doesn't
always have to be a single individual,
but it can be.
Thank you. Oh, thank you very much.
Shy. Hi, Mich. Hi. I know you've taken
some time before in the past to diagram
your own scout ship. And I know that we
did a meditation once where um we all
went onto the mother ship and went
around and explored. Yes. Um but I
wanted to know if tonight you would just
take a few moments and just diagram a
little bit one of the mother ships and
what the different sections are for. And
um I I know that each one might even be
different, but if you could pick one.
Well, we will use the same one we have
used before that in your terminology
would translate out into the name of the
solar wind. Okay. It is approximately
one of your miles in length almost just
about and the idea is it will be a
cylinder in four generally speaking and
will have many decks within it. But
those decks are also in your terms
cylindrical. a cylinder within a
cylinder within a cylinder within a
cylinder and so on for approximately
what you would call 30 cylinders
within. What this will be is that you
can then circumn the entire cylinder on
any level all the way around and then
decks are aortioned accordingly to
different sections. In that sense, there
are approximately what you would call
three main engines that bridge all
decks. one in the center and two near either
one in the center and two near either
end. These are also cylindrical or
discshaped in fashion and in that sense
are cavernous bridging all decks what
you would call a 60deck
cross-section. The idea therefore being
that there are 30 cylinders which means
you have from the outer skin down to the
center core 30 decks and then of course
a repeat of the 30 decks from the center
core out to the other
side. The center is where all the
engines are connected and in the very
center there will be what you would call
a non-inhabitable space all the way
through the central core of the ship
that will be the drive mechanism in
colloquial terms.
at either end in also a cylindrical
fashion is what you would call
colloquially your bridge at either end
in the very outer shell will be what you
call the hanger bay for various scout
crafts that come and
go there will be the idea once again
also of manufacturing of many of these
scout craft in that outer hole
the ideas also will contain in the outer
hall many different forms of environment
to accommodate many different life forms
from many different civilizations.
Why just the outer one? Because it is
the easiest access. As a ship enters the
hull, obviously the first deck they hit
is the outer one. So they can then
simply propel their craft right into an
environment and step right out of their
craft at home. Understand? Yes.
Then as you progress toward the center
of the ship, you will find there will be
many different levels and decks that are
relegated to various form of exploratory
enterprise, as you would call it,
research in that sense. There are also
vast arrays of open space that are
relegated to very park-like atmospheres
where we enjoy the idea of nature and in
that sense bring it with us.
The idea is also that there will be many
levels simply for
experiencing different environments to accommodate
different environments to accommodate
different beings to shift from one
environment to another as they may
choose to do. These might be called
pressure chambers in a sense although it
is not exact as you mean the term. There
will also be the idea of the
communication stations that we have
called in very very colloquial terms,
not literal at all. The communication
stations we have termed the chapels in
that sense which are rooms, chambers of
crystallin formation that allow an
individual to be touched directly in
with the infinite. There will also be
what you would call amplification
modules that allow individuals to tap
into specific frequencies of different
dimensions for the purpose of some of
the channelings as you call them that go
on in this form of communication. For do
remember that the most natural receiver
device is already living beings.
The idea also is that certain other
decks will
contain many of the ideas that you would
call leisure activities in that sense
where individuals may simply play. And
there are whole simulated environments
in that way that individuals can create
simply by a connection to the main
computer of their consciousness and can
explore different realms in that way.
almost as if they were literally in your
terms physically visiting those
dimensions able to exist in those
atmospheres without actually existing
physically within them. You understand?
Mhm. There will also be what you would call
There will also be what you would call
the association council chambers wherein
can be the projection of many different
levels of consciousness to gather in
meetings as it were to understand the eb
and the flow of the organization and the
communication that goes on between the
hundreds of worlds of the
association. There will also be the
creation of
experimental as you call it
environments. environments we have not
encountered per se, but environments
that we can create in that sense to
explore and experiment with the many
ways that the universe can manifest
itself. Large and vast areas are given
over to the creation of entire ecologies
on the ship so that we may understand
the full workings of any particular
planetary society by literally
recreating vast areas of their entire
ecosystem. Would you have any earthlike?
Yes, you do.
Yes. And on the solar wind, as on Essani
itself, there are a few dolphins.
[Music] There will be a few other ideas, a few
There will be a few other ideas, a few
other chambers whose purpose in that way
will not necessarily be that easy nor
brief to describe.
Okay, this is sufficient. Thank you very
much. Thank you very much. Thank you
very much.
Shy. Yes, I'm coming. Oh, what? I'm
sure. I'm Frankie. Hello, Frankie. Um,
the mic up, will you? Oh, that's right.
I'm tall. I'm tall and I'm Frankie. All
right. And I've just No. Okay. Almost
all of you are most probably taller than
I am.
um they they talk about how you teach
best what you most need to learn and and
all of that. So I I feel that perhaps
relationships is the area that I've come
in to have as an area of expertise.
Sometime I hope in the near future you
what I hope. Hope. Okay. That means you
I hope. Hope. Okay. That means you
doubt. Um apparently that's probably one
of the reasons why I'm asking questions.
Oh, can you all hear this person?
Okay. Speak louder. Speak louder. Okay.
Be bold. Yes. Um the thing in my entire
life that's excited me the most is a
relationship that I'm in right now. All
right. And um by following that
excitement, I found like some of the
most incredible teachings in my life and
wonderful feedback. Yes. Now there are
What do you wish to do with that
information? Uh I'd like
to be as clear as I can possibly be
about it. Yes. so that I can have the
clearest relationship possible and be
able to share that with others. All
right. And I feel like um some clarity
is still necessary. I still have in what
area? Okay.
um in the way that the relationship
seems to show up on the surface, there
still seems to be some dichotomy in that
it is the relationship that I want to
have and would like to have for what I
can see to be an eternity or through
this lifetime. A wall, right? Um
different different feedback from what
he says it is to what I say it is yet
not really different in the
manifestation of the relationship. So I
want to understand why there seems to be
the dichotomy. Um I guess I want to know
that the relationship is all that I have
seen it to be and believe it to be. The
relationship is anything you create it
to be. Uh in some ways I must feel that
I don't have all of the skills to be
able to do that. Maybe. But what skills
do you think you need other than the
living of your life
to the fullest?
[Music] Well, I guess I feel like I want to have
Well, I guess I feel like I want to have
the clearest communication skills. All
right. And can you imagine what those
might be?
Um, I'm starting to think about it in
terms of energies and uh kind of a
knowing acceptance. All right. You mean
a trust? Yeah. A knowing acceptance
doesn't necessarily mean, however, that
you settle for something you do not
prefer. Right. Understand?
And that also means that you are willing
to allow whatever changes do occur to
happen. Uh the first again first relationship is
Uh the first again first relationship is
with you to yourself. Right? Now
sometimes a single individual you may
have a man in agreement with to reflect
the idea back to you for the duration of
what you call your lifespan. Sometimes
not. Sometimes many individuals.
Sometimes both. Mhm. It will depend.
Well, I I'm most interested in this
particular one for now. Yeah. And it may
be the idea that can manifest for the
duration of the lifespan. Uhhuh. But
first and foremost, if you know that is
so, then allow whatever is happening
within it to be representative of what
needs to be in the relationship, but
only to the point where it is not in
that sense an absolute polarization of
what you prefer to experience in your
own reality.
Right. Okay. Well, it's a somewhere in
between right now. So, I'm Well, are you
still learning? I am still learning.
Then continue to do so because that's
what any relationship is for. Right.
Plain and simple. And if you are going
to be with this individual, as you say,
for a long time in your terms of time,
then there are simply going to be the
opportunities to learn many and varied
subtle things. Yes. Enjoy the path. You
are getting out of it at any given
moment. Obviously, what you need to get
out of it if that's where you prefer to
be. Okay. Well, one of the aspects that
I'm curious about is how I can take
action according to what excites me.
Yes. And um still be
respectful of whatever space that he
might want to have in his life. Do you
trust the relationship?
Still here. All right.
Then in that sense, take whatever action
represents what really excites you. Mhm.
But also at the same time recognize that
if another individual is not ready or
willing to receive a particular
communication from you in the way that
you are ready to give it then trust that
that is also a part of the timing. Okay.
Are there keys that I might have in
terms of some of the aspects that I've
been working with energetically to um be
able to understand better how to
communicate in the moment uh more
lovingly more respectfully
um how to make communication over a
distance even though the distance seems
to exist
um and I don't have access to talking to
him or seeing him every day or being
with him all the time in that way but
you are always connected right so are
there keys keys to knowing that and
utilizing the space to actually expand
upon my energies or my ways of
communicating. One way would be to
express yourself in many different ways
as well. Uh-huh. Is there any other
service that excites you to be doing it?
Outside of the relationship or within as
you mean it outside the relationship.
Um, it will all be a part of the
relationship, but as you typically mean
it, yes, outside the relationship. Okay.
Um, yeah, I I would like to take all
that I've assimilated and be able to
communicate it to people. And I feel um
then as you do so, and as you form an
outlet for communication in that way,
you will continue to learn the things
you need to learn to recognize the
timing within the relationship more
precisely. It must be expressed in both directions.
It must be expressed in both directions.
Yes. Understand? Then it will be a full
circle. Mhm.
So that's where I should put my
attention. I'm not going to tell you you
should. That would be a good place to if
I I would suggest that it will allow you
to be more well-rounded. Uhhuh. And
therefore give yourself more capability
of recognizing the timing on either
side. Okay. Understand? I I feel a little time
Okay. Understand? I I feel a little time
pressured with the holidays cuz my sense
or my excitement tells me that I would
like to be with him during the holidays.
We understand that. But also pay close
attention to the idea that sometimes
there's a very fine line between the
energy that you actually are honestly
labeling excitement and when it becomes
anxiety and desperation.
Uhhuh. Because that's not really
excitement and you're being dishonest
with yourself if you call it that. Mhm.
Understand? So if I can get clear that
it's excitement, then maybe I can have
it. [Music]
[Music]
Merry Christmas. Thank you.
Thank you, Bashar. Frankie,
Shannon,
good evening, Bashar. And to you, good
day. Um, I came here to experience your
wisdom. I've never been here before.
Don't forget that you are experiencing
your own. Thank you. But we are only a
reflection of what you all already know.
And every time to us is the first time
as well. I did not put my name in to be
selected. And yet my name was called.
All right. And the only
thing the only thing that I can explain
this to is that you had some
communication that you wish to deliver
to me. So that is my question. What is
the communication you wish to deliver to
me? Nope. It will be the communication you
Nope. It will be the communication you
wish to deliver to yourself.
Now we will begin once again in the form
of the question. Are you doing in your
life what excites you the most?
I'm searching for what excites me the
most. When do you assume you might find
it?
Let me ask it another way. What would
you really like to be doing that you're
not doing?
Um, have you ever had any kind of a
fantasy? Well, a a
satis a satisfactory a satisfactory
primary relationship satisfactory
primary relationship. But as we have
already said that begins with you,
right? So, aside from that idea, in terms of
So, aside from that idea, in terms of
actually being of service, doing
something, what you typically call
making a living, what do you want to do
that you're not doing?
I want to
um spread out spread myself out to the
point where I I I feel that I have a a
good relationship with myself. Yes.
Okay. How do you express it in your
physical actions? In my physical
actions? Yes.
Um in terms of uh of living a life of
giving? All right. And does that excite
you? Yes. All right. And does it allow
you to feel in that sense that you are
infinitely abundant and can attract
everything you desire when you really
need it? When I'm living life that way?
Yes. All right. Are there times when you
do not live life that way? We all do. I
beg your pardon. I don't.
Please speak for yourself. There there
are there are times when I am I am not
constantly living a giving life. All
right. Would you prefer to constantly be
living a giving life?
Yes. Well, then why aren't you?
What definitions do you contain that
make it seem as if you must from time to
time not live in a full ecstatic way? Interesting concept.
Interesting concept.
Yes, I do.
Do you want to discuss it now or would
you like to ponder?
Um, I guess
it's it's looking inward.
And when you start looking inward,
you're not
um living a giving type life. Oh, no,
no, no, no. Looking inward is the key.
What must go along with it is doing
outward. Looking inward and acting
outward with that inner knowledge.
Even when you're acting on your own
wants. Yes. Why not? Okay. As long as you know
Yes. Why not? Okay. As long as you know
that you are doing so with full
integrity and that you deserve what you
desire, then why
not? Do you believe you deserve what you
desire? Definitely. All
right. Then do you believe you have a
clear definition of what it is you say
you desire?
Yes. All
right. Do you really honestly desire it?
Yes. All right.
Is your overall intention clear in
life? Your attitude, your approach,
it's becoming more clear. All right. And
are your actions clear? In other words,
do you act upon the opportunities at any
given moment that excite you the most
that you are capable of acting on?
Whether they appear to be connected to
what you think you want or not.
Um, I think I'm getting to that point
that I am. Yes. All right.
Then you are in that sense on the
threshold of creating what we would call
in ship technology a
flashover where you can simply
understand that any definition you
believe yourself to be most strongly
will be the reality you experience plain
and simple. But that a as you have
already understood the first
relationship is with yourself to
yourself to the infinite. And then the
idea of the relationship of yourself to
all other beings
equally by allowing the relationship you
are to all other beings to be equal.
That is how you are able to consciously
clearly choose any particular individual that
choose any particular individual that
represents a reflection you desire to
share. Many times when you place more
importance on one particular thing than
it deserves to have above and beyond
anything else in terms of devaluing
everything else. then you do not create
any quality that makes it easy for you
to pick and choose because not
everything's now on the same level.
When the thing you really
desire, even though the desire may make
it seem to be more important, and even
though that thing may be more
representative of who you are, that
doesn't mean that that desire and that
representation makes that particular
idea or object or person, place or thing
literally more important in a value
sense to any other thing that could
happen in your
life. When you equalize everything,
that's what gives you the greatest
ability to choose anything you want
because everything's on the same level.
You don't have to reach very far to get
it. It's all right here, right now,
right with you, right
within. You simply once again radiate an
idea and that's what you
attract. But many times if an individual
thinks they really need it, then they
are placing an undue importance upon it.
They are creating it to be a desperation
and that vibration is what keeps it at
bay. Understand? Yes. Is this being of
Understand? Yes. Is this being of
assistance so far? I think it's great.
Now, the idea of this primary
relationship, what do you imagine it
would be like? I've given up the idea of
of of projecting ideas. I'm just I'm at
the point where I've stopped projecting.
Why? Well, I've I've stopped projecting
ideas to the point where I'm reaching
out for one specific thing. And well,
you can still do that. All we are saying
is do it without invalidating everything
else. Okay. Do it recognizing that it
may be your preference. By all means,
allow yourself to
project. But what do you define the idea
to
be? How do you define primary
relationship? Well, I'm
I'm looking for a relationship that
would looking for someone who would be
an inequal reflection if as you say.
Yes. Um a reflection of what? What would
they be reflecting to you?
Well, someone to share a life with. Yes.
What would you be learning about
yourself in that interaction?
What I don't know, which is what
I I can't say what that is now. Oh, all
right. Fair enough.
If I did, I would know. Oh, but you see,
you do know.
You do know. On some levels, you do
know, right? In general, though, we are
not asking you for specifics. In general
categories, what would you be learning
about yourself by being in a
relationship? Would you be acting differently in that
Would you be acting differently in that
relationship than you are acting now?
Depends on the interaction. Probably
not. Of course. But depending on the
interaction, I would be growing. Yes, of
course. And uh you're always going,
right? But let's say right now, let's
say you were in that relationship.
What would the differences be? The
differences be I would probably be
living life at least at the present on
that constant exciting level that you
were talking about. All right. Then live
that way now and you can attract the
relationship more easily.
Good. Because if that's the way you will
be in the relationship and that's not
the way you constantly are now, be that
way constantly and the relationship
cannot help but be attracted into your
life. Because if that vibration is
representative of what the relationship
is, then be that
vibration and you'll have it. Live life
passionately every day. Yes. As we have
said, the most important thing of all is
the thing you're doing now.
Thank you. Well, thank you. Live in the
now. Live in the now. It's the only time
there is. It's the only place there is.
Right here, right now. When you live in
the now, anything else that's going to
happen in your life won't have any other
place or time to happen in except now
because you will not create there to be
any other place or time for it to happen
in
dreams to you. Thank you, Bashar. Well,
thank you very much for allowing us to
share and interact in a spontaneously
created way. At this time in and with
much joy, you may all participate in a
short break. We will resume contact in
approximately 10 to 15 of your minutes. [Music]
How's it going [Applause]
[Applause]
in the other room? [Music]
Oh, I'll say by the
way, some mother ships have the ability
to disassemble portions of themsel to
create whole planetary colonies if
necessary. shooting. [Music]
[Music]
Hello, Bashar. And who you good? I'm
hoping that you can give me some
insight. More hoping. All right. I am
hoping. Hoping. Hoping. Hoping. Yes.
Why? I have a wonderful daughter. A
wonderful daughter. Yes. And she has
been married for 11 years. Oh. All
right. And she has wanted a baby more
than anything in the world. More than
anything in the world. Right.
uh she had an operation to clear her
tube so that she could have a child. And
in the last 10 months, she's had three
major operations and ended up $10,000
poorer and no baby. Now she is very
weak, very depressed, all right. And can
you give me some insight as to why this
is happening to her? Maybe on the
harmonic convergence she was 35 years
old which is a seven completion the way
I understand it can be maybe maybe not
absolutely precisely meant in that way
in this particular vibrational case as
we sense it there may be other ideas as
well but can you answer some questions
on her behalf? Yes. Why does she want
the child? She's always wanted a child.
She's a motherly type. So she she loves
children. She that's her whole identity.
That is her whole identity. Well, it's
been very important to her. Why? Well,
probably because I was a motherly type
and my mother was a motherly type. My
mother had a hard time giving birth to
me and I had a hard time giving birth to
her. I see. And the it's like a spiral
of energy that keeps repeating itself,
getting worse every generation. So old
definitions that continue to be
reinforced from generation to
generation, right? All
right. Those definitions may be all that
creates the block in that sense as you
call it a
block. Does she really believe that it
must be that
difficult? Does she want to believe that
it has to be that difficult? No, I'm
sure she doesn't. All right. Has she
allowed herself the opportunity to get
in touch telepathically with the
consciousness that could potentially be
the child? I think she has uh she was
raised with the idea that we create our
own reality. Right. That she could bring
into her life whatever she However, she
may be under the assumption that she has
to do all the work.
Why not let the child help?
Mhm. How does she do that? Well, have a
How does she do that? Well, have a
conversation with it. Say, "Listen, I
need some help here.
I don't have to do this all by myself. I
made an agreement with
you." The child, of course, knows this,
being not a child at this time.
But now she doesn't have any tubes. So,
how can she have a child? She can. It is
still possible. It is still possible.
Yes. It may simply be that with each
successive generation you have created
what appears to be more and more and
more limitations and yet transform them
and transform them and transform them.
Perhaps now the strength of all of those
limitations is vested within her so that
she can create one of the greatest
transformations of all.
So she's breaking a karmic pattern. You
might Yes. In a sense. Yes.
Now, the idea in and of
itself of what you colloially call, and
I do not mean to in any way, shape or
form tie in what many of you have been
brought up to think of as religious
connotations. This is completely aside
from the main thrust of this idea that
we are about to share. Understand? Yes.
It is quite possible to have what you
typically call an immaculate conception.
An energy conception. Mhm. Understand?
That would be a tall order. if you say
so.
But that might be to some degree the
position she has placed herself in
knowing she can create it on some level.
That she is energy, that matter is
energy, and that the typical
routes within the body that usually are
what need to be followed to create any
particular physiological manifestation
that you call a birth. do not
necessarily completely apply
anymore. We would suggest some
inspiration for this
individual. There are available and
again not that they have to play out the
way this literature would indicate but
there is literature available on your
planet to indicate the idea of what
might be called energy births,
manifestations even sometimes that come
and go.
totally absolutely in your
terminology medically medically
checked
medically reinforced and
reinforced and
yet the birth can come and go. One
moment there is a child, the next moment
there isn't. Then the child is back
again and then it isn't. And then it is
and then it isn't. You mean physically?
Physically. That's That's a little hard for me to to
That's That's a little hard for me to to
believe. That's all right. You're not
having the baby. That's true.
You don't have to. Now, if this and I'm
sure this child already exists in a
sense, yes, as a consciousness, and
again, remember, it isn't a child right
now. All right. This being, yes, could
it appear through an adopted child? Yes,
it could. And that might be one of the
ways that the manifestation can occur.
Mhm. Just assume once again that no
matter what the circumstance is that has
come about, that does not have to be
looked at as a preventative. It can be
looked at as the way that determines the
route that will actually serve the best
of all concerns one way or another. And
it can be done in an adoptive fashion.
It can be done in an energy fashion. But
the idea is to be in touch with the
child and allow all that are involved to
participate in the recognition of what
is going on and why. When it is truly
allowed to be in touch, when the
information and idea for why the birth
is occurring is actually played out.
When the full understanding is there for
the reasons for the agreements, then it
will be and can be more obvious as to
exactly how those agreements can be
fulfilled. The expectation that they must be
The expectation that they must be
fulfilled in a certain way is usually
the only thing that causes in your
society any type of what you label to be
a block, an
expectation. So sometimes if you focus
so strongly on that particular
expectation and that's not really the
way that's indicative of the agreement
that's been made, you will create
circumstances in your life to show you
in no uncertain terms that the route is
different than you thought. Hence, as
you say, perhaps the cutting of the
tubes. Well, now I know it's not going
to be that
way. So, what other way could it be?
Now, perhaps I am pointing myself in a
direction that shows me there are other
ways it could manifest. Because if I
really feel the vibration and strongly
know it is representative of who I am,
then the manifestation must be there.
The agreement must be there. And all I'm
doing is showing myself that it is
probably most likely, most quickly, and
most easily available to occur in
another way other than the way I have
been taught it must occur. So what do
you think about petri dishes?
You know, put if you wish the idea
again, whatever attracts you the
strongest. But the idea is to get in touch with the
But the idea is to get in touch with the
consciousness first. First and do not
necessarily have to, as you say, stumble
around blindly.
Allow her in a meditative state to know
she can be in communication with that
consciousness. Relax. Send love and
receive the love within what you call a
maximum of 3 days of your time is all
that is necessary to receive in either a
dream communication or in some sort of
physiological synchronistic symbol. a
sign and a signal and a communication
from that being to let her know beyond a
shadow of a doubt what the route is that
the being can most easily
take. Understand? Yes. Thank you. A
coincidental signal will pop into her
life within 3 days time after she
centers within herself, sends
unconditional love to the being that can
be the child and then just opens up to
receive that love and receive the
information. Whether she immediately
recognizes what it is or not is not the
point. Let it come out. Know she has
received it and let it come to the
surface within the 3day span from the
point that she does that. Understand?
Okay. The unconditional love is what is
most important. So that isn't using
human will to create something. That in
a sense it is. Uhhuh. But the idea of
going with the flow is when you're in
control. The struggle to try and control
the surface idea is actually a
resistance to your flow, not a control.
True control is going with the flow
because everything in life is already
under your control.
Well, she always thought that, but then
this doesn't seem to be under her
control. But it is. It is only that the
definition of it has a particular
meaning to her and in that sense has
allowed her to believe she is thrown off
track because she is simply sidetracked
by the original meaning that has been
handed down from generation to
generation about the way she thinks it
has to happen. Again, remember no
circumstance has built-in meaning. You
supply the meaning. No matter how it
looks on the surface, it doesn't mean
anything when it happens in your life
until you assign a meaning to it. The
meaning you assign to the circumstance
is what determines what effect you get
out of it. So just because it looks on
the surface to be a certain way, you
don't have to automatically assume that
that's negative or difficult. Assign a
positive meaning to it. Well, there must
be a positive reason for it happening
this way and then you'll get the
positive effect of it. Very good. Thank
you. Thank you very much.
Sharing. One moment. One moment. Tell
her happy birthday.
Oh, and to also send that message to the
and to also send that message to the
being. Happy birthday. Happy birthday.
Very good. Shooting. Hello, Bashar. And
to you. Good day. Um, big pardon.
How's that? Okay, great. Um, as I told
Daryl earlier, I was representing myself
and someone else. So, it's her question
I'll I'll ask you first. Yes. Um her
name is Adrienne and she's been trying
very very hard uh for the last year to
make a job transition. Um she wants to
become a TV news writer. All right. And
does have some limited experience but
wants to get a more permanent job in
that industry. All right. Is that what
is most exciting to that being? Yes. Is
that being acting like a TV news writer
or is she still acting like someone who
is trying to become a TV news writer?
There is a vast difference in those
attitudes. Well, she's going to hear
this. I'm afraid she's going to kill me
for saying this, but it's the truth.
Yeah, she's uh
I won't tell her there's a videotape of
this. Um I believe she's still acting
like she's trying to be news. This in no
way, shape, or form is a condemnation
nor a blame. The idea simply is a matter
once again of the fact that your society
has created so many definitions that
sometimes they seem to be what you are
doing when in fact the definition you
are doing is not anything like what you
say you prefer. You think it is because
you think it's attached but it is its
own definition that really has very
little to do with the thing you actually
want to be. All the trying in the world
is not the doing of the thing. When you
finally do something, it's because you
finally did it, not because you tried to
do it. All the trying usually is simply
the time you think or believe is
necessary to allow yourself to really
believe you can finally do it.
The idea therefore to put it on very
simple terms is that your friend may
simply not be paying attention to the
fact that there may be many
opportunities she is not allowing
herself to take advantage of because she
does not necessarily think herself
capable of acting on those opportunities
because she is not yet the person she
wants to be. But the only way she'll be
that person is by starting to act like
that person now by doing the things that
person would do. By being that person as
we have shared many times and again this
will be brief. The idea is to use the
imagination as a tool in the following
way. If there is something you want to
be that you believe you're not, now
create the visualization of that person.
See the you you want to be and see that
you acting in the way you want to act,
doing the things you prefer to do. Then
connect and junction with it with all
your senses. Feel what it would be like
to be that person. Taste, smell, hear,
touch, everything. and have the attitude
of what it would be like to be that
person. Have the style of that person.
Do things in the way that person would
do, not in the way you're doing it now.
Then all you have to do is if there's
any circumstance or situation in your
life that you don't know how to handle
as the you are now, give that
circumstance and situation to the you in
your imagination, in your visualization,
in your picture, give that situation,
hand it over to the person you prefer to
be that you have created yourself to be
in your image of yourself. Then watch
what that person does with it. See how
their attitude is different from yours.
See how they handle it successfully. See
their boldness and their conviction. See
the excitement and the gusto as you say
with which they do that idea. See them
successfully transform it. Then do what
they did. And you'll get the same
result. That's what your imagination is
for. to create a mirror image of the you
you prefer to be and then have the
boldness and the conviction to act like
that you and you will create the same
vibration. You'll get the same
lifestyle. You'll get the same result.
That's how to use your imagination as a
blueprint as a template in that way. But
it takes a boldness and a conviction and
a willingness to understand that as soon
as you conceive of that image, that is
who you are. All you have to do is act
like it to get the same results. If
there is anything, any habit pattern,
any attitudinal approach that you would
be doing differently if you already were
that person, differently than way you
are doing it now, do it the way you
would do it if you already were that
person and you will be that person. What
you put out is what you'll get back.
Thank you.
Individuals always, always, always are a
100% energy. No more, no
less. If you are doing something that
you really want to do, 50% and something
you do not prefer, 50%, you cannot
expect any further manifestation of the
thing you really want to do more than
50%. It's simple
It's simple
mathematics. If you are hanging on to
something just to play it safe to have
something to fall back on just in
case, then you are not really trusting
the you say you prefer to be. You are
not really putting 100% of the idea in
the direction of the flow you want. I
guarantee as soon as anyone does, you
will get it.
If you believe you're ready for it,
that's another
idea. All it takes is an examination. As
we have already said to some degree, but
now I will put it in its original linear
form. What is the clear
intention? What is the clear definition
of what you want? What is the clear
desire? Do you really want it? What is
the clear deservability? Do you believe
you deserve to get it? If all of those
are clear, then act with clear action
upon whatever opportunities present
themselves that excite you the most at
any given moment. Whether they appear
connected to what you want or not, the
excitement tells you they are, and they
will get you where you need to go.
That's it. Thank you. Thank you. And
yours. Okay. Mine is uh I'm in the
process of producing a film. All right.
Um the script all by itself seems to be
drawing all the the needed personnel to
uh to make it. All right. The only thing
I can't seem to be able to get my hands
on is the funding.
Most mostly because I don't know where
to go for it. All right. Once again,
there are many forms of communication
and contact in literature and outlets
that you may simply not be aware of and
may not in your terms be taking
advantage of because they may appear to
be too obvious. But there are other
individuals that have already done what
you want to do, are there not? Quite a
few. Yeah. Why don't you go and talk to
them? Most of them have gone the studio route
Most of them have gone the studio route
and I'm trying to go the independent
route. Are there individuals that have
ever gone your route before? Yes. Go and
talk to them. Let them rub off on you.
Literally. If anyone has done something
that you want to do, associate with
them. Watch their
vibration. Watch how they
act. Listen to how they think. Look at
their approach to
life. Copy it. Be the vibration. You
will still do it your way, but you can
match their vibration. And if you do,
you'll get the same result. You will act
upon the things they have acted upon
because they were willing to see things
that you simply are not allowing
yourself to see because you're not
thinking like they do. Go and learn how
they think and you will see the same
things they saw.
Understand? Yes. Thank you. Thank you.
It is not something to do as an isolated
being. Be involved with all those that
can and you may be surprised to discover
are more than willing to assist you in
letting some of that vibration rub off.
Do you have any particular direction to
go? I mean there's so there are so many
people out there who you will know the
ones. do your research
and also remember that by having shared
this idea now there may be a few
individuals within the group this
evening of your time that can also
recommend either individuals or
literature that can be of assistance to
you. All it takes is putting it out
there letting individuals know how they
can be of assistance and then they will
give you their recommendations. Take
whichever advice feels most correct to
you. And if that is your desire, put the
desire out there and then let the
synchronicity in your life attract to
you whatever it is you need in terms of
a source of information. If you have
that desire, just put it out there. Then
go about your life acting upon the
circumstances that excite you the most.
One of those circumstances will attract
you into the appropriate circumstances
to give you what you need one way or
another. Understand? In other words, if
you have done everything you can do that
you can imagine you could do, every
opportunity you are aware of has been
acted upon and you are still not getting
the result, then simply maintain the
fact that this is your desire. This is
what you desire. This particular idea,
put the vibration out. Then act upon
whatever you can act upon that excites
you the most even though it seems
unconnected. Let's say, well, all right,
I've done that. What is the most
exciting thing I could now do? Go for a
walk. Well, that doesn't seem to have
anything to do with All right, that's
the most exciting thing. I'll do it. Off
you go. And all of a sudden, as you're
walking and just daydreaming and looking
around, you come across, oh, let's say
what you call one of your bookstores and
you wander in and you're not thinking
about anything in particular and you
overhear a conversation. Oh, this book
was most helpful for this, this, and
this. What? Where is that book? All right,
What? Where is that book? All right,
over there. All right, thank you. All by
12. And there is the information you
need which you discovered by doing the
thing it excited you the most to do.
Taking a walk. Understand? Yes. One
always flows into the next. Excitement
is the thread. It leads to all other
things that excite you. Follow it. Thank
you very much. Oh, thank you.
Shing.
Hi Bashar. My name is Lisa. Good day to
you. Um you had said last time that um
in your civilization um that you were
free of illness. Yes. And that we would
take us 50 to 100 years to get to that
point on the average. That doesn't mean
that an individual can't do it right
now. Right. Um and that can change by
the way. Of course, it doesn't have to
take that long. Um well my question is
I'm a nurse and I find it difficult to
understand why people choose to be ill.
Well, they do not always do it
consciously. Many times because of the
way you have created your society to be,
they simply are not taught that there is
any other way to process what they have
to process. So they choose whatever will
be the quickest way even if they think
the only way will be through suffering
because they may not know there is
another way to do it through peace and
joy. They don't have to be sick, but
because your society fundamentally
teaches you from, as you say, day one,
you're not in control of your life. What
else can you do? Sometimes I see
understand it is not that it is always a
specific conscious choice. Sometimes it
can be, but more often than not, these
things are the result of the fears that
you buy into. That is the choices we are
saying you make by buying into certain
fears by being
diseases you create disease.
Understand? Yes, I do. Um I have a
question in particular in in comeomaosse
patients. Yes. Um I've experienced them
as not actually being in their bodies
and sometimes they are and sometimes in
a sense they are not. Well, where do
they go when they're not? Well, they can
travel astrally.
I see. It is again akin to what you
might call an outofbody experience. But
perhaps this will be of assistance to
you as well. All of these things are in
your terminology very typical ways to phrase
terminology very typical ways to phrase
the idea of your spirit and your body
and the relationship between the two.
Your spirit does not actually exist
inside your
body. Neither does your
consciousness. Your body is your spirit
in physical
terminology. Your consciousness in that
sense has created your body. Your body
exists within your consciousness. What
appears to you to be out of body travel
is actually simply the expansion of your
consciousness perspective. So that all
of a sudden your perspective is quote
unquote out here and all of a sudden
your body is at the center of your
consciousness rather than your
consciousness being simply so tightly
focused that it appears that the only
place it exists is within your body but
your body actually exists within your
consciousness. I see. So is there a
purpose for us to be sick? I mean we've
decided that we we've chosen this or
again the purpose can simply be that
individuals can learn certain things
from it if they wish to do it that way.
Anything can serve a purpose if you use
it in a positive way. But the idea is
that you do not have to be ill. And one
of the primary purposes to some degree
on one level is to get so sick and tired
of being sick that you finally decide
you don't want to do it anymore.
[Music] When you are truly sick of sickness, you
When you are truly sick of sickness, you
won't be sick anymore.
Now, you have done it in almost all the
ways you can possibly do it. And any
escalation of disease you may now be
experiencing on your planet, in a sense,
to some degree, is the last vestigages
of these ideas coming out and
accelerating because there really isn't
very much time left for your
civilization to experience things that
way. Understand? Yes. Thank You can always
Understand? Yes. Thank You can always
reflect to an individual the following
idea. For this is the thing that has not
yet been taught for thousands of years
on your
planet. Every individual is as powerful
as he or she needs to be to create
anything they desire with integrity
without having to harm anyone else or
themselves in order to create it. That
is what you are not taught.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Shooting.
All right, D. And to you. Good day. It's
a beautiful day down here. I don't know
what's happening down there. Up there,
over there.
Uh uh I have a question about uh cachas.
Yes. I was reading a book about them.
They had different stories about them.
Yes. And there was one story where they
uh the actual cacas were interacting
with the people. It wasn't the men
wearing the masks. I understand. And uh
they said that um after a day of dancing
and such that the the men were around
the fire and one of them made like a
joke of the cachas like something
disrespectful and then there had been a
cachacina present and he went back and
told the other cachas and they I don't
know if they warned him or not but they
came the next day and um killed all the
village. I guess there was like a few
women and children. I was just wondering
if that was like an interpretation of
something. Yes and no. The idea is is
that when you are dealing with Kachina
energy, you are dealing with a very raw
state of universal power. It manifests
itself in an archetypal way in a way
that appears to be the way they appear
to you. That is not their absolute
appearance. They do not have an absolute
appearance. But the idea is also that
since they are such a raw state of power
then the entire fundamental structure of
the universe what you put out is what
you get back is amplified a thousandfold
in their presence. It is not that they
are in that sense actually performing a
hostile act. It is that if you do tap
into their energy and then you create a
negative vibration you can cause vast
negative vibrational manifestations upon
yourself. Yeah. They said that after
that the cacas gave them word that if
they wouldn't interact with them anymore
personally that they would you know to
make the masks and to uh when the men
put the masks on then they would get the
spirit you know would come into them but
they wouldn't interact after that face
to face because they recognize that as
far as your civilization is concerned
interacting with them at the level that
sometimes you interact would be
analogous to sticking your finger into a
live socket. Wow.
Understand? If I wanted to just be in contact, I
If I wanted to just be in contact, I
just have to have the desire and the
intent. Yes. And simply understand that
your intention is one of integrity and
joy. And you will always feel the
amplification of the energy in a
positive way. It is simply that they are
such a raw state of power that any
positivity or negativity that is in that
sense thrown at them or toward them will
be automatically bounced back again a
thousandfold, perhaps even more. That is
a loose
terminology because in that state when
you are involved in their vibration you
are right at the fundamental crossroads
of all universal realities because they
are those consciousnesses that quote
unquote inhabit the planes in between
the universes. Therefore they are
responsible for sustaining the very
fabric of the structure of all the
different universes themselves in a
sense. Understand? They are as we have
called them many times an
extraterrestrials's extraterrestrial. They are outside all
extraterrestrial. They are outside all
the experiences that we both you and I
would typify as normal universal
realities. They are interwoven into the
very fabric of the structure that
sustains everything you and I call a
universal reality.
So I wouldn't be getting to more than I
was asking for because no my intentions
are good and you will only receive in
that sense whatever you can handle. It
is simply that that individual made a
choice to operate on a particular level
as told in the story but then on the
same level chose to reverse the polarity
while in
midstream. Think what that would do to
many of your electronic devices.
It will do the same to all of you if
you're standing in the flow.
Understand? Yes. That is all there is to
it. So simply have the intention of
going in the same direction you started
out in and you will find that it will be
in your terminology quite safe and quite
enjoyable. Okay. Thank you. Thank you. Sure.
Hi Bashar. Andrew you. Goodbye. I was
wondering if you could uh tell me a
little bit about my past lives. Maybe,
maybe not. Again, remember that we are
usually at first hesitant to simply go
ahead and label many of these ideas
because we do not want to draw you out
of the present where all of your power
is. The idea therefore will always be
for us to ask you first, what areas are
you most drawn to? Because each and
every one of you have the strongest
ability to tap into anything you have
ever been. So open the doors for us
first and we will see what we are
allowed to share with you. Well, I sense
a certain dichotomy in my life. I mean,
all right. In what sense? I feel a
knowingness and a spiritual awareness,
but yet there's something clouding that
or holding me back from holding you
back. Are you using your awareness to do
the things that you really want to do?
Yes, I'm working on it. Working on it.
All right. I mean, I I feel as if I'm
growing in that area. No. All right.
What is it you do want to do?
I want to uh lessen my holes that I have
on myself or maybe uh you want to what?
Put myself in touch with the tools that
will allow me to uh expedite
all right what I'm after. But you are
creating so many steps. What is it you
want to do once you have the tools?
I want to free my spirit by doing what?
What do you mean free your spirit? What
is your definition of that line?
Living my life as a free and loving
being. All right. What is stopping you
from doing that now? I'm not entirely
sure. Well, all right. Does it seem like
there really is anything stopping you
from living that way? Yes, it does.
What? I don't know. That's what I'm up
here asking. You know, if I knew that, I
would uh I could figure it out. It seems
very uh very elusive to me. But if you
don't know what it is, maybe it doesn't
really exist. That's possible.
Is it? Yes, it is. All right. Well, how
about this? If it is possible, why not
act as if that is the way it is? And if
anything really is there, then you'll
find out. Ah, that's true. How about
that? End of subject. That's it. Thank
you. Thank you very much.
Keep it
simple. shouting.
Hi, Bur. Good day to you. Um, I'd like
to know why do people take on the
characteristics of other people that
they hang around with? You know what I'm
Because they start identifying with
their vibration and start mirroring it
because they in that sense identify with
them. They wish to reflect to them
certain ideas. They wish to join a
particular miniature consensus reality
and flow in the same direction. So they
can in a sense work together as one even
though they are individuals. That is why
individuals in love will very often
exhibit similar traits to each other and
know each other's thoughts because they
are identifying with each other so
strongly that they are mirroring each
other's vibration. It is not that anyone in that
vibration. It is not that anyone in that
sense is literally reading each other's
minds directly. It is that when you
identify very strongly with an
individual and you exist on the same
frequency then you translate your
thoughts in the same way or a similar
way to the way they do and you become
very much alike even though you still
have differences. But I mean just like
when you go up and you first meet
someone just the way they speak, you
start speaking like them even though
you've never met them before or you
start acting like him or doing whatever.
Because as a form of communication, it
allows you both to express to each other
that you are willing to see in the other
their validity. It makes communication
easier because you are reflecting back
to them an aspect of themsel that you
discover within you as well. It is
simply to put it on a very simple level
called mirroring.
And when you mirror someone, not in a
mocking way, but in a truly identifying
way, it allows a flow of communication
to go more easily because you are once
again creating a similar vibration, a
similar wavelength by literally copying
each other's format and it allows
communication to flow more easily
because you're on the same wavelength.
Literally, you can create the same
wavelength by physically mimicking
someone else. Again, not in a mocking
way, but your body language, if you
identify it strongly with another
individual's body language, will
automatically create a flow of
communication, not only on a physical,
but a non-physical level, and will make
communication between you easier. That's
why it's an automatic
thing. Understand? Yeah, I think you
very much,
Shing. Good evening, Bashar. And to you,
good day. I'm so glad to be here with
you again. Go. All right. And I most
compliment Daryl on his wonderful
t-shirt with whales. That's what I want
to talk about. Whales. Whales. All
right. Uh, I went to SeaWorld yesterday
again. All right. And getting to know
you. Where are they? Oh, yes. I think
they are. I'm certainly feeling that
they are. I Yes. This time I was able to
pet the pilot whales. Pet the pilot.
Yes. They are so wonderful. And I felt
during that interaction with them when
they one of them actually stayed in
front of me and let me pet him for some
time. All right. And I felt through that
I was really
contacting the consciousness of pilot
whales everywhere in a sense. Yes. To
some degree. This has been something I'm
very interested in because Oh, right. As
I spoke to you before in Hawaii, I'm um
working with the International Wildlife
Coalition on a project to allow the
Pharaoh Islanders up near Greenland to
perceive that they don't really have to
slaughter pilot whales for sport, but
there are other ways to interact with
them. Yes. Much more positive, much more
loving ways. Yes. And so ways that the
whales would also prefer. Yes. I'm
sure. So, through the interaction with
these two pilot whales at SeaWorld, I I
really felt that.
And I don't know if I mentioned this
before. I guess I talked a friend about
it. Um, I actually took a a very smooth,
sturdy rubber um, actually neoprene, I
guess, beach ball down there a few weeks
ago and threw it into the middle of the pool
and threw it into the middle of the pool
for the dolphins to play with. And my
one concern, I knew that the dolphins
couldn't do it themselves or uh, no one
could be injured. And I knew management,
you know, wasn't too pleased about the
idea of anyone doing that, but um I knew
they couldn't hurt themselves. And as a
matter of fact, the girl that was on
duty there took it out and then she gave
it to me bec because she said she didn't
have the authority to throw it back in,
but she
[Music] I told her that I had put it in. She
I told her that I had put it in. She
said, "Well, I can't throw it back in."
So, she let me do it. And my one concern
was that perhaps because the pilot
whales are so large that they
conceivably could swallow it. All right.
Although I didn't think they would. Not
really. No. And what happened was they
swam around and they played with it, but
they just pushed it with their noses.
Nice. And I felt that they
were they had actually picked up that
idea that I had. Well, to some degree,
but understand they already knew it.
They were to some degree reflecting and
what you in that sense were sensing as
your desire for them in a sense you were
actually picking up from them. Ah
although it was a two-way idea but they
already understand the parameters of
their environment to that degree. Yes.
It would be analogous let us say to
someone tossing you what you would call
a tennis ball.
Do you think you could swallow that very
easily? Now I see your point. It would have to
Now I see your point. It would have to
be a ping pong ball. Yes. And even then
you have what you call your gag reflex.
That's true. Why is it then that the
dolphins occasionally do swallow foreign
objects and some sometimes uh f it will
depend upon the symbology. Remember that
they are still individuals as well and
they have in many ways certain ideas
that they are willing to play out within
their own lives in different ways.
certain symbols that are reflected to
them in certain ways and society
patterns that to some degree they also
are reflecting in their individual
motives. Understand? Yes, I do. Oh, well, thank
Understand? Yes, I do. Oh, well, thank
you.
Would you be willing to share something
with us about orcas? My friend Karen's
here and we're both Well, you know what
we already have shared about the idea of
the orca? The sorcerers and the samurai
of the sea. Yes, the black and white of
polarity that when you in that sense
mimic their path then you are very
boldly expressing conviction and in very
many ways there is no turning back. I
have felt that more and more lately.
They are the expression of polarity
consciousness itself. And as you have
already suggested, as we have said, they
are the samurai and the sorcerer. They
are the warriors of the sea. Not meant
in what you would call a negative way,
but they have that spirit of conviction.
They tunnel through different
dimensions. And if you ride with them,
you must expect to go on that ride with
your eyes open.
and be prepared for all the changes that
occur for they are very strongly
transformational beings and any
structure that you may have built up
that doesn't fit in their world will
come apart very quickly
they will allow you to face anything you
might call a fear and process it now
yes I know this is true yes that's why
it's so exciting to me to go to SeaWorld
and see them playing with their trainers
see the the love and the interaction and
the trust. Yes. Um yesterday there were
they be brief. Be brief. Yes. They had
two more orcas there. Yes. From uh a
facility in Ohio that are there on
vacation. And so there were four orcas
and four trainers and they actually rode
them out of the out of the the water up
onto the platform and it was
magic. It was great. Thank you.
Thank you, Bashar. Love to you. Oh, love
to you. And Esasani as
Sharon.
Good evening, Bashar. And to you,
goodbye. I would like you to interpret a
dream for me if you will. Maybe. Okay.
Maybe you can too.
Um, I had a series of three one scene
dreams. If time is short, I'll just ask
you the first one. All right. I dreamed
that I was in a relatively bare room.
There was like a lenolium or marble
floor or something and there was a very
dark skinned man sitting against a
wall. He was all huddled up like he was
in pain or fear or something. All right.
And in my dream, I walked over to him
and I placed my hands on the side of his
head. Hey guys. And someone said
something to him through me.
And then the scene honed in on
me and I had a shirt on with a white
collar and on the
collar were the letters C u EO and then
a space and then the letter U. Do you
have any idea what those letters meant?
[Applause] [Music]
There are aspects, pieces of the
vibration. Continue for a moment. Well,
that was the end of that dream. What did
you say to the individual? I don't know.
It was like a a my dreams that when I
have them, when I remember them, they're
all telepathic. There there never seems to
telepathic. There there never seems to
be words.
One [Music]
[Music]
moment. Some of
this to some degree on one level is a
Leorian connection to aspects of
yourself.
Some of it is a connection to other
cultures as well, but mostly this is a connection. One
moment. What do you do?
I I don't work. What do you do? Well, I
uh read a lot and study a lot and try
very hard to grow.
I read constantly trying to understand
the spiritual aspects of life.
Where do you think that is heading?
Where will it take you? I don't know. I
I hope to a closeness to God to an
understanding of that.
Do you understand that you are made of
God? Yes. Do you understand that
everything therefore that you do in a
sense is an act of God?
Yeah. How much closer can you get?
Well, I still feel that that there's
almost like a veil between us and our
understanding of what God is. The veil I think is
of what God is. The veil I think is
becoming thinner and thinner. Yes. In a
sense. Yeah. But that veil is only a
definition of one reality to another
thing you think is another level of
reality. It is only the definition of
your dimension as you have defined it.
One moment. Have you allowed yourself to get
moment. Have you allowed yourself to get
into
touch with the polarities within you as
well? Have you examined the idea of not
only the positive but the negative ideas
within you within me as an individual?
Yes. Yes. All right. How do you feel
about the ideas of negativity? Uh
I I am I am clearing out most of the
negatives in my life. The one I'm I'm
digging them up, understanding them,
looking at them and and and learning
from them. All right. Then you are
transforming them into positive energy.
Right. All right. Very good. Do you
understand that negative has no more
power than anything else? That
everything is equal? Yes. And that these
things are just choices. Yeah. All
right. One
moment. Is there any particular place
upon your planet physically that you
would rather be than where you are?
Yes, some place that's very quiet. Which
is Oh, maybe the mountains. Any
particular area?
Uh, yeah. Mount Shasta. Maybe. Mount
Shasta. Maybe. Mount Chasta. All right.
You're sure now? Yes. All right. What
will you do when you go there? And when
will you go? I think we're in a long
guessing game here. Yes and no. Okay. If
I The idea simply is is that as we
perceive your energy, there are in your
terms many gaps in our ability to access
certain information. Therefore, we are
guiding you around, steering you around
to see what other information is
released in this process because there
is something that in that sense is
preventing us from giving you a direct
answer and usually that has to do with
the process that you are still
unfolding. Therefore, we do not have
access to something that will interrupt
your flow. So, we are in this sense
discovering certain aspects, certain
parameters, certain definitions about
you so that we can see how this flow
ties into the question you have asked.
Well, I think that if I had the time to
really spend by myself on Mount Chasta,
yes, I would spend that time
trying to Okay. I would spend that time
discovering Yes. my relationship to to
God. All right. How about your
relationship as God?
Or does that sound offkilter to you?
And if so, why? I believe that we are
all a part of God. Yes. But remember
that every part contains the whole.
Well, it's like the ocean is consists of
many drops of water. Yes. But the drop
of water is not the ocean. Oh, yes, it
is. It has all the properties of the ocean.
It has all the properties of the ocean.
What's the difference? Quantity.
That's a definition.
Maybe let's put it another way. Okay.
Another analogy that we have used is to
think of a grid spread out long and
flat. Lines this way, lines this way,
stretching to infinity. All right. Okay.
Take what you call a shiny ball bearing
reflective surface. Put it anywhere on
the grid. All right. Okay. The reflection of
grid. All right. Okay. The reflection of
the entire grid is in that ball
bearing. The entire grid. All the
information, any information you could
discover anywhere on that grid, you can
discover all in that one spot in the
surface of the ball bearing. Understand?
Yes. Everything you call physical
reality is only the product of the
information that it is, the definitions
that it is. One drop is the whole ocean.
Whether that makes sense in your
physiological reality or not, one drop,
if it contains the entire idea of the
information of the ocean, is the whole
ocean. And it is only a matter of your
definitional degree that makes it seem
to be different.
Well, in now if you're turning that
around to us all being God. Yes.
I think the potential for us to all be
God is there. But I think we have to
clear a lot of negatives and I think
there's a great deal of growth that we
have as individuals. Well, I'm not
saying that's not the case. No. But it
is more than a potential. Okay. What
what I would do on Mount Shasta would be
discover what discover the potential in
full. All right. But it isn't a
potential. It is what you are.
It is what you are.
I understand the terminology you are
using. I know the way you mean it. But
all we are suggesting is that what may
give you a more accelerated ability to
get in touch with what it is you say you
want to get in touch with will be to
understand that that's what you already
are. And all that you're doing is
discovering that. Well, what I am is
that in the raw I'd like to polish it.
All right. Okay. To some degree that is
so polish away. Okay. But the idea is
that when you do polish it, you will be
that shiny ball bearing that reflects
everything. Oh, I I believe that is true
of all of everyone. Yes. Now, that
aspect of the dream to some
degree is representative of
that. You are speaking to yourself in
the dream. That individual that you took
in your hands and spoke to to some
degree is a portion of your own
consciousness. A portion that contains a
certain definition. A certain definition
that makes you still seem to be within a
universe rather than recognizing
yourself as the
universe. This is the whole symbolic
idea of the transformational age on your
planet completely. Any acceleration that
you do will be the process of
discovering that you actually are the
dimension that you previously thought
you existed in as a part
of. That is the whole idea of growth and
expansion. To actually recognize that
you are the dimension you previously
thought you were only a part
of. But in whatever way, shape or form
it serves you to do this, have a
wonderful time. We would simply suggest
that if you do have a propensity to go
to a certain place that if a certain
place does attract you, we suggest that
you do in fact go because that will be
the magnetic field that will be most
aligning to you to accelerate you in the
ways you desire to be accelerated.
All right. Thank you very much. Well,
thank you very much for your expression
and for allowing us to see the aspect of
the infinite you chose to be.
[Applause] [Laughter]
Bashar to you. Good day.
There's something I've been thinking
about and reading about a lot recently.
It has to do with question of free will.
Yes. Versus control. And I'm thinking
Versus control. And I'm thinking
specifically, do you mean control in the
sense of destiny? I mean control in the
sense of mind control through mind
control. So things like implants.
Implants. Yes. Yes. And I'm wondering to
what extent implants are
actually used
um wondering to what extent Atlant
Atlantean techniques of implants have
been used in the past and to what extent
people today are implanted either by
extraterrestrials or are still carrying
implants from Atlantean times.
The idea you are calling out as an
implant can perhaps more precisely be
called a seed. And in this way, the idea
of a seed is not something that
controls. It is something that
unlocks. It is something that allows
there to be transformations that are
conducive of the vibratory agreements
that individuals made usually prior to
the physical life. They are in that
sense receivers not controlling units.
They may be in a sense altering units
but only in the format that the energy
they are implanted into already exists
only in the format that represents the
unfolding. That is a portion of the idea
of the agreement that they
made. It is an accelerative device in
that sense but it is not really a device
as you understand it at all. Yeah,
that's what I've been wondering. Um, is
this something that the soul has to
agree to in order for it to happen?
Absolutely. It does not ever happen
against your
choice. It cannot happen against your
choice because your choice creates you
to be a certain vibration. Whatever
vibration you are cannot be experienced
by whatever is not your vibration and
you cannot interact with anything that
is not on the same frequency in general
terms. Understand?
Yes. Does that answer your question
sufficiently for now? For there is not
much time remaining for this
interaction. Yes, I understand that.
Will that do? Yes. Do not worry about
the idea of control. You always have
freedom of choice.
Always. Always.
Always.
Always pleasant dreams. Thank you,
Frankie. At this timing, allow us once
again to share with each and every one
of you our utmost appreciation and to
remind each and every one of you that
there are no accidents and every single
thing that has occurred this evening of
your time has on some level sparked and
opened and unlocked a door within you
all. You are never present to hear
something that does not serve you on
some level or are not present in some
way to be of service in allowing all
other individuals to come to the
determinations they desire to come to.
You all play a part no matter what the
degree of significance of any particular
act for any of you. You all play a part.
You are all an orchestration of energy
and there are no accidents in your
gatherings. We thank you for being that
individual and collective
reflection. Once again, next week of
your time, we will reflect some other
ideas in the
format in honor of your all hollows eve
of what you call a ghost story. our
version. Until such timing, we extend
our deepest appreciation for your
willingness to support and generate and
co-create this interaction as it
unfolded within the dream we are
dreaming together now. Because this is a
dream you are dreaming right now. Wake
up and live the dream you prefer to. You
might as well. We thank you and bid you
a fond, ecstatic and
refreshing good day. Good day. [Music]
How did it go? [Applause]