All right, I'll sit. How are you all
this evening of your time as you create
time to exist?
Allow us to begin this interaction, this
evening of your time, with an idea that
we have shared now and then during the
past week of your time with a few
individuals in the form of what might be
called a little bit of a pre.
The individuals that therefore are aware
of what we are about to share with the
rest of you, we would simply ask that
they refrain from joining in to this
particular section since they already
know what we are going to say. for the
rest of you.
Therefore, we
will in this sense utilize the talent of
the pointer for this brief exercise by
requesting five volunteers.
and
flee. And simply in this way, when you
are thick, please in your terminology,
stand. Now the rest of you may ponder
along with this exercise within your own
imagination. We are going to
We are going to
ask the five volunteers. Thank you very
much. A
question. Would you in your terminology
from this side to this side count out
yourselves? 1 2 3 4 5. All right.
All right.
Now the question we are going to ask
this evening of your time is also going
to be the topic if you wish for this
evening dialogue. When we ask this question in
dialogue. When we ask this question in
turn 1 2 3 4 and five give whatever
answer you feel is appropriate to the
question and I will tell you now and
this goes for all of you none of your
answers will be wrong.
They will all be correct. However, we
are seeking a specific answer in a
specific format because it has a
particular impact that is pertinent to
this dialogue this evening of your time.
Understand?
The question and the title beginning
with number one.
What is the most important thing of all?
Correct, but not the answer I seek.
Number two.
Number three,
connection with all that is correct, but
not the answer I seek. Number four,
correct, but not the answer I seek.
Number five, personal empowerment.
Correct, but not the answer I seek. You
may all sit down. Thank you very
much. Now, whatever answers the rest of
you came up with, they are all correct
in that sense. However, the basic idea
before we give you the specific answer
will have to do with ideas we have
shared with you on all of these levels
and an incorporation of all of those
answers into one understanding.
We have discussed the focus of allowance
that is necessary to create the reality
that you desire to create. And we have
discussed the idea that the present is
the only time in which you ever
exist because it is the only
experiential time that there is and you
create everything from the present and
you discover everything you need to
discover in your life in the present.
Therefore, the fundamental idea for
allowing yourself to be able to let your life
yourself to be able to let your life
flow as quickly as it possibly can to
transform into what you desire it to be
as quickly as you possibly can is to
extract from whatever circumstance is
going on in your life at present. all of
the ideas that that circumstance is
there to teach you, is there to reflect
to you, is there to show you. For when
you have in that sense used up the
present present, then the next present
can come in. But if you do not use it,
if you deny that what is going on in
your life has anything to do with you,
then you do not use what you have
attracted, what you have created in a
positive way, you do not make room by
not using it up for the next thing to
come in. So the longer you take to use
what is presently in your reality, the
longer it will take for any other
opportunity to find its way to you.
Because the only place you can be found
is the present. You will never be
discovered in the future. You will never
be discovered in the past. You can only
be discovered in the present because now
is all there is.
Therefore, just as a gentle reminder,
the answer that we seek to the question
what is the most important thing of all
is the answer the thing I am doing
now. Always the thing you are doing now
because it is the thing you are doing
now is the most important thing in your
life. Otherwise something else would be
happening. Whatever it is that is going
on in your life now that is where your
focus needs to be. If it is elsewhere,
then you in that sense are not allowing
your reality to change as quickly as you
say you desire it to change. It is the
impatience of waiting for something
better to come along that makes it take
longer. For knowing that nothing better
will come along. Yes, it may be
different and more expanded and in that
sense even be more representative of
what to prefer, but judgmentally it is
not better intrinsically. For whatever
it is you are doing now by definition is
obviously what you need to be doing in
order to get whatever else you are going
to get. Every moment is a stepping stone
that leads to every other moment. They
are all there for a reason. There are no
accidents in that way. Nothing slips
into your life that is not
representative of what your belief
system about what is possible in your
life attracts to you because your belief
creates all your reality. So if you are
discovering something in your life, if
you are discovering the circumstance and
situations that are going on at present,
understand that whether you prefer them
or not, that is what belongs there
because that is what reflects to you who
you are at that moment. What it is you
are dealing with at that moment. What
aspects of yourself you are discovering
at that moment. What services you are
providing to others at that moment by
being in that circumstance and in that
situation. Now now is all there is now.
Now now it will always and ever only has
been now.
now.
Beautiful. Allow yourselves to relax in
the present to settle in and become
comfortable with the idea of your life
in the now.
And then watch how quickly things
accelerate through you. Because
remember, life does not happen to you.
It happens through you. And the more
room you make, the faster it can flow.
And in order to make that room, all you
need to do is use the presence
completely by living in it completely.
That is all you have to do
fundamentally. You all follow up. Amen.
We take this opportunity once again to
extend to you our utmost appreciation
and our greetings to you in being
willing to co-create these interactions
with us and function as ambassadors of
your world and allowing me to function
as an ambassador of mine so that bit by
bit and day by day we may create the
third reality in which we can both be
considered as equals and interact. more
openly your world, our world. We thank
you for co-creating this opportunity and
we thank you for being willing to
discover all that you can discover about
yourself to become the individuals you
prefer to be to know that your life is
in your hands, that you are firmly in
control. And
remember, please our
please our
motto. Do not believe anything I say
just because I said it. Believe it
because it works for you. If it does
work for you, you are the beings who
determine what your life will and will
not be. We are simply being of service
to reflect to you more probable ways you
could look at yourself more probable
choices and opportunities you might care
to explore. But those decisions are
yours and you have the power to make
them. Plain and simple. Remember that no
matter what you have been taught to
think of yourselves, we believe in you
utterly. And it is only that belief and
that faith in your ability to create
your reality that allows us to be able
to serve you in this way. And so in
return for the gift you have given us of
allowing us to experience you, I ask you
now, how may I serve you?
Good evening, Bashar. And to you good
day. Um there's a situation in our
country where we import oil from other
countries and this undermines the entire
political situation in the world and
there is said to be a great deal of this
oil off of the California coast. Um the
government would like to extract this
oil and there are many groups of people
who feel that it would pollute the
environment and so it's a very great
controversy and I was wondering if you
could discuss it. In what way? What do
you want me to do about it? It's your
planet. It is up to you to decide what
type of power you wish to express in
your world. And remember, you are your
governments. You're not separate. You
have the ability to communicate and
equalize through love, not
accusation. Through sharing, not attack
these ideas, work them out, talk them
out, share them out, and decide what
would be of best service to all
concerned. Now, many individuals in your
society are now working on what you may
call alternate forms of power. Using the
electromagnetic field of your planet has
always been possible to your society for
quite some time, and it will afford you
unlimited power in a non-polluting way.
Many individuals are beginning to
explore these ideas. It is simply up to
what you will determine will be your
priorities as a society, as a world. But
bring all the options out in the open.
discuss them openly with everyone. Allow
everyone to see what options exist so
that they can decide for themselves what
they do and do not prefer. But it is in
that sense essentially up to you. It is
your world. This is a decision that can
only be made by your people. In what way
could we possibly assist you beyond what
we have already said? Well, I think I
was interested in learning more about
alternate u ter types of energy such as
electromagnetics. Okay, then by all
means explore and research the avenues
that many of your people are now
beginning to explore. Many of these
ideas were initiated into your society
several times and some of them can be found in
times and some of them can be found in
the works of the individual you call
Tesla. In that way, you can research
this and research all that is now being
discovered in your society about the
idea of
superconductivity. For these things tie
together very nicely and will allow you
an
understanding within the idea of the
generation of metallic crystallin
materials that can generate a flow, an
unimpeded flow of electromagnetic energy
that can be directed in many different
ways. Do your exploration if that is an
area that excites you. Follow your
excitement, follow your intuition, and
you will attract to yourself all the
necessary information that you can then
act upon and bring to your world, to the
surface of the consciousness of your
people, other alternate methodologies
that they can then add to their
configuration of how they wish their
world to be. Understand? Yes. Can can
the use of quartz crystals also be
instrumental in this? Yes.
Okay. Now there are many ways to amplify
these ideas. The idea first of all is that if
ideas. The idea first of all is that if
you wish high precision then the
crystals in of themselves must be highly
precise, clear and cut very precisely in
certain ratios to each
other. Any number of configurations will
do different things and have different
effects. Experiment with the idea of mathematical
Experiment with the idea of mathematical
ratios, especially the ones that you
find in nature. And if you cut your
crystals with those ratios, they will
exhibit magnetic amplification. Your
pyramidal structure based upon what you
call your Giza pyramid has already
allowed many of you to understand that
all it is is an amplifier, a lens, a
magnifying lens for magnetism, which can
be focused in a certain way to do
different things. allowing there to be
highly conductive materials perhaps such
as you are familiar with conductive
materials copper and the like as you
know it
when formed in different formats in
different configurations and placed
within some of those crystallin
structures you can find an increase in
the flow of those
conductors a lot of these ideas have to
do with highly conductive materials and
rotational mass
and pure pure mathematical forms, shapes
that in and of themselves represent
deviations in the magnetic field. Study
the whole idea of resonance and
vibration because everything is created
of different varying vibrational
frequencies of a prime energy chord.
Study the idea of tone, sound,
resonance, for that is the motivating
force that translates into almost every
physiological phenomena you are familiar
with. Study those ideas. Understand how
every object is actually created
holographically out of different
patterns of overlapping frequencies of
energy. Break them down in that way.
Study and examine them. Measure them in
that sense. Define them as vibrational
equations and you will unlock the very
ability to pattern anything in any way,
shape or form and in any time space
framework you desire to. All these ideas
are avenues that are open to all of you.
Go into them with your excitement. You
will attract the opportunities and the
information you need. Go within your
meditative state. Trust your intuition.
Trust your imagination and follow the
pictures that you get in terms of
formulating the experiments you would
like to try. You will discover a lot.
Understand? Yes. Does this assist you
very much? Thank you. Well, thank you
very much. Enjoy sharing.
I have a shark. And to you, good day. I
was wondering if you could reflect to me
why that I'm creating my right knee to
hurt and be stiff. All right. What
information have you gotten about it so
far? I've come up with a several
different ideas, but the knee is still
hurting. Okay. The first one was that it
was u thinking about ideas about aging.
All right. And being unable to do what
it is that you would like to do. All
right. And what do you think about aging
now?
That I don't prefer to do it. Why not?
Why not?
Because I wouldn't be able to do some of
the things I enjoy doing like dancing
and horseback riding. And I prefer to
have a balanced life. And I guess that
depends on how you age. Right.
Is the idea of age in and of itself in
your mind debilitating?
Yes. I guess what I associate with it.
Oh, I So you're only making a reference
to that particular style of aging that
you call debilitating. When you say age,
we assume you are not simply referring
to the idea of being chronologically a
certain age. You are referring to the
idea of being physiologically a certain
age in terms of a debilitating nature.
Yes. Yes.
Now, are you already doing the thing in
your life that excites you the most?
I'm working on it. Working on it. All
right. Do you have a definition of what
that might be? The thing that excites
you, not really, but the two things that
excite me the most right now are a
channeling class and then um a art a
ceramics class
in a sense that is
redundant for both are forms of
channeling. Now, in what way do you see
yourself fully expressing the idea of
who you are? What picture comes most
strongly to mind?
Sort of like walking like dancing.
Walking like dancing. Dancing
like All right.
And what has that got to do? In other
words, how does that tie in with the two
things you have said excite you the
most?
Well, I feel a lot of um sensation of
motion when I'm uh exploring my
imagination. Sensation of motion. Very
good. Very good. Now, do you think that
what you are perceiving as the sensation
of motion by going into these particular
endeavors, does it give you
the feeling that you are moving too
quickly?
Sometimes I feel a little fear with it.
Is that why you are slowing yourself
down? I don't know. All right. It is a
I don't know. All right. It is a
suggestion. Sometimes individuals will
create the idea that they cannot be
flexible nor move fluidly to purposely
slow themselves down because they fear
the rate at which they perceive they
actually can move thinking that it will
be too much for them. So they become
hobbled, crippled in that sense, they
give themselves the debilitating age
factor so that they will have an excuse
to not move too
quickly. But that is all right. It is
not a judgment that we are saying this
idea. Do you trust that as fast as you
will find yourself capable of moving
that you will be able to handle it?
It's always seemed to me that I'm moving
too slowly, not that I'm moving too
quickly. But that is the polarity
judgment that represents the fear in
that sense of moving too fast.
You can be manifesting in your joint the
belief that you are moving too slowly.
But when you believe you are moving too
slowly, you must have somewhere in your
mind an image of the opposite end of the
motion, the high-speed motion that you
think you desire.
Now, we began this evening's
conversation with the idea that the
quickest way to get anywhere is to live
in the present, to not try to push
yourself too fast, for that is when you
do strain yourself.
Understand? Yes. Now, how quickly do you
think you need to get where you want to
go? The sooner the better. The sooner
the better. Why don't you like where you
are?
No. Why not?
Now, we are not saying you have to
prefer where you are. But do you
recognize that where you are still
serves you? Yes. In what way?
It's allowing me to look at a lot of the
um beliefs that I have that are creating
a lot of negativity in my life. All
right. Is it giving you an opportunity
to recognize that you no longer prefer
those beliefs? Yes. All right.
Will you stop trying to rush?
Will you allow yourself to recognize
that the pace at which you are
discovering these beliefs is the pace
that is easiest for you to absorb? And
as soon, paradoxically enough, as you
relax into that pace, it will speed
up. Understand? Yeah. Is there anything
you could possibly discover about
yourself that cannot be applied in a
positive way?
Oh, I've been wondering about that. All
right. I've discovered a lot of negative
things recently. But cannot the
information that you discover be applied
in a positive way. Can you not transform
what may have been a negative
manifestation into a positive idea?
Yes, I can. A lot of times I can see
that in the future that I'll understand.
Yeah, that's the thing. Is that why
you're in such a hurry to get to the
future? Because you don't think you can
understand it now.
Someday I'll understand it. Someday I
better hurry up and get there because if
I don't I'll kill myself first.
Well, that's how I feel about it because
a lot of times afterwards I can really
see that I get a lot of um joy and
understanding out of some of the
negative emotions and activities. But
I'm tired of doing the negative emotions
and activities so that I can get to the
joy later. All right. But you don't have
to do it that way. You know, I know, but
I don't seem to have any other way to do
it right now. Oh, all right. Well, now
as you have just stated, have you not
recognized in what you call the past
that you have arrived at places that
allow you to appreciate what you went
through in the past? Yes. Well, since
you know ultimately you're going to get
to a place that will allow you to
appreciate where you are now, why not
appreciate it now while you're still
there instead of waiting to appreciate
it later? Cuz it feels like I feel these
very intense negative emotions. Oh. All
right. and I'm not enjoying it. Oh, all
right. But remember that emotions are
reactions to belief. If you are feeling
these negative intense emotions, the
feeling is there to point out some of
the beliefs you may simply have chosen
to have within you, some of the
definitions that you may have within
you. And it is only the definitions in
that sense that is causing the negative
reaction. So you can use the negative emotions now
So you can use the negative emotions now
that they have gotten you in touch with
the idea of the negative beliefs you may
have and you can redefine those beliefs
right now. Can you name one of
them? One of the negative feelings, one
of the negative emotions, one of the
negative ideas, one of the negative
beliefs. Can you name one of them? Well,
I was very upset that I couldn't go uh
to my dancing class and I decided that I
had a negative belief that um my body
would deteriorate if I was unable to um
walk and dance. All right. Very well
said. Now, why should you choose to
believe that? Because you know it is no more
that? Because you know it is no more
solid than how much you choose to
believe that it is. Why should you
choose that definition of reality? It
has no more power than any other
definition you could
concoct. Why do you choose to believe in
that one more than any other?
It just seems to me to be true because
I've I've sitting if you just sit there,
you'll become stiff and rigid and your
muscles will deteriorate. All right?
When you change that belief and
understand that you're always flowing no
matter what position you're in, then you
will not start to stiffen up when you
stop moving in the way you think you
ought to. You will understand that in a
sense you never really go anywhere
anyway. And that paradoxically,
therefore, you are already everywhere,
which means you're already in constant
motion. If you start to feel the energy
of life moving through you, then you
will not necessarily have to assume that
physiological motion is what is
necessary to sustain your flexibility.
I really enjoy those ideas and it seems
like they're too negative ones or the
positive ones. All of those ones that
you just repeated, I really enjoy them,
but it seems like they're too far
outside of my belief system to help me
any. Let me ask you a question if I may.
You have just said you enjoyed them. I
assume that means you heard them. Yes.
Well, if you heard them, they must be in
you somewhere. Otherwise, you would
never have recognized that I was saying
anything. Remember that we have said if
you can perceive it, you must contain
it. So, just because you have the
ability to perceive it means they must
be in you somewhere. Otherwise, it would
have made no sense to you at all. It
would have seemed as if the channel's
mouth was moving
and and all you would be doing is
saying, "Did you say something? Did you
say something? I'm sorry. Did you say
something?" If you heard it, that means
it's in you because you had to create it
for yourself in your reality in order to
hear it from me because you are your own
reality. Understand? Yes. It's got to
exist within you if you can perceive it
in anyone
else. So all you have to do is know that
if you can conceive of it, it's a part
of you. It's an option like any other
option, a belief like any other belief.
And you can choose to believe in that
one if you say you enjoy it more than
the other
one. And as soon as you recognize that
you do enjoy it, that's a recognition of
your preference. And once you have
determined what your preference is, then
you have it. That's it. You have
redefined the idea and all you need to
do from that point forward is act like
you really have a new definition and you
will loosen
up. It is only literally the
inflexibility of your belief that is
creating the rigidity in
you. Understand? Yes. Now if that sounds
good to you then adopt it as your belief
system. All belief systems work. They
all work. And when you choose one, it
will always create a self sustaining,
selfreinforcing system of reality
because they are all true. So if you
prefer it by saying you enjoy it, then
recognize that your preference is the
decision made. That's it. You have
recognized it. You have adopted it. You
have said that's what I want. That's for
me. And as soon as you say that's for
me, that's you. That's it. You have
changed. All you have to do is act like
it. Clear action based upon what you
have now defined as your clear intention
and your clear definition of who and
what you
are. Recently of your time, we spoke
about the idea of the three parts.
Clarification of self. A clear
intention. B. Clear definition, clear desire, clear
B. Clear definition, clear desire, clear
deservability. C. Clear
action. Now that you have a clear
definition of what you prefer and a
clear desire to prefer it, as long as
you are clear about the idea of whether
you deserve it or not, then act upon it
with clear conviction and you'll get
it. You have every right to choose
whatever reality you
prefer. There is no one in creation who
will say different. or who can say
different understand? Yes. So become
more flexible within your idea structure
and every single aspect of your body
will loosen
up. Remember just as a tiny reminder
once again you are energy. Your
scientists know this. Mass is energy.
Energy is mass.
The only reason that mass would become
rigidized is if the patterns of energy
become rigidized in their concept.
Understand? Yes. Does that serve you?
Well, I'm just feeling very sad about it
because I I don't believe that I could
just sit and have my body become more
flexible. Why do you choose to not
believe it? It is a choice to not
believe it.
Why do you choose to not believe it? How
does it serve you to not believe it? We
are not saying that you will be
immobile. But the idea is is how does it
serve you to choose to believe that that
will happen to you in that
way? Why is that your preference over
any other definition?
I don't prefer it, but it's just it's
what I believe that I need to keep
moving or else I would become
inflexible. You are making a
contradictory statement.
If you understand it is a belief and you
understand that your beliefs create your
reality, then obviously you are
preferring that belief or you are not
willing to believe that a new belief
will automatically replace the old
one. Is that the case? You simply do not
believe that a new belief will
automatically replace the old one.
Right? Why not? That's a belief too.
I believe that a new belief will not
replace an old belief. That's a belief.
Why believe that
one? All of these things are
definitions. They have no substance
other than what you give
them. You are choosing to believe it.
That's your choice. I can't change your
mind for
you. Is up to you.
And it is your choice to be sad about it
if you wish. But all these things are
choices. In a sense,
paradoxically, it should show you that
you have the ability to change it
because you know you're creating the
sadness and you know you're creating the
doubt and if you can create those, you
can create anything.
So why not create what you really prefer
by simply knowing that by changing your
definition the change has been
made is up to you. You can believe it's
that easy or you can believe it's more
difficult than that. And whichever you
choose is representative of what you
think you need to learn in whatever way
you think you need to learn it. Do
remember this. You are an infinite
being. You are eternal all of you. And
no matter in what way you choose to live
your life
now, you will eventually change because
change is the only constant.
All right. Well, I was just wondering if
how would it serve me ultimately to keep
holding on to this belief? All I will
say is this. Sometimes one of the
patterns we recognize in your society is
that an individual will simply not allow
themselves to believe they can change
something until they get good and sick
of
it. Maybe that's just your
way. Sometimes an individual will
believe that they have to reach the
bottom of the barrel in order to believe
that all other opportunities are now
truly up and equal.
You don't have to do it that way, but we
have recognized that that is one of the
patterns your society does. If you don't
believe it can be done easily, then you
will drive yourself crazy with it until
you simply get tired enough to say, "All
right, all right, all right. I've had
enough." Oh, where did it go all of a
sudden? You mean it was as easy as that
all along? Oh my. Oh
my. Maybe that's why. Okay, thank you.
Thank you very much. And all of you
remember that each and every one of you
by applying anything anyone says can get
something out of all these interactions.
If you are here to hear these
interactions on some level they all
apply to you.
Sherry. Hi. Hi. I have uh not had my
period in quite some time. No. What? Um
any conventional figure this one out for
yourselves. Um any conventional uh tests
that I've had have all come back
negative. I'm not I'm not pregnant. And
um
I'm I'm wondering wondering what I'm
wondering uh I guess they they they told
me that it would be best they they they
to have um a menstrual cycle at least
every 3 months. Why? Because they felt
that
They felt that it could um turn
cancerous if I didn't. Why? Because I
guess they're basing it on their
statistics. Yes. That go into explicit.
Do you fit the statistics or are you an
exception to the rule? I don't know
whether I fit the statistics. You don't
know. Decide right now. Okay. No, I
don't fit the statistics. Thank you.
Now, are you really worried about it or
are you just being a good
person and playing along with them so
that they will feel good about what they
are telling you? Well, it's not that I'm
trying to make them feel good. Um, no, I
think that I I consider that the way I
think and the fact that I'm part of In
other words, you are using them just to
check your belief system. Yes. That
would be one way of saying it. All
right. Was it an appropriate way of
saying it? It'll do for now. Thank you.
You always have the capacity to do an
internal check. Well, I internally I
feel all right. Yes. Sometimes I tend to
be a a bit of a procrastinator. So, I
don't look at things and until they're
smack in my face. So, I don't know if
this is one of those things. Sometimes
that can be procrastination. Sometimes
it can be living in the moment. Depends
on how you look at it. Well, I' I've
been looking at it the other way. Living
in the moment for quite some time. All
right. But there's been a a little thing
in the back of my head which told me,
well, maybe you should go have a test
and all that. All right. And now you
have had your test, right? And they are
they are negative and therefore
you are still not at rest. Well, and
then I've been um attempting herbbally
to to force it to happen and nothing's
happening. All right, then. If in that
sense by aligning yourself with the
natural order of things, it still
doesn't happen, then why not assume that
you are now a part of the natural order
of things the way you are. Okay.
Well, you don't have to. Okay.
Don't sound so overjoyed.
Um, I I boy the natural order of things.
I prefer to fully trust.
I prefer to fully trust that that
everything's fine. I'm checking
everything.
What do you mean by that?
What does the word imply in your
language? Everything. Everything. Are
you willing to trust that everything is
fine? Yes. We know you meant everything
with regard to the idea you specifically
mentioned, but we have taken the liberty
to include the broader definition of the
word. I gathered that. That was why
question. Yes, I
know. Is everything fine? Yes,
everything's fine. Well, thank you very
much. You know it
is. You really do. And understand this.
If for some reason you should decide to
create something you did not
prefer, by knowing that everything is
fine, you will always give yourself
ample opportunity to deal with it in a
way that will also be just fine for you.
Understand? In other words, you will
always catch everything in
time. Always.
Okay. Oh, thank you very much. By the
way, Mhm.
to some degree, what the idea of not
having the period is indicative of is
one way to show you that you are
completely living in the now. For time
hasn't changed that much for you. And in
a sense, I could put it this way, since
you stopped having it for you, in a
sense, a month hasn't gone by yet.
Understand? Yeah, I understand that.
Does that serve you?
Yes. For well, it's kind of funny when you
For well, it's kind of funny when you
think time hasn't gone by. I understand
it's that it's the the dichotomy of of
things accelerating and standing still
at the same time. Yes. Okay. So, that's
it. Yes, it does. Well, thank you very
much. Thank you. That means I haven't
aged. Well, bye. You are getting younger
every day.
Silling.
What do you mean, Bernard? Unto you.
Good day.
I I would like some insight in the
treatment of liver cancer. Liver cancer.
All right. Now, have you been paying
attention to some of the things we have
already been saying? Yes. Yes. All
right. Now, we have shared with many of you at
Now, we have shared with many of you at
many times some ideas about what you
might call
physiological treatments for any type of
disease at
all. It will always depend upon your
belief system primarily as to whether
any of these ideas will work for you,
however, and it will always depend upon
the reason for why you have attracted
the idea and created it into your life.
For if you have a good enough reason to
hang on to it, you will regardless of
any so-called cure because only
individuals cure themselves no matter
whom they go to. So there are many
ideas, many ideas. First of
all, one idea can be to understand from
what you may call a consciousness point
of
view, the symbolism of what you may call
the filtering
system in that sense of the liver and to
recognize that if you believe there are
ideas in a sense cancerous ideas within
a consciousness and that they must be
filtered out, then that may not actually
be an integration. process. It may be a
process of trying to segregate those
ideas from you, not accepting them as a
part of you to be balanced, blended, and
transformed rather than gotten rid of or
expelled from the consciousness.
Sometimes therefore a reaction to the
idea of attempting to get rid of what
you may believe to be negativity or
cancerous ideas within you can cause a
buildup in organs that symbolize the
idea of the filtration system of the
body. To some degree this has been some
of the primal reason for the general
creation of that disease.
So first and foremost if an individual
begins to understand metaphysically
speaking as you say, consciously
speaking as you say, energy speaking as
you say that it is not about getting rid
of anything but about integrating facing
and going through the ideas then you can
transform ideas into methodologies into
ideas into opportunities that serve
rather than trying to get rid of them as
if they have no business being in
anyone's life.
Now one very strong methodology which
your society is only just now beginning
to play around with I shall say and I do
not mean that derogatorily is the idea
that the body is an electrical conduit a
magnetic conduit and you can create
electrical fields magnetic field very
strong field vibrating at certain frequencies
field vibrating at certain frequencies
one of which would be 7 and 1/2 cycles
per second the frequency electromagnetic
ically speaking of your planet. And by
immersing a body in that electromagnetic
field, you can create a conducive
literally a conductive atmosphere that
may allow the person immersed in that
field to allow themselves to realign
with the natural field of the earth. For
when an individual is bound to the
natural electromagnetic field of the
earth, there can be no disease at all of
any type in any way, shape or
form. That is one way to create such a
magnetic field. You have just recently
in your society invented devices
called magnetic resonant imaging scanner
devices. Some of these are used to
diagnose but tuned to different
frequencies. They can also be used to
cure something that your scientists are
only just beginning to
realize. Also the idea has been
discussed and much literature exists in
your society about the notion of
treating the physiological body like
what you would call an electric battery
and simply recognizing disease as being
out of potential out of electrical
balance. And recreating an electrical
balance in the body will allow the
energy system to flow in the natural way
they need to realign and flush out and
transform all the imbalance back into a
balanced state. You may do your research
on that idea and there are individuals
present this night of your time who can
assist you in directing you to some of
that literature. These are two of the
strongest ways. There may be other ideas that come
ways. There may be other ideas that come
up that you may call cures of various
types but every kind of a cure that you
invent if it works for an individual
will only be a exteriorized reflection
of what you already believe is possible
for you.
So, does that serve you? Yes. Thank you.
Oh, thank you very very much. And
remember that even in the creation of
disease, even though it may start out
from a invalidational and judgmental
point of view, from a negative point of
view, recognize that because you are in
that sense choosing your reality that
someone who even chooses a disease does
so out of strength because they know
they can handle whatever it is that
disease will teach them.
Then you can self-empower the being to
recognize that they in creating it have
the opportunity to create it in another
way to transform it into another
creation.
Thank you. Thank you.
Exciting dream energies to you this
night of your time. Focus on the idea of
blue white electromagnetic light and
align with the magnetic flow of your
planet. Sleep
well. Sharing. Good evening. Bash and to
you. Good day. Thank you. Uh, I had a
question regarding a place where I go
mentally and emotionally that I would
like to go less frequently. Where is it?
Well, I'll describe it in just a minute.
Oh, what?
It's accompanied by the event of closure
in almost every area of my life so that
I find myself for the moment without all
my old purposes and connections. What
about letting some new ones in? Well,
just at the moment they're beginning,
but there's a tremendous space. A
tremendous void. A tremendous void.
Good. Why does he say good? She says,
Why does he say good? She says,
"Yes, that's a good question." All
right. Oh, thank you. I will answer
it. Remember
this. A void is not the nothing you have
been taught to think it is. In a sense,
the void or what you have recognized as
a void, an emptiness, actually contains
99% of all creation. So to speak, the
only part you usually see is the 1% just
an arbitrary figure that represents the
reality you choose to focus on in any
given moment out of all the probable
realities you could create. So the void
is not empty by any means. It is full of
potential realities.
Individuals when they allow themselves
to go back to that place of the
void know that they are aligning with
the fundamental cord the prime frequency
of creation itself taking themselves
back to the ultimate center out of which
they can then create any reality they
desire. So first and foremost, some of
the idea of the seeming constriction is
only the definition you are applying to
the so-called void, assuming that it is
in that sense a shutdown as opposed to a
complete and total connection to all
that is. Understand? Yes. Is this
assisting you so far? Yes. Has it
rearranged your point of view of the
idea of visiting that space?
Not yet. Partially. Partially. In what
way? In that if I began to play with the
idea of it just the void containing
unlimited possibilities instead of
emptiness, it would feel different. Yes.
Yes. Well, does it not feel different
when you think of it that way? Yes. Then
it is different, isn't it? Yes. Are you
willing to play in that space? I guess
that's the only space there is.
All right. Does that help you then? Yes.
Well, thank you very much. I have one
other part to that. All right. Uh the
the mental and emotional part I was
telling you about was that I have this
sense of holding myself together with
thoughts. Well, that's all you are.
Well, I I'm these feelings too. The
thoughts are somehow holding together
against overwhelming
feelings. Do you know what I mean? Yes.
Look at it this way. And remember this
idea. What you are as a personality is
not really who or what you are
ultimately a personality is an
artificial construct an artificial
projection of consciousness of the
consciousness that you are. It is
composed of three things like a prism
belief emotion and thought. So the idea
is that you are literally an artificial
construct and anytime you change the
idea that you are as a consciousness you
will disassemble the prism of your
personality and reassemble it. Let it
disassemble and reassemble. It will not
be the destruction of your
individuality. Understand? Mhm. You
always recreate
yourself all the time. You don't even
know you're doing it. So natural a thing
is it to do now. Simply you are becoming
conscious of the fact that you
dstructure your persona and restructure
it. Because the idea of this
transformational age upon your planet is
to become consciously aware of the
mechanisms you are using to create your
reality so you can create the reality
you prefer. So just because you are
witnessing now consciously a
destructurization of your personality,
do not assume it is the destruction of
your individuality. It isn't. It is
simply now that you know you are a set
of building blocks and you can rearrange
the idea and the definitions in any way
you care to. It is simply now that you
are awake and aware during the operation
because you no longer need
anesthesia. You no longer have to be
unconscious in order to
change. At first, that may seem a little
unsettling to you all. Oh, but you'll
get used to it.
Let it
flow. All right. All right. Thank you
very much. Thank you very
much, Sher.
Hello, Bashar. I'm to you. Good day. Uh,
Bashar, I'd like to talk to you about my
dog, Mof. Who? Dog? All right. Can you
all hear this individual? I'm sorry. My
dog Mof is about 12. Speak up. Speak up.
Okay. He's about 12 years old. Yes. And
I've spoken to you before a long time
ago about him, and
he's reflected a lot to me, but he's at
a point now where he's suffering from
incontinence. Well, he's not suffering
actually. That's we understand.
And uh it's been going on for about 4
months. All right. And uh I'd like some
help with what it's mean. What what it
means what it Well, first of all, it may
simply mean that that guide and that
reflection obviously is now able to
begin to move on. the more you have
absorbed what he has reflected to you.
The more you take it internally, the
more you become the idea that was being
reflected to you by the animal
consciousness, the less need there is of
the animal in that format. So it can now
move on and transform itself into a new
state, a newly energized state that can
then re-enter your life on a more equal
level rather than one that simply has to
support the idea of the things you were
facing as lessons in your life. So send
your unconditional love to the animal to
allow it to know it can move on if it
wishes to. It doesn't have to hang
around to make sure you've got all the
ideas you need to. It doesn't have to
reflect uncertainty, hesitation. It can,
as you say, make a clean
break. Understand? Okay. Yes, I do. Send
your unconditional love, your trust that
the animal has served you in that way.
And therefore, it can now transform into
a more equal energy because you now have
incorporated the idea of that being
within yourself as a reflection, as a
guide. You are now willing to take the
responsibility for creating those
reflections to yourself so that the
animal can simply in that sense share
your joy of equality and play with you
by transforming into another format that
you may discover very soon. Okay, thank
you Bashar. Well, thank you very
much. But I have done nothing.
Sharing, hi. And to you good day. Um, I
wanted to ask you about a year and a
half ago, I created a disease in my eyes
and it's very painful and it has a lot
of discharge and dies and it blurs my
vision and it made me very sad and it
made me very withdrawn. And about 6
months into it, I was in a bad car
accident, okay, with a drunk driver and
I was hit in the head and it hurt my
inner ear system and knocked me off
balance. I'm discovering the path that I see to
I'm discovering the path that I see to
the cure, but the cure isn't coming very
fast. And I want to know if you can give
me an answer to get to the cure. I do
not mean to seem redundant, but are you
doing what excites you the most at this
moment? Yes. All right. What is it?
Discovering myself.
That is a
given. That is automatic.
What are you doing in terms of doing
something in your society as a service
that excites you the most? How are you
expressing what you are learning about
yourself? Just learning about yourself
is automatic.
H got me.
Is there nothing that excites you that
you desire to do in life with the you
you are discovering yourself to be?
I have not discovered that. Well, you
can. Do you want to? Yes. Go ahead.
I don't know where. Oh, all
right. I'll make a suggestion. Now, we
Now, we
assume not because it is us, but we
assume that because you are in this
interaction that this interaction is the
most exciting thing you can think of to
do at this moment. What will you do when
you leave this interaction, this night
of your time?
I will be better. Oh, all right. Better
in all ways, not better to help. All
right. But what will you do?
If I knew what I would do, I would know
the reason. You don't know what you're
going to do when you leave here tonight?
Just tonight? Yes. That is what I said.
Tonight. This interaction. No, I don't
know what I'll do when I'll leave here
tonight. Are you going home? Eventually?
Eventually? Then you knew that. Yes. Why
didn't you say so? Because I thought you
meant immediately. All right. Well, what
will you do immediately?
I don't know. What do you want to do?
Have fun. In what way?
Any way it appears.
What way will you create?
I don't know. All
right. Here is the crux of the symbolism
for you. When you take the initiative to
you. When you take the initiative to
create the reality and stop just sitting
and waiting for things to happen, then
you will have a need to see
something. But if you assume that all
you have to do is stay in one spot and
let things happen around you, then you
don't need to see because you're not in
that sense using those
facilities. You need your eyes to act
upon the opportunities that come into
your life. But the idea is not just that
opportunities come. It is that you act
upon them. And that means that you
decide because you have the conscious
commandment and the conscious
decisionmaking ability to do so to say
this is what I will prefer to do and
then do
it. Now we understand the idea of
flow and to some degree some of your
condition is the result of learning to
strengthen your inner vision as well.
But the idea sometimes can be
overcompensated in the sense that you
think that the inner vision is all that
is necessary. Just the realization of
the energy will not manifest it into
your life unless you recognize that you
have the ability to do something with
the realization. So
So
your situation of not knowing what you
will do is
simply not
recognizing that you have the ability to
decide what you want to do and to do it
rather than waiting for some more
blatant sign that needs to be more obvious than
sign that needs to be more obvious than
what is simply obviously around you to
some degree that is one of the reasons
for the clouding of your vision as well
because in a sense you are making it
more difficult to see the subtle things
around you as if they have no meaning
for you. You are attempting to force
something into your life that is so
blatant that you can't miss it even with
the vision that you have.
The idea is not that you have to create
idea is not that you have to create
those opportunities with trumpets
blaring and fireworks flaring. The idea
is to recognize that the opportunities
already exist all around you and all you
have to do is initiate them by acting on
them and deciding what it is you want to
do and then doing it. When we say what
is the thing that excites you, we are
not necessarily referring to the idea of
coming up with an idea that will be the
most exciting thing you will ever do in
your entire life. We are talking
literally in the moment. What is the
most exciting thing out of all the
things you are capable of doing that you
want to do and can do right now? That's
it. Moment to moment right here in front
of your face. Not out there. right
here to some degree. The idea again of
the clouding of the site is to allow you
to start focusing here where all the
opportunities are right here within you
not out there in that sense of waiting
for something to present itself in a
very blatant way. Now keep it simple.
This is not a complex idea. This is not
a test in the sense of how we are asking
you what you will do.
Keep it simple a step at a time. You are
having this interaction. Now we assume
therefore that is what it excites you to
do. When this interaction is over, we
will assume that it may or may not
excite you to sit down. You may decide
to leave. You may decide to sit down.
You may decide to get a drink of water.
But each and every one of those actions
is a decision on your part. And it is as
simple as that with any level of
anything throughout your entire life.
This is what I prefer to do. And you act
on it in whatever way you are capable of
acting on it. So if you discover out of
all the things you are capable of doing
when you leave this interaction this
night of your time that going home is
not the thing that excites you the most.
Do the thing that does excite you the
most. As long as you're doing it with
integrity, it will be the flowing of
your path and it will clarify all levels
of your
vision. Understand? I understand. Does
that serve you? That serves that one.
What about the ear and the offbalance?
All right. It is simply your way of
showing you that you have been operating
in an offbalance definition. And also
many individuals, especially those that are
individuals, especially those that are
willing to allow large energies to
channel through them, will give
themselves a large wrap in the head to
reorient and rewire their
brain. In a sense, this is what you have
done. And it has also served the double
purpose of simply reminding you that you
have been functioning in an off-balance
manner by an off-balance definition. The
idea is that yes, feel the energy flow
in, but you live in a physical reality.
Act it out by doing what excites you the
most in and outward expressive modality
because you live in a physical world and
expression is what shows that you have
the conviction to express what you are
conviction to express what you are
learning about yourself.
If you just keep it to yourself, you are
not fulfilling the reason for why you
chose to be among all the other people
in your world. They have to be able to
see who you are through your actions to
see what you are learning and
discovering yourself to be in order for
them to be able to be served by you and
in order for them to serve you in turn.
Understand? Yes. Does that assist you?
Yes, it helps me very much. Well, thank
you. pleasant and very clear intentions,
definitions, desires, deservability,
dreams and actions to you. Thank you.
Sharing. Hello, Bashar. And to you, good
day. Good day. Um, I am right now
researching and exploring the different
methodologies of realigning the
electromagnetic energy of of the
physical body. Oh, I can you all hear
this individual? Oh, I'm sorry. Okay.
Um, and realigning the energies of the
physical body and I'm working with color
and sound. Exciting. Yes, it is. It's
very exciting. And um I would like to
know from you. I heard you just mention
to another gentleman who was up here
talking about a liver uh dysfunction
that he was experiencing about um a
specific force field to place yourself
in. as a magnetic field. A magnetic
field pulsing at 7 and 1/2 cycles per
second approximately. Can you just
visualize that? Yes, you can. Wonderful.
Okay, then then that answers my
question. Well, thank you. That was
simple. Thank you, Bash. Remember that any
Thank you, Bash. Remember that any
physiological phenomena is only an
externalized reflection of what you
already imagine to be true for you
anyway. So if you are willing to
dispense with the idea of the
intermittent symbol then you can simply
manifest it directly with your belief
structure. Great. Thank you. Thank you very much.
Great. Thank you. Thank you very much.
Sharing.
Hello Bashar. And to you good day. I
have a question about a fear that I
became aware of a couple of years ago.
Speak up. Speak up. Speak up. I have a
question about a fear that I became
aware of a couple of years ago. Yes. Um,
it's a fear of Is it still with you?
Yes. All right. It's a fear of speed. A
fear of speed. A fear of crashing if I
go too fast. Crashing if you go too
fast. And it started out very simply
that if I was with someone who drove too
fast or did a jack rabbit start or
something, I would just get terrified.
Rabbit start.
Yes. Here is such a trip.
So my question is where did the fear
come from and what can I do to keep it
from limiting me as it does at times?
May I ask you a question? Yes. Thank
you. If you went as fast as you thought
you could go, do you think you would
outdistance everyone and leave them
behind? Yes. It leaves me with a feeling of
Yes. It leaves me with a feeling of
loneliness.
Loneliness. Do you
recognize that for every vibration you
are willing to be, for every frequency,
for every reality you are willing to be,
there is always an infinite amount of
beings already waiting on that level for
you to join them.
But then I would have to leave behind
the No, no,
you will encounter the aspects of those
individuals that already exist on the
level you're going to.
to.
Now the idea again is to understand that
the external
representation does not carry meaning
intrinsically. Therefore, it's not a matter of leaving
Therefore, it's not a matter of leaving
someone behind.
Literally, the idea simply is that
everyone already exists on every level
there is to exist upon. Everyone has an
aspect on every level. Some of them are
more or less focused, more or less
concentrated, more or less expressed,
but they have aspects on every level of
reality you can possibly exist upon. So
you will still be dealing with them in
an overall sense, but you will be
dealing with the version of them that is
most representative by the level you
have now created yourself to exist upon
as well. So you haven't in a sense left
them behind. You have joined another
facet of them. Understand?
Kind of. But it sounds like I'm already
somewhere else. We are only using your
colloquial language because there is no
other way to say it. You never really go
anywhere. Not literally. All motion is
an illusion. It is all here now. It is
only the idea of listening to another
program because you have shifted your
dial. Understand? Yes. The other program, the
Understand? Yes. The other program, the
one you are no longer listening to is
still there. It is simply that you are now
there. It is simply that you are now
expressing a preference for another
program. Now you don't have to feel the idea of
Now you don't have to feel the idea of
loss or regret or sadness. That is only
based upon the assumption that you
actually are literally detached from
them. You
aren't. The idea also is that you can be
of best service to them by being most
fully who you are. Because then if they
desire to join you by seeing who you
fully are, they then get an idea by
seeing the example in you of what it is
they need to be to match you to join
you. Now if they don't want to match you, if
Now if they don't want to match you, if
they do not want in that way to share
with the you you prefer to be, then why
would you want in that sense to share
directly with
them? Understand? In other words, the
idea of having a
friend that a resents the changes that
you make by definition then means that
that person was not really being a
friend. And by judging that you can lose a
And by judging that you can lose a
friend just by changing in a way that is
natural for you is to not really believe
in what friendship is and eternity
is understand. Yes. You will always be
with all of your friends. The ones that
are willing to match your
frequency. The ones that are willing to
look at those ideas. Now any other
individuals that are not willing to look
at those ideas can still be your friend.
But the idea is that you will be of best
service to them by being fully the
friend you know yourself to be.
Otherwise, you're only giving them half
a picture of yourself. And that's not
friendship either. So in a sense, you
are not there for them if you're not
being fully who you are by going where
you need to be. Understand? Yes, I do.
Does that assist you? Yes, it does.
Well, thank you very much, my friend.
Thank you, Bishar.
Sharing. Hi, Bashar. And to you, good day.
Hi, Bashar. And to you, good day.
I too have a question about some fears
that have been All right. Well, do speak
up and share with all. I have three
fears that I Oh, three fears. Nicely
ordered. Maybe it's one fear. Anyway, all right.
Maybe it's one fear. Anyway, all right.
um that that I've been running my life
and I'm really sick of it and and I'd
like some help to overcome it and
resolve it as best I can. That you have
been doing what with your life?
That I've been running my life. Running
it or that I've that I've allowed to run
run my life. Oh, all right. Or what do
you prefer to be? What do you prefer to
do? Do you know? Um yes. Well, what is
it? I prefer not to feel this way. I
prefer to be All right. All right. But
we did not ask you what you don't
prefer. I asked you what you do prefer.
I prefer to feel more empowered. More
empowered. All
right. I was married and I recently
ended a committed relationship and the
same feelings um keep coming up and I
and it's a problem for me. The one is a
feeling of being abandoned. abandon uh
irrespective of who ends the
relationship and also I realize that I
would like to be able to surrender more
in the in to the person that I'm
committing to and also I have a fear of
being vulnerable letting my inner child
be vulnerable and I feel this divine
vulnerability um expressing my deep inner needs deep
um expressing my deep inner needs deep
inner needs why are you afraid to
express your deep inner needs you have
not given me your full definition of
vulnerability. What is your full
definition of vulnerability? In other
words, when you express these deep inner
needs, what do you believe will be the
result of that expression?
Um, I'll be hurt and abandoned. Left. In
other words, you have a negative
definition of vulnerability. Criticized.
Um, being told I'm wrong. All right. In
other words, you have a negative
definition of vulnerability. Yes. All
right. Now, would you prefer to have a
positive definition of vulnerability?
Very much so. Oh, all right. I can
suggest one. You don't have to take it.
Just my suggestion. However, to me,
vulnerability is the willingness to be
open to all that is in full and total
trust. The willingness to be open to all that
The willingness to be open to all that
is in full and total trust is what you
are talking about when you say
surrendering. It is actually taking
control. It is not giving up control. It
is taking control. That is true
surrender. But the idea simply becomes
effortless. And that is why many of you
think you're actually giving up control
because to you the only reason you feel
you're in control is when you're
expending effort. Yeah.
Therefore, when you open up in complete
vulnerability and understand that if you
are opening up to all that is, then you
are connecting to all that is to
infinite creation. By opening up to all
of it, you are connecting into it. And
if you are connecting into the infinite
creation, then you are connecting to
infinite strength, infinite power,
eternal power. And if you are willing in
that sense to trust it in a positive
way, you will then flow that infinite
power through you every time you are
willing to open up all the way. That is
vulnerability. That is power. That is
self-empowerment. That is surrender. And
that is control. It is all boiled down
in the one word trust. Trust. the
mechanism of trust which is the absolute
knowingness that you exist for a
reason. And therefore with that
perspective and that attitude, you
recognize therefore that you deserve to
exist in the manner you have determined
you would prefer to exist for no other
reason other than because you say
so. That's it.
That's all you need. Just say I deserve
it. Why? Because I exist. That's why.
Because I have been given the capability
to say and to know I deserve it. That's
why. I don't need another reason. And
when you understand that, you will
understand you are connected to
everything. And when you are connected
to everything, you will know it is not
possible for you to be abandoned.
Now, an individual in your society
shared with us a very creative
interpretation of one of your languages
words. Yeah. This individual recognized
that your word a l o n e could be
pronounced alone or all one.
alone or all one.
Which do you prefer? All one. All right.
Then if you know that being alone is
being all one, you can never be
abandoned because you are always
connected to the infinity of creation
itself by being fully open to it and
allowing it to flow through you. It may
only be the definitions you are applying
to your relationships, the expectations
you have been taught to think ought to
be there, rather than letting the
relationship be what it is for. that is
creating the difficulty you are
experiencing. For the only difficulty
usually comes from the type of
definition you have about a
circumstance. There is no circumstance
in and of itself that is inherently
difficulty causing. Only your
perspective and definition of the
circumstance can cause difficulty in
your life. Yeah. Understand? Yes. Does
this assist you? Yes. I I've also chosen
to grow through channeling and I'm
learning to express myself as a clear
vocal channel. All right. My question is
how can these issu how might these
issues color or um filter my clear
channeling process? They can color it.
If you are not willing to trust yourself
because if you're not willing to trust
yourself then in that sense you are not
allowing yourself to be a clear channel
because you do not think of yourself as
complete. Yeah. as capable, as
deserving. But whatever it is you are
experiencing in terms of your agreement
to experience that energy, yeah, is all
for the purpose of allowing you first of
all to choose how you wish to define
yourself. For the whole idea is to serve you as
For the whole idea is to serve you as
well. If the channeling doesn't serve
the channel, if the channel is not
allowed to be fully who the channel
needs to be, prefers to be then the
channel cannot be of service to anyone
else. It would be pointless. Yeah. So
again it is simply an issue of
trust. Understand? Yes. Remember as we
have shared with many
individuals you do not need a special
reason in order to know you deserve what
you prefer. If you exist then obviously
you deserve to exist. Otherwise you
wouldn't. Infinite creation is very
clear about
that. Yes. If you exist, infinite
creation must obviously believe you
deserve to treat yourself with the same
respect. Why
not understand? Yes. And be a part of
the infinite whole. Be the infinite
whole. Your version of the infinite
whole. That is what all the parts are.
Different versions of the whole.
idea, you are no less that idea than
anyone else or you wouldn't exist. Yeah. There
else or you wouldn't exist. Yeah. There
are no incomplete creations, no
extraneous and pointless ones.
Understand? Yes. If you exist, by
definition, you must
fit as you are. Not that you can't
change, but you must fit as you are or
you wouldn't exist. So, lighten up on
yourself. All right, I got it. And when
you lighten up on yourself, you will be
enlightened and your energy will
accelerate upward and your vulnerability
will become power. Understand? Yes.
Well, thank you very much. Thank you,
Bashar. At this height, you may all
enjoy a short break. We will resume
contact in approximately 10 to 15 of
your minutes.
How's everything going?
Please have a break. There's
refreshments in the other room. And you
can also get uh order tonight's tape
tonight from Lynn around the corner if
you'd like.
About 10 15 minutes. Adolf continue.
Adolf continue.
and who you would die. Uh I'm looking at
the book on um the new metaphysics
and there is a chart there which uh
really attracted my attention and my
interest and I became aware that I felt
like I understood it but not
intellectually. So I would like to ask
you to explain it a little bit more. All
right. In a simplified way. Which one?
This is the positive and negative
manifestation. Sorry.
Do you mean the idea that
contains the notions of winning and
losing? Yeah. The idea simply
is as you read it off that individuals
can create as you already know positive
methodologies or negative methodologies
to teach them what they wish to learn.
In other words, they can learn through
effortlessness or they can learn by
creating the idea of struggle. Different
degrees of this idea are simply
represented by the listings on the chart
all the way up from the idea of winning
through the idea of losing. Now these
are your notions. The notions the labels
you have applied to these concepts and
that is why we have used them in that
chart. Individuals can simply win
because they know they win. They can
lose because they believe they lose. And
all the variations in between of playing
to win which makes it take some time.
Playing to not win which makes it take
more time and always keeps as you say
the carrot out there because you enjoy
the idea of getting there rather than
being in a certain place more than
having the idea. Then there is the idea
of playing to not lose which is just
below that middle line which in that
sense means that you are quote unquote
just barely keeping up with everything.
You are not really quote unquote losing
but you are never rising above a certain
level within your own estimation of
self. There is always quote unquote just
enough but never an expanded idea of the
more that you seek. Then there is the
idea of playing to lose which means
you're not really losing so much in that
sense but you are playing the game. You
are creating a repetitive cycle in which
it seems you always give yourself a
boost up only to create the idea of
crashing back down. And then there is
simply the idea of losing reaching what
we have termed as you have termed at the
bottom of the barrel which can in a
sense connect directly into winning to
the completion of the cycle. Because as
we have said when you reach the bottom
of a barrel everywhere else is up. So in
that sense it simply represents the
polarity spectrum of the different
mechanisms that people can use to create
methodologies. It is a different way of
understanding how individuals look at
themselves and the particular
overall format or categories of the type
of energy game they might be playing
based upon what they believe to be most
likely in their reality. Does this
clarify the idea to some degree? Yes, it
does. Where is just playing? Oh, it is
all of those. I see. All of those are
playing. Uhhuh. Right. Then uh on the
other side of the
chart refers to that's not clear. Is
that positive action? In other words,
the positive side is action and is
represented by the ideas of winning,
playing to win and playing in that sense
to not win. Those are the positive
sides. They are above the line so to
speak. All of that is the positive side
and is represented by action. Below the
line as you say is the idea of
negativity and that is reaction.
Mhm. Does that explain the idea? Yes, it
Does that explain the idea? Yes, it
does. Oh, thank you. Thank you very
much. Okay. Goodbye for now. All right.
Hello again.
Sharing. Hello, Mr. Ambassador. And to
you, Mr. diplomat.
Thank you and
welcome you.
Um about 18 years ago I I
learned that uh you develop love for
someone. One way anyway, very effective
way is by being of service, excuse me,
and giving of yourself. I fell in love
with a gal just by being of service to
her. A gal. A gal. Nice. Female type.
[Music] And um she didn't give a about me,
And um she didn't give a about me,
but I loved her. And it was that Did you
want her to give to you? [Applause]
[Applause]
Well, I was hoping that she
was my help obviously out and I didn't
get anything. Oh, all right. Fair
enough. So,
So,
um I've applied that to uh every
relationship that I've been in since
then. And I I have attracted a number of these
And I I have attracted a number of these
relationships
um such that the partner that I had been
in relationships
with was reluctant or begrudged giving
to
me. And it it has caused me a lot of
um wonder what the heck's going on. The
pattern that I've created in giving in
relationship after relationship and
having people
not give back to me. Although I'm not a
needy person. I'm almost I'm I'm very
self-sufficient. So it's rare that a
person that I ask for something from
someone, right? But I don't believe that
I that I reject whatever help or giving
that they might have. But I find them
begrudging me this. You'd help share why
I created this pattern. Well, is it an
opportunity to reflect to the idea of
that person your unconditionality?
Well, certainly I'm being of service by
example. All right. But but what I don't
I enjoy being of service. Yeah. But I
don't like the one-way street of it. Why
is it a one-way street? Because they are
begrudging me being of service to me. In
what way? Why do you specifically need a
specific individual to be of service in
a certain way?
If your love is
unconditional, then you are served by
the total all in whatever way you need
to be. I do understand whether a
specific individual chooses to be a
reflection of that is not really the
complete issue. You will still get what you need
issue. You will still get what you need
from somewhere. Oh, absolutely. I do.
All right. But it then what difference
does it make? There just seems to be an
imbalance in the relationship.
Why? If you are in a relationship to
reflect to someone the idea of
unconditionality, then obviously you are
saying that they do not exhibit
unconditionality. It is a perfectly
balanced relationship. Well, the thing is I don't
relationship. Well, the thing is I don't
go into the relationship at least with a
conscious decision to go in for the
purpose of reflecting unconditionality.
Why not?
Well, I don't go into it without that.
But I you know I I don't select my
relationships to say well I'm going to
show this person who doesn't understand
unconditionality. We understand what you
are saying in that sense. Yes. Okay. But
the idea simply is that are you willing
to reflect unconditionality or not?
Yeah. Then reflect it and I do. All
right then. Don't
expect anything in return and you will
get everything you need from wherever
you need to get it from.
Yeah, I do understand that. Why not
simply attract yourself into the
understanding that if you are willing to
know you are getting it from wherever
you really need it to come from, then
there may be maybe
maybe an individual or several
individuals that will be
able to give you the service that you
require. It may not necessarily turn out
to be the one individual. You are
assuming that it might be or must
be but it will be
someone. Yeah. And therefore in that
they will by definition provide the
service that you need. It won't matter
from where it comes because it will feel
correct and it will fulfill you. So far
it hasn't felt correct. I mean I do I do
get service from wherever I need it when
I need it. Well, then to but I mean it's
like um if I say hey will you iron my
shirt and she says no. Yes. How dare you
ask me to do something for you? And I
say but I do things for you all the
time. Said well I don't want to do it
for you. You have to go someplace else.
All right. Um may I ask you a personal
question? You do. Why are you in the
relationship?
Well, not that you necessarily have to
find someone who will do that specific
thing, but we understand the general
idea of sharing that you are talking
about. And if you simply find that
you're in a relationship where someone
is not willing to share equally, why are
you there? Now, are you asking me that
as I shall I'll use the term challenge
to ask me why I've remained in the
relationship or are you asking me to
define why I truly am there at that
time? Why have you remained in it?
Well, this is a process and I'm aware
that it's a process and I'm still in a
process of understanding why it is that
I would remain in a relationship that I
have found uh well all right although
that doesn't necessarily mean that you
can't work it out somewhere else but
working it out somewhere else may mean
getting out of the relationship that's
okay too yes and I have done that I have
done that at every stage where I found
the other person not sharing in some
balanced way I have gotten out of
relationship. I've done this several
times. All right. The question is why is
it that I continue to attract what seems
to be a pattern instead
of attracting uh some kind of a balance
exchange. All right. One idea is that
the overall balanced exchange can come
from many different sources. In other
words, if you start thinking of many
different sources as one individual,
then you'll recognize you are in an
individual relationship that does give
you what you need.
instead of necessarily assuming that the
individual people in and of themselves
must represent through a specific
conduit the idea of the sharing that you
see. Okay, I do understand. In other
words, being the switcher and the mover
that you are means that you will create
your accessibility across a number of
circuits. Mhm. Not necessarily just one.
Okay, I do understand that and uh I have
found that to be quite workable. All
right, the flip side of this coin is
that um whereas I don't expect every service
um whereas I don't expect every service
from one individual, there are certain
services which a particular individual
could and very could very easily offer
me. Well, so but specifically will
refuse to give that service. Yes. So
the question is why do I keep it
cracking? Why do you keep demanding it?
What? I can't hear you.
You're offering me something. In other
words, why do you keep looking for that
specific idea? Why are you focused on a
need for that specific idea? It is that
type of focus which creates the
repetitive pattern. Why do you keep
looking for that particular avenue of
expression? What what particular avenue
are you talking about? Well, let's use
the example of someone who will simply
not iron the shirt in exchange for
something you have done. Why do you keep
looking for
that? I don't I don't specifically look
for that. I just I just feel that if I'm
in a relationship where I'm willing to
do just about anything for somebody, it
makes sense that it would be natural for
them to be willing. Oh, it may be
natural, but maybe they're functioning
in a normal mode rather than a natural
one. Now, overall, I understand what you
are saying. No, quit. You're giving me a
hard time.
No. All right. You want me to iron your
shirt?
Or is it that you wish me to iron out
the situation? No, not at all. I I just
feel that there's something more
fundamental to this than ever reflecting
to me. All right. Yes. But we also find
that for some reason we do not have
access to it because there is still
something about this particular process
that quote unquote should be obvious to
you and until it is the door isn't open
to us. In other words, I'm still working
through the process. Yes. Well, I'm not
surprised at that. Well, all
right. All we can share is to relax with
the process. relax with the apparent
repetition and remember that nothing
really is ever really truly repeated.
Nothing. Yeah. So perhaps as a
suggestion if this occurs
again quote
unquote give it a new meaning a
completely new meaning completely
different than any meaning you have ever
given it
before and see what happens. Or can you
suggest one such meaning so I can get a
feel for what you're talking about?
Well, let me ask you
this. Have you
involved these
individuals who choose to make these
refusals in a conversation that allows
them to explain their reasoning to you?
Yes. And what have you gotten? Mostly
gibberish. What are you defining as literally?
What are you defining as literally?
Literally, I get um excuses. All right.
They they come up with reasons that
they're quoting past incidents that just
didn't occur. They got things from what
I channel to be previous lovers that,
you know, that refused to do them in
service. And they then they reflect they
they somehow
um have a belief that I'm the lover that
refused them in service and they put
that on me. This is the kind of thing
that I would get.
One moment. There is a small crack in a
moment. There is a small crack in a
door.
A small question if I may.
I guess thank thank
you. What are your notions of the
idea of being in
general deprived?
That's an interesting question. My
notions in general, I I don't know that
I have a Oh, I can be said another way.
What are your notions in general of the
issue of deservability
in general? At least on an outer aware
conscious level and I have no reason to
believe that doesn't filter down to my
belief system. I believe that everyone
deserves anything that they
want. What do you believe about how an
individual might feel they have to go
about allowing themselves to allow
anything they want? I believe they need
to act with integrity. All right? And
excitement will get them there. All
right?
If every single individual that you
involved yourself with in a relationship
of this
type created the same quote unquote
refusal, every single one, how would you
feel? Did he? Why? I just I wouldn't No,
I wouldn't I wouldn't say shitty. How
would you feel? Um,
what would you be forced to look at?
Well, I think you're driving toward the
idea of deprivation. And I am not
driving toward anything at this moment.
Okay. Cancel, blank, empty. What would I
feel? I would feel that I would Let me
rephrase. Imagine if you will now with
me. Go into your imagination on a little
journey through time. Let's imagine you
are now at what you call the end of this
physical life. Okay. All right. Let us
assume now however old you are, however
young you are, does not matter. But let
us assume you know that you have done
everything you are going to do in this
life and you are simply pondering for
the last few moments the idea of what
the life has been to you and there. All
right. If you look back from that point of view
If you look back from that point of view
on these
circumstances, is anything popping up in
your imagination about an area that you
could have been looking at that now at
this point from this perspective you
recognize all too clearly about the
reasons for those interactions? Now, are
you talking about a hypothetical life or
the one that I've lived right now? Let
us say the one you have lived right now.
So, I would have to be at the end right
at this moment. Okay. I I You are at the
end of the life right now. Look back to
this now to the ideas you hold within
you now and look from the perspective
that you are literally wrapping up your
life. Okay? And now you look back on
these circumstances truly look back on
them and recognize now from your now
perspective how they fit and what
purposes they serve. Does anything come
up in your imagination when you drift in
that particular idea that you are not
seeing at this point?
or I shall say that you did not see back
then. Are there any new perspectives on
it from the perspective you have now at
the end of your life that are different
from the perspective you had when you
were in the middle of those
circumstances about what purposes they
served?
I'm I'm I'm looking all right and I'm
not seeing anything at this stage. Since
the accessibility seems relatively
closed to us, we would suggest that this
evening of your time, you go into one of
the relaxed meditative states, whichever
you prefer, and allow yourself to
examine this circumstance from the
perspective we are suggesting now, as if
you are literally at the end of your
life. Mhm. looking back upon it and
seeing from that perspective what you
may not be allowing yourself to see
now but doing it when you have the time
to relax and truly drift in your
imagination and see what pops up right
now may be a little too confining to
allow you to expand in that way. So this
evening of your time when you are
drifting off to sleep, imagine that you
have if you wish to imagine that you
have already died and look back upon the
life itself with the expanded point of
view you would assume you would have
being a non-physical being. Okay? And
see what pops up in your dream reality
or even just before you drift off to
sleep. Well, I don't mean to prolong
this because I know that there are
people waiting, but I do know that um in
a sense I have a feeling that in a past
life that there has that this relates to
something in a past life that I have
brought into this. All right, let that
be a part of the overall idea. You may
discover or explore tonight, but simply
see what comes up and see how the pieces
fit and share with us if you are willing
the next time we converse what you have
discovered. All righty. Oh, thank you
very much. Thank you.
Shooting.
Hello, Bashar. And to you, goodbye.
Hello. Um, this is the first time I've met you.
Um, this is the first time I've met you.
Me, too. In terms of meeting you. This
is the first time I have ever done this.
Ever. Ever. Ever. So, we get to be in a
totally fresh moment. Absolutely.
Starting from zero right now. Go. I'm in
a dilemma. I I have two things that I'm
supposed to be doing. Supposed to
supposed to supposed to. I have a lot of
supposed to in my mind. May I remind you
that you are supposed to nothing. Good.
But that you can anything. Well, well, I
Well, well, well. I want to I want to
make a decision that will help me. Oh,
go right ahead. In the future. In the
future. What about now? Well, now I I'd
rather do nothing. Nothing. Yeah.
Nothing. Nothing. Nothing. Travel and
and not That's not nothing. Well, I
don't want to worry about money and
don't commitment. Well, don't don't
worry about them. Just let them manifest
in your life as representative symbols
of abundance when you do the thing that
excites you the most. Well, I' I'd
rather have some of the things that
excite me the most give me better money
so that I Why? Because then I wouldn't
have to do the things that don't excite
me. Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no. Fix me. Fix me. You
are not broken. broken.
Now
remember, remember,
remember,
remember, not dismember, remember. Pull
yourself together.
consolidate, integrate. People always
tell me I have to focus and there'sh
focus. Focus. Focus is not effort.
Effort. Effort is not concentration. No.
Okay. Focus is allowance. Focus is
clarity. That's all. Just clarity.
Clarity of intention, clarity of
definition, clarity of desire, clarity
of deservability, and clarity of action.
That's focus. That's all there is to
Clarity of desire is about 10 things and
people tell me one moment. Yes, you can.
Oh, one moment. Now, first of all, first
definition, abundance. Abundance.
Abundance. Abundance is simply the
ability to do what you need to do when
you need to do it. Period. That's all
abundance is. Now, it can come in the
form you have on your planet that you
call money. But there are also many
other ways abundance can express itself
and it will always express itself along
the path of least resistance. Just like
electricity, when you broaden your
definition of what you think abundance
is, then you will allow all the
different ways it could come to you to
come to you because it doesn't always
have to come in the form of money. And
money is not always the quickest and
shortest route. That's right. So
somebody could give me a ranch.
Absolutely they could. But when you are
expressing the idea that excites you the
most that you are capable of acting upon
then everything else that excites you
becomes a detail under the thing that
excites you the most and will all fall
into place according to your strongest
and clearest definition and excitement
and intention. Everything else becomes a
detail that is subordinate to the most
overwhelming thing that excites you that
you are capable of acting upon. If the
thing that excites you the most, you are
not capable of acting upon, do the next
thing that you are capable of acting
upon that excites you the most. And it
will lead you into the circumstances to
give you the capability of acting upon
the thing that excites you the most that
you may not have had the capability of
acting on a moment before. Excitement is
the thread that leads to all other
excitement. As long as you're acting
upon the things that excite you the most
with integrity, which means functioning
as a whole idea and not stopping to
think of yourself as a collection of
parts or compartments that is scattered
here and there. But recognize that all
the different things that have your
attention are all part of the same whole
idea and will all fall into place
automatically when you act upon the one
that represents your strongest
intention. Then you can flow. That is
focus. That is trust. That is allowance.
That is willingness to understand that
everything by definition that excites
you must sit and will have a perfect
timing in which to do so. Understand?
Yes, I understand. Excitement is your
physical translation of the vibratory
energy that represents the path you
chose to be. That's what it is. That's
what it's for. It tells you three
things. One, as we have just said,
excitement tells you that it is the
thing that is most you. Two, it tells
you therefore that because it is the
most you, it is the thing you can do
most effortlessly because what would be the
effortlessly because what would be the
point of struggling to be you? Third, it
tells you that it is the thing that you
will be able to do most abundantly by
the definition we have given you because
then it will allow you to keep doing the
thing that excites you the most in a
more expanded way.
Therefore, you will automatically be
able to attract the opportunities to
allow you to do the thing that excites
you the most effortlessly and
abundantly. Maybe not always in the way
your mentality expects. Maybe not always
the way your society says it ought to
happen, but always, always, always the
way that represents what is most
effortless and abundant for you to do
the thing you need to do. when you need
to do it. Not a moment sooner but not a
moment later. Understand? Yes, I understand. So
later. Understand? Yes, I understand. So
let co incidents and synchronicity
abound in your life because that is how
life works when you let it. There are no
accidents and nothing nothing nothing is
too good to be true.
Nothing nothing nothing nothing.
I'll take that to heart. Thank you.
Well, thank you. Thank you very much.
Does that serve you? Yes, very much. Oh,
thank you. You are welcome. Thank you.
Sharing.
Oh, the shark. I'm tell you goodbye. Uh,
I'm about 80 lbs overweight and I'm
starting to lose weight again. No. All
right. This time I'm working with my
belief system and changing my Oh, what I
want to eat, but I ran into something on
a transcript from Dr. Peeles. Did it
hurt? No, it might. He says that if you know
No, it might. He says that if you know
some people want a slim body in this
life that they have the body that they
need to fulfill their purpose in this
life. Yes. And if they wanted a slim
body they would have a body that would
eat five times a day and never put on
any weight. Correct. Not that you cannot
change but the idea is to simply
understand that many individuals create
the idea of weight for many different
reasons and some individuals create it
for a reason that actually is of service
both to them and perhaps even to other
people for a
while. I see. Now there are many
different reasons why you may create the
idea of weight and I can simply define a
few. One will be the idea as we have
discussed with many individuals that you
are literally waiting to do what excites
you the most. And since mass is energy
and energy is mass, when you do not use
the energy and flow it through you by
waiting to do what excites you the most,
then all the energy will come in, turn
to mass, and hang around you until you
decide to turn it back into energy and
use it and flow it by not waiting to do
what excites you the most. Secondly,
sometimes an individual when exploring
the idea of accelerating will believe
that if they do not add some weight to
ground them, they will become flighty
and airy and lose touch with the earth.
So they will create balance to hold
themselves down because they think they
need that to balance themselves and keep
them in contact with physical reality by
creating so much of physical reality
around them. Some individuals will think
that this new energy they are
discovering within themselves is so
accelerated that if they don't have a
little bit of a buffer that by the time
they get to acclimate to it, it could
burn them out, strip them raw, thin them
down to nothing. So they will add a
little extra weight so that by the time
they get to where they want to be, they
will have used up just the right amount
of weight and will be exactly who they
want to be. These are a few of the
reasons. Look, I see. So sometimes you
can understand that you simply assume
that it is to your best benefit
sometimes to have the idea of the way.
Not that you really need to have it, but
the way you might be thinking about what
it is you're learning and doing in life
might simply be reflected in your wisdom
of taking care of yourself in a way that
will allow you to know beyond a shadow
of a doubt that you can do whatever it
is you want to do and explore whatever
it is you want to explore. And that by
the time you get to where you want to
be, quote unquote, you will not be
burned away. Understand? I do. Does this
assist you? Yes, it does. Thank you.
Well, thank you very much,
Sharon. Good evening, Michelle. And to
you, good day. Yes, good day. Actually,
I meant to say good day. Oh, thank you.
Good evening.
I talked to you about this um last
November. One moment. One moment. Yes,
it is because in the area of my planet
it is
they continue.
I really uh enjoyed the description of
dawn on your planet that you gave us a
couple weeks ago. Oh, thank you. We have
many of that variety of tree that like
some of your flowers open up totally
upon the approach of sunlight. The whole
tree is quite collapsed and thin during
the night and opens up all its branches
creating the canopy of the jungle during
the day which does not exist at night.
Do you spend much time on the surface of
your planet at all? Do you go down to
picnics from your ship? Well, in a
sense, yes, though we do not eat much. I
know. Well, that's lovely. I I've thought of
Well, that's lovely. I I've thought of
that often. I sort of create that idea
of being on your planet. All right. Very
enjoyable. good preparation for creating
your world to be the way you desire it
to be. If you wish to use us as a
template, that's fine. I do that a lot.
All right. A lot of us do. How may we
serve you? Well, I want to talk to you
about hot flashes. Hot flashes. Yes. I
for the last year and off and on for
several years before that have been
experiencing my body
just getting so hot. It comes on in
about a minute. I'm just dripping sweat
and I feel as though I'm going to burst
into flame. Oh. All right. Now, I am
doing what excites you the most. Okay.
And I've had some ideas about this. One
has to do with acceleration. Yes.
Because I feel I'm accelerating at work
speed sometimes. Oh, why? So, I would
like you to reflect to me. Um, I'd
really like to integrate this in a way
that I wouldn't be experiencing it in
this manner. All right. How about having
a cold flash to balance it out? What a
great idea. I've um in fact I've
entertained that notion of you know
creating an arctic freeze instantly. All
right. The idea once again to some
degree can be connected to the
technology you are now discovering upon
your planet called superc conductivity.
When you crystallize yourself, cool your
temperature down by being more and more
as you are becoming in the moment. In
that way, the acceleration you are
feeling doesn't necessarily have to be
experienced through the friction of the
hot flash. You can by becoming
superconductive allow the energy to go
through you without resistance
whatsoever. Well, I've been
Well, I've been
um kind of relaxing and going with it.
All right. As much as I can. for some
degree you are still going to be
connected to some of the idea systems of
your physical reality as well and you
are simply playing some of these out in
terms of what your society expects at a
certain timing in your life. Yes. Well,
the last time I talked to you last
November, we had a conversation that
ended with me saying, "Well, I saw this
coming and you said maybe that's the
answer." So, possibly I expected when I
got to a certain age that I would need
to go through this, right? But you could
always transform it. You can always
transform it. Look at it this way. Now
you are clear enough if you are willing
to be recognizing it that way in your
own mind to simply treat it as raw
energy. Not that it necessarily brings
any particular reason that you have to
delve deeply into but simply treat it as
an after effect that you are still
connected to in terms of your society.
And if you treat it simply as raw energy
and you become more superconductive by
cooling down and crystallizing then the
energy can go through you unimpeded
without resistance and without the
friction that creates the hot flash.
Okay. I I understand the concept because
I've done that with anger my own. All
right. Very good. Resisting it. Very
good. Then use your imagination to
create the methodology that works best
for you. And your imagination will
crystallize you. Remember all of you,
your imagination is a template, a
template and a library of all the
probable frequencies and realities you
can be. When you imagine something you
desire to be and you create that
picture, that image of you in that
situation doing the thing you love to
do. All you have to do is watch the you
in the picture and feed that you
different situations and see how that
you would handle them. Then all you have
to do is act like you see that you
acting and you will be that reality.
Filter the situations in your life
through your imagination. Don't filter
your imagination through the situations
in your life. Because your imagination
will show you how you can most easily
transform any situation into one that
the you prefer to be will be able to
handle in a specific way. That little
you running around in the picture of
your mind is the you you can prefer to
be. And if you simply act like you see
that individual act with regard to any
situation you feed him or her, then
simply mimic, mirror the methodologies,
the attitudes, the language, the body
language, the approach, the conviction
that you see that little you in your
imagination have. And as you mirror it
and as you mimic it, you will radiate
that frequency in your reality. and you
will have and attract the life you see
in that picture of the ideal you. That's
what your imagination is for. That's why
it is as powerful a tool as it is.
That's why we always refer you back to
it because it's all you really need. It
gives you every methodology that will
work for you if you simply pay attention
to how the you in the imagination
picture acts and then act that
way. Understand?
It is very simple, very simple.
Also at this timing, we would enjoy
sharing with you the simple notion that
no matter to what other levels you are
connecting, no matter from what other
levels you are siphoning
information, remember that because you
are your own reality, you are always
creating your own
version out of your own energy. energy
of whatever else you may be connecting
to. So all that you are ever really
coming into contact with is yourself in
another format in another
modality. Therefore the whole idea of trusting it
Therefore the whole idea of trusting it
is simply the recognition that it is
after all only you.
So perhaps a little motto will remind
you to let it through. It's only
you. Let it through. It's only you.
No resistance. No resistance. Super
conductivity. At this timing, we extend
to each and every one of you our
superconductive appreciation and our
appreciation and our
unconditional love. We thank you for
allowing us to experience the sharing
that you are. We thank you for
cocreating the dream of this reality and
the reality of this dream. We bid you a
fond and exciting and loving good day. [Applause]
How'd it go?
Thank you all for being here