a [Music]
say how are you all this day of your
time as you create time to
exist Let's Get
Serious s i r i u s that may be your
entitlement tonight if you wish Let's
Get Serious the idea being on behalf of a
Serious the idea being on behalf of a
request made last week of your time to
discuss the third part of the Triad of
Your World our world and the world that
orbits the star you call serious to
illuminate some of the idea of the
energy of the beings that exist in that
particular Stellar system of
awareness we have discussed from time to
time with you the IDE
that there are different levels of
consciousness as you call it some of
which in your terminology exist in
physiological manner some of which exist
in non-physiological manner more in what
you would call etheric state of
dimensionality energy State of
Consciousness the
idea of the Triad of energy represented
by your planet of Earth our planet of
esani and the civilization round serious
we have labeled
s will be representative of the Body
Mind and Spirit of an overall
Consciousness that together our three
civilizations form not that you do not
belong not that we do not belong to
other Triads other patterns other
interactive levels of consciousness as
well but this one particular
Triad has a lot to do
with the definitions of the route shall
we say that you are taking in your
upward spiral in your Ascension in your
acceleration of awareness within
yourself it is to some degree more
directly representative of manifestations
representative of manifestations
reflected back to you of your own higher
Consciousness in many ways even though
they are beings unto
themselves there is an affinity a
connection a link between the energy of
the star system Sirius and your own
Earth in many different ways
now serious civilization have contacted
your planetary Civilizations for quite
some time thousands of your years as you
count times but something that we have not
times but something that we have not
completely discussed before in specific
detail is that they have interacted with
your civilization from many different
levels for they have had in what you
call the past a more physiological
counterpart that to some degree not only
talath but in your terminology somewhat
physiologically interacted with some of
you from time to time in your past
civilizations your past cultures upon
your planet now we have at one time described
planet now we have at one time described
as you your world is in your terms third
planet from our sun and our world asani
is third planet from our sun we have
also to some degree said that the planet
the world that is represented by the
serious Consciousness is also third in a
sense from the Sun but not third in the
same way not spatially
dimensionally for there are three levels
of the civilization of syrius one that
you would call fourth density one that
you would call fifth density and the one
to some degree you may be most familiar
with through these interactions the
sixth density level that is called
sasin where they are totally
non-physical as you would understand
physicality and exist more or less in
what you would call an energy State an
energy CA now their ancient fourth density
CA now their ancient fourth density
representative cell to some
degree were
as many of your ancient cultures
perceived them amphibious but not
exactly to the degree that they were
described in some of what you call your
ancient American Indian your ancient
African and your ancient Sumerian lore
they were not in your terms literally
half fish as has been described in some
of the
deification that your planet has created
of them to represent them
by but they were understood to some
degree to be of somewhat amphibious
nature in that sense and that is why
among many other reasons there is such a
strong state of
identification between the Syria
civilization and the civilization on
your planet you call the Dolphins and
the whale and why they have been in
telepathic communication for many
thousands of your years they are similar
in energy format in many ways and while
the physiological configuration of the
old Force density serious civilization
was not like your dolphin and whale
civilization their energy was sufficient
to cause what you would call a
camaraderie an empathy an identification
to take place and so there
Communications have been ongoing for
quite some time even while the land
human civilization on your planet has
been waking up from its deep sleep of
forgetfulness now some of those
interactions that took place here here
and there to some degree are
responsible for some of the
representations of
cultural religious political
economic ideas that manifested and
Blossom upon your planet we do not wish
to impart the idea or impression that
extraterrestrials are complete
responsible for the entire idea of your
cultural phenomena sociological
phenomena no but some interaction has
taken place and has created in your
terminology changes in the course of how
you saw events as a
society because none of you are original
to your planet
anyway many of you have all of you have
connections of A Sort to other
dimensions other levels of existence and
some of these were simply established
from time to times in various modalities
but as the serious civilization
progressed and
accelerated in your terms
Evolution took place they
transformed from the physical fourth
density state into a more quasy physical
non-physical fifth density state and
then into a completely nonphysical sixth
density state but to some degree because
all realities exist in a sense at the
same time all interactions on all levels
are still taking place especially
because in your civilization you are
still Awakening out of third density
into your own fourth density
manifestation now the serious
civilization does represent to some
degree our own higher
Consciousness they are representative of
the evolution my civilization is most
directly headed for as we move into the
idea of fifth density from our fourth
density existence the last stage of
physicality as you are moving into that
last stage of fourth density physicality
and eventually will in a sense take our
place in the Triad we will take their
place in the Triad they will move on to
another idea altogether and then another
member another civilization will then in
your terms fill your as you say shoes in
the dryad now we have said that most
likely most likely not definite but most
likely this will be a civilization
within the star grouping you call
Barnard star cluster they are
approximately this Civilization now at a
point equivalent to what you would call
your Renaissance historical
Renaissance historical
term now the serious
civilization is much again in an energy
sea they are in a state of complete
Consciousness if you wish any kind of a
representation of their world as such
you can perhaps give this physiological
analogy imagine
a ball of clear light clear energy on
the surface and as you sink slowly into
it it becomes white white white energy
and the more you go toward the center it
then condenses and collapses into what
you would call a bright electric blue
electromagnetic energy and at the very
center is what you would typically call
a black hole
gate now this idea
of their existence existing as energy
forms in an energy sea allows them to
either project themselves t empathically
as individuals or as one homogeneous
energy one homogeneous Consciousness and
to some degree it can be said
technically speaking that they do this
projection and communication with other
civilizations that that black hole gate
at the very center of their world it is
an interdimensional gate that links to
all levels all dimensions and through
which they can communicate in either
Direction with any level any
Dimension this idea
now has allowed them this gate now has
allowed them to as you say step
up their ability to communicate with
many of you now that you as a
civilization have stepped up your
ability to receive the idea of what you
would call higher frequencies higher
vibrations May I take a moment to remind
you once again biological life is the
most efficient transmitter and
receiver so recognize that as each and
every one of you in your own way in your
own time decide to open yourself up to more
time decide to open yourself up to more
expressiveness of the Consciousness that
you are more recognition and
expressiveness of the frequency that you
are you will become more
sensitized to the frequency they are
always bathing beaming your world in
because they are always sending an
unbroken radiation of unconditional love
and energy thought forms thought
patterns for you to tap
into in that sense
now approximately in your terms of
physical counting that star their star you call
counting that star their star you call
serious is within what you would call 10
approximately of your light years in
your terminology in your physical
Dimension it takes 10 of your years 10
of your Orbits for a beam of light to
reach from your star to their star from
their star to your star but understand
that the telepathic link is
instantaneous that what you call the
black hole gate circumvent physiological
space connect all dimensions in the
immediate here and now and through that
it is as if they literally overlap you
literally overlap you are intertwined
with you even in much the same way that
we are and all civilizations and all
dimensions are intertwined
holographically with each
other each and every one of you and each
and every being has that same Central
gate that same Central black hole in a
sense through which you can receive and
send any idea any information can create
any interaction and
interaction and
so you can always be aware when you are
in a very energized and balanced and
relaxed and ecstatic State be aware of
all the frequencies all the spectrum of
energy and information that is always
available for any of
you to rise the crest of that way
always identification with with their
very high energy can assist in your
acceleration but it is not that they are
doing it for you you must meet them
halfway in a sense that is where we come
in for we are to some degree
representative of the halfway vibration
between you and them we are the band in
a sense of mentality of electromagnetic
energy of Consciousness that represents
what you are to some degree becoming
what you are headed for in your
civilization we are in that sense by by
allowing identification to take place
between our civilizations reflecting to
you your own self-chosen future in a
sense not that it will be specifically
as we have chosen to express our
civilization you will create your own
version of it but the energy the pattern
the identification will be very similar
and then once again as you then move to
the Stars open to the Stars you will
literally be FL going sliding on
Starlight using light itself for all
that you need all your power all your
understanding recognizing that light is
the Matrix in which all information that you
Matrix in which all information that you
need is intertwined and
interlocked and when you open that light
by shining as a brilliant star yourself
you will then match the frequency of all
of creation's life and know everything
you need to know right
now as you
are you are made of
light so when you lighten
up and don't be so
serious then you too will
reflect the serious
nature of their
Consciousness and your own higher self
and Fuller
self we thank you for having such
a interesting language to play around
[Music] with there will be
more in what you would call the near
future of communication directly from
serious energy as there has been from
time to time in your past through these
interactions but as changes occur and
expansions occur also accordingly will its energy
occur also accordingly will its energy
reflect those changes and expansion now
one moment one
moment you have heard us discuss many
times the idea that the Transformations
you go through in no way shape or form
need to be in your terms
catastrophic and that the things that
you fear in that sense generally will
attract you into negative circumstances
because fear is of a light vibration to
negative ity and you know we have
discussed that you always have an
opportunity to transform anything in a
positive way and in your terms to
alleviate and relieve a lot of the
negative pressure so that even though
things may be felt towards what you
might call even a negative Direction
they do not have to be felt in as strong
a manner as perhaps it would have been
had you been completely locked in the
idea of negative perception and fear and
so therefore understand that what we are
about to say in no way shape or form for
those those that are familiar with us is
meant to project into you the idea in
any way of unsettling
nature but we would in this sense simply
allow you to know and in no way shape or
form is this an
absolute but there is in our perception
a
likelihood depends on you a
likelihood that within what you call the
next week of your time there may be a
little shaking going
on but [Music] [Music]
relax
relax at this time allow us once
again to extend to you our deepest
appreciation in allowing our
civilizations to interact with your
civilizations that is human sitation for
your two alien species upon your
planet we thank you for allowing our
association to interact with your
Association so that together we may
become one Association of love and light
and joy in return for the gift of your
willingness to co-create these sharings
now this day of your time I will ask you
how may I you good day I have a question
um 27 years ago when I was born my
biological parents decided to give me up
to other parents to raise me right and I
was just wondering about the biological
parents if they are still living in the
LA
area in your terminology this is sketchy
for us it is our immediate perception
that one is and one
isn't however it is our stronger
perception that they simply acted as
facilitators for something that your
quote unquote life parents did not find
the timing to
do and simply brought you in when it was
most convenient so that everyone would
be together at the appropriate timing
this happens very
often in a sense therefore recognize
that what you call your life parents
have been your biological parents before
in other lives it's simply that the
timing didn't work out that way this
time so others that are very familiar to
you who did not necessarily need to
maintain the existence of what you would
call a child facilitated as the Gateway
through which you could maintain and
attain physicality and then simply gave
you over to the parents to some degree
you had made an agreement to be
with understand mhm is there a chance
that we may um meet my B biological
parents and I meet in the
future it is possible but it is a
stronger perception that this may not be
like until either much later on in your
until either much later on in your
physical life or even after the physical
life itself when reassessments are made
some of it depends upon the things you
explore there is always an opportunity
to meet them in what you call your dream
reality that is what you call your free
zone where all the ideas all the
ramifications and manifestations that
you wish to maintain as a specific idea
in physical reality can be unlocked for
a while you can always meet them in what
you call your dream reality and the
stronger perception you have of the idea
that physical reality and dream reality
are one ideas then you can accelerate
the possibility of interacting with at
least one of them in physiological terms
however it is our immediate perception
that this is not something which may
happen in what you call your near future
and does not need
you great thank you very much will this
suffice yes that's fine thank you V
thank you
Shing hi this is the first time I've
been here oh is the first time I am
interacting with you too yes very good
um I'm curious about channeling and yes
do i Channel if so could you all of you
Channel okay anytime you allow yourself
to flow any complete creative expression
through yourself with joy without doubt
that's channeling
that is the expression of the fullness
of your being it does not have to be an
association with what you colloquially
call a another entity in order for it to
be channeling you're all channeling in a
sense you are actually channeling the
personality that you are too the person
that you think yourself to be is
actually channeled because you can
actually be any person any Persona you
wish to be it can change your persona is
in a sense an artificial construct so
even the idea of maintaining a
particular personage is actually a
channeling you could change it
completely sometimes even
physically understand so far yes so in
that sense you're channeling okay now
the question actually is if the idea
intrigued you in what way would it
excite you the most to allow your
recognition of chaning to express itself
got it yes no tell me no no that's my
question for you because it's up to you
to decide what is the most exciting way
you wish to express yourself so you tell
me because I will give you this the way
that you are more often than not
attracted to is the indication of the
way you can probably do it as you say
best so are you attracted to do it in
any particular
way I'm I'm not sure I'm confused I
guess IUS all right that's a good
start a good way to allow yourself to
open up to more things to create that
state of cusion that unlocks you from
your previous assumptions and allows you
to broaden your definition that's what
confusion is for at least in my world
the idea therefore is to understand and
recognize in your imagination What
definitions do you have of the idea you
call channeling and which of those
definitions attract you the strongest I
have a lot of family members that have a
deceased so therefore I feel that
sometimes when I talk about them or that
kind of thing then I speak
and it's as if they're telling me to
tell them sometimes it is however once
again remember it is not always the case that
remember it is not always the case that
when an individual in your terms
physically dies that they have nothing
better to do than hang around waiting
for you to contact right all right this
we have discovered has become somewhat
of a mythology on your planet okay they
have busy lives to live they have new
things to learn they have to orient
themselves to completely what is to them
new reality great they are very busy
however many of them will choose to be
in your terms guides and there will
always be at least some level some
aspect of the Consciousness you knew
them to be that will be able on some
level to quote unquote hang around and
respond to your interaction so yes that
can be one way if you feel that you can
be of Aid and assistance in the
facilitation of information from
individuals that have had physical lives
on your planet and that that information
may help individuals who still have
physical lives on your planet then that
can be one way is that the way you are
most strongly attracted to is that the
way that excites you the most is there
any other way you could express the idea
or would want to express it uh the only
other way I can see it is with animals I
work with animals and it's non you know
so there's no nonverbal communication as
such but you can verbalize it for your
own species yeah or does that excite you
to think of doing it that
way it has an P but change I'd like to
change that oh right go right
ahead I don't know you don't know
where's your imagination I it's been at
rest for while sure I see well let's
wake it
up now but I still it's still it's still
with the animals there's a whale still
with the animals there's a whale that
has you know a netting completely around
it in San Diego why can't that be helped
I mean why why not that's what I'm
saying why well then should I down there
and help it
is that what you want to be no I don't I
don't think I'd be of use you don't
think you'd be of use why not no why not
um cuz I physically couldn't do it why
not I'm not a swimmer not that good of a
swimmer that I there all right but would
your proximity to that location perhaps
attract someone who is and who could
help you possibly well all right you
don't have to you say sweat about the
details the details take care of
themselves as you act upon your
strongest intention act upon it key word
act upon it you will attract if you need
help all the help you need in whatever
way you need it automatically because
those are the details that fulfill your
strongest intention you are holding back
from making a move taking a step that
you really want to take because you are
saying well the detail they're not there
then you are not following your
instincts you are worrying about about
the details rather than simply following
your intuition and trusting that the
details will take care of themselves
which they always do right well thank up
to you up to you completely completely
completely up to you but I can guarantee
100% that when you follow your strongest
intentions you will always accomplish
what you
want understand yes so if that does
excite you if it does motivate you then
by all means go but it's up to you if
you feel you can be of great assistance
where you are then be so in whatever way
you can be but recognize when you are in
fact denying your true feeling that if
you really are more motivated to go down
there even though you have no idea how
you're going to help if that's your
strongest motivation go because it is
your strongest motivation for a reason
you don't have to immediately
analytically know what those reasons are
what the details are that will round out
the idea but if you act upon it with
conviction you will find out if you
don't you won't and you wonder I wonder
what would have happened if I would
have I wonder I
wonder now if something in your terms
negative happens don't blame yourself
for not having done that's not going to
help the whale mhm understand yes but if
that is the area that excites you the
idea of communication with what you call
animal Consciousness then act upon that idea in
Consciousness then act upon that idea in
whatever way you are literally inspired
to
act it is an inspiration
following does that help you yes thank
you well thank you for allowing your
imagination to wake up
yes thank you very much you are welcome
thank you sharing good day Bes to Fourth
density by changing in their brain
pattern yeah you we want discuss now not
all of them but a great deal of them
have done so the idea simply is that
some of it was in your terms done as you
say physically
surgically some of it was done then
later simply
mentally most of it really simply has to
do first of all with the belief and
understanding a true knowledge that
physical and non-physical reality are
simply different expressions of the same
one existence and that there really
isn't a big difference between the two
until you make a big difference between
the two that was their first thing
remember that they lived in a society to
begin with that perpetuated the reality
of
Dreams understand such is the Aborigines
yes and therefore if you know and if you
are brought up to know dreams are real
then you can concoct the dream and step
into into it literally and it will be
another vibratory dimension of
experience and you will then in your
term disappear from the other dream that
you were dreaming
before understand yes so one very strong
method of assistance they left behind
are the idea of the crystal skulls that
you may be aware of on your planet for
they contain in what you might call
magnetic molecular structures
holographically within the skull all the
patterns of arrangement that are
necessary in the neuronic pathways of
the brain to create the same effect they
are left as Keys as markers in that
sense the easiest way to align yourself
to allow the skull to align your
neurological Pathways of electrical
activity in the brain to match their
brain activity to be able to open the
same doors is to sit yourself in front
of one of the skulls and look into its
eye if you find in this way that the
eyes reflect to you
ideas and images of things that you may
have pressed within yourself belief
systems that you may have bought into
that now are allowed by the skull to
Bubble to the surface if you find you
cannot face them and if you are fearful
of them and can integrate them you will
not align you will not open the door and
that is what you call the Safety Lock if
you can align if you can allow yourself
to clear with love and light then all
those doors will be able to be opened to
you in that sense all it takes is the
alignment the skull in that sense can be
used to reflect that alignment to you
but individuals who cannot handle that
idea will allow themselves far too much
fear and will not be able to even face
the skull for a very long period of
time understand yes so that is one way
you can match their idea did they create
theol yes although not all of them some
of the older ones in your terminology
date all the way back to what you would
call adalante in
time they did match some of them but not
all of them the Mitchell hedge's one one
of the oldest so that's Atlantean rather
than Mayan Moro and more many other
things one final question can you tell
me if the Mayan culture of flattening a
newborn child's head to make it flat and
pointy had something to do with this
procedure it did not so much have to do
with that specific procedure it had more
to do with a
representation of a physiological symbol
of what you call Simply higher
intelligence the idea to some degree of
creating a certain pressure in a certain
area now this did not have to be done
this to some degree was done
ritualistically a little bit from some
ancient misunderstanding some of it was to
misunderstanding some of it was to
create a certain degree of pressure in
one area to
relocate certain ideas or Pathways
neurologically to access other areas of
the brain more than the ones that your
species was used to accessing also to
some degree some of this practice was
for the purpose of mimicking beings they
had actually encountered whose heads
were shaped more like that and they
considered to be of higher intelligence
than yourself understand where were those
yourself understand where were those
beings from not
now okay I thought I'd try all
right I'll give you credit for
that some of of it did have to do with
the setting up the beginnings of the
procedure however but it was not the complete
however but it was not the complete
idea it does not have to be done that
way some of it also was stemmed
from a negative
reaction to things that happened in the
destruction of
Atlantis in an attempt to suppress the
thought centers that they held
responsible for creating the mess to
begin with understand yes does that answer
with understand yes does that answer
your question sufficiently it does thank
you well thank you very much have a
wonderful time in your exploration and
Discovery thank you Bashar well thank
you
sharing hello B and to you good
day well I'm hoping that you can help me
One Moment One Moment do speak up so
that all May
okay I'm hoping that you can help me to
understand why I keep creating a reality
that I do not prefer oh I see all right
this is in the area of intimate
relationship all right I was um I'm from
India and I lived there most of my life
I was 16 when my parents arranged my
marriage to someone who was uh
physically and emotionally abusive no
all right so after several years I left
him yeah then I got got into another
relationship where he was even more
abusive all right then I came here yes
and here well is really surprising no
but I mean I don't I don't like this oh
all right all right you are changing you
are learning it does not have to
continue at all but the idea at least on
the surface that is relatively obvious
is that you are simply going off of Old
momentum old reactionary energy and
because of a greater fear you are
continuing to attract act similar ideas
mostly because of the fear as a reaction
to the idea that you might run into it
again because you simply were brought as
you say ingrained with belief systems
that make that seem to be more likely or
at least made it seem to be more likely
that you would attract that type of
individual simply because that is the
impression that was created within your
makeup when you were young but it's not
in my conscious belief why but you can
now get back in with the original
definition it may in your terms take
some time but it does not really have to
take very much time the idea is for you
to create a very powerful pictorial
representation of who it is you would
prefer to be and to see yourself engaged
in what you would call relationship with
other individuals in what you would
delineate as a positive modality can you
in your terms conjure up such a picture
yes all right do you believe beyond the
shadow of a doubt that the image you
have in your imagination of yourself
having that positive interaction is
actually something you can do yes do you
believe it is something you really
deserve yes I all right now do you
believe it will take some effort in
order to actually create that
scenario I don't think so all right but
the fact that it isn't there means one
moment okay
First Step do not judge what is to be
automatically negative just because it
doesn't match your
expectations because it isn't
automatically negative and many times in
fact as we have observed in your
civilization almost all the time the
only reason that in your terminology
something would seem to continue in a
negative state is because you have been
taught that this means this and this
means this and if you see this that's
negative if you're getting this that's
negative and there's no other way this
can be MH you are dealing with very
fundamental core definitions now the
idea in and of itself that you do not
have what you call a relationship that
is not inherently
negative it just
is it doesn't have a mean meaning I
understand that you have a desire but
just because for right now your life
does not necessarily contain what you
think ought to be a reputation of that
desire doesn't mean that your life right
now is
negative understand yes I'm quite happy
the way I am but I just feel that what's
I mean maybe this is something I should
learn from this B of relationship well
go ahead that is also one of the first
things you can ask yourself is what am I
getting out of the perpetuation of this
idea now do understand something else
you have had many strong reflective past
lives as we perceive your energy one of
the things you have chosen to do as we
perceive your list of agreements is to
serve and this does not mean you have to
suffer but is to serve as a reflection
of someone who is going to break a lot
of sociological mes and patterns and
you're willing to serve as a reflection
for individuals that may in their
terminology be a little bit weaker feel
that they are a little bit less strong
and give into their negative side and
take it out on you but the idea of your
reaction of of your reaction you
standing up for what you believe is true
for you in the faith of what they
present to you can help them change as
well and to some degree once again not
meaning you must suffer because of the
agreement but to some degree we perceive
you have made an agreement to be willing
to be reflective to these individuals to
show them in no uncertain terms what
their behavior will cause you to do so
that they will no longer have what they
desire because of the way they act so
you have been willing to some degree to
function as a reflective mother image
lover image sister image in that way
again it does not mean you have to
suffer and in a sense in all reality you are
and in a sense in all reality you are
progressing quite rapidly you are taking
very strong steps you recognize as you
have said your core happiness all you
need to do is recognize that you can be
of service you can fulfill the
agreements you made and at the same time
you can then attract into your life
individuals that are representative of
your definition of who you prefer to
be but create that strong definition one
of the things that may be creating what
you experience to be a time lag it seem
that you may not have created yet a very
strong definition of who it is you
actually want to be you may have been
saying that's not who I want to be
that's not who I want to be that's not
who I want to be but have you completely
reversed it into this is really who I am
who I want to be yes
I think I have maybe not 100% maybe 95%
95 all right then let me ask you another
shall we say standard
question are you doing in your life the
thing that excites you the most as an
individual yes I am and what is that I'm
a graduate student in uh Clinical
Psychology all right and I psychology
I'm doing therapy which is what I
therapy [Music]
[Music]
interesting so you mean that you have
chosen to assist individuals who are in
your ter having difficulty being at
peace with themselves yes well
then you are doing that to some degree
with a few people you have interacted
with in other lives as
well these individuals
both the first one more than the second
more often more strongly have both been
your children
both and to some degree all you're
doing is creating a process of weaning
for them this will not take
them this will not take
long this will not take long we perceive
there may be one more
individual that will be representative
in the same basic light but will not be
in your terminology quite as negative in
the their expression yes that's over I
mean all right the third one is over all
right you are very
rap very
quick very quick you are moving very
rapidly do not worry about it in a sense
the timing of your ability to ask this
question now in a sense means you are
changed you are changing you are
recognizing the reflection of yourself
in a sense you have created your own
therapy in that sense in this moment
right now you are really right in the
threshold all you really need to do is
recognize the connection even if you are
not completely analytically aware of the
unconscious connections previously
recognize that you have been of service
you have made agreements in this way to
allow them to learn different things and
that now you if you have already done
the one two three have let your children
go and now they must let their mother go
and be who she needs to
be it is your timing now now One Moment
One Moment One
Moment is there any particular area on
your planet that you are considering
moving to other than where you are now no I
to other than where you are now no I
like it here all right one
moment very highly accelerative Time For
You especially in what you call the
upcoming March
month let it proceed between now and
what you call your May month you are
very strongly linked to certain cycles
that are going on that we have recently
spoken about and you may find much
change happening before what you would
call your fifth month which in a sense
is also what you call your month of
motherhood it is where you will
ReDiscover many of your powers by then
and in your terminology be clearly
aligned with your course of action and
see many more representations of that
strong reflection of yourself given back
to you by the individual you will be
encountering in life you are doing just
fine thank you but by your May month in
our perception right now you will see
far more physical manifestations of the
fact that you are doing just fine well
thank continue to be of service continue
to be of
light let the children go let them grow
up on their own now you have fulfilled
your agreement to them in that
way as we perceive it there were only
three that's nice to
hear and again hence the perfectness of
the timing of this recognition on your
own
thank you can I ask you another little
related question I'm thinking of writing
about my experiences in India and it can
help many individuals I was waiting
until I stopped feeling a victim well
thank you because you sto creating it
but they understand what you mean and
now I as we have said you can be a
social mold Breaker by all means use
whatever methodology is at your disposal
that it excites you to use to
communicate your experiences so that
others can be benefit
as well they will be you will reach many
you might even become quite
controversial well I got divorced in
India where nobody gets divorced so I
was all right you're ahead on that
aspect so but I yes I want to help uh
people who uh are in situations like
mine but who who find it hard to leave
you are helping continue to be to the
fullest you can who you are that's all
you need to do you're doing just fine
thank you very much well thank you very
much for your conviction and your
boldness and for choosing to recognize
how much strength you actually have by
choosing such a high degree of
limitation on your world to work your
way through you will be an inspiration
and are thank you thank
you you are very
familiar very familiar with the
energy not just because of this
particular life of what you call the
area of the
Himalayas very
familiar very
familiar watch your
dreams watch your
dreams yes I I love the Himalayas that's
for sure that's the one thing I people
ask me what I miss about India and I say
I miss the himz yeah watch your
dreams pleasant dreams to you thank you
for thank you very much
Shing hi Bashar and you good day our
friend Strawberry can't be here this
evening and he requested that I um send
his love to you oh all right strawberry
by foxy right and then I have a question
for myself all right which is on the
subject of unconditional love
unconditional love
yes I wonder if you can give me some sort of
I wonder if you can give me some sort of
techniques or something
for uh more easily creating
unconditional love I find that what is
it you don't trust about your life hm
that's interesting well thank you I
always Endeavor to come up with
interesting questions
the idea of feeling that you cannot give
over to unconditional love is simply the
idea of not fully trusting the events
that occur in your life as having a
reason to be there oh what is it you
don't trust about yourself that you
would create a life that you couldn't
simply allow to happen
unconditionally H I never thought of
that oh all right think about it see if
that helps you okay that's really all
it's all about
the whole issue of placing conditions on
things is because you have
doubt huh about the natural
flow understand and so and it's
self-doubt oh
absolutely okay because in a sense even
if you are quote unquote projecting that
doubt onto someone
else why would you attract into your
life someone who would not in your
terminology fit the idea you know you
are remember that we have said if you
know you are positively oriented that
even if someone else in your life even
if they have a conscious intention to be
negative towards you you will only get a
positive effect out of anything they do
in terms of the interaction they perform
with you so if you know you're oriented
that way and you know that's all you're
going to get because that in a sense is
the filter you have created what to
doubt you can be unconditionally loving
to them because you know that they are
still serving you and that by being
attracted into the life of someone who
is willing to be a positive reflective
example of that love you are also
serving them understand yes yeah thank you
them understand yes yeah thank you
eventually perhaps in some individuals
they may catch the realization you know
they may say no matter what I try to do
to you you always come up as you say
smelling like a
rose how do you do it well unconditional
love oh teach me about that they might say
oh teach me about that they might say
and then you'll be able to understand
yes thank
you okay first step toward unconditional
love relax okay trust
relax okay trust
yourself you know what you're doing even
though you can create yourself to exist
as segregated Consciousness and then
create portions of that Consciousness to
seem as if it doesn't know what it's
doing right relax relax all those
definitions relax all those separations
relax all the doubts and let them melt
back into one knowing
self that feels great the doubts only
occur when you create the definitions
that cause more segregations and
separations then of course there is
doubt because you create yourself to
seem as if you are out of
touch with pieces that you have created
yourself to be of course then there will
be doubt of course then there will be
more conditions you have a lot more to
juggle let all the definitions melt back
into one then it's all right in front of
you it's all right within you it's easy
it's simple it's clear it's obvious
does this serve you yes very much well
thank you very much thank you
bye sh hello Bashar and to you good day
sh hello Bashar and to you good day
um a good topic I have a tendency to
take myself real seriously um about 11
years ago I had what I Perce perceived
to be and still do extremely
discontinuous experience oh all right
and I have them all the time
and uh it as you put it created uh
catastrophic circumstances in my life
all right and I was wondering how I
might be able to turn this into a more
positive experience and all right well
what can you learn from it in a positive
way well that uh it all starts with how
you look at it you know yes all start
that way all of
it are you continuing to Define it as
negative or can you learn something
positive from can you at least give it
the foundation of understanding that now
you have a much clearer idea of what you
are because now you really know what
you're not at least that yes at least that all
not at least that yes at least that all
right we'll start there okay um created
in a positive way on any level and it
can begin to transform all the way as
you say up and down the spum one of the
perceptions that I have had that I was
this this experience lasted long period
of time I guess it hasn't really ever
ended in a sense
[Music] correct but one of the perceptions that
correct but one of the perceptions that
I've had that I've been unable to
resolve is that I don't know how else to
put it than the body that I was born in
yes uh is not the same body that I'm in
now of course not
that's through every moment of time you
exist um that the body that I was born
in is somewhere is in another place and
the body that I'm in right now is in is
right here yeah
so so
what are you expecting me to find this
unusual or
something oh okay am I deflating some of
the definition I'm not sure all right
definition I'm not sure all right
is there some reason if I may why
this definition of difference should
make a
difference is there some reason why this
definition should be
important yes why well it's it's my
perception that my body yeah is Li there is another
that my body yeah is Li there is another
body that looks like this that is lying
some place that um has no spirit in it
not possible okay because
remember your spirit isn't in your body
your body is your spirit in physical
terms well and the illusion you create
in your world of leaving a body is not
literally mechanically what's happening
it's your perception of it because of
the way you have defined your universe
and because you see things that way
that's the way you perceive it to be
happening but that's not what's
happening remember that your
Consciousness is not in your body your
body is in your Consciousness so if for
some reason you have decided to have a
bational experience and have what you might
experience and have what you might
typically call two bodies going on at
the same time they both must be within
the same Consciousness you are they both
have to be aspects of the projection of
the one idea the one being the one
entity you
are understand uh Perhaps Perhaps all right
understand uh Perhaps Perhaps all right
keep it simple use a simple picture
begin to think of yourself more as an
energy being all right okay and let us
say you are an energy being for now with
many facets like a crystal all right
okay each facet can be looked that as
another body projection another face of
the infinite Crystal that you are all
right okay
now so you just happen to have in fact
actually all of you actually have this
all of you have more than one body going
on at the same time overlapping that's
what we call counterpart Consciousness
it is the same thing as having what you
would call a past or a future life it's
simply that it overlaps your immediate
time frame this is very common now you
have created an
ability in this life to recognize that
you can look out of more than one window
at a
time and so you have made an assumption
that you have abandoned the old window
have abandoned the old window no another
aspect of your Consciousness is looking
through that
one there are no true through Vacuums in
creation so you haven't abandoned
anything you have simply shifted your
perspective in the way that you very
creatively agreed to have it shift in
this life to begin to experience the
true malleability of your Consciousness
and the degree to which you can perceive
yourself from different directions you
have created in the sense a polarity
exchange you decided all right well I'll
live one part of my life from this
perspective and then make a switch all
at once all at once
understand okay this is something once
again that in many civilizations is very
normal to do and in your civilization is
becoming at least a possibility to
happen more often because you are
exploring all the different ideas that
Consciousness and what you call
physicality is only the Consciousness
you are seeing itself from a particular
direction or point of view there is no
husk lying around
if it truly served no purpose in your
understanding to really maintain what
you would call that other body it would
simply convert back to energy back to
the idea of the totality of the
Consciousness that you are it would be
in your terms reabsorb that if it does
in fact still physiologically exist then
understand it's probably very busy right
now but what you have simply done is
actually created a phase shift of
perception understand okay it's all
right you're looking out of another
window in the same
house C can you tell me why I am drawn
to
Mexico one moment
yes because some of the ideas of this
type not exactly in exactly the same way
some of this type of Personality
exchange was experienced by many of the
natives in that area in many different
ways sometimes in your terms chemically
sometimes once again mentally because
they understood that the body was only a
projection of
Consciousness and in a sense to some
degree it is where the Expressions come
from of being in someone else's
shoes understand no
no keep it simple you are TR trying too
hard to understand what I'm saying I am
meaning it quite literally as I am
saying it let us suppose in that past
life in what you call the Native
American culture in which you have had
many lives you consider yourself to be
one personality one body all right so
far yes all right then another person
comes and stands in front of you are you
following so far yes then you greed each
other and in what you call the wink of
an eye you're looking at each other from
each other's
bodies understand I see so you're used
to this idea so it's something that you
have decided to experiment with again to
loosen your definitions up the
definitions you have bought into in this
particular culture but the reason you are attracted
culture but the reason you are attracted
is because some of what you are
experiencing now you are an old hand at
back there in those other lines it was a
very natural thing to do to see each
other through each other's eyes it was
one very strong way of understanding
true intimacy to really know what the other
intimacy to really know what the other
feels
like understand yes because of the
social definitions that I grew up with
it seems that this can be easily
perceived as Insanity oh yes yes yes yes
yes but do understand if that is so then
we are aware of many many whole worlds
that by that definition are quite
crazy but it is not something that has
not been experienced in your Society
before at one time it was quite a common
thing for many cultures once again now
that you are all exploring all the
different ways and integrating all the
different ways you have ever experienced
yourself in all the cultures you have
lived in throughout all your lives all
these tools are coming back to the
surface and each and every one of you
are exhibiting whichever one of them
represents the idea you are most closely
associated with in this
life simple as that have a good time
thank you well thank you very much let
me ask one more quick all right okay um
it would I'm having some confusion in
discovering what it is that is most
exciting to me then take it Moment by
moment the simple as that that's it it
will always lead you to anything else
that may represent what you might call a
life career that would be the most
exciting thing you could do but when we
say do the thing that excites you the
most we do not mean you have to have
such a project in mind simply if you do
at any given moment the thing that
excites you the most that you are
capable of doing with full Integrity it
will always lead you into the
opportunities and the circumstances to
give you the ability to do the next most
exciting thing that will come along all
excitement is a thread it leads to all
other excitement and it continuously
expands and accelerates
forever so take it a step at a time we
will assume once again not because it is
us but because you are here right now
that having this conversation is the
most exciting thing you could think of
to do right now when this conversation
is at an end what will you do do the
most exciting thing with Integrity that
you are capable of acting on and it will
automatically whether your mind knows it
or not lead you exactly where you need
to be to discover the next most exciting
thing that you will be capable of doing
continue to act moment to moment live in
the present take it a step at a time
that's all you have to do all right
thank you very much then have a good
time great thank you shutting
great thank you shutting
hello Bashar and are you good day good
to talk with you again oh you as well
for the very first
time I talked with you before about um
someone that I had met that felt like um
the imaginary friend yes okay and you
told me that I was going to find out
something about them yes and meanwhile I
did an inner dialogue
session um inner child talking to the
child and I had a lot of sadness oh and
um releasing you know
releasing I beg your
pardon I did not quite
translate it it didn't feel very good
while I was experiencing it well all
right let it go the more you trust it
the more you let it go the more you will
acclimate the better it will feel all it
is in your terminology is in a sense
toxins leaving
you toxic
ideas okay so as you quote unquote pass
them you may be disoriented you may be
nauseous for a while it will pass the
faster you pass
them okay um the the information that I
felt like what I
got was from a friend that just called
me out of the blue and
sounded very similar to this person Gary
yeah what I was experiencing with him
that we would have a wonderful time when
we were together but he wasn't putting
out energy to see me I was the one that
was putting out the energy to see him
and this friend just called and started
telling me about how she was like that
yeah and how that was some sort of
defensive kind of thing that she had
within her something and and it was um
yeah that perhaps that was something of
what was going on between us all right
and was this conversation that you
attracted to yourself enlightening yes
well it was it it from the most
unexpected as you say directions will
always come the answers you need once
you begin to take the steps in the
direction of who you intend to be
uh that it that was very enlightening
and it helped me to
understand um it helped me understand a
little bit more after that I kept going
through those same uncomfortable
feelings that I had when I was in the
session and I was crying and I was
feeling sadness and hurt and sometimes
for many of you it will take a little
while to understand you don't have to F
them that way anymore again it is
usually old definitions that perpetuate
what you would call the same feeling
because a feeling is always a reaction
to what you believe and insist on
believing to be true so it may simply be
the idea that you are in your terms
transforming your old
pattern well that's what I was wondering
is um with this person yeah
whether whether it was um better for me
to just let go of the whole thing and
don't even see the person if that's
what's causing me to be hurt let me put
it this way well the easiest ways to
approach any idea is to have the Clear
Vision have the clear intention have the
clear desire radiate it to the strongest
and brightest of your ability and forget
about it get on with your life doing the thing
it get on with your life doing the thing
that excites you the most that you're
capable of doing because then when you
put that idea out just by getting on
with your life will you run into the
opportunity if you're going to run into
the opportunity most quickly to allow
you to see the feedback of whatever it
is you put out but if you stop and worry
about the details you make it take
longer the det worry about the details
you make it take
longer the details always take care of
themselves and will always present
themselves to you in your life in the
form of the most obvious direction to
take the thing thing that excites you
the most even though it may on the
surface seem to have nothing to do with
the direction of the intention you
originally put out if it comes as a
circumstance with excitement the most
excitement you can do follow it whether
it looks like it's going to get you
where you thought it would or not it
will put it out know it is working for
you forget about it do what you can do
act upon what you can act upon let it
come back to you in the way that will
serve you
best understand yeah yes that's exactly
what um my friend told me to do and I
forgot you see how good you are at being
a bright and shiny mirror and being
surrounded by all sorts of loving
Reflections that give you exactly what
you need yeah I that is the biggest
thing I think I learned this week
yourself thank you very much well thank
you very
much thank
you sharing
hello Bashar and to you good day first
thing I'd like to thank you very much
for the uh a couple of weeks past the
topic of uh
sound sound and the the sound the sound
yes and then story of the sound One
Moment One Moment wherein three
individuals were looking for a sound
that could change everything and
discovered finally when they quote
unquote gave up looking and sat down and
relaxed at the sound simply
[Music] was the sigh of release continue the
was the sigh of release continue the
little Rose for example is a is a nice
little way of
uh smelling that Rose taking in the
loving Essence
and the
Sigh nature itself can always allow you
to key into that
vibration and become
one in breath in light in
love conspire with
nature that's what conspiring in your
language means breathing
together the question I have is is sort
of uh it's part of a dream and uh some
way tight end with the the pyramid and
the Sphinx I believe no all right the
the dream as I keep uh I I think it's a
dream I'm not too sure what's the
difference continue uh I see a clock a clock like
continue uh I see a clock a clock like
it's 12:00 always exactly 1:00 2:00 yeah
and uh it seems like there's a tie in
uh it seems like there's a tie in
something with the pyramid and the
Sphinx the pyramid is a symbol for us
right probably many but it uh the the
meaning of the uh the Fire Within right
yes it is also a symbol of Eternity as
well as is the
S another symbol for the thinks is that
a uh being that it's half man half
animal uh a reminder to man to man not
to let the animal part of us sort of
control us
no it is more of a reminder of your
blending and an extension of naturehood
from you and your original understanding
of yourselves in your own wisdom and
power as a reflection of the infinite
mhm it is the blending of what you call
nature and Humanity reminding you that
you are an extension of it now on the
negative side it can be representative
of some of the idea of what you may call
the quote unquote Beast Within
you but you don't have to look at it
that way okay continue the the dream part
way okay continue the the dream part
with the clock is there anything you can
any any light on there well again to
some degree it is your recognition that
these things represent the idea of
Eternity Infinity
Infinity
remember imagine now if you
will what you may call phanic
energy phanic energy those
individual and you are very familiar
with this energy those individual
who Chanel through themselves the
Chanel through themselves the
representation of the infinite
energy what you call the
sarcophagus is the symbol of your
ability to express literal
immortality the phanic energy the Sphinx
the pyramid are symbols of
immortality understand this now
for much of your time all of
you as you perceive and create
yourselves to quote unquote age in your
life you say that there comes a time
when you all begin to ponder your
mortality now that you are living in the
moment and recognizing your eternalness
you're going to begin to ponder your
immortality and really recognize it a
Crystal sarcophagus imagine
sarcophagus imagine
that a crystal sarcophagus that
represents the idea of the energy in
Crystal and form to you of immortality
of infinit of eternalness of the fact
that you never die you only
change mhm phanic energy you are very familiar
mhm phanic energy you are very familiar
with it
thank you very
much there will be more to come but not
right
now thank you
again if you wish this evening of your
time when you in your terms lay yourself
down to
sleep imagine in a comfortable fashion
the idea of seeing your body Within the
idea of seeing your body Within the
crystal sarcophagus and see what
happens in your
dream just a suggestion should be
interesting I think so thank
you One Moment One Moment One
Moment and do
remember that much much much much
much of the ancient phanic
energy and all the energy we are
discussing has to tie in directly with
the manifestations and the symbology of
what you call
Osirus sirious mhm thank you thank
you shoting hi hi I'd like to know what my
shoting hi hi I'd like to know what my
purpose
is I'd like to know what my purpose
is what your purpose is MHM
I take it you and I have never
interacted before before
no all
right brief
explanation do you understand that you
are a reincarnational being yes do you
understand however that this life you
are living now only has One Life to Live
yes do you understand you have never
been this you before and you will never
be this you again
good therefore do you understand that
the purpose of your life is to be this
you to the fullest you possibly can mhm
how you do that is up to you and the way
you discover how to express your full
purpose of life is to do what excites
you the most because that's what
excitement is for to key you into the
energy that represents your strongest
purpose in life you see all the things
that many of you talk about what can I
do what is my purpose what is my mission
when you talk about this project this
expression this methodology all of these
things are simply different ways
different Avenues different conduits
through which to express your purpose
none of these projects in and of
themselves are your purpose in life they
are your method your chosen method of
expressing the purpose of your life the
purpose of your life all of you simply
being to do what excites you the most
and be of service by doing so to be the
fullest you you can be because you'll
never be this you again you've got one
shot at being this you live it to the
fullest by doing what excites you the
most with integrity and you will always
fulfill your purpose how you do that is
up to you that's why you have free
will now is that too simple no does that
answer your question sufficiently sure
does that work for you I suppose you
suppose is there something that excites
you more than any other thing not right
now not right now does this conversation
excite not really not
really all right why
not I don't know yes you
do perhaps the first thing if we may
suggest is to learn to hear
yourself and be
heard now you have heard us discuss the
idea of doing what excites you at any given
of doing what excites you at any given
moment
yeah yes
yes yes
yes perhaps the definition of excitement
will assist
you excitement are you paying attention I'm
excitement are you paying attention I'm
paying attention
excitement is your physical Translation
your physical
interpretation of the vibrational energy
that represents what you chose to be in
this life the things in your life that
excite you at any given moment more than
any other thing is representative of
what you call your path in life act on
it and it will lead you into more
excitement more expanded expressions of
excitement that's all you have to do
Moment by moment follow what excites you
the most with Integrity act upon
whatever you can act upon that excites
you the most if there is something that
really excites you more than any other
thing but you can't act upon it then act
upon what you can act upon out of all
the next level of things that excites
you the most and it will lead you into
the circumstance to give you the tools
to act upon the other thing that excited
you that you couldn't act upon before at
any given moment do what excites you the
most and understand that what's going on
in your life right now at any given
moment is the most important thing or
something else would be happening
everything in your life fits everything
in your life belongs even if it's
something you don't prefer to be there
if it's there it's because your
definitions your belief systems have
attracted it so it still has a purpose
in being there if only to show you that
you don't prefer this to happen again
learn from it in a positive way by being
Overjoyed at having discovered what your
belief is so you can change it in the
way you want to use every situation in a
positive frame of reference and your
life will become what we call an
ecstatic explosion of coincidence always
in the right place always at the right
time time always interacting with
exactly who you need to be interacting
with what you all do anyway but when you
do negative synchronicity many times you
don't know it many times when you're
interacting with individuals that
represent things you don't want it's
because you have within you the belief
systems of things in that sense that
aren't representative of who you are and
so you attract the circumstances and the
individuals to show you this is not what
I want but it's negative synchronicity
you're still attracting the reflections
to show you that you can prefer
something else use it in this way and
everything will be transformed into a
positive and every single moment of your
life will be as ecstatic and open and
fascinating and curious as it is when
you are a
child be a
child that's all you need to do a child
knows that simply by being a child it is
completely fulfilling its purpose in
life because it is a child in all the
ways it can be
completely absolute
conviction that's all it takes whoever
it is you now prefer to Define yourself
to be whoever it excites you to be at
any given
moment be that you with complete
integrity and absolute
conviction and you will explode from
ecstasy does this help you yes it does
thank you very much
sh Bashar I have an interesting tale to
tell oh all right do unwind your tale oh
wonderful to start ahead and move back
speak up so that all may share to start
in this was one of the very few planets
that used money as a method of
distribution of goods and services in
the way that you use it yeah in the way
that we use it well I'll have to ask you
sometime how somebody else uses it all
right um as I see it this method of
distribution is supported by the
maintenance artificially of a scarcity
yeah and if we
had um oodles and Boodles of power drill
cheap power yeah every place that
everybody could use yes an artificial
scarcity could no longer be maintained
and we would move more quickly into to
that point where we don't need money to
distribute things and you have as you
say oodles and Boodles of power now you
mentioned the other day that we could
tap electromagnetic energy from the
earth and just have all the energy we
needed we haven't quite gotten to that
point yet not collectively but some
individuals on your planet have well I
would like to run across that one I may
have run across the step prior to that
which may put out the kind of energy
which is the precursor to what you just
mentioned all right and it's a it's very
simple It's usually
the uh the application of old technology
which is uh actually Refrigeration
technology all it is is low temperature
phase change industry yeah and all these
people are doing is taking
a huge evaporator sticking it out on a
roof connecting it up with the usual
kind of equipment compressor and so
forth that's generally used in
refrigeration and pumping heat from the
outside in when they need the heat now
since this Freon boils at minus 28° and
anything over absolute zero which is I
forget something like 278 de below zero
everything around has heat in it so all
they have to do is pick up the heat and
put it where they want as there are many
projects that we are aware of that are
being designed upon your planet to take
advantage of the idea of temperature
exchange from one level to another both
in your atmosphere and in your oceans
many of these projects have been
designed now this is one way to generate
the idea of power but it is not directly
the electromagnetic idea we have been
discussing but in your terms it is
sufficient for many tasks well I ran
into a very interesting young man
that has been working with this for the
last 10 years and has run a foul of the
authorities uh in Boston and in
Washington in fact they wiped his
business out because of course he began
to infringe on the big electric
companies and so forth and so on so now
what he's done is he's going to the
American people he has worked up three
packages that you can buy if you wish
all in a bunch which is marketing it is
assembly and and
[Music]
um installation thank
you uh he's marketing all of this for
$5,000 and has worked out the details of
all of these phases so any and every
American person that wants to get into
this business on a Grassroots basis can
get into the business and start out in a
very small way what he's doing he's
trying to Tap The Grass Roots so that
understand this will be proliferated
every place so that nobody and no big
group no big oil companies can go in the
idea of what you call your networking
facilties will be one of the ways to
allow channels of communication to be
open so that many of the things that
your Society has discovered can once
again come to the Forefront and not
remain as you say suppressed because
there are many such inventions that if
all brought to the Forefront would
create completely unlimited power for
your entire
world well um this man has also uh stop
yes go with what excites you explore and
discover and
experiment share the information in
whatever way but do understand it is our
suggestion that you not remain fixated
on the idea of the suppressive sign mhm
because if you create it to be a battle
it will be well I wondered if that was
why he had been wiped out a couple of
times and now he's going for the Third
time on this the idea to some degree is
interconnected with that yes but a lot
of it simply has to do with many of the
fears you have all been but up with
about the idea of not being able to
share the information because of what
you have created your Society to be and
also then it forces you into interaction
with that aspect of your Society so that
you can open up lines of communication
so that eventually in that sense
individuals that are positively oriented
can quote unquote rub off on individuals
that are negatively oriented the
interaction does serve the purpose do
not fear it and do not
antagonize the idea but by all means
proceed in whatever way you feel is of
best service to all do you think you'll
make it this time I cannot predict that
it is up to all of you I have looked at
that thank you very much we thank you
very much at this timing you may all enjoy a
much at this timing you may all enjoy a
short break
we will resume Conta in approximately 10
to 15 of your many how's everything how's everything
[Music]
going there's Refreshments in the other
room and if you want a copy of tonight's
tapey Lin around the corner and she'll
fix you up it's $10 for the two tapes
[Music]
I right I'll say
continue hello Bashar and good day to
you I'd like to do a little sharing a
little uh T testimonial for the ideas
and principles that are related here and
that is uh the one of trust in my my
life more and more I've been uh uh
trusting in a positive nature and I just
want to share with you all the more that
we all do this it's it works every
single time no yes really yes by m oh
thank you you're very welcome and thank you
you you're very welcome and thank you
you are very welcome um you see if I may
you may many of you ask for proof proof
proof proof
proof prove this prove that is this real
is it not prove it prove it prove it all
right it can be
proven use the information
it always works that's the only thing
that is important to
prove thank you thank
you and
um our dreams are true too yeah I've
been doing so many things that excite me
I haven't been having having enough time
to
work so who are you so I dreamt that I
got five out of six numbers on the lot
though and I
did just 3 weeks later and uh that made
this trip to uh the keys much more
enjoyable all right I've turned many of
them then very many and the swimming
with the dolphins yeah also turned many
things within my being and it was one of
the most tender moments of my life the uh
most tender moments of my life the uh
six days I spent two weeks ago
and and I decided to create an
interesting uh scenario actually Judy
who went with me did a similar one with
me it seems to be a little have been a
little stronger the symbol of nausea yes
not only the first time I swam with the
dolphins the last time the day I left
and every day for the week after and
didn't have anything to do with an upset
stomach so I could eat the worst food
and feel better you were adjusted
Ah that's what I assumed but I just
thought I'd get some confirmation on
that and it's been uh the tuning seems
much finer now yes understand that
Dolphins can make very fine Sonic
adjustments that they can yeah thank you
very much we thank you very much for
truly learning how to play thank you
thank you Shing
hello Bashar and to your good
day um I have this job that I'm in right
now good
now um I work with children's services
and I investigate child abuse and
neglect and um I'm having a lot of
difficulty with the job um how
so I think the hardest part I'm having
is I facilitate taking children away
from their parents right and I'm not um
I feel really bad about this um why cuz
I I don't want to be the interference
and yet I do I mean there's this two I
some split between the two why but do
understand also and we know in your
terminology that there are a few more
factors than what we are about to say
but do understand that those parents
have attracted you in a sense to do so
mhm they are aware of the functions in
your terminology of individuals such as
yourself and your Society they are aware
of the actions and interaction they are
having they are aware of what you may
call the consequences of those
actions understand yes uhhuh okay so
recognize perhaps not that we are saying
that the
methodologies that may be being used in
all of those services are necessarily
all always as positive as they could be
but do recognize that if your intention
is of a positive service to the children
then in that sense perhaps you can look
at it not as taking the child away from
the parents but giving the child back to
itself that yeah that's the way I like
to look at it all right then do so um
you will always attract the opportunity
for all individuals involved in the
interaction to learn what they need to
learn from it as long as you represent a
very strong and brightly shining light
again it will rub
off okay um the the other part I had was
difficulty with the the denial or the um
resistance to the parents to change to
help these children but that is their
choice of course uhhuh it's hard for me
to keep on coming against that well
you're not coming against anything again
do not make a conflict out of it do not
make resistance out of it if you are
doing what you are doing out of love and
service and know that you are to the
best of your ability with all the
Integrity you can Master then you are
simply shining as a light you don't have
to feel like you are creating friction
in that
sense understand yes share what you are
willing to share from the heart allow
them to experience the idea that the
only reason there is the negativity at
all is because they have a great deal of
fear about themselves and are simply
projecting onto the
child sometimes the idea in your Society
of facing that you have that much fear
can be in and of itself a fearful
recognition but the idea once again is
simply that do not forget the child also
chose in that sense to be born to those
individuals and also the playing out of
the scenario of attracting you into its
life the child's life is a part of what
the child also wishes share with the
parent that chose to be born to okay so
that the child is also assist Thing by
making the decision to attract
you understand yes yes it's a nice way
to look at do understand you're not
doing it by
yourself okay okay um why why would I be
um involved in all these people's lives
like this I'm not sure my participation
and why I'm you're not sure well I know
on on a level I'm doing my job but what
I'm saying is is it what you want to do
it's because I come so in involved in
the family life and so many families
lives because you are willing to be of
service to allow yourself to be an
example for change how can you not
become involved when you have chosen to
do what you have chosen to do how can
you not be involved automatically in the
intertwinings of intimacy and
relationships is that not what you are
being of assistance with yes well how
can you not be a part of it how can you
not recognize that each and every one of
those is your
family in a ense
that's a good point how can you not
recognize that you in that sense are a
child of the family of your
Earth and are simply speaking with the
voice that you have for the other
children thank you very much um I have
one more thing um my twin sister's here
with me and um the question I have to
ask you is that we're very opposite very
different so and I mean just completely
opposite and I was wondering you are
nice polarities for each other well we
learn a lot from each other well yes of
course then what more is there to say
that obviously serves the
purpose okay you can see in the idea of
your twinness a mirror reflection in a
sense of all the things that are
polarized to you so you can learn more
and more of who and what you wish to be
and vice versa it is a very creative and
clever way that many of you have created
to show yourselves reflections that you
need to see that you will not
necessarily exhibit from your own
self that is one of the services of
twinness it really really reminds you in
a very strong and graphic way that
everyone around you is literally a
mirror in this life and there are
certain other things I wish to
experience and to some degree by the
definition of the society I am being
born into these things are quote unquote
mutually exclusive by one person
experience both of them but not by
two so how about if I become two people
who look the
same representative therefore that I am
the same basic idea but experiencing the
polarity of
itself understand yes thank you very
much thank you both very
much and thank the one that you both are
Shing um could you please I I noticed
that you do something that looks like
mudas with your hands as you speak and
this is simply an automatic reaction of
many different things an automatic
reaction in the Channel's body sometimes
it will be as you say directed by us and
sometimes it will be quite automatic one
of the things it represents is an energy
balancing that is going on not only for
channel but for us to be able to
communicate with all of you another
thing sometimes it represents is a
literal orchestration of the combined
energy of our Consciousness in this
interaction another thing that sometimes
it represents is exactly what you use
your own hands for the idea of
underlining a particular Point calling
it out to your
attention sometimes however and more
often than not what the idea is
representative of is the fact that there
are many levels many levels that I am
communicating with you upon the physical
Channel only has a few ways to show you
to physically interpret the fact that
you are being communicated with on many
different levels one of them is vocally
another is simply the hand motion it
lets you know you are receiving
information on levels that you may not
be hearing in in an audible fashion
understand Yes actually when I was
waiting to come up here um to talk to
you I was trying to get in touch with
the question I wanted to ask of you that
would excite me the most and my feeling
was that um I just um I wanted to have a
non-verbal interaction with you and this
probably isn't an appropriate time and
place to do it but
um yes many times the idea of what you
call nonverbal interaction will happen
between yourselves and us in a
spontaneous method when we are focused
on the issues at hand and interacting
with other in spontaneous way very often
when you call out a specific desire for
such a thing that specific desire in and
of itself places so much focus on the
idea of the non-verbal interaction that
it actually Cuts itself off short it
usually happens more often than not when
it is a spontaneous and unwatched
thing and sometimes and in no way shape
or form is this meant to be derogatory
but very often because of the level of
vibratory frequency that many of you
operate on the idea simply be that I
will not be able to pick up on the idea
of your thoughts very often if your
vibration is to unlike the vibration
that we are because teloy is a matter of
strong identification of like
frequencies so very often we will not
pick up upon the idea of your tath
thoughts simply because they may not be
of the frequency that is representative
of the modality that I am being at any
particular moment but when it occurs it
usually occurs
spontaneously understand yes does this
assist you yes thank you very much thank
you very much and pleasant dreams to
you Shing hello and you good day I don't
know this is the type of question to ask
you but from it's me standing here what
do you feel for my
[Music] presence one
moment the first thing is I feel Yello
Nish yellowness as you say an energy of
yellowness it's cuz I'm scared I don't
know why but it is not the idea of yellow in
why but it is not the idea of yellow in
that sense per se it is the idea more of
the use and examination of your
analytical side of your mentality the
idea of posing questions to yourself and
Reflections to yourself and ponderings
to yourself in to some degree a thought
process mode so the first vibration we pick up
mode so the first vibration we pick up
from you is
yellowness as a frequency as an
energy now there are a few patterns
forming directions Loops
swirl self-reflection self- consideration One
self-reflection self- consideration One
Moment One Moment
a Rosy Glow in one particular area
indicating a lot of heart
energy do you feel very vulnerable in
certain circumstances are you explor the
idea of vulnerability in that way of
opening up your heart in that sense in
Intimate terms yes are you afraid to do
so um I don't know I've been going
through a lot this is what's the second
part of the question is lately I've been
feeling the presence or something that
happened in a past life I don't know why
it keeps coming ever since I came out to
California it's really strong out here
it's to the point where one time I woke
up and I couldn't remember who I was but
I was I remembered that I should
remember the room and I sat in front of
a clock that I got for my graduation
that I should remember and I sat and
watched the time go by and I couldn't
remember who I was I I remember that I
should remember all this but I couldn't
remember oh all right I was someone else
and it's it's been coming in Parts like
that it's almost it's someone or I'm
sure it was me but or something keeps
coming into to this life and and distra
distracting me and distracting you from
what distracting me I don't know from
what from my life your life my life
present present what is it is it what
you want it to
be from what I know yes from what you
know all right what do you
know oh um from what I know want what do
you want that's a really hard question to
want that's a really hard question to
ask I mean answer why
because what do I want yes what do you
want happiness I happiness happiness I
want to be loved you want to be loved
you are loved
infinitely you are made of love then why
does this thing or whatever this
presence keep coming back to me and it's
just it keeps coming in my mind it's
almost um like I want to be hypnotized
so I can go back to my past life to
understand what is going on some degree
that be representative and of assistant
but if I may let us say wind the
conversation back a moment I would like
to point out the idea that you said that
this thing is seemingly distracting you
from the life that you are but you are
saying that the life you have contains
many wants which means the life you have
isn't the life you want what if what you
are feeling is not a so much distraction
from life you want but a quote unquote
orientation towards the life you
want what about
that okay well does it seem like that
could be
possible does it seem like you are being
distracted from a life you don't
want H I can think about it oh more
yellowness more
yess think sink sink all right the
yellow band of mentality all right fair
enough how do you feel if I may change
the subject okay when you think of
greenness how do you
feel alive alive all
right does any other coloration come
into your
fancy not at the present moment no oh do
you have a favorite
color um
white that is all
colors a
totality you like what I don't have a
real favorite color oh all right then
white it is all colors what does it
signify to you
whiteness cleanness cleanness
Clarity Yes sounds like you've heard
this [Music]
[Music]
before oh one or two or a thousand
time but once again every time is the
first time so I'm hearing it for the
first time because you are you and I am
a different me
now this
whiteness representing
Clarity does it also seem to represent a
full expression of self
energy in a way yes all right now you
have I will assume being paying
attention to our conversation with other
individuals this night of your talk yes
is there anything in
particular that excit you more than any
other thing that you're not yet
doing that you could be doing but that
you don't do for one reason or another
details I heard you talking about
someone earlier about ignoring the
details yeah that's has a lot a lot of
things that I don't do is because I
worry the details oh all right for the
moment at least in this conversation
let's put the details aside they can
come back if you want them to but for
right now ignoring the details as you
say is there an idea if you didn't have
to think about the details that you
would love to
do not at the present moment I can't
nothing is coming to my mind
spontaneously have you ever had a
picture of something you would really
have liked to have done but didn't
because of the details no basically
every everything that I've pictured I've
done yes yes oh all right and these
things that you have pictured have they
been things you wanted to
do well
well interesting well you are saying you
have no problem doing things you don't
want every one of these things I
pictured that I didn't want to do I was
able to do with no
problem all right fair enough so you
have the power recognize you have the
power to do what you picture I guess
what I'm asking is how do I focus it how
do
I we are perhaps in your estimation
going through the back door but that's
all right reason for
for
now these things you say you did that
you didn't necessarily want to do uh is
that a correct
estimation no not really all right you
did want to do them yes oh all right did
it give you happiness to do these things
no why not I don't know it's like I I'm
doing everything that I should be doing
right now but yet I feel something's
missing everything you should be doing
can you name some of these things you
should be doing well I'm living where I
want to live I work with what I want to
work with I work with the type of people
I want to work with stop start again and
name all these things specifically
living where you want to live in what
sense do you mean that do you mean in a
enir or in an area or area all right as
the beach the beach the beach all right
that beach and this makes you happy yes
all right we got
one and you are working you say doing
something that makes you happy as well
yes what is it television television
can you be specific um well everything
in the aspects of tech technical of
Television you how to edit um
yeah shoot exactly tape this is how I
learned about you is because we were
dubbing a tape for someone in here all
right there are no
accidents now the idea of all these
things you are saying gives you pleasure
to do these
things that's just it um there's
something missing all right all right
may I ask you a question go ahead why
are you doing all these things do you
have some particular intention in mind
that is represented by the reason for
why you are doing all these things and
learning what you're learning because is
there some way you wish to apply all
this knowledge I I suppose I take it one time
knowledge I I suppose I take it one time
one day at a time and it will come
whatever it's going to come One Moment
One Moment back up
again do you have I'll put it this way
some ultimate application for all these
things you are
learning do you have in your terminology
a goal in putting together all the
things you are learning and applying it
in a particular
way a goal in television or a goal in my
life well let's start with
television oh God we could be all night
um do you have a particular goal in
television no I do not no you do not so
in other words these things you are
doing them why are you doing
them that's a good question well thank
you why are you doing it because I guess
I'm I in my mind somewhere it says I'm
supposed to I supped to graduate from
college I'm supposed to move out here
I'm supposed to pursue my
career your career career how did you
decide upon this career um I like
television you like television all right
you like it all right now is there
another way you could express the idea
when you say I like television do you
mean you like the mechanical device yes
itself yes well what you call the Box
itself no no I'd like the aspect of uh
putting it together putting a show
together making it all work you like the
creative aspect of the assemblage of the
information and the presentation of the
information thing correct ah you like
that so you like putting it together
correct you're sure now I want you to be
sure I'm sure all right all right all
right so in that sense then are you
saying that what you are doing is
enjoyable for
you yes all right now is there somewhere
you wish to take this do you wish to put
together your own shows as you say is
that something you would like to do it
hasn't come into thought no hasn't come
into thought well think about it right
now is that something that you could use
all the things you are learning to apply
that towards would that excite you in
other words when you say I'm excited and
and about the idea of the
creativity the idea of Television itself
the presentation the information does
that mean then that you get your thrill
as you say by putting this all together
does that mean that you would really get
a bigger thrill if you put it all
together yourself yes oh
well so are you saying then that this is
something that you can in your terms
work towards okay I'm asking you well yes yes
towards okay I'm asking you well yes yes
I guess I can do you find that that
would be happiness for you or exciting
for you it would be exciting but I don't
know of happiness I think happiness as
far as that's you're talking about work
oh One Moment One Moment
One now you are telling me I
believe that excitement in one area of
your life does not necessarily mean
happiness in all areas is that what you
are saying I don't know I don't know the
qu say well you have just I will assume
intimated to me that since you said I am
talking about work that if you became
excited about what you do as a work that
that wouldn't necessarily mean that
other areas of your life would be happy
is that what you're
saying I guess that's not what I meant
oh what did you mean I meant that in a
way that my work I'm excited about what
I'm doing in my work I've come a long
ways I've I've accomplished a lot and
but are you saying that your work even
though it's exciting doesn't make you
happy no I guess I can't say that either
it does make me happy oh well all right
then are you doing something that makes
you happy and is exciting for you uh yes
I'm in the progress of it you're what in
the process of it I should say does that
mean you're not there yet I'm getting
there why aren't you there now because
I'm on the stepping so what so what what
in other words is that not a part of the
idea of the
doing okay or have you created an
assumption that these particular steps
as you already
said may be only necessary but maybe for
you they're not you see here's the
idea perhaps you have been focusing on
the details so much that you do not even
allow yourself to begin to conceive of
what you may call the over all intention
of which the details are a
part if you
can discover as to some degree you have
just done at least as an example now
this idea that let's say the broader
idea is that yes yes yes I like putting
it together I want to put something like
this together
myself but I'm not doing that again I'm
focusing on the details and the details
don't make me
happy now it may only be your assumption
that the details you are using are the
only ones you could have used
there may be other details that can
automatically happen in your life to
still give you the knowledge you need to
do the thing that really excit you and
you simply are not finding those details
the ones that you could be happy doing
because of your assumption that only
these details the ones that don't make
you happy are the ones you have to do in
order to someday do the thing you really
will be happy doing are you following
this so
far the idea therefore is to not focus
on the details is to finally understand
if you can get a notion of what the
details you are working with now might
lead to focus on the idea of what it
might lead to and then work it backwards
from there to discover and attract into
your life whatever details can get you
there that are also as representative of
Happiness as the final thing itself you
see the thing itself exists now what you
call your ultimate goal of expression
and experience and happiness exists now
no it exists now let the final thing
send you the details that are
representative of its energy the details
that will get you there but the details
that will be representative of the same
energy not the details that are not
representative of the same energy is
this making sense mhm there are many
ways you could do what you want to do it
may only be that you are confining
yourself to doing it in ways that you
think you have to do it and those
methodologies those details may not be
as representative of the final thing as
you think let the final thing Envision the
think let the final thing Envision the
final thing be the final thing get
excited about the final thing and let it
send you details and methodologies to
get there that are representative of the
same energy
because the details can be as exciting
but not when you focus on particular
ones that you think you have to use and
those may not be representative of the
final thing you want to
do you may be working with a lot of
assumptions that you have to do it
exactly this way and well yes someday
this will make me happy but the way I'm
getting there doesn't make me happy you
don't have to choose a and well yes
someday this will make me happy but the
way I'm getting there doesn't make me
happy you don't have to choose a path
that is not representative of the
happiness you want in a sense that's
contradictory if you are doing details
in that sense that are not
representative of the thing you
ultimately say will make you happy then
those details will not get you
there trust that the thing that makes you
trust that the thing that makes you
happy the idea the scenario the vision
whatever that is that you know would
represent your happiness and excitement
can send you details and methods and
paths that are only representative of
the same level of energy and that all
the details can be happy to you can be
just as exciting as the thing they will
ultimately lead you to because they are
extensions of
it understand is this making any sense
to you yes it is is it working on some
level for it yes it is is it clarifying
some of your concepts for it yes how do
you feel better in what way are you more
[Music] green can you feel that I'm more green
green can you feel that I'm more green
or am I still yellow to you you're a
little Greener take a few more deep
breaths with your mouth
open how does that feel
better do you feel pretty green
little bit little bit green what would
allow you to feel as green as you can
imagine
feeling when you think of feeling green
what do you
picture well don't think about it well
you told me to think about it no I said
what do you picture
I picture metal I piure life all right I
picture life life itself oh very good
life itself which means
experiences yes yes all
right any symol that works for you that
helps you feel green picture it and
picture yourself involved with
it and breathe it in and be the idea and
attract to yourself the methodologies
that are representative of your
connection with nature and life itself
because nothing in life has to be
tedious there are always methods that
are completely aligned with the thing
you want to do that will get you to that
point you never have to do or use
methods that have nothing to do with
final result
result
understand okay let yourself discover
them naturally now one moment we still
perceive to some degree that there may
be a few definitional barriers within
you one
moment may I ask you a question
mhm how would you
feel or or to be fair how do you think
you would
feel if you yourself were on
television how does it feel when you
think of that
idea I don't know I've always wanted to
be behind the camera not in front I
understand I'm still asking you a
question