And then you is is the solar system
similar to your solar system? Similar
not exactly. We are however like you the
third planet from our sun at
approximately what you would call 120
million of your mile
age. Our day is not very different from
yours. Little tiny bit
longer. Approximately what you would
call just over 25 of your hours. But
because our orbit is so much wider in
that way, you will find that we have a
year comprised of what you would call
454 of our days as opposed to 365 of one
quarter of the
hour. We have planets within our system.
Again, different configurations, but
similar as a system goes. Our central
star is yellowish green and goes by the
title sha. The first planet is called seo. The
sha. The first planet is called seo. The
second is called teni. The third is
ours. Then the fourth is pest. Then
there is an area that is called vamar
which means the zone for it is open
where a planet should be. This is
because there is an outer world that
comes in a very erratic orbit and has
swept that particular area clean of
debris in that way but also extends in a
parabolic orbit far beyond the orbits of
any other world.
Then beyond that there is the double
world occupying similar orbits called
takupani. The dancers if you will in the
ancient language because their orbit
allows them to shift and move as they
orbit the central
star. So it is like many systems but it
is unique like your own system. You only
have five planets. No. How many there
are approximately what you would call
seven and they're the physical representation
and they're the physical representation
of what as our solar system as physical
representative of collective unconscious
energy. They are representative in many
ways of the different aspects of our
consciousness, in our terms, in our
symbology, most of which at this time
for us is quite ancient and in this way
is not so much paid attention to
literally anymore in that sense. For we
now know that the system is also the
combined collective consciousness of the
total idea that we are, even as yours is
in that way. And that your system, our
system, and the stellar system around
the star you call Sirius are three
aspects of a trinary overall
consciousness that in general represent
your system physical, our system mental
and Sirius being spiritual. In that way,
we tend to now look at the relationships
of whole systems rather than the
labeling of the relationships of any
particular planetary phenomena within
any one particular system.
Yes. And Christ mastered this system. In
a sense, the idea of the Christ
consciousness, yes, is the combined
collective consciousness of your system.
It recognizes itself as its own entity
and it recognizes itself as the
combination of all consciousness within
that system. Our collective embodiment
of consciousness is referred to in the
ancient language as
shakana. And in this way, therefore,
what you would call your Christ
consciousness, our shakana, and the
combined consciousness of many other
systems together will form the
consciousness of what we call shakana
sha, light of whites, the infinite
creator, who follow. Does that assist? Yeah. Find
who follow. Does that assist? Yeah. Find
you. Then you um when I was about 11 or
12 years old, I had a dream that I was
taking aboard
UFO. Um, can you clarify whether that
was a No, it was very real. Do remember
this. The
majority The majority of interactions
between members of your society and
members of other
society, whether they
seem physical or not, are actually more
of a mental or astral encounter. They
may seem physical from time to time and
from time to time they may be in your
terms truly physical. But a vast
majority of even those encounters that
seem physical will actually be dream
impellers as you have experienced in a
very lucid fashion in an astral fashion.
You follow me? Yeah.
Will you care at this time to describe
and or define the beings as you remember
perceiving them? I don't actually
remember. Do you remember their eyes?
Um, what I remember about it was that I
was I was taken aboard and shown
something. Yeah. And it was very very
important that I was told but I cannot
remember what it was that I was told.
That is all why? For you see, many of
the ideas that are shared with you in
those dream realities are shared between
them and your higher
consciousness. Those ideas will come out
in your physiological life when the
timing is appropriate for them to come
out. They are planted within you in that
way. You are reminded on a certain level
just to let you know that when a certain
circumstance comes up, you will know
that you have what you need to fill that
gap. Even though you may not know what
it is right now, you are now preparing
yourself in many ways. You are now
learning to become in a sense the being
that will then be able to know what you
will then need to know.
You will then need to know it. And at
that point when you do know it, that is
when you will also have all of the
ability which is what you are learning
now to apply what you will know then.
Okay. I have another question. All
right. Um do you have a faximile of
astrology in in your solar system? Not
exactly. We recognize the concept that
you are speaking of,
astrology, as a recognition of the
interlocking vibratory patterns that go
into making up the idea, any given idea
of any physiological universe or local
therein. And it can be expressed in a
sense in a mathematical relationship to
some degree. It can be understood
similarly to the way individuals on your
planet understand it. Perhaps the
following analogy in that when you are a
analogy in that when you are a
non-physical being and decide in a sense
to project yourself into physical
materiality, whatever vibratory pattern,
whatever ripples in the primal energy in
that physical universe are going on at
the time you inject yourself will of
course in a sense be
solidified as the physical form you perceive
as the physical form you perceive
yourself to be. And so of course your
physical form is in a
sense a frozen version of the vibrations
that existed at the timing you became
physical. And so from that, if you melt
the ice a little, you can read the
radiation that speaks of the vibrations
that were going on at the time. And
therefore, to some degree does
determine the overall quality of the
prism, the crystal that you have
congealed into.
But also astrology is a very instinctive
tool. And much of what is perceived of
course is reliant upon the astuteness of
the individual doing the perceiving as
well. So it definitely is a cocreative
event. I see it as a reflection of my
I see it as a reflection of my
perception or any individual's
perception of their beliefs within that
dimension. Basically, yes, it is a
recognition, to put it very
colloquially, a recognition of some of
the general overall contracts or
agreements that have been agreed to be
adhered to in order to create the game
of any particular dimension or universe.
Yes.
Yeah. Thank you very much. Yes. Yes. Is
it not true that there is no such thing
as time and that the agreement
was made not in time. Well, yes, in a
sense. Of course, recognize we are using
your colloquial phrase all. Well, there
is such a thing as time when you choose
to believe there is. As we have said,
the illusion is real while you are in it
or appears to be. So, there is a concept
of time that is real while you choose to
experience it. But yes, in the overall
fundamentals and since it is your
creation then it is in that sense not
really binding. You follow me?
Yes. From that level all agreements are being
From that level all agreements are being
made right now.
In the same vein, is it not true then
that uh
Jesus who was known as the Christ and
soul and Mary were twin souls and that
she indeed was a virgin physically.
Well, in a sense, yes, because it was an
energy activated cell, right? Thanks.
Thank you. Guys,
Guys,
um could you give me some information
about uh records that are
supposedly between the pyramid and the
tombs that contain information about
previous civilizations that have been
here on Earth? Are you aware of this? To
some degree, it is primarily between
what you would call the Great Pyramid
and what you would call the Sphinx.
Right? Again, this represents a timing
when there is more awareness, more
willingness, more
sharing. These ideas may come to light
somewhere between what you would call
1988, 1994 or six and can represent
again some records as you say of what
you might call the truer history of your
world. Yeah.
Uh second question, can you shed some
light on the volcanic ash or whatever it
is deposits that uh have supposedly been
found during uh previous to ice ages.
There's not so much many times the idea
volcanic although some of it is. Much of
it is also what you would call
meteoric. You follow me? Right. Four.
Your relatively recent theory has some
credence of the idea of polarity
reversals and what you would call mass
extinctions being related to the idea to
some extent of meteoric bombardment.
You follow? Yes.
Yes. Can you explain why uh Uranus is
the only planet whose axis is it was
brushed in a very close encounter in
many different ways. It had some of its
gravometric potential removed to a
different local within the world. It was
brushed in a way by a body what you
might call a very dark gravitational
body which does sweep your solar system
from time to time.
that the dark sun to some degree. Can
you explain this um metaphysically?
What does represent? It represented the idea
does represent? It represented the idea
basically of your world in a sense
tipping into a subconscious well realm
of hidden things of dark times of
negative experiences. In many
way it was in a
sense the turning away of a portion of
your consciousness from the light that
you are. So that it was a true expression of
are. So that it was a true expression of
polarity. Since only one pole at any one
time on that world faces the sun, the
other always faces out into
darkness. You follow me? Yes. In
astrology, it represents um uniqueness
and suddeness and creativity. Oh yes.
These are the reflections of the attempt
to rebel against those dark forces or to
regain creativity. To some degree it
simply stood as the signal if you will
of what was going on in this particular
system at the time, an outer marker if
you will of the polarity that was now
being experienced and expressed in your
system. And yet it carries that symbolic
reference archetypically. Yes. Yes. Oh
yes. Oh, you intuitively understand what
it represents in terms of your timing.
Yeah.
Mer one moment.
There will be but a few moments
remaining for this interaction this
evening of your time. Proceed.
Um secondly, last time I talked to you,
I asked you for the metaphysical meaning
of Uranus. Yes. Of the planet Uranus.
Nice. And from what I understand
symbolically, you gave me the symbolism
for Saturn. Understand there are many
Saturn. Understand there are many
different degrees of symbolism and also
there are many different attributes to
the particular mathematical tool you are
using. Now in one level the idea of your
honor does represent certain
subconscious knowledge,
right? Um can I answer it for you maybe?
In your own terminology from your own
perspective. Okay. From what I
understand, Utar um from what I can
understand the symbolism of it, it is
similar to my perception of yours. All
right. And you said that in your civilization
And you said that in your civilization
you see
events of the both both polarities make
one event. Yes. Okay. So what I
perceived was that the symbolism
actuality from what I understand and
what I perceive Uranus has to
exist because of Saturn. In other words,
there is one event all life. But that is
true of your entire solar system, right?
I recognize that all life. Uh my other
question was uh you said that there was
seven months gestation for birth
civilization. Um, I guess you meant in our terms. Yes.
Um, I guess you meant in our terms. Yes.
Correct. Okay. You don't have a moon. We
do not have a moon. Okay. Does this
represent the fact that the masculine
and feminine forces were never
separated? Never.
Okay. [Music]
Um, oh, also I would like to know if you
could give me some information on the
civilization and the metaphysical nature
of Proion. One
more. This may or may not translate very
well in your language. The first
perception, the first quality, shall we
say, is of that which you would call
perhaps tubular energy, vortex
energy, vortex
gates. They are in a sense a
mentality that expresses
itself in a series of interconnecting
layers and levels.
The level of proon that we are familiar
with does not identify strongly with
your dimensional
plane. Although it does make use of an
ethermagnetic type of
mentality similar to the one you express
your mentality in in your physical
existence, but uses it in a
method that is almost impossible to be
experienced in your dimensional plane.
They are extremely rarified. You may
even call them gaseous, but we are not
necessarily referring to what you would
call their bodily form.
They are an inverted
society. Inverted into each other,
through each other, transparent in many
ways to each
other and yet at the same time highly
refor mostly is through the aspect of
myself which is in that sense his future
self and the serious connection is my
future self. So it forms the complete
triad of energy that is represented by
your world, our world and the world you
would call sistine which orbit the star
you would call
Sirius. It is a
balanced energy. The connection is there
because communication is necessary on
all three points of the triad in order
for there to exist a fulcrum upon which
a lever of transformation can be moved
to assist your earth in acceleration.
The connection is not as
direct perhaps as some of other
individuals upon your world might have
for it is basically a connection of
purpose of specific purpose specifically
for the transformational energy that is
necessary. The connection
between my world and the physical
channel is more direct. Although there
are tangential connections with Sirius
expressed in some of the individuals
with whom he associates to act and
assist as a balancing
factor in terms of
energy. Is this making some sense to
you? Yes. I was curious because Uranus
was in conjunction or in the same area
of space from the perspective of our
solar system at the time of his entrance
into material physical reality.
It is because
basically since Sirius represents the
fulcrum that will move the polarities
together and blend them in a sense then
it simply can function as a symbolic
expression that one of the primary
reasons in the contract we have made for
the channel being physically existent
upon your world at this time was to do
what is being
done to come through those subconscious
realms that have for a long time
maintained distance between the polarities upon
distance between the polarities upon
your planet and with that energy coming
from Sirius let us say blasting through
that door to create a vortex that draws
the energy of the polarity together with
it and brings it down to
earth you understand
thank you um I'd like you to help me
analyze a dream a little bit that I had
it was
u my wife and my son and I were in a
school and somehow I had this school was
getting ready to let out and everyone
was going to be coming out very quickly
and I was the first one out and I ran to
a parking lot where there was a vehicle
and it was for my son to ride in and I
had to hurry up and fix some brake or
something on the vehicle to keep it from
rolling back.
And while I was looking while I was
fixing the brake on the vehicle, I
looked up and there were four
extraterrestrials is what I perceived
them to be. And they were aiding me in
that uh with telepathy. I guess they
uh with telepathy. I guess they
indicated that there were tools on the
on the passenger seat. Yes. And uh you
know, if I may interrupt you from Okay.
Many times in your dream realities, you
are in many ways attending
schools. You are learning many things.
All of you. When you wake up, you may
interpret this as a literal school.
Although obviously it is not in the
format of what you call your physical
world education
system. And when you learn the things
you learn and you go running off quickly
to apply
them, in no way, shape or form do I mean
this derogatorily, but many times you
are most amusing to watch.
For many of you will still carry with
you even on that astral level the
assumption that certain things must be
manipulated very quickly otherwise they
will slide back into the format they
used to
exist. Simply, you were told in no uncertain
Simply, you were told in no uncertain
terms and with much love that the tools
you needed, if you felt you needed them,
were right
there and that we would assist you in
any way, shape, or form to allow you to
fix the brakes so you would not slide
back. Of course, it was never believed
by those beings that you were going to
slide, but you were acting out your
play. You are acting out your symbols
that would allow you to know with all
certainty that you would not slide back. And
back. And
therefore, it is with much
thanks from those beings and ourselves
that you allowed us to participate to
some degree in that particular play.
degree in that particular play.
The the vehicle never did slide back. I
did stop it. Yes. And you are the
vehicle. Now in physical terms,
is there anything that you can add to
that? I mean generally the concept was
clear to me. Yes.
Um just that you are learning many
things on that astral level.
I I assumed that the vehicle was for my
son that that I was preparing it to some
degree. You are a vehicle in a sense
that you are preparing for your
son and he is preparing vehicles for
you. Yeah, I'm aware of
that. Simply, it was an indication that
you are all exhibiting forward momentum
and there will be no need for any of
what you colloquially call repeat
performances. You follow? Yes.
Thank you for allowing us to watch.
Thank you.
At this time,
allow us to extend to each and every one
of you individually and collect our
deepest
appreciation in your
willing to participate and
cocreate this
dream this night of your
time. When you wake
up, you kind of begin to allow
yourselves to
live your dreams.
Now at this
timing in a more spontaneous
manner as the now I now am and as the
now you all now are. I will also suggest
at this moment an entitlement for our
interaction other than all is
vibration for that was the underlying
foundation of what we will be
discussing. But what will capture the
imagination is the entitlement live your
dreams utilize that dreams plural live
your dreams. Thank you. Our unconditional
Our unconditional
love, our excitement to you
all. We bid you exciting dream lives and
life dreams. We thank
dreams. We thank
you for the gift that you
are. We bid
you. Thank you.
Um I'd like to share a couple dreams
with you too. Um one is
um I was having a dream of uh
interpreting the shadow self and its
connection to the dark body in the solar
system. And um in the stream I
recognized or I perceived that uh the
distance between this dark body and the
sun was relative
to our development on Earth as far as
how far we were in perception from our
shadow self and the ego structure that
we know. All right. Um then I was
looking at a horoscope that was supposed
to have been mine and on it it said uh
EM1 Arcturus. Can you give me any
insight on that? What that would the EM1
Arcturus to some
to some
degree you can recognize the
electromagnetic vibration of Arcturus to
be the higher vibratory resonance plane
that contains both the polarities of the
bright star and the dark star
represented in your system. And that if
you can simply focus on the fundamental
vibrational frequency of the tip of the
triangle, you will then contain them
both. And in containing them though, you
can shorten any distance you may
perceive exists between
them. For you are looking down
symbolically from another plane of
existence altogether when you look
through the eyes of Arcturus. A symbol
that can be utilized that we have shared
with many of you to help you focus on
the vibratory plane of Arcturus energy
and consciousness is a white 12-pointed
star against an
orange circle against a black
background. You understand? Yes. Will
this be of the system? Yes. Um my second
dream was I was talking through the
physical channel um over the telephone
and we were carrying on extremely rapid
conversation. Um I I guess it just
seemed to be about every aspect of life.
And after we were finished talking and I
have hung up the phone I decided that I
could now go experience everything and I
did everything in an extremely
synchronistic way. It was just one thing after another
way. It was just one thing after another
was just falling into place.
This needs no interpretation. No, I
guess not.
Thank you for making that connection and
allowing the lines of communication
between yourself and all other aspects
of yourself to be open. By the way, you
are counterparts.
Yes. Thank you. Thank you very much. Um,
I have one more question. All right. Do
you have uh any information on a
consciousness that goes by the name of
Huba? Yes. I'm okay. Go ahead. Generally
speaking, though it may represent a few
other things depending upon the specific
individuals that are connected to
it, Kuma is the name of the planet in
the Orion systems that the majority of
Orion connected individuals come
from. It is the ancient
language in the ancient tongue. Kuba
manma means kuba is
hope. It is in a sense or was I shall
say a statement of pride and at the same
time a statement of control.
Therefore, to some degree, the term kuva
represents now the ancient energy of
negativity, the dark body side now being
blended with what you are learning in
this incarnation and allowing it to
become lit up.
So you are bringing back in that way the
so-called past and blending and balancing it with
past and blending and balancing it with
the so-called future in the present.
Does that assist you? Yes. Uh I
understand that I was told by another uh
channel that I was connected with Yuri
Geller and would you find that the
individual you call Geller is also very
strongly connected to Orion. Okay. Thank
you. Thank you very much. You may find
that the energy you call kuva like any
world can be representative of a
collective consciousness and can
function as an entity in and of itself
in a sense.
Many strong
magnetic
applications have to do with the idea
and the vibration of
huva. To some degree, some of this can
be brought out to the surface or
explored through minimum uses or contact
with the mineral upon your planet you
call hematite.
Thank you. Thank you.
you and then you um is that why the uh
on the news a baby dolphin washed into
into shore I think it was in San
Francisco. Yes. Is that it has something
to do with the idea now of showing you
the level of energy that is the
strongest. The idea of the level that is
coming to you interacting with you and
it will meet you on your own terms if
you will not meet it on it. It will come
to you as it has. Um do you sense a a
stronger convergence or equal um in
February 13th of 88?
There is some preparation on the idea of
February, but also once again do not
forget that of every year, especially
between now and your year 1990, one of
the strongest dates will be your March
15th as it always is.
Can you explain why? That is simply
indicative of the vibratory pattern of
going to another accelerated level. Many
of you already recognize this. You call
it the eyides of
March. It is simply a recognition of a
connection to conscious, subconscious,
and unconscious aspects of yourself. The
making of assessments of those portions
of yourself, the integration of what you
are ready to integrate, and the stepping
up to a new level from that point
forward. It is a very natural cycle of
vibratory overlap in your society. So
basically as we all accelerate um we're
doing this in leaps and bounds because
as more people become more accelerated
yes it is geometric logarithmic
the idea is that there will be highly
compacted acceleration by your year 1
19990 which will allow there to be more
conductivity more conduciveness to
allowing more blatant interactions
between your civilization and the
civilizations within in the association
of worlds.
Okay. I have one more question. Hey, can
you uh explain the difference between
this uh transformational age and other
transformational ages that have um come
upon our planet? I mean
astrologically we're actually entering
the age of Aquarius which undoubtedly
we've done before since that's based on
the wobble in a sense of the earth ais.
Now you have experienced high
degrees of compacted negativity whereas
you had not before. So you are coming
into this transformation with a high
degree of accelerated energy. Okay. So
we're coming out of the loop. Yes. Okay.
You are now exiting the cycle of
negativity at a highly accelerated rate
faster than you ever have before.
It is as we have used before the idea of
the rubber band analogy. As we have
said, transformation is not the product
of mediocrity. And you can look at the
idea of all the negativity you have
experienced as having a rubber band that
you have pulled very very very very far
back into the negative. When you let go,
just think how far and fast it's going
to go into the positive. That is the
main difference between all the other
cycles and this one. because you are
coming out of a highly compressed cycle
of negativity which is going to shoot
you very abruptly into a very expanded
cycle of integrity. Okay. So I what I'm
seeing then I've just figured out is the
conclusion of a cycle in February which
in preparation for another new uh
beginning of March a subcycle if you
wish. All right. Thank you. And also
your energy is strong enough now to
allow this cycle of integration to be
the last
cycle. In approximately 2 to 3,000 of
your years, you will no longer need to
be physical as a race at
all and you will leave your
earth and allow others who may wish to
have similar experiences to what you
have experienced to come in and use the
planetary vibration. Some of you may
remain as
guides to let the new influx in on a few
of the secrets of
Earth, a few of the ideas they might
expect when limiting themselves to such
a high degree of focus in physical
reality as you have. Remember that our
very affectionate name for all of you is
masters of
limitation because you have in very many
ways none at all. You have experienced
more boldly than almost any other
society we are aware of all the
different ways you can experience
limitation and
negativity. This makes you very very
well-rounded.
A process to go through to allow us to
be what we already are. Yes. Right. Yes.
In a different way. Thank you. Yes.
fish. So when we use uh 100% even in um or it
So when we use uh 100% even in um or it
would appear to be third density, we
could dematerialize objects or
absolutely why
not. Although in a sense, well, if you
wish to pick at
straw, doing that would actually place
you in what is colloally referred to as
the fourth density. But in a sense, yes,
you could do this. We basically do that
anyway. Yes, you do do that all the
time. But of course, we are saying doing
it consciously is what makes the
difference. You are always
dematerializing, recreating your
physical reality. Because even to create
what you call a motion, even the moving
of your hand from here to here is a D
and rematerialization process because
nothing actually ever moves or goes
anywhere. That's your illusion. You are
creating recreating different frames of
reference and you are creating a
continuity to unite them all into what
you call a fluid motion.
You never go anywhere. You never move a
thing. It all takes place within the
idea that you are and you project an
illusion around yourself so to speak
that it is taking place outside of you
physically. So the simple idea is that the conscious
So the simple idea is that the conscious
mind merges and blends with the
spiritual will like so it becomes the
simple idea is that the conscious mind
is the spiritual will. Right. Yes. But
the way it stands now, the way we
perceive ourselves is that um the
conscious mind has to judge which things
fit and which ones don't. When in
actuality they all fit. Yes, they all
fit. It is all as you say relative.
That's all it is. There is no the truth.
The truth is composed of all truths and
all truths are true and all truths are
real. The only one background reality
that is common to everyone in creation
is simply that you
exist. You are a part of creation.
That's it. Everything else is your
individual or collectively agreed upon
variation of the same theme. Creation
creating itself in all the ways that it
can just because it can. Because that's
what creation is.
Does that answer the question? Yeah. I
have one more. All right. Um I've been
reading a lot and and heard a lot about
uh Hooa Huba and Spectra. Yes. Uh and
their connection with Yuri Geller. Yes.
Um can you expand on that if you have?
All we will say or allowed to say for
now is that they are polarity
representations of different energies to
which that being is connected. One of
which is ancient Orion Kua. One of which
is what you might call future plleadian
spectra. Okay. I feel like I have a
strong um future self that is related to
you in a sense. Yes. Okay. Is that or am
I interpreting the counterpart aspect
between myself and the physical channel
or is that the same thing? To some
degree it is similar and analogous and
mirrored to some degree in our reality.
Okay. Um, could it be said also that we're
Um, could it be said also that we're
just accessing the same collective
unconscious? It can be said so and that
is so true. Okay. Thank you. Thank you
very much. You may all enjoy a short
break. We know the whole idea of how we
feel in that sense. We trust ourselves
as aspects of the infinite. Understand?
Therefore, we interact spontaneously
without necessarily having to really
plan anything, without having to make
sure everything will go as planned. We
do not need the insurance of having
something to fall back on should what we
go for fail. All these ideas are doubts
and mistrusts of the true
unconditionalness of our love.
Understand? Is this making sense?
um than you. I remembered more about my
extra terrestrial intera
extraterrestrial interaction when I was
11. All right. Um the spaceship was
shaped like a top. All right. With and
it looked actually like a top with a
knob on top. And what they were showing
me were charts, some kind of charts,
star charts. Thanks. Um, can you expand
on that? Well, simply recognize that you
were in a very symbolic fashion being
shown the energy of the patterns, the
interlinking patterns of the stars that
you in your terms as a tool rely on very
heavily. Now, in following, you were
being given an intuitive understanding
of the web and the matrix of
interconnection energy through all the
stars in all the galaxies. So you could
understand the fundamental foundational
matrix network web of energy vibrational
agreements that will allow you to
intuitit your senses of service to other
individuals through the tool you have
chosen to use. Also, you do have to some
degree connections in many ways, in many
lives to some of those systems. And in a
sense, some of the information quote
unquote, I use this loosely, that you
receive comes from individuals quote
unquote stationed aspects of yourself,
stationed in some of the star systems
you were shown. So that you are
constantly feeding to yourself a network
of energy that you can tap into and
utilize through you, channel through you
instinctively to lay down a groundwork,
a foundation for the patterns that
assist you in describing to other
individuals some of the agreements they
have made for their lives. Yes, you just
answered all of my questions. Thank you.
Um, okay. After that period, I was 11
years old. I went into a four-year
period where I trained falcon heavily. I
was extremely excited about that. Can
you tell me what that symbol what is the
symbol of the falcon and eagle? To some
degree it represents the release of the
soul into another realm and it is also a
very ancient Egyptian symbol in that
sense. You have strong connections there
as well and you have performed many of
the same functions that you perform now
in ancient Egyptian times. Yeah. Thank
you. Well, thank you very much.
You following on that note, um is there
a correlation between the number of
planets in the solar system and the
duration of gestation? There can
There can
be although recognize that that may
simply be arbitrary to a particular
system. It is not a given rule. Correct.
Just in maybe one dimensional. Yes.
Okay. Um I asked you about Proion last
time. Yes. Okay. I feel that this energy
is in my connection to being able to u
intuitively change to all of these
different levels in my counseling and
astrology. All right. It is your key. It
is your crossroad. It is your gate. How
do you wish to use it? Just like how you
very good. Are you enjoying yourself?
Yes. Well, thank you very much. One
moment. [Music]
[Music]
It is also in many ways what you may
call your furnace or what we have
referred to as your crucible of change.
It
is the
chalice in which you can melt down the
reality you consider solid and allow it
to be reformed and recristallized.
It's done. Thank you. I'd like to ask
you some space questions. four right
scientists believe that um our solar
system is surrounded by a bunch of
comets and that the dark body as it
comes in every few million years or
whatever it is it it's what started the
perturvation of the comets into the into
their orbits is that is true then s okay
what is the symbol for the
comet as has already been described in
much of your society
It is in a sense the clockwork to some
degree of your system. The portent of
change itself, of the shift of
consciousness itself. It is as what you
might call the minute or hour hand
sweeping by to let you know that a time
is now changing from one level to
another. Certain ideas of periodicity of certain
Certain ideas of periodicity of certain
comets will represent certain ideas of
periodicity within your society or let
us say vice versa since everything in
the physiological universe is your
projective symbol and represents
something going on in your consciousness
itself to begin with.
As an example, the idea you call the
comet of Halley with its approximately
76 of your year
periodicity represents what you call the
typical lifespan as you have lived it
now in modern times of your human body.
But now that your idea of lifespan is
changing, now that your idea of the time
flow is
changing, the last time you saw that
This is the last time you will ever see
that comet. It will not be
returning. It will in your terminology
be impacted somewhere on its journey as
we read the energy
now. but represents different ideas,
different eras, different epics,
different times of change, different
gates and doorways that you are passing
through. They are the minute and the
second and the hour hands of your solar
system to some degree. Okay. Um the last
time it came, I perceived the energy as
um mixing in a lot of past selves and
different levels of probable selves.
Yes. uh because it represented the idea of
uh because it represented the idea of
lifespan itself and therefore now
because this is your convergence
era it represents all the idea of the
homogenization of all things you have
learned in many different lifespans.
Yes. Okay. So that's why you don't need
to see it anymore. In blending all that
idea together you now far exceed and
outstrip its periodicity. Okay. Because
during the period when it came into the
solar system it was very close to the
sun. I experienced a lot of uh deja vu
of deja vu. Yes. Overlaps of different
vibratory frequencies of different
perspectives that you are on physical
and non-physical planes. Okay. Um can
you give me your reflection of the
supernova and uh 197 1987a which was in
the uh crab nebula? Oh no not the crab
nebula. I'm sorry. Uh tarantula nebula.
When you see these things, of course,
the timing in which you see them is to
some degree the idea significant for
you. But do of course also remember that
it did not actually happen then. It
happened many millions of your years
before. 170 million. Yes. As a matter of
fact, but the idea of when you see it
does fit into the overall timing of when
you are awakening to different ideas
within yourself.
Sometimes the idea of nova can represent
many of the explosive revelations that
are going on within your consciousness.
The magnitude of those revelations as
they take place interconnectedly within
the mass mind of your planet. They can
be reflections of that level of
light. Understand? Yeah.
Um can you explain a little bit about
your perception of nutrino?
To some degree they represent an idea
that you have which does not exist
exactly in the way for now you might
think. It is that essence or particle if
you wish to call it that although that
is a rather arbitrary
terminology. It is that essence or
particle that has to do with one of the
factors that is allowing your
consciousness or reflecting I shall say
your consciousness is now understanding
or beginning of understanding that the
physical and the non-physical are the
same idea. This is why you have termed
it in a sense a massless particle. The
idea, the concept that you are even able
as a society to come up with the idea
that something could be a particle and
yet possess no mass is the beginning of
the indication that you are now willing
to allow consciousness itself to become
a part of the equations of your physics.
That you are now recognizing that
physical reality and non-physical
reality are simply different expressions
of the same primal energy. And the
nutrino to some degree represents the
threshold or one of the threshold
symbols of physicalness into
non-physicalness of non-physicalness
into physicalness of the idea of the
birth of something from nothing and the
reinforcement of nothing from something.
It is your beginning of the blending of
all these concepts into one homogeneous
understanding that you are the creator
of your reality itself. And you are now
simply giving yourself symbolic building
blocks to make that seem possible in
physical terms. Because the idea as has
been expressed by many is that if a
particle doesn't really have mass then
in a sense it can be affected by
anything at all anything else which
doesn't have mass per se including what
you call consciousness. Understand?
Yeah. So it is in a sense a particle of
consciousness expressing itself in one
way a way that now is more expressive of
the similarity between physical and
non-physical reality. Okay. So that's
like kind of like in vacasillating
between Yes. Okay. When a supernova
occurs is this is the reason why we get
a a charge of them a little bit
preceding the light or the Yes. because
they are existing at what you would call
the absolute speed or limit of the vibration
absolute speed or limit of the vibration
of your physiological universe because
in a sense they are the support
mechanism of it itself. They ride the
wave of the universe itself at its
absolute limit of light. Yes. But a type
of light that you are not completely
aware of yet.
Okay. That light which defines the idea
of physical reality itself. It is
something a little bit different than
the vibration you call your typical
visible electromagnetic spectrum.
Okay. Um, one more
question to some degree.
Yes. Um, you said before that the
asteroid belt was a planet that exploded
evidently. Yes. We exploded it. The
civilization thereupon. Yes. And since
many of you are reincarnational in that
nature now from that world. Yes. Okay.
And the Earth and Mars shifted orbits to
some degree. Yes. Okay. With with not
too drastically, but to some degree.
Yes. So they didn't actually switch
orbits. They just changed each other's
orbits to some degree. Partly
responsible for the idea of the state of
the Martian surface as you see it now.
Okay. Would there be any remnants of
physical civilizations on Mars?
To some degree. Yes. Okay. But it
wouldn't be because of its or present
orbit. It would be because of the
previous orbit that existed. Yes. Okay.
Thank you. Thank you. Oh, thank you very
much. Is that the same as one moment?
What is that the same as the triangle
and the state of equilibrium? I mean the
rest state is what you're talking about.
The point the apex of the triangle to
some degree does represent that idea.
Yes. Okay.
Thank you. Thank you. Is this your one
moment? One moment. One moment. One moment.
Ma'am, could you uh give us some
reflection about the idea of uh King
Arthur and the Knights of the Round
Table? Another time.
Another time.
There is much information that is now
coming up that can be shared, but for
now, another time. There is in a sense
so much information that to go into it a
little bit now in that sense would not
do it. One
more in the next interaction that we
have with you. We
will as a subject discuss more of what
you would call the Arcturian
ideal. It will be in that sense
available and we will in your terms have
the title. But at this time, we must now
title. But at this time, we must now
extend to each and every one of you our
deepest appreciation for having
co-created these interactions with us
this day of your
time. We extend to you our unconditional
love and once again our reflection of
our deepest belief in your ability
because you are aspects of the infinite.
There is no doubt about it and no
question whatsoever in our perspective.
You are capable of creating what you
wish because you have always created
everything you
have. You are that
powerful. We thank you for this
co-creation and the sharing of this
dream time. We wish you exciting dream
lives and life dreams. And remember it
is in a sense one of the
things. Transform, redirect, redefine. Be what
Transform, redirect, redefine. Be what
you prefer to be. It is that
easy.
Guaranteed. We thank you and bid you a
fond and deeply loving good.
Second idea that we would like to
discuss briefly is something that in your
briefly is something that in your
terminology we promised to discuss last
time we interacted with you and this may
have specific i specific resonances for
certain individual. It may not hit all
of you in the same way but allow us a
brief moment to as you say catch up on
oh shall we say unfinished business. The
idea will be a reference to what you
have called the Arthurian energy, the
Arthurian legends in your society. For
many individuals are beginning to get
back in touch through different symbols,
different archetypal energies of
consciousness on their planet. And one
of these archetypal symbols is what you
call the magical energy, the sorcery
energy. The fact that you are the
creators of your reality, what you have
called the Merlin energy, the arurian
energy. And yes, of course, as always,
the guavier energy for all ideas must be
expressed as polarity, female and male,
to be balanced and whole. Therefore,
recognize there is now existing in your
society some little which can aid and
assist many of you in delving a little
bit further into the true energies that
existed in that time frame of your
history. This literature exists now in
the format of what you would call a book
or as you wish to books. And these
titles are simply referred to as a
greenstone and b eye of fire.
These two books, these two aspects of
literature cover a great deal of the
true energy, the true momentum of the
energy that is spawned from those times
and even from other times more ancient
than that. For the Arthurian legend in
that sense is not an origin point, but
it is simply a continuation point of a
very ancient energy that stems all the
way back and further to what you would
call avian times in your society. It was
taken up by individuals that were
offshoot remnants of Atalantean
civilization called the Druid faction of
which many of you have connections in
this gathering this day of your time.
This Druid connection, these ancient
sorcerers or magicians as you say in
your England area upon your planet were
attempting to recapture their connection
to nature that they felt they had lost
with the destruction of your
civilization of Atlantis. And in this
recapturing they became aware they
became sensitive to many different
energies many different ideas with which
they could reconnect to nature to your
basic naturehood and your basic power as
an aspect of infinite creation.
This reconnection involves many of what
you have come to call magical practices
in this way and the realization that
many substances on your planet can be
representative of great focusing of
power such as stones and crystals and
plants and animals and even yourselves
in that way. Do remember by the way that
all such notions of tools such as your
crystal are in themselves yes a
representation of energy but they are
triggers and catalysts for the release
of the energy that already exists within
each and every one of you. It is not so
much in other words of the power that
you may perceive in utilizing crystals
comes from them. It comes from you, but
you allow the crystal or the tool to be
a reflection and a mirror to allow you
to trigger that energy through the
crystal from yourself to see it
manifested in obvious way. But the idea
of these two words, green stone and eye
of firing ball, the idea of two stones,
one green, one red, that do represent
the transformational age upon your
planet and represent a group of
individuals that sought to replay in
modern times, as you say, many past
lives they had had by coming together
and rediscovering these artifacts which
had been hidden for quite some time. In
rediscovering these artifacts, they also
rediscovered much of what you call the
true history of the Arthurian legend in
that way. One of which we would like to
point out, especially because of now the
importance of the balancing of the
feminine masculine energy upon your
planet. The idea relating specifically
to Guavier in that sense, which is in
your terminology, your ancient language,
not the true name, which was originally
in the original language, Guvo. Now,
Guavo in this sense was not the idea of
what you may
call the maiden queen that is depicted
in much of the legendary in that sense.
The idea is that Guvo was what you would
call a sorceress barbarian queen who
made her way with many of her people up
to the area of England and became inshed
in the idea of the druidic practices and
many of the individuals that were
involved in the druidic practices and
the idea of the societies and
organizations of nighthood in that way
and became co-partner in that sense with
many of those
individuals and This legend in your
terms has boiled down to the idea of a
particular king and quote unquote his
queen. We recognize that the idea of the
submersion of the feminine aspect is
something that is a result of the way
your society has unfolded for the past
few hundreds of your years. But the idea
is to bring that balance up again and
recognize there's a great deal of power
and connection to nature on the feminine
side represented through the barbarian
queen as you say guo and also balanced
on the other side by what you call the
merlin energy the sorcerer within each
and every one of you the magical being
that each and every one of you would
have created to live. The whole idea of
what you would call the cutting edge of
Excalibur, the sword that is represented
in that way does exist has been
discovered and is a part of the
literature we have referred to. The kilt
of the sword contain the red and the
green stone which represented the
balance and the cutting edge between
physical and non-physical reality. All
these ideas and all these symbols have
been to some degree diluted in some of
the legendary and some of the mythology
that you have wrapped around this idea.
Many of these events were quite
different and many individuals who have
very strong druidic past life
connections are now finding themselves
realigning with the idea of either
mathematical pursuits, alchemical
pursuits, scientific pursuits or
astrological pursuits in this way
because they are recapturing the flavor
of the timing of the precision of the
energy and recognizing the passage of
cycles as they play out upon your
planet. You are now at the end of a very
strong cycle of limitation and
negativity and beginning a new cycle of
positive recognition and
realization. And in these ideas are what
we are here to assist you with to
reflect to you as a mirror the wakening
up within each and every one of you of
your own source of power of your own
recognition of the ability to create the
lives you want to create and to use your
imagination to delve into anything that
you would call your past and create
anything that you would call your
immediate future. It is all up to
you in these interactions. Allow us to
remind each and every one of you that we
are here not so that what we have to say
will be placed above what you understand
about yourselves. For you know far more
about yourselves than we can ever know.
But we are here perhaps to approach you
to reflect to you yourselves through
what you may have allowed to be a back
door that is open that you do not
necessarily have the awareness of that
exist but to allow us in a sense to walk
through that back door to open it a
little wider with you and to allow
certain ideas to come to the forefront
of your consciousness.
We in that sense if we remind you by
radiating a particular frequency of
energy to you that you have the ability
to match that energy that you have the
ability to live your lives in ecstasy
that you have the ability to express
yourselves as the magical beings you
are. But understand miracles what you
call miracles in life they are not the
exception to the rule. They are the
rule. The idea of all the struggling and
the pain and the suffering that you have
experienced for many thousands of
lifetimes that is the exception.
Miracle is the natural order of things
falling into place automatically when
you allow it to because life works when
you let it. The idea of seeing miracles
in your day-to-day existence is becoming
far more commonplace now as you begin to
realize that what you have called for so
long physical solid reality is
absolutely nothing more than you have
been taught to dream that it is.
Physical reality has no empirical
existence aside from the definitions you
have been taught to give it. Even your
own physicists and your own scientists
are beginning to discover that this is
so that what you perceive in your
physical reality is only what you have
been taught to think that you must
perceive. And all the seeming solidity
and unmovable and impenetrable ideas of
physical materiality are only so
seemingly unchangeable because of the
definition you have that they are in
fact solid. They are your thoughts. They are
solid. They are your thoughts. They are
your energy. They are projections of who
and what you are. Getting in touch with
this consciously and realizing it
consciously and acting upon that idea
consciously is what creates the idea
that you have always referred to as true
magic. It is not an issue of mind over
matter. It is an issue of realizing that
mind and matter are the same thing. So
as you become more conscious of the fact
that there really is no separation
between what you have called mind and
what you have called matter then you
begin to see that as you think so you
experience. It is as simple as that. And
in all the interactions we will be
having with you this day of your time it
will always boil down as you say to that
one fundamental idea. You are the
creators of your experiential reality
whether you consciously are in touch
with that or not. Part of our service to
you is to assist you in becoming more
consciously aware of how you have
created the realities you have been
experiencing so that if you don't prefer
what you've been experiencing, you can
understand why you have created it and
so you can get in touch with that,
integrate it and create what you want to
create because you are aspects of the
infinite. In your biblical literature,
it says you are made in the image of
God. But how many of you know what that
means? God or what we call all that is
is literally infinite creation, a
multi-dimensional being. You are made in
that image. All beings within creation
are made within
that are aspects of the infinite. In
your biblical literature, it says you
are made in the image of God. But how
many of you know what that means? God or
what we call all that is is literally
infinite creation, a multi-dimensional
being. You are made in that image. All
beings within creation are made within
that image. And what that means is that
you're multi-dimensional creators
too. So what we are doing here this day
of your time in this interaction is
reminding you how you can begin to act
like you are a multi-dimensional creator
with conviction, with trust, with
knowingness.
We at this time extend to each and every
one of you our deepest appreciation in
cocreating this interaction with us and
in choosing to act as ambassadors and
representatives of your society because
that is what you are right now. Make no
mistake about it. You are representing
your entire planet in this interaction
right now. For there are many many many
worlds that I am representing in the
association of worlds. And I thank you
for allowing me to function as an
ambassador and a representative of all
of them. For there are many listening in
now through me. In these interactions
day by day and bit by bit. Your world
and our worlds create more likelihood
and more opportunity to begin one day to
interact face to face. But that will
only occur when you are functioning as
equals not only to us but to yourself.
This day does not have to be very far
off. The more willing you are to
accelerate that process now, the sooner
it can occur. We thank you for the
opportunity to generate that likelihood
between us because we do desire to
interact with you because through you,
we are given the opportunity to see that
many more ways that the infinite creator
has of expressing itself to be. You are
just as valid as any being within the
universe. And we are here to remind you
of that.
In return for your gift of allowing us
to experience your consciousness, I will
ask you now, how is it that I may serve
all of you? Thank you very much for your
sharing. You and then you. Um, is there
an Arcturan connection to the Arthurian
philosophy? Yes, there is. And the idea
of Arcturus, the star system you call
Arcturus, is that which represents to
some degree the pinnacle of a system
that allows energy from other systems to
come into the one you are connected to.
It is, shall we say, the dispersal gate
through which energy from other systems
and other dimensions is dispersed into
the dimension of experience in which you
exist as well. It is the monitoring gate
in that sense and therefore represents
the idea quote unquote of rulership or
kingship although not meant in a ruling
sense. You understand? Mhm. But yes,
there is a very strong connection. What
is my connection to it to the
Arthuran or Arthur? I am not going to
get specific in terms of lines except to
say that you already understand again
the idea of your connection. your idea
of the connection to energy cycles
expressed in what you call alchemical or
mathematical or astrological terms all
those being tools and symbols to
represent the recognition of cycles of
energy within creation. So the Arthurian
connection in a general sense in an
overall symbolic sense arthurian
Arcturan connection in that sense is to
be one of the beings that is familiar
with monitoring and dispensing the flow of
monitoring and dispensing the flow of
energy to various systems as they
require it to represent the different
transformations they are going through.
You are in that sense therefore
functioning as a
gate monitor. You understand?
Does this make some sense to you? Yes,
it does. It is also strictly and
strongly connected into the idea of what
have been constructed upon your planet
and are called the idea of the stone
circles and the stone gates because they
are energy vortex gates through which
you are connected to many different
dimensions. Understand? Mhm. Does this
assist you? Yes, it does. Thank you very
much. Yes.