a little th good day to you this day of
your time how are
you allow us to begin this interaction
this day of your
time with what might be titled a cozy
little chat now we usually discuss many ideas
chat now we usually discuss many ideas
with you in these interactions at the
beginning of the session that deal with
what you may call fundamental tools
fundamental methodologies by which you
can allow yourself to get more closely
in touch with the Creator that you are
with the reality that you have created
with the methodologies by which you can
create the reality you
prefer and to some degree in this
interaction this evening of your time we
will touch upon these ideas but mostly
we would simply at this time enjoy
speaking with you individually and
collectively in a
relatively informal manner just sharing
of thoughts sharing of
perspectives sharing of our
sensation of the momentum that has been
generated by these interactions and all
other interactions you have co-created
with any
Consciousness anywhere at any time
throughout your entire planetary
civilization in this transformational
age all the ideas that we have shared
with you all the ideas we have reflected
back to you as we have always said are
simply reflections of the things you
already know within yourselves to be
true we have not really taught you
anything fundamentally new we are simply
mirrors being of service to reflect back
to you the power you already have at
least we believe you have it you don't
have to and sometimes many of you have
to and sometimes many of you have
expressed to us in our interactions that
it may seem difficult for you to believe
that you have this ability to create
your reality the way you prefer it to
be all right so be it it is all right
you are all doing just fine no matter in
what way you choose to do
the life that you have created to be
your own you are all doing just fine for
remember remember and take it to heart
even though you may have the experience
in your reality of what you call
physiological death you never really die
you are all Eternal you are
all the
infinite and what you call physical
death is only a a change of
format a change of
perspective change of
methodology may seem drastic to you but
remember you have always been infinite
and you have experienced physical death
many times and yet here you
are doing just
fine and so truly
understand that if you have a fear of
the the changes you say you want in your
lives all right if you have the fear
acknowledge it acknowledge you have the
fear and as many of you have recognized
you can still say I have the fear and
I'm going to do it
anyway because you know that no matter
what happens you will still
exist even if what you did resulted in
what you called your physiological death
not that we recommend it but even if
that were the case even if that is what
you created you will still
exist you will still be
alive you will still be just
fine all the things I have shared with
you about your imagination is the
primary tool about all the methodologies
that can be utilized to create your
reality belief systems emotions and
thoughts intentions and actions
integrity along with imagination all these things
along with imagination all these things
we have discussed all these things we
have shared they are all perspectives equal
shared they are all perspectives equal
to any other perspective you may choose
to create to some degree they are
descriptive of some of the fundamental
mechanisms of
creation but how you choose to interpret
them through the Persona you have
created yourself to be is up to you and
you can allow them to work in many
ways we have discussed that there really
is no one way that all methodologies of
expression of the self as an aspect of
the Infinite Creation by definition are
all valid and equally real and equally
true I have discussed all these ideas
with many of you over the course of what
you may call the four years of your time
that we have interacted with you through
this particular
Channel always always we ask you to
remember never never never never
never to believe anything I say just
because I said
it you have equal ability to determine
what is true for
you just as I have the ability to
determine what is true for the reality I
prefer to be I am only sharing with you
what works for me it is up to you to
decide whether or not you wish to adapt
it and adopt it into your reality to
decide if it works for you we re
recognize as a
civilization that you may now be
proceeding in Pathways in methodologies
that are similar to methodologies that
have worked for us and therefore we
recognize that some of our methodologies
may work for you
fundamentally but that's up to you
completely utterly up to
utterly up to
you there is
absolutely nothing we can do
nor would want to do to force upon you
the assumption that you have to do the
things the way we do
them we love you
unconditionally and again we have faith
and belief that you will do whatever you
really believe you need to do to be
whoever you have defined yourself to
be sometimes many of you have approached
us as if we know
everything we do
we know everything we need to know to be
who we are at any given moment just as
you know everything you need to know to
be who you are at any given
moment but the focus that you are in
right now the Persona that you are right
now the focus I am in right now the
Persona I am right now does not
necessarily have to have conscious
analytical recognition of everything in
Creation in order for me to exist in the
way I am it is known to all of us on
what you have called and created to be
other levels of reality but the
information that you really need to live
the life you're living is always
available to you and what is not
immediately available what in that sense
belongs to other levels you do not
always need to live the life that you
are living
now one thing I can guarantee
you that we do not know and will never
know is when you will choose to
know that you are the creators of your
reality I will never know that that is
completely up to
you you will always be the first to tell
us when you know that to be true for
you I will never be able to tell you
when you are going to decide that you
are the creator of your reality and when
you are going to decide to act like
it that is not for me to know it is for
you to know for you to decide when you
have decided then I will
know and I will be more than willing to
allow you to tell me for it will give me
great joy to know anything you have
decided is true for you because I love
you as you are
and we thank you for the opportunity to
interact with you the you you have
chosen to be individually and
collectively for in experiencing your
civilization always we are given the
opportunity to expand our understanding
of Infinite Creation are all the ways it
can manifest itself through you you
expand our concept of
creation and for this gift we thank
you in return for this cozy little
chat once again I will simply ask you
now how may I be of service to you good
day vashar and to you good day thank you
very much for your opening speech or
chat it was really
interesting um I would like to discuss a
situation that exists on animal
experimentation as many of our
researchers and scientists use animals
to test um test things that they don't
want to use on humans and I was
wondering if the animal has an agreement
to do this and if it's cruel to the
animal to some degree there is an
agreement it does not excuse any idea of
acting outside of Integrity on the part
of the
human but the idea also is that animal
Consciousness doesn't always necessarily
experience things in the same way that
you would
however there is a very simple solution
as you say if and when your scientists
begin to understand that Consciousness
can be a part of their equations a part
of their understanding then they can
allow themselves more direct
communication with animal Consciousness
and the animal will simply tell them
anything they want to
know they do not have to take an animal
apart to learn the thing they need to
learn if they start to identify with the
vibration of the animal Consciousness
they will simply know what they need to
know if they use their imaginations and
their Consciousness in that way any sort
of a model any
sort of a structure any sort of a
template a blueprint an understanding
can be gleaned through the imagination
by simply performing the identification
with the consciousness of the animal and
allowing the information to simply come
to you it is simply that your society as
of yet is not willing to place its trust
in the ability to be able to do that it
still is thinking externally that it has
to gain its knowledge outside of itself
in the externalized manner of taking
apart the physiological Universe in
order to put it back
together now you can learn about many
things this way but as you have observed
it is to some degree a very slow or can
be very slow and tedious process because
the more details you create in that way
the more you pick things apart the
longer it takes in that sense to put it
all back together if you simply deal
with it as a whole to begin with then
you will have whatever understanding you
need at that moment if your scientists
are willing to trust their instincts and
intuition in that sense the animal part
of themsel and increase that
identification with the animal that they
are examining or researching then as
they identify with it as they literally
become the human version of that animal
then they will be able to understand how
they work because you will work the same
way you will have the same feelings
within you the same degree of
Consciousness the same instinctive
self-reflection and you will know the
answers to the things that you
seek that is in that sense from our
point of view the simplest way well in a
sense wouldn't if they could do that
with an animal they could do it with a
human then they wouldn't need the animal
to be a model well what do you
know surprise
surprise yes that is
correct how does this relate to the
genetic experiment experiments they did
during the times of Atlantis to some
degree it is similar in that timing
there were the creations of many beings
phys logically speaking that were
manifested outside the Integrity of your
race beings that were used in your
terminology for many menial tasks and
were in that sense subjugated dominated
enslaved were created only for the
purpose of serving in a menial
fashion so many of the things you are
now experimenting with in your society
that you are labeling genetics
are very similar to some of the ideas
that were done in the very Beginnings in
Atlantean times recognize of course that
all that is happening is in your terms
the repetition of a cycle begun so long
ago the playing out in a different way
of a similar idea because most of you
are the same beings that play those
ideas out in Atlantean times and in
having generated the cycle of negativity
that you did you have now played through
that cycle of negativity and have
brought your yourself to the same
threshold again the same threshold of
the same Powers now deciding whether to
use them with Integrity or outside of
Integrity as was done before so it is
your opportunity as a society to decide
now whether to learn to identify in
energy terms or to continue to segregate
in physiological
terms understand very much does that
assist you very much thank you very much
bash thank you very much sharing
bashard my name is George
GE greetings greetings what I would like
to know is what would it take for me to
be able to exteriorize out of my body at
will what exercise or what meditation so
that I have control complete control out
of exteriorization or would I need a
master you are a master everyone is a
master however a valid
methodology would be to find some that
already does it and mimic them because
the more you identify with someone that
does something you want to do the more
you match their frequency and the more
you match their frequency the more you
become capable of doing what they do
because you operate on the same
wavelength so one very strong
methodology would be to find someone
that is doing the thing you want to do
and mimic them follow them in that sense
not in the sense of following them
because they are better but simply
mirroring them because they are a
reflection of of the idea you wish to be
understand so far yes so that is one way
but remember that a master will be the
first one to tell you that you are a
master as well and they are only
mirroring back to you the capability
that you have already innately within
you and the only reason you may not be
able to experience that capability May
simply be because of the beliefs and the
assumptions and the definitions that
your Society has given to you about that
sort of thing because the way you
perceive that you have to go about it
may in of itself short circuit you from
doing it because your definitions may
not allow you to understand what it is
that needs to be done
so first of all as we have already
discussed if you can find a pattern in
your reality that you can copy by all
means do so the second idea would be to
create that pattern in your imagination
create an image of yourself doing what
you want to do then all you have to do
is take the situation and the
circumstance that you have at hand and
hand that situation to the imagination
you that represents your ability to do
what you want and watch the imagination
you in your meditative picture see how
that you handles the circumstance and
then simply do what that you does follow
your imagination mimic and mirror copy
the imagination picture you have that
you have created of yourself doing the
thing you want to do understand yes
secondly in that sense after the
mirroring aspect either with an outside
person so to speak or within the
imagination self is to
realize that even though we know in your
physical reality it seems as if you are
actually leaving your body you're
not your Consciousness does not exist
inside your body literally it is a
colloquial point of view that you have
because of of the physical world you
have created yourself to live as the
idea simply is is that your body is
within your Consciousness not the other
way around so what you are calling
astral projection or Detachment from the
body is simply an
expansion of your
Consciousness that allows you to now
perceive things per se beyond the bodily
limitation but you don't actually leave
it all together if you assume by
creating this picture that your
Consciousness is a bubble a sphere and
right now it is simply
condensed to the confines of the idea
the definition of your body then imagine
that that bubble simply expands so that
your body is now at the center of it but
your perspective your perceptive ability
is on the skin of the bubble so as you
expand the bubble expanding your
Consciousness in that sense to include
clude the body and other ideas then you
have the perspective from your point of
view that you're actually leaving the
body all you're doing is actually
enlarging the definition of the
Consciousness that you are so that your
body becomes a part of
it understand yes so one idea also is to
Simply relax more and more and
understand it's not a matter of will
power it's not a matter of effort and
struggle in that sense or concentration
in the disciplines sense it is a matter
of allowance relaxing letting go and
examining the definitions you have of
physiological reality one analogy may be
as follows I'm not saying this is the
case with you but simply to assist
individuals in understanding how these
things can work is that if an individual
wants the idea of what you have called
separation from the body because they
think that physical reality is a trap is
limiting and they're using the idea of
astral projection to run away from
physical reality then that idea is what
allows you to securely lock the key lock
the door and not allow the idea of
astral projection to occur because an
expansion will never occur at the
expense or the
invalidation of where you already are it
must always occur at the inclusion and
the enhancement of where you already are
so if astal projection is being used to
run away from physical reality you will
never allow yourself to have that
experience it's when you understand that
physical reality is just as free just as
valid just as joyful as what you assume
the astral experience could be like
that's when you create less difference
between the two and when you create less
difference between the two in your
definitions that's when you allow more
of a blending to take place and that's
when you realize that the physical
reality isn't really different per se
from an astral reality they are both
extensions and both expressions of the
same one reality just in in a different
format in other words your spirit once
again is not in your body your body is
your spirit in physical terms when you
understand that there is less separation
than you thought between physical
reality nonphysical reality when there's
not so much of a fence between them then
there will be no effort to break through
that fence they will simply start to
blend merge together dream reality will
be recognized as the physical reality
physical reality will be recognized as
the dream reality you will start to lose
that tight definition you will start to
fade back and forth one to the other
physical reality becoming more dreamlike
dream reality non-physical reality
becoming more solid to you so in
softening your definitions of physical
and non-physical reality you can also
accelerate the process of what you call
astr projection another idea is to allow
yourself when you drift into dream
states to tell yourself that you will in
the dream wake up and know you're
dreaming for as soon as you do that you
will realize that you are in fact
astrally projecting that is another way you can
projecting that is another way you can
also attract into your reality whatever
methodologies already exist in your
literature that can benefit you the best
but remember your imagination is the
prime tool and can always come up with a
methodology that will serve you best if
you relax and
trusted thank you well does that serve
you uh yes but I'd like to have one more
question referring to that would self
hypnosis Aid that relaxation it can it
is a tool like any other tool and if you
feel it will work for you then by all
means you can utilize that tool remember
that any hypnosis is self
hypnosis how about the light
meditation how about what the light
meditation the meditating is on light as
we have already said any tool is valid
if you are attracted to it then you're
attracted to it for a reason if you're
not attracted to it then that's an
indication that it probably will not be
that strong for you with Integrity use
the tool that it excites you the most to
use that's your indication that that is
the one that will probably work best for
you at this moment because it excites
you the most that's your indication you
could go on forever saying well how
about this one how about that one
they're all valid a different individual
will find that this tool will trigger
something within them more than another
tool will and it will be different for
another individual yet again decide what
attracts you and use it but remember do
not forsake the physiological reality it
is just as valid and the whole idea of
learning to astrop project is not to
escape physical reality it is to
integrate physical reality with the
non-physical so that you literally
become living light living dreams
because that's what reality is it's only
what you dream it to be anyway only what
you define it to be all right thank you
very much a pleasant
dream  hi Bashar unto you goodby uh
hi Bashar unto you goodby uh
since we create our reality can you all
hear this
person speak up speak up okay uh since
we create our own reality we create our
own disease and sicknesses right um many
of these through your unconscious
beliefs because you have created
yourself to have an unconscious side so
many of the things that you do not
necessarily prefer in life many of the
things that you would call negative are
usually the product of belief systems
that you have bought into that you don't
even know you have that's why many of
the ideas the diseases the negative
situations come up that's why they
manifest to show you look this is what
you believe in is this what you want
if not then transform it because now the
physical situation has put you squarely
in touch with what belief you have that
has created it now you can change it
that's why the manifestation occurs to
show you you have the belief so you can
change it doesn't occur to show you
you're stuck doesn't occur to show you
you're stupid it occurs to show you you
have the belief so you can change it if
you don't prefer it well I don't prefer
this congestion I've had for two weeks
and I didn't know what caused it how
does it serve you to have had it in
other words what have you learned about
yourself by having had it what has it
allowed you to
explore in what direction has it guided
You by having had
it well just tried to make me see what
um it is not trying to do
anything what have you learned about
yourself by having had it I don't know
well all right that's up to you to
discover in a sense the idea is to
understand first of all that if you have
created it then you must have a reason
allow yourself in your meditative states
to explore what that reason might be
allow yourself to understand that if
there is something that having it
teaches you about yourself then discover
if you're willing to learn the same
thing without that particular tool many
times what you call diseases in life are
simply there because you do not allow
yourself to learn the same lesson in a
positive way and so you bring yourself
into a corner and force yourself to look
at certain things in your life by
creating a disease that then focuses you
in the area you need to be focused now
sometimes these ideas can be in your
terminology speaking linearly in time
some of these ideas can be carryovers as
you say from other lives but that
doesn't mean that the control is back in
that other life the control is right
here right now in your present always so
if you can in your terminology ology get
a
handle on how it has served you to have
that idea then you can understand what
the reasoning is behind it why you would
have believed you would have to attract
something like that you can simply ask
yourself what would I have to believe in
order to have this
manifestation then once you understand
what the belief might be that has
attracted it you can then redefine it
and in redefining the belief you will
redefine the entire experiential reality
and you won't have it anymore any symbol
that has served its purpose does have no
need to stick
around you can transform it but the only
way you can transform any physiological
event is to own it first and in owning
it it means take the time and examine
with honesty and
Clarity what reason you would have to
have something like that in your life
examine all your relationships all your
associations see how you believe about
them see if any of these examinations
all of a sudden
increase the effect of the disease
because when that happens sometimes
that's your indication that the thing
you are now looking at in your life is
the reason you have attracted the idea
of the
disease now you say you have experienced
the idea of what you call a congestion
yes yes all right now usually we can
begin this examination Always by by
asking the fundamental question of
everyone are you doing in your life the
thing that excites you the most no why
not afraid to
why to security conscious security
conscious now if you really understood
what the idea of doing the thing that
excites you the most was all about you
would realize that doing the thing that
excites you the most is the most secure
thing to
do because doing the thing that excites
you the most is being the truest to who
you are and that's why it is the most stable
are and that's why it is the most stable
and secure thing you actually can do it
is only your assumption based upon what
you have been taught by your Society to
believe that playing it safe is the true
security it
isn't because it always creates
doubt it always creates the idea of
trying to be someone else something you
may not really be
doing what excites you the most with
Integrity is always the way to create
the highest degree of stability and
Security in your
life and this is not simply some
philosophical point of view this is an
actual description on mechanical terms
of how reality is created excitement
represents the thing that you chose to
be in this life that's why excitement
exist it is the vibration that
represents who you are so if you do the
thing in life that comes to you that is
the most exciting the thing you can
imagine would be the most exciting thing
to do that is the most stable direction
to move in the most secure because it
will bring an effortlessness with it and
an unlimited abundance with it to
continue to do the thing that excites
you the
most so saying you're afraid to do it
simply means you do not understand what
the excitement
represents it is simply saying that you
believe that playing it safe is more
representative of who you are than the
thing that excites you and if you stop
and think about it you will realize that
that's not
so you have no real reason to be afraid
to do it other than your assumptions of
what your Society has taught you might
happen but those things will only happen
if you buy into them if you simply know
you have no need for that idea because
you're willing to receive all the
information you need to receive in a
positive way then you will receive the
information in a positive way and you'll
be listening for it and you'll allow
yourself to hear it when it comes in a
positive way when it comes in subtle
ways you won't have to be hit over the
head by your circumstances in order to
pay attention to it that's usually the
only reason that individuals create the
idea of struggle and difficulty and
disease to show them beyond a shadow of
a doubt this is not you that's why
you're suffering because you're trying
to be someone you're not anytime you are
being who you are you will never never
never suffer never
struggle all struggling all pain comes
from resistance to your natural
flow that's why it's there so if you
have any degree of constriction within
you it's because you're not letting the
energy you are flow through you in a
natural way you're trying to be normal
not natural understand yes are you willing
natural understand yes are you willing
to act upon the opportunities that exist
in your life that represent what excites
you the most and believe that you will
attract the reality that represents your
ability to do that
thing yes I am all right then as soon as
you flow in that way all
congestions and constrictions will clear
out because you are simply congesting
yourself you are backing yourself up in
that sense by not allowing the energy
that is you to flow in a free manner
understand yes does that assist you yes
it does thank you take it to heart not
because we said so but simply because it
is who you are if you believe that to be
true and allow it to soak in in a
soothing revitalizing refreshing opening
clear breathing
manner breathe yourself into the reality
you prefer oh open
prefer oh open
up all right all right pleasant dreams
to you as well there will be more
information of a concentrated nature for
you in dream reality as you colloquially
call it
enjoy sharing
greetings Bashar and to you good day uh
I have a very close friend who Liv in s
speak up speak up so that all may share
who and what you are okay I have a very
close friend in San Jose he's very
spiritual very aware about a year ago he
felt compelled to go into a bookstore
and then he felt compelled to go to a
certain shelf ni and on that shelf he
found this book it's called The Book of
the unfolding yes and contains some very
profound passages all right there's no
copyright or publisher or date and we're
wondering where this book came from do
you know anything about this book it
came from all of you another version of
all of you what might be called an
ascended version of all of
you there's a symbol inside here and I
was wondering if you might know what it
means can you define it it is it is the letter
can you define it it is it is the letter
I and it's in a sphere a white sphere
okay a black
background thank
you it is the symbol of the ascended
version of All Of You the
I that you all are together as one now
what you may colloquially to some degree
referred to as the Christ Consciousness
can be one way to refer to
it but let us not leave it simply at one
label it is simply all of your
Collective Consciousness in a different
frequency that has come through some
individuals who simply allow themselves
who recognize basically what it was and
put it out in that way for other
individuals of similar vibration to
attract themselves to it as a marker as
a signpost that they are aligned with
themselves understand yes I do thank you
well does that serve you yes it does
thank you thank you very much for being
a part of that
eye welcome
Shing hi B and to you good die I'm
Basher too oh I I want to know one thing
what is the source that Jan or or
F once
again the source is Jin or
FTA you are asking for a source yeah I'm
asking your source is it Jin or
fisha are you using other then what is
termed the Channel's natural language to
describe these ideas yeah then they are
not translated to us for the channel
only understands his native
tongue same
tongue the
idea of what you call the terminology
Bashar mhm that
came through to be representative of us
Abu Bashar you are missing a point
mhm only the language that the physical
channel is programmed with Will Allow
there to be a translation because the
channel subconscious will not recognize
anything that in your terminology is not
what you call
English and therefore the terminology
will not reach us where we are for I am
not where you are this is a telepathic
link I am not in your physiological
presence only my Consciousness is linked
with the consciousness of the channel
and whatever the physical channel does
not understand will not translate back
to my Consciousness can you use use what
is termed an English definition for the
words you are using I don't know we do
have English termination or not because
can you describe the idea in English
terms you you pick the word Basher the
same same source which brings the
Basher repeat the two terminologies Jen
and
fr because Bashar has two sources only
one is Jane and one is fisha so just I
was curious to know that you are getting
from Jan or through
fishta understand that it is neither and
both for we are a balanced and Blended
understanding that recognizes all
polarity if you are seeking a single
Source then recognize that the single
source is simply the all that is the
Infinite Creation and it is from the vibration of
Creation and it is from the vibration of
the frequency of the Infinite
Creation that we are mirroring to
you does that serve you okay yeah thank
you thank shoting um
shoting um
Bashar good day to
you okay um um I have um before the
harmonic convergence I I talked to
somebody um a psychic and she asked me
this question she she asked me if I was
a walk-in yes and um I didn't know so I
told her I didn't know but it's been
bothering me because I've been coming
here and you've been talking about
Reflections and so I was wondering if I
was a walk-in or not you are in a sense
an Ascension of yourself many
individuals will refer to the nature of
what you call a walk-in to be something
that has quote unquote replaced the
original Spirit not the one that was
born unto the
body but the idea simply is that many
individuals will also Ascend into their
higher selves and that is what you have done
selves and that is what you have done
you have accelerated your own energy but
in that sense you are colloquially
putting it the original Spirit of the
body that's what I felt it was very
confusing when she asked me that it is
simply that different individuals will
recognize the energy in different
terminologies to some degree on one
level there really is no difference
between a walk-in and an
Ascension because all must be a part of
the same Consciousness anyway and simply
represents a different frequency of that
Consciousness even if you think it is a
completely different individual it isn't
really on the fundamental
level in terms of the consciousness
itself it can be on the personality
level a completely different individual
a completely different person but not on
the Consciousness level that is simply a
different frequency of the same one
Consciousness understand yes I so I'm
the same person you are not the same
person but you are the same
Consciousness a person is what you
simply refer to as your artificial
construct of physiological presentation
the personality is not representative of the
personality is not representative of the
total Consciousness that you are
understand this life you are living now
as a physical being do you have other
lives yeah I yes all right you do do you
believe that you do yes all right
understand that time is your illusion
and all these lives are going on
simultaneously yes well I think so all right
yes well I think so all right
all we are in that sense describing is
that all the lives you have ever lived
are living now or will ever live all are
aspects and projections of one single
Consciousness understand yes and any
changes you make in the Persona in any
given life are representative of other
extensions other aspects you may appear
to have the same bodily form but that's
simply a convenience of your Society so
that you can recognize yourselves as the
the same basic idea but you actually do
become a different person every time you
change a thought every time you change
an emotion every time you change a
belief you literally become a different
person because a person is an artificial
physical construct composed of beliefs
emotions and thoughts it is like a prism
that allows the white light of the
overall Consciousness that you are to
focus through that three-sided prism and
manifest in the diverse spectrum of
physiological reality but anytime you
change any one side of the prism the
light comes through in a different way
and you present literally a different
face so to
speak there are
civilizations in which when you change a
belief change an emotion or change a
thought the physical body changes
abruptly as well but simply that is not
the definition of your
civilization you have created the
convenience of keeping a similar
physiological form with every change so
that everyone will simply know you are
basically the same being but that
doesn't mean you're literally the same
person because a person is simply a
representation in physical terms of an
idea that your Consciousness is being at
any given
moment understand yes so you are a
different person but you are the same
consciousness
understand yes but why did she ask me
about um when I was a child um when I
was 9 years old to ascertain the idea of
the personality you were then as opposed
to the personality you are
now to understand the difference of the
frequency between the old you and the
new you oh I see understand mhm does
that assist you yes thank you very much
thank you very helpful thank
you
Shing hello Andrew you good day uh I'm
so glad she asked that question oh all
right because I had the same question oh
all right and um there was another
aspect to it which
is are there any extraterrestrial beings
in this room beside yourself at this
moment all of
you understand that none of you are
original to your planet none of
you
understand now there are also many other
beings on different frequencies that you
cannot perceive many Spirit forms many
extraterrestrial projections in that
sense that are simply in your terms
beyond your sensory ability to perceive
but each and every one of you have
connections into every level as well so
fundamentally speaking you are all also
extraterrestrials even though you are
all born on your
Earth understand I think I do everyone
comes from everywhere and therefore
everyone comes from nowhere in
particular that is why when the
individual ask us whether we came
through one energy or another energy
there simply is no way to label that as
far as we are concerned that is a
differentiation that for us does not
exist that is that individual's
interpretation and it is valid but those
symbols do not apply to who we are we
are simply not of your sphere of
influence in that way we are not of your
labels and the terminology that we have
chosen of Bashar has more than one
meaning and it is simply used as a
convenience now in one level it is
representative in the sense that we have
already many times referred to ourselves
as your future selves so in that sense
we are Humanity on another
level understand yeah and so in that
sense you could say we are your ascended
selves you could say we are your walking
cells but all of these things are quite
arbitrary labels and it all depends on
the point of view you have at any given
moment but we are not confined to any
one format or our Consciousness even
though we have a physicality we are
still Consciousness and can be
represented in any number of ways there
is an aspect of us and an aspect of all
of you that exists on all levels level
so so to say that you are one way is not
the to say We Are One Way or Another is
not the complete
story we do not come through any one
particular idea we come through any
Avenue and any doorway that serves you
in an integrated
way understand yes so you yourself are
expressing yourself on Earth at this time as the
yourself on Earth at this time as the
expression as the point of view as the
perspective that serves you and serves
everyone else in a life that is going on
well you know that changes time to time
it changes from second to Second moment
to moment right always you are
redefining and recreating yourself a new
a new a new you are always a new
person
always so the walk-in stuff is just to
sell books right
it is a real event we are not denying
its validity it is simply that sometimes
it will take on more of the
characteristics of what you classically
call a walk-in and sometimes it won't
but it's still basically representative
of a similar idea an Ascension an
acceleration of energy of Consciousness
a different frequency even if it seems
to be a completely different Persona a
completely different individual it still
by definition must be connected to the
same soul to begin with
understand yeah because remember your
spirit doesn't exist in your body it
doesn't literally leave and nothing else
literally comes in the energy that is
there is the energy that is there it
changes its frequency and can change its
definition and that is a real reality
that is a real change because that's all
reality is a shift in frequency one
reality to another is a shift in
frequency they're both real so in a
sense a walk-in and an Ascension can be
the same thing and they are both
accurate perceptions from different
points of view it is all relative that's
all we are saying it is neither one or
the other it is both always both always
always always all
polarity is always one in the
center all polarity must always come
from One
Source understand yes and that one
source is simply all that is the
Infinite Creation so the
Creation so the
label is not so much what is important
it is what you wish to do with the
energy you feel yourself to be if you
wish to express yourself in the fullest
way you can you will be being of service
no matter how you label who you are no
matter how you label how you got to be
who you are if you know your functioning
with an integrity and you're doing what
excites you the most you will fit you
will be of service you will live the
life you chose to
live understand yes does that serve you
yes it does does it answer your question
sufficiently yes it does well thank you
very much thank you
sharting hello Bashar and to you good
night I have a question about my son all
right he is very self-destructive all
right has been for 2 or 3 years perhaps
age 19 i in what
way he uses a lot of drugs all right and
alcohol all right have you shared with
this individual some of the Notions we
have discussed about externalizing your
power to some extent when he was a
little younger and was still living with
me all right he has not lived with me
for the past year all right and even
before that time he seemed very
unwilling to let any of the ideas in all
right but that's his choice is it not
yes it is my question
is why is he doing this and is there
anything that I can do perhaps in the
way of sending energy during meditation
that might help to heal him I suspect
that in some way have you sent this
energy I haven't tried it yet I why not
because I just thought of it oh all
right then understand you're sending it
right now
and of course any support any faith and
any belief that you can send to any
individual unconditionally will be felt
now they don't have to use
it but you can reach them on a
fundamental electromagnetic level that
it will at least give them the best
opportunity to use that energy in a
positive way so by all means send them
the energy they will receive it it has
already been received since I've tried
many ways to reach him and have not so
far succeeded is there a way that I
haven't thought of that might be more
successful that he might be more open
only the unconditional
love if that individual is not willing
to sit down and have a dialogue with you
if you are not in that sense capable of
allowing an interaction to occur if you
cannot co-create an interaction wherein
he will be willing to at least examine
different options then all you can do is
send him the love send him the energy
and attract with your belief with your
trust and your faith an
opportunity that will automatically
occur that can then provide the
circumstances necessary wherein at least
some ideas can be shared but not out of
desperation not out of belief that he is
weak out of the understanding that he
does have
strength all he is doing is putting his
power externally rather than internally
thinking that the tools the symbols the
drug as you call it is what carries his
ability to do what he wants you can
create a conducive atmosphere you can
literally radiate an electromagnetic
frequency that may like a compass allow
him to home in if he truly desires to
and co-create with you an opportunity to
sit down and discuss some ideas but do
not force them upon him just provide an
opportunity to understand that every
individual is as powerful as he or she
needs to be
already to create whatever reality they
desire without having to hurt anyone
else or themselves in order to create
it all you can do is provide an
atmosphere to afford the individual an
opportunity to hear these things he
chooses so now that you are radiating
that energy simply assume you will
attract and of information can be shared
or you will allow him to attract an
opportunity into his life whether it
involves you or that will allow the
information to at least Fai but it is
always going to be up to him as to
whether or not to look at it or believe
in
it in that sense that is really all you
can do for you cannot force anyone to
change that will usually only cause a
reinforcement of the negativity they may
already be
creating so love unconditionally s UNC
strength and send your belief in him
your belief that whoever he is whatever
he is wherever and whenever he is he
does have the innate ability to attract
the reality into his life that will
allow him to discover his own power send
your faith send your belief in his
strength and that will help him create a
conducive atmosphere to attract an
opportunity a mirror a reflection in
which he can then see his own
strength understand yes I do is there
any reason for me to pursue the idea
brought up by a therapist that he might
be
schizophrenic well in a sense you can
simply recognize that all of you are in
the sense that you all have many
different aspects to the overall Persona
you believe yourself to be what you
typically call a schizophrenic is simply
someone who has not been taught how to
bridge what they have created to be a
gap in the communication between one
idea of thems and another idea of
themsel they have not been taught how to
communicate that idea back to the
mainstream of your Society because they
are not considered valid points of view
so in a sense you can validate his
points of view it's not that you have to
worry after him in terms of having a
negative manifestation that you would
recognize as schizophrenia but
schizophrenia is simply a recognition of
different aspects different points of
view within the overall Consciousness
that you are and an understanding that
they do all fit and they do all exist
for a reason they are simply different
expressions of the same
Consciousness understand yes so even
though his behavior might be labeled by
some to be crazy or insane quote unquote
he still has the power to
absolutely as a matter of fact
individuals many times in your Society
who allow themselves to exhibit what you
call insane Behavior usually simply
showing you that they really very
blatantly have the power to tap into
other realities because that's usually
all the insanity represents is their
perception of another reality that is
just as real to them as yours is to you
but your society says they have no way
to validate that reality no way to
communicate that reality back to the
mainstream Society because the
mainstream what you call your consensus
reality won't buy it and so they lock
themselves in their own cycle because
they know it's
real understand yes
approximately approximately this is a
very very rough idea and only used to
provide a rough analogy approximately 80
to 85% of individuals you call insane
are simply unable to communicate the
different realities they know are
real now that is why you have also
recognize there's a very fine line
between what you call insanity and
genius what you call a genius is simply
someone who perceives other realities
and knows how to communicate them in a
way that your Society finds
applicable that's the only difference
the individuals you call insane simply
aren't aware that there is a mechanism
by which they can communicate what they
perceive in a way that can be applied
into your Society that's the only
difference understand yes so that would
also account for the reason that so many
supposedly insane people also have very
high iq's
yes I suspect that my son whatever
reality he's experiencing is frightening
him a great deal and I'm wondering if
he's using the drugs to um kill that
awareness to some degree yes but again
you see it is from a lack of
understanding that all the Fright
originates from within the individual
and that he himself always has the
capacity to transform it into Joy the
continuance of the assumption that the
drug is what has the power is the
reinforcement of the frightening idea
for it is a continuation of a removal of
the power from the self
understand yes is there some way I can
recommend to him that he can let go of I
have already given you that the
frightening thoughts I have already
given you that teach him that the power
to create the reality always has been is
now and always shall be within him you
can suggest that no situation is inherently
suggest that no situation is inherently
causing only the fear you have of a
situation creat any negativity in the
situation there's nothing inherently
built in to any situation that
automatically causes negativity of it
causes the negativity so he can choose
his response if he doesn't like the
thoughts he can simply ignore them
understand it is always a matter of
trust and that is not to say that you
have to learn to do something you have
never done before many times we perceive
that when we say to your Society just
trust you think oh now I have to learn
how to trust no you always trust you
have always trusted it's just a matter
of whether you trust more in negativity
or positivity the mechanism is the same
what you put into it is always what
comes out and there is nothing hiding in
the mechanism that has a mind of its own
that will change what you put in and
turn it into something else when it
comes out these things don't have a mind
of their own you have always used Trust
to create your reality but if you trust
more in negativity that's what you get
if you trust more in positive reality
that's what you get so it's not a matter
of having to learn how to use trust it's
just a matter of using the same trust
and putting positive ideas into it so
that positive reality comes out of it
it's the same analogy you use for your
computer garbage in garbage
out what you program it with is the only
thing it's capable of returning to you
same mechanism understand yes I do so you can
mechanism understand yes I do so you can
share that idea with him as well but
again it's always going to be up to that
individual to decide whether or not they
choose to prefer to believe that that
will work for them but you can point out
that it always has because they have
always gotten what they trusted they
would get understand yes I do what they really
get understand yes I do what they really
believe is the most likely reality they
can experience is always the reality you
get change the definitions you change
the reality and you can also remind the
individual because they may be
experiencing a high degree of emotional
fear remind them all emotions are
reactions to what you already believe to
be true emotions do not come out of the
blue they don't come out of the block
either they come from the belief you
believe in most strongly that generates
the reaction you call an emotion and an
emotion is also the driving mechanism
that manifests the belief you have the
strongest belief the strongest emotion
positive belief ecstasy manifestation
negative belief fear manifestation same
mechanism that's
all understand yes I do does that serve
you it does thank you very much well
thank you also for having
agreed to share life with that
individual and you can remind them they
agree to be in the life they are
living it has always been by
choice always once they own it they can
change it in any way they want to but
you cannot change what you do not
own understand yes thank you thank you sh sh
Bill
Bill k k Cynthia King are next and then
Floria Royal are next please come
everybody who put their name on there is
on the list so please come and find out
where you are and please the first the
next two or three come up are you
enjoying your raffle
it's almost perfect oh it is
perfect I'm grateful to be the next
prize hi Brar happy anniversary
anniversary to you as well um I I really
didn't have a particular question in
mind I just I will just go in further in
what the lady that was just up here was
talking about because it relates to me very well
about because it relates to me very well
all right I'm a sober alcoholic um I
went through a period in my life where I
beg your pardon what that means is that
know what it means yeah but the idea is
that if you truly are a different person
then you are not the old one no matter
what anyone tells you that's why I say
sober but that's it mhm you're not a
sober alcoholic okay that that is good
because that's what I was going to ask
you about um my belief in that system is
that I came into this life and one of
the big lessons for me to learn was um
lack of power powerlessness all right
that is a big one for almost all of you
in this lifetime and chose drugs and
alcohol as the symbol or vehicle to
express that
powerlessness Having learned that lesson
uh I am now self-empowered yes uh
particularly over the chemicals uh the
program that I'm involved in which is
known as alcoholics anonomous uh has a
spiritual Foundation yes and proclaims
that my sobriety and those who are
willing to be sober having experienced
the lack of power through the drugs and
alcohol is contingent upon uh daily
reprieve contingent upon a spiritual
condition yes in a sense yes okay um it
is a valid tool in that way however
there is a slight misconception I shall
say in the idea or the assumption that
once you are one thing you are always
that thing because if you truly do
change you really are by definition no
longer that person literally you do not
have the same past you do not have the
same future you are a completely
different reality then this would go
against one of their Foundation beliefs
that it's a disease that progresses
regardless of whether you use the
chemicals or not that uh a person who
has been clean for 20 years can go and
uh use drugs again and arrive at the
same point can but it is
mostly of the
automaticity or the idea of a habit
pattern that usually is responsible for
the individual recreating it again
nothing inherent in the idea the belief
in the habit pattern is what usually
causes an individual to recreate
it understand yes because if an
individual always feels that they are
fighting against a habit fighting
against a pattern fighting against a
tide then it's a very easy thing to feel
that you will quote unquote slip back
into it and therefore some individuals
simply do not believe they can keep up
the stamina but when you understand
there's no stamina to keep and nowhere
back to slip then you can simply stay
where you prefer to
stay I I see you related because that
term is what's used when a person does
go out again slip yes um again it is
usually only the assumption that an
individual requires stamina to stay out
of a certain idea that causes them to
believe they can slip right back into it
understand any true slippage would
always bring You by definition because
anything else you're doing is holding
yourself out of Center so if you're
going to slip anywhere it's always going
to be back to
Center you can't slip back into
something that is already outside of
Center understand I think so you can
create it you can choose it from beliefs
but it's not a true
slippage anytime you really Let Yourself
Go and slip you slip back to the center
mhm because that's the point of
because that's the point of
equilibrium so in the sense that I'm uh
creating for myself based on the belief
that I have uh I get uncomfortable if I
go more than a week or two without
sharing with these people without going
to a meeting or finding someone to in a
sense give it away to the message that I
if that's your methodology and that
works for you that's all well and good
but simply all we are suggesting is that
pay attention to the ey IDE of the
belief of why you feel
uncomfortable because it may simply be
that you are buying into the assumption
that if you don't do that you might
slip and that idea in and of
itself can be what causes you to create
all over again the thing you used to be
MH simply because you do not necessarily
believe that you have a lifetime worth
of stamina to stay out of that but if
you understand you don't need stamina to
stay out of it all you need are clear
definitions of what you prefer to be and
then there's absolutely no way you can
become anything you don't prefer to be
then you will not be a struggle it will
not be an effort you don't need stamina
it will just be the definition you have
created and that's it yeah cuz I found
myself going through a a process whereby
at first the obsession was lifted uh
then then I'm at a point where it's not
even an issue in my life the idea is
that whenever you define yourself to be
but contain idea you simply will not
have the urge for anything that is
rep for me based on of my belief system
that I need not go again to another
meeting uh or pick up the book again and
still say stay clean and sober that if
you really believe it yes let's look at
it this way there may be an assumption
that this area of stamina or area of
slippage is some sort of an interim
phase between two distinct
beliefs it isn't it's a belief unto
itself if you generate the belief that
you might SL belief what can you expect
to get from the idea except slippage mhm
if you believe in slippage you will
slip understand yes I do can you tell me
something about the uh the origination
of this program it seem because it's a
spiritual program and there are a lot of
Concepts in there that I hear again it
is simply through you through
manifestations of insight and
Imagination in many different
individuals upon your Planet but also
there was some filtering and some
assumption based upon the ideas that
needed to be presented at the time it
was originated a lot of those ideas not
necessarily apply to the society you are
now they were in that sense beneficial
for the time in which it was created and
they can be beneficial now but it
depends upon what time an individual
defines themselves to be
within for many individuals can simply
accelerate beyond that particular tool
for once again like anything it is
simply one way one tool it is valid it
obviously works for many
individuals but it is only one
way and even the definitions that it is
can be adapted to the changes that
individuals create within
themselves in that sense let me put it
this way any tool that cannot change
with the changes the tool creates in the
individual in that sense is not a flexible tool and
in that sense is not a flexible tool and
therefore must either become
obsolete or Ang is the tool create in
the individual understand yes that makes
individual understand yes that makes
sense to me well thank you very much
thank you
Bashar
sharing good evening Belle and to you
goodbye um my question has to do about
my mother her name is Christine Hammond
okay and she's always experienced some
kind of like paranoia you know whether
it was someone why because she's very
afraid why because she doesn't
um I don't know I guess CU have you
asked yes but she she won't she won't
let me in she won't she won't disclose
any information afraid of you too yeah
oh all right um and so now it's it's
gotten bad where she's um people are going to
bad where she's um people are going to
wait a
minute break into her house and rape her
and kill her and people are coming
through her ceiling
and um relax
okay you are among friends you know I
know all right
um so she's afraid that people are
coming after her and that um her house
is bugged and tapped and that this
particular individual named Alex and a
particular individual named Laura that
live in her apartment building are out
to kill her and rape her and um and that
her PO her water poison everything you
know all right all
right so may I ask you a question yeah
well thank you very
much now
do you believe you can ask her the
following question do you want to
live can you ask her that yeah all right
if you ask do you want to live now an
individual may say well of course I do
right however now let me add also the
idea that if this individual in no way
they perform will choose to believe that they
perform will choose to believe that they
create their own reality then there may
be in your classical sense some
difficulty in explaining this idea to
her right for if she is not willing to
understand that she has created this in
her reality then she may not get the
point that's right I I tried that all
right however you may simply ask do you want
however you may simply ask do you want
to live now if they say yes
then you can perhaps
ask why would you want to live if you
believe life is so
rotten and see what answer you get from
that it may allow them to finally face
the idea that it is their perspective
that is creating the idea of life to
seem rotten they may not really want to
stop living and if given the opportunity
to start understanding why life doesn't
have to rotten then they may start
searching for clues in their lives that
are positive for ideas and examples of
life that are
positive okay I um understand yes I do
um but if the individual really says
they want to
live then allow them to simply answer
well why why would you want to live if
you really believe life is this
terrible okay all right and then it can
get them to examine it might get them to
loosen up in their paranoia because that
is only negative definition right I I
have a a feeling that if I could
just she's very defensive and will scrap
the issue and etc etc so I feel if
there's something that that you can
share with me maybe I mean I I put
pieces together about her childhood and
and my grandfather and and my
grandmother and and things that happen
but I don't know if if there's something
something just real definite I wish if
there was something like just like a
particular instance that I can just
remind her reflect to her of maybe
concerning her father that I have a
suspicion of One Moment One Moment One
Moment One Moment okay take three deep
breaths
will you do a
favor yes all right you don't have to
okay every day every day
flowers and
fruit and in your terms simply other
natural food in
food in
small brilliantly designed by
you baskets to
baskets to
her every day bring her the things that
remind her of
nature of the countryside of Meadows and
Fields grass Sky trees ocean bring her
the f things of nature the cones of the
pine tree can be very conducive to allowing
tree can be very conducive to allowing
her to be in
touch with a natural
self bring every day it does not have to
be
large in your terms does not have to be
expensive but flowers of beauty things
to allow her to begin to remember that
she is a part of Nature and deserves to
feel beautiful natural feel that she
beautiful natural feel that she
fits now at first she might Rebel
thinking that the things that do fit
into nature are mocking
her but bring them bring them and soon
she will be surrounded by a completely
different environment every single
day do that for about three of your
weeks and see if there is any
difference all right
okay thanks
than
shootting hello Basher and you
goodby uh I'm Kenneth the last couple
weeks I've been up on Mount chesta
enjoying the speak up speak up speak up
KF okay uh last Saturday morning I was
awakened there was a fairly strong
Breeze and I had this sense that your
small spaceship was over the trees a
spaceship was over the trees a
projection of not in physical terms a
projection of energy and some other
things the can you explain that a little
bit simply an acceleration of the
electromagnetic field around you a
reflection of the emotional state around
you for all of your wind and weather is
a reflection of your combined emotional
States all of you so an acceleration of
the electromagnetic field a quickening
of the pace a quickening of the pulse a
clearing of
channels thank you very
much how have your dreams
been there's been some interesting ones
but I am I don't they're not coming to
mind right now will you do me a favor
but of course oh thank you you of
course Margo
Margo
Margo Margo Margo Margo Margo she's at
the front door Margo Margo Margo Margo
Margo
hello enjoying your break
cozy little chat all right we would like
to discuss with you the opportunity of
having another cozy little chat with
Kenneth in the manner you call Voice
dialogue okay to find some ideas within
himself that he may be surprised to
learn are
there all right all right thank you oh
thank you enjoy your cozy little
chat and see what comes up for you in
the way of clearing out some channels
within you not anything truly blocked but
you not anything truly blocked but
simply that there may be some surprises
for you all right thank you very much
thank you and thank
you at this timing just so Margo will
not feel alone you may all
enjoy a short break and we will resume
contact in approximately 10 to 15 of
your minutes [Applause]
how's everything going great there's
Refreshments in the other room get copy
of tonight St order now you can have it
tonight right around the
15 minute
break until you good
day oh maybe six weeks ago
about right one moment
yes everyone
remember everything everyone has to
say you in your own
way none of these things that you are
hearing from anyone
else otherwise you would not
be so it
is anything anyone
shares idea to your life to see what for
you is up to
you yes experience it had happened some time
yes experience it had happened some time
ago from one
mention right and
back having some things that for me are
I'm sure they are for
many on
people but I want to know what
this right it is your increased
sensitivity field of your planet
different are now becoming more visible
to more of you because SED to them
things that were
of light are now becoming
visible what it is to be accelerated as
an
energy the frequency of a
higher things that used to be invisible
to you on
those because you move into the range of
being able to proceive matching that
frequency in other
words because my vibrations are
changing you are all
lightning literally is there a re
because this is the transformational age
upon your remembering that you are
your remembering that you are
all you are all becoming
awakened you are all beginning to
realize that you physical reality and
the more
conscious the more conscious awareness
you have of all the energies you use to
do
that I ask you one short question all
right just kidding
does the
name to some degree the you would call
it would be representative
generally an aspect of your own future
or
higher being made manifest to you there
can guide behind it and can be in your
source of energy behind it
but are experiencing right now
basically the aspect of your own higher
cons to the same
level does that is true yes thank you
very
almost that you feel a
vibration Z in your language or an
X at the beginning of its
labeling a vibration that represents a
connection higher or future self
specifically
goodbye I have a problem Oh a problem
yes a
problem and I don't understand how I'm
to
hand so that all may share my problem
trying to relocate to this
area very much but they are
having and I don't know
what changing do they really want to yes
changing do they really want to yes
they uh there's some
physical they want to be close to me
and with with me all
right now have they allowed
now have they allowed
thems go of where they
are and we do discuss this
that they are working on it all
right when they finally let go
of the new
location their first priority in their
Linea as well okay
now also to some they can lighten up on
the physical space
represent they can begin to connected to
you that they are intermingled with you
understand the desire of the physical
Pro however they can a little bit on the
definition for so much of physical
proximity to
represent ability to be in touch with
you as are all always in
touch always
telepathic always you are always
together okay now
there are a few little
space that need to
arrange that represent your degree
degree of comfort your
expectations to some
degree belief systems or
definitional about what it is they are
going to
find once they come to terms with that
then they can allow the space to now
some of the spaces that they wish to
move into of some of these
into of some of these
definitional they have not Consolidated
yet about what they will
find understand yes very much the
understanding that if they truly unquote
I will say
guided in that
direction your physiological
proximity trust that they will will
fit understand yes they will by defition
you cannot wind
up and let
go if it truly
repres the most in of
in of
what together
best so allow them to be clear about why
they are where they are
where they want to move when they are
clear about their
definition clear about their deserve
ability clear about their action then it
will of
course the good parts to come the
good once again the
imagin for that purpose if you can
in a picture a scenario
a you say of what you
desire cumstances that exist in your
life and through the imagination see how
the have a VI in the imagination would
handle the
circumstance if it really is
representative of the you will handle
the circumstance differently than your
all you have to do is copy the way it's
hand and you will get the same result
that's what your
imagination create the blueprint that
you can follow see the U in your
imagination getting like the U in your
getting like the U in your
imagination understand
yes to scan the
scenario themselves fitting
in they want to be and allow
aptitudes that and when you have an
attitude that you become the vibration that
that you become the vibration that
location when you know you belong that
vibration you
cannot anywhere else you will
automatically to slide you location you
are the
vibration simply allow them to become
the vibration of in and they will
automatic you cannot stay in a
plate I
understand is to let them vibration home
vibration home
now with
you spark their
inspiration all right thank you very
much Shing and to you
good weeks ago you talked about
creating a body that had approximately
7 a second could you tell me a I could
create that as a you can't create it as
a physiological thing created in your
imagination and it
can what about
physically simply generate a magnetic
field that
pulses second how how can I do that
research your technology okay you have
off strong magnetic
field how would it be best to
play know right now I know that you said
allowing an individual for
a to lie in a state of rep magnetic
field no
longer 10 of your
minutes Aid in syst them in
some they cannot tolerate the field
longer than 3
minutes and that will be sufficient it
will be
highing and
aligning Now understand something
is
accelerated then have to face
what some people first to appear to be a
negative acceleration align themselves
and become super conductive there's no
everything Rises to the surface
absolutely all right how
what well understand that if it is there
then it is an aspect of themselves that
they won't dive into it and let you
don't run
away you can handle it
otherwise it is what you want always
remember you have your own always
regulating system if you want to shut it
down you can and you don't have to be
rate yourself for having done
so oh all
right little too
fast slow down if
someone minutes what would the
repercussions be
now I do not want to
generate attitude or belief about what
Kur but simply recognize again that if
you realize that if it allows an align
allow individual to face things they may
at first find unpleasant well
just generally speaking generally you
will have enough self-regulatory me so
that long before you ever get to a point
where it will really do you any damage
you will probably r from the
field understand yeah I do remove
do remove
yourself all you to feel a little edgy M
can be your signal that you've had
enough all right yeah yeah but it in
that way crystallizing and super conductive
way crystallizing and super conductive
causing
does that assist
you that well thank you very much
by anytime you wish to find the
basic of
any in terms of cycles per
second is divide would call the
circumference along the Equator into of
light and you will
get represent the cycles of second of
the understand when I do my
understand when I do my
research keep it simple thank
you it is in your
terminal appro appro
9 8
to9 because we are on the verge of non-material
non-material
how and to you Mr
di thank
you
day all right for you good evening uh
because on my planet ni
planet ni
okay yes I'm not in your plan
somewhere on your planet it is good
dayere on my planet it is good evening
as okay that's see
that's that we straighten that out
yeah your energy is
coming yeah thank
yeah thank
youning question oh
joined the
association rendition of it
yes now you're
getting but you see we are aware of the
idea of of Star Trek and call your
Association your Federation your group
that you are labeling the Klingons have
Jo within the context of that program
yes you will see so upon the Advent of
the uh of the
uh
great that I really want to
ask 30th you watching
channel is
Rel yes and how you
perceive event of
abortion your positivity and before I
know
that the negativity would be that
point of how much empowerment you take
of how much empowerment you take
away probably in any is
probably function because
it
basically a fetus since the we'll assume
that that
baby yet uh it's and it may be more
positive if if it's more
appropriate survival or or
growth it will not the fundamentals of
the circumstance depend upon the reasons for
circumstance depend upon the reasons for
the as to whether it is more of an IDE
or negative okay not the are neutral so
if is excited by the idea of a and it
doesn't seem to have any
other that she would judge
would postive generally speak the idea that
postive generally speak the idea that
you
call does not really need to planet and
to some
degree a little bit of being out of
yourselves and so in that
sense or less
considered energy are very aware and in
energy are very aware and in
communication with
all within yourself
so to speak they need to create the
idea of abortion because you will simply
know that you will not be pregnant when
you do not need to be and therefore will
not necessarily have to do one step
removed after the fact ini abortion I
guess we're still working say that we
will get pregnant when we quote
unquote not me I mean
only only a portion of obviously perhaps
only yeah but yes idea okay go I wanted
to share you as to report the results of
my what you suggested I didn't do
it do it oh all right what I was screw
the whole thing I'm not worried about
it finally learned my lesson that
and there is to be a I'll say
barrier to getting to the heart of the
matter right in the middle or at the
process that I don't want
to interrupt the process I
just after it's done I look back and say
oh
yes allowing yourself to recognize your
liability oh all right
you're welcome
welcome
shoting hello Bashar my name is all
right and I'm excited all right I am
always excited to
speak I am the responsibility that I
create all right for about 10
years and um with are you having a good
time there's been good times
all right feel that it's my
right feel that it's my
responsibility or it's mine whatever
that's a bad word but not a bad it is a
judgmental one it is Jud respons have to
mean blame respons be
recognition integrity and to choose and
freedom to
create my next concern oh all right with
um
imately and
job the lack thereof it may seem oh no
no no no
no into a psychic
account to solve all my problems and I
didn't know I had no it didn't help me
the the
psych that
um in a previous
life all of you have been at one time
[Applause] oh who are you
oh who are you
now feel about it and I don't somehow
feel pun strin you're
not say but yes it
is that I can't get over tell me that I
was not of people in my
spirit all right
Deni but was not senstive
food and
clothing so now you are being by
yourself to look from the other side
however the opportunity in no way for
means experience a negative
manifestation that point of view it's to
be an opport and understand the
mechanism of that point of
view how do I make it work all right all
right you allow it to work because let
it
so first of all again it may with definition
abundance ability to do what you need to
do you need to do
it I didn't say anything in there about
money money is one of the ways on your a
very valid way to express no denying
that right now you have money however it
isn't as many of you have been taught
way to express
abundance you think that if you don't
have money you don't that's not
so paradoxically one of the EAS to begin
to
allow into your life all other forms of
abundance into your life as well and not
definition to money
abundance the ability what you need to
do when do it
so given
moment acting with Integrity ones you
the most
you flow into your life that bring the
ability to do represents most who you
are now ability that abundance that flow
may not be what you have been taught
expect that it must
be but it doesn't always have to be the
way you have been taught to expect
ites path of least
resistance if
someone would to be able to come up to
you simply give you something needed or
exchange with you something that you
needed would
you that you had to have the money
accept the gift problem accepting
problem accepting
gifts but I've worked on
that take the money May I
remind all right but may I remind you
one thing gifts you can give to allow others
thing gifts you can give to allow others
to
give on that why are you working so hard
don't you believe you deserve
it all right do you
now well then let you so that you can
give to
them do the thing that excites at any
given moment that you are capable of
your integrity and you flow of
individuals to interact with you will be
able to serve by being who you are and
that will be able to serve you allowing
them to be who they are
you don't allow them to be who they are
who you
are so that generates momentum of
Interac on
all if something needs to be in your
represented by the vibration you that
requires that it come in the form of it
will be there or an opportun it will be
there but if other let them be just as
represent abundance as the money because
they are following this advice
and now make a difference in the
other understanding s yes the life I am
living at this time does it all work at
one time and whatever you define
yourself to be in the changes your
past because there is
only easy now one you see it is easy my
next one question about I had with
people that
went I have in my
hand experience of an Angel and I must
admit that I was the last go up there
and see an angel all right else did I
didn't expect to but I about that and
not everyone went there it may sound
simple but go to this place didn't which
I think is is true some people from the
local papis to this particular
place it matter of frequency if you on
frequency as something you will see it
if you're not you won't to someone who
does show this picture if anyone wants
to see it there a connection between
this saw a a figure had a feeling
of connection is there a connection me
and the people on the the group
particular well first of all the most
connection is that you're all on the
same doing similar
ideas chose to go to a specific area for
perhaps your own reasons energy
idea to express a certain frequency of
yourself in a similar fashion enough to
allow enough of you with another level
of conscious are calling the Angelic
level reflect back to
some of you the fact that you are
getting in touch with
more what you were looking at is a
mirror all the angels in the sky just
there is only
one I know I'm not know that's you guys
are name there is anation to that
vibration with in which you
found if you
you can
simply as
Shasta it is representative of a multi
Consciousness understand that you can
see multiple manifestations and you can
see manifestations but it's all one as
far as the Angelic level conc it
considers itself only your world breaks
it it is was a reflection of the
combination all of your higher conscious
is this Angel
available it is
you it's a reflection combination of
your colle Consciousness it isti but it
is also a of the combination of your
Consciousness so of course you all the
time because it is you and you are it
I'll think it over thank you that is
what I meant by one it is you
you
shoting good day to you this night of
create time to
exist thank
you uh I realiz anything I need to hear
from you anymore thank you and I realiz
having an exciting life getting more and
more exciting think you can't stand
exciting think you can't stand
it do you think stand it to be 10 times
more exciting yes
aund yes a thousand
times then we will for allowing that
level of
allow to
be we thank you for your remind you that
individual who is willing to experience
their ecstasy makes it that much easier
for everyone be able to do so because
youate that frequency into your reality
then there is an opportunity other
individual to discover that aspect
within the reflection of
the that you are everyone makes a
difference single one of you all have
infinite amount of
impact you all do all make it
different each one of
each one of
you
because one of you
is all that
is
manifesting all the unique that it
can so of course if you change you
change everything you are you are
your
of we have
said we will not
we will not
know when will
decide to act
will be the
first extend each and every one of you
individually and
collectively our uncondition
excitement our joy our ecstasy our love
our spontane
spontane
and thank you for sharing the dream that
together we are a unconditionally loving
good day and good [Applause]