you very much. Okay.
Do you have a list of people from last
uh you want me to announce this first?
Sure. Go ahead.
All right. I'll say how are you all this
evening of your time as you create time
to exist.
Allow us to begin this interaction this
evening of your
time with a discussion and if you wish
the labeling of this discussion
consensus reality. The idea that you each and
reality. The idea that you each and
every one of you have recognized for
many thousands of years to be the quote
unquote world, the reality, the universe
you have assumed you live in. You have
created yourselves to live in that which
you recognize to be the
commonality for everyone is what we are
referring to as the consensus reality.
The reality you all agree to have common
ideas about the commonality you all
agree to have. In other words, to put it
very simply, the idea that the majority
of you, the consensus of you have agreed
at this time, as we perceive it, that
you are quote unquote sitting on chairs
in a room somewhere in a particular
local upon your planet. That is
representative of one of the ideas of a
consensus reality. It doesn't have to be
perceived that way by any of you. You
can perceive yourself in any way, shape,
or form you wish because what you call
physical reality, as we have discussed
many times, literally has no empirical
existence aside from the definitions you
have been taught to give it. In fact,
there is no it to give definitions to.
Your definitions in and of themselves
are the physical reality you experience
seemingly externally from him. That is
your definition, one of your definitions
of physical reality, that you can
experience it seemingly separate from
you. That's one of the definitions that
creates the notion you call physical
reality. And so each and every one of
you creates that reality in a similar
fashion using similar mechanisms of
belief and emotion and thought and
consciousness in terms of how you apply
it. Your definitions will vary to some
degree because each and every one of you
is a unique individual. But nonetheless,
you also in order to let us say play the
game of the particular physical reality
that you are playing, you must all
generally agree on some similarities in
order to have any similarity of
experience or commonality of experience
at all.
This consensus reality forms at least to
some degree an automatic background that
allows you to not have to think about it
all the time. You simply have put it on
automatic in general. However, now in
your transformational age, now that you
are as a society delving into the very
notions of consciousness itself, you are
now finding, I shall say, loopholes in
that consensus reality. Now that you are
becoming aware of the fact that you
actually create your own reality, now
you have given yourself the tools to
find those so-called loopholes or soft
spots in your collective definition that
are somewhat alterable. And finding one
means you can find more, means you can
create more. Not that it necessarily in
and of itself is an absolute goal that
you must absolutely unbalance and
eradicate the idea of the general
consensus reality that you have as
physical beings. But that you can now
find that your individual expression of
the consensus reality, your individual
expression of physical reality has a lot
more, as you say, leeway than you used
to think. You are now capable of
bridging space and time, of manipulating
space and time and physical objects in a
far freerier way than you used to think
was possible because you are now
recognizing that they are extensions of
you. Physical things are simply your
perceptive definitions of the idea of
yourself as a physical being. And so you
now find you can play around with the
idea a little bit more than you used to
be able to or used to think you were
able to. Consensus reality will remain
somewhat similar for all of you even
though it will change in its own way. As
you each in your own unique way as
individuals add your new perspectives,
add your new points of view to the
overall consensus reality. You allow the
entire idea to shift in ways that then
change the ability of every individual
within that reality to make even
broader, more sweeping changes
individually. You all follow along so
far? Each and every one of you has
impact. Each and every one of you makes
a difference to the consensus reality.
Whatever perspective you choose to
prefer is the perspective more
representative of who you now know
yourself to be. That adds a vibration.
It adds a frequency. It has impact on
the capability of the total whole to
know there are that more opportunities
in reality, that many more ways you
could experience the idea of the
physical reality that you have chosen to
exist as. You are all experimenters. You
are all inventors. Each and every unique
point of view that you believe to be
truly you that you have the conviction
to put out there in your physical life
acts as an example a reflective mirror
for everyone else so that they can see
oh look one more opportunity one more
new way to express the idea of creation
through ourselves. one more perspective
that is added to the overall amount of
perspectives that form the consensus
reality that we could use, we can adapt,
we can employ within our reality and add
to the overall whole a new way, a
broader way, an expansive way to see
ourselves. Each and every one of you
plays your part. You all fit, you all
belong. You cannot be, you cannot exist
where you do not fit, where you do not
belong. So remember, in the overall
sense, no matter what your perspective
is, no one can really be quote unquote
ahead of or behind their time. If you
exist now in the way you exist now, it
is an absolute reflection of what the
overall consensus reality needs to
express the totality of itself at any
given moment. It is in that sense always
a balance sheet and no matter what any
individual is doing, you are a part of
that whole balance sheet. You are a part
of the now. You are a part of the
vitality of the life that is expressed
as your collective civilization at this
time. Even though many of you may in the
past have had visions of things that did
not manifest themselves, doesn't mean it
wasn't appropriate to begin to introduce
those ideas in your society to lay the
foundations for other individuals that
would in your terms come later or maybe
even yourselves, reincarnating and
taking up where you left off in another
life, laying a foundation for yourself
in the future, which many of you have
done. The idea also is to begin to
realize that since you are a collective
consciousness and because as individuals
you have created the idea that you have
an outer aware consciousness, a
subconsciousness and an unconsciousness,
you have created those notions in your
collective consciousness as well. There
is a collective outer consciousness, a
collective subconsciousness, a
collective unconsciousness as well. And
many of you have had the experience of
dealing with many of these levels. They
are called your archetypal substreams.
In that sense, you have found many gates
and doorways, many visions, many
experiences that are not usually
explained by your outer aware conscious
state, but can be explained as
interactions you are having,
intersections you are having with the
collective mass unconsciousness. For if
you have created within your
individuality an unconsciousness that
can hide things from yourself, then in
the collective unconsciousness, there
can be realms and projections and faces
and facets of consciousness that you can
run into that many of you have called
mythological in nature that are no less
real. It is simply that you have not
allowed them to blend in the consensus
outer conscious reality. But they do
belong and do fit in the consensus
unconscious and subconscious reality.
Now that you are exploring the idea that
the notion of subconscious and
unconscious are really only your
definitions and there really doesn't
empirically exist a barrier in your
consciousness that you are one
homogeneous consciousness. Many of the
things you have ascribed in the past to
mythology and in that sense what you
call imagination are now beginning to
bleed through to blend into your outer
physical awareness. So many of you are
having conscious visions conscious
daydreams seeing time and space become
very malleable seeing visions of
different kinds of beings and levels of
consciousness that can project
themselves to you even as you did in
times past. The idea of many of the
encounters that beings say they had with
different levels of consciousness that
you would call some of your mythologies,
what you call your goblins and your
fairies and all these ideas are simply
interactions with different levels of
the mass consciousness expressing itself
in whatever way represents symbolically
the best way that any particular
individual can relate to the idea of
that portion of the collective whole.
Are you all following along?
You don't have to retain all of this
analytically. We are progressing at a
certain pace in transferring this
information to you because the pace we
are progressing at in delivering this
information is also reaching you on many
different levels that you have created
yourself to exist
as. One other idea that we would enjoy
sharing with you is to allow yourselves
because of what we have talked about
what we have now mentioned about all the
different levels that your reality
exists within is to learn to really
appreciate the fullness of the
consciousness that your reality is and
not necessarily ascribe or assign
interactions with many different types
of consciousness to something that
really must come from beyond your
reality. Even though there are, as we
are the idea of extraterrestrial
consciousnesses, we are still to some
degree represented by the energy you
have to work with on your planet. We can
only use the energy you are made out of
to represent ourselves. You can only see
your versions of us made out of your
energy to be able to perceive us anyway.
So we simply remind you that no matter
what you perceive, you are always
perceiving it out of modeled out of your
energy. The energy that is represented
by the earth that you are. There are
richness, vast richnesses of experience,
gateways and doorways into different
dimensions of yourself, of your
collective consciousness right on your
own planet. You do not have to go
seeking out in the stars to encounter
other levels of consciousness in that
way. You can always go within. You have
many, many, many different realms of
experiences going on all within your own
reality. Your own Earth is a very rich
and multi-layered experience. You have in
multi-layered experience. You have in
the dolphins and the whales, aliens on
your very own planet. You do not have to
find them out among the stars. The idea
is that you have many gates, many
doorways to go through. Many different
types of levels of interaction can be
had on your very own planet. You are a
rich and exciting world. Learn to
appreciate in that way all the variety,
all the diversity, all the different
ways you have chosen to experience
yourself. And remember, even many of the
things you think are encounters from
other civilizations are actually
encounters with different aspects of
your own civilization. you are not
allowing yourselves to be consciously
aware of yet. You have many different
interdimensional gates between which
what you call the past of your society
and the future of your society can
interact with your present. Many of what
you call the UFOs that you see in your
skies do not come from other planets.
They come from your planet. different
dimensions of experience in your past,
in your future, different alternate
realities in your present that are
absolutely attached to the world you
are. You are a very rich and
multi-layered experience in and of
yourselves. So, first be aware of the
richness of all the layers you have
created. Feel free to
interact, to blend
together, to integrate all the different
doorways, all the different levels and
aspects of information your
consciousness is. That's what will put
you squarely in touch with all the
consciousness that we are. When you are
functioning more as truly one world as a
consensus reality that while proceeding
in one particular momentum direction
still appreciates and values and
validates and strengthens all the
individual expressions within itself for
that is a complete being. If a being
recognizes itself to be or has created
itself to be made of many parts, then
the equalization and the validation and
the strengthening of all of the
individual parts is what makes you a
unified whole. To unite and unify does
not mean you lose your individuality. It
means you strengthen it. Because only as
equally strong components do you have a
completely strong unified whole.
You all follow along.
We express at this timing to each and
every one of you our absolute delight at
your willingness to function as unique
and individual ambassadors of your
society. And we express absolute delight
in allowing us and me to function as
ambassadors of our respective societies
within the association of worlds.
In return for the gift of your
willingness to share at this time and in
accepting your invitation to share, I
ask you now how may I serve you? Good
day Vashar. Good day to you. First I
want to say thank you last week for your
opening talk. It was connected me very
directly with the piece that I was going
to be performing the following Saturday.
It was like as if it described it to a
tea. So that just made me feel Thank you
for allowing us to reflect your ability
to connect into other aspects of
yourself. Proceed. Okay. My question has
to do with two aspects of two dreams.
The first dream had to do with um I was
feeling myself like pulling out of my
body in a dream state. And it felt the
same as when I leave my body when I'm in
a nondream state. And um as I was
leaving, I felt my one-year-old baby
that sleeps in the bed with us um say
like choose consciously choose to come
with me. Um so it wasn't as if I was
dreaming about her as it really felt she
was coming with. So she came with me and
we came to a place where where a place
like right before you choose to to you
choose what images you're going to make
in a dream. Nice. And so very good, very
exciting. Okay. So it progressed and progressed
Okay. So it progressed and progressed
and we appeared at this place and I saw
the channel um Darald and his fiance and
I was not clear why they were there and
we just like acknowledged each other in
the same dream space and went on. And
now the part I want to ask about was
when I came back into my my body, I felt
like a a like a a condensing back into.
So I really got that it was about
expanding, not very good, buddy. Good,
buddy. Good. And then when I was in my
body, I felt like the warm body of my
husband and I was like laying next to
him and then I like felt something going
in between us and jumping over us. And
when I looked up, I'm not sure if I was
awake or not, but it was like this
dolphin going back and forth and between
us. And then and then I like kind of
just stayed there watching. And then it
it was like my baby. Then it was my
baby's shape. And she just looked
straight at my face and gave me this big
grin and then just started laughing and
laughing and laughing and stayed up the
rest of the night. And this happened to
be about 2:30 to 3:30. Stayed up until
about like 4:30 or so. and kept laughing
and jumping all around and like just
real excited. What is unclear about all
this?
Well, I knew you talked about um the the
dolphins youth changing places with the
human youth and so I guess I was
wondering if if that was going on. Look,
in a sense, but also dolphin
consciousness interacts with all of you
on your dream realities where you are
generally, at least for now, more
willing to allow interaction between
different consciousnesses to take place.
So, you were simply being assisted in
many different ways as a guide would
assist you. Being shown the idea on many
different levels of the fact that you
are now learning, really learning what
it really means to play, what it really
means to be the creator of your reality.
And how ecstatic that is. Now the
idea not as a goal in itself, not as
something you have to try to do. We are
not attempting to focus you in an idea
of limitation. But now the idea is to
arrive at the same perspective in your
physical reality that you know you now
have arrived at in your dream reality.
That place just before you choose the
images that represent your physical
life. So you can see yourself in action
as you choose and create the symbols you
attract in your physical life.
Understand? Yes. That is the idea the
perspective of play that you are being
shown in that sense. And you are also
being shown that on that level your
child is not a child and in a sense you
even though you may be an adult can
still act in a childlike manner.
Understand? You are blending your energy
with all, recognizing the agreements and
the reflections of all that you have
created a family with. It is simply that
your family contains a few more members
than you may physically think it does.
And many of you have as family members
dolphins as well.
Yeah. Because many of you have shared
the idea in different incarnations of
dolphin body, human body. Remember, you
are the same type of soul. The outer
appearance doesn't determine in that
sense what you are. You are two alien
species on your planet. You are
interchangeable and many times in what
you call your past have been
incarnationally interchangeable and are
becoming so again. Whether it has to be
in an incarnation of one life to another
or whether you could allow yourselves to
be interchangeable as energy as
consciousness within any particular life
doesn't matter. But you are now blending
into the families that you are that in a
sense you once were. It is simply that
some of the members of your family swim
in the sea.
Understand? Yeah. So that brings me to
the second aspect of this other dream
where where okay all this other stuff
happened but suddenly like everything
else stopped in the dream and I and I
was laying on this operating table and
there was like five surgeons, men and
women around me and they made a hole in
the bottom of my spine in the at the
base there about the size of a between a
quarter and a half a dollar and and they
were and it kind of hurt and I was going
and then they were sticking tuna fish in
the cocoa and squeezing out the water
and the oil and kept sticking tuna in.
And I thought, I wonder why they're
doing that. And then when I turned
around to look at one time I looked, I
saw the size of the hole. And then later
on when they had finished, I felt okay.
And I looked at the hole. It was just a
small incision vertical.
And I wondered what that some of this to
some degree is ancient memories of
Atlantean connections. Oh god, I knew
that. Why did you
[Music] ask? Some of it to some degree is
ask? Some of it to some degree is
interaction with what you would call
extraterrestrial consciousness. And
together it is a blending to create let
us say to synthesize in a symbolic
terminology the bringing together of
your awareness of some of those dolphin
connections and some of the Atlantean
connections and some of the
extraterrestrial connections in blending
it all together all the different levels
symbolically into simply now a balancing
a blending a centering of all the things
you are attached to connected to all the
things that give you sustenance in that
sense. Understand?
It is a synthesizing of many different
points of view. You have been into one
idea, one new being, one new persona.
Cuz like a couple nights later, I asked
in my dream before I went to sleep, what
does the tuna fish in the hole mean? And
and again, what came to me was I was in
front of a body of water and I stuck out
a fishing pole and I thought, I hate the
fish. I don't want to wait for hours.
And then I just said I waved my hand. I
said, "Oh yeah, I can call them." And
they came. A fish immediately just came
up and took a bite and I I reeled it in.
Guys, so the idea is simply your ability
to draw in all the information you need
to rely upon that as delivering
information. The dolphins to some degree
now and then on a level that for now we
will not technically explain can
actually use the idea of what you call
your tuna fish to act as gobetween
messengers chemically speaking between
themselves in certain ways and it is one
of the reasons they are around aside
from the idea of sustenance what you
call many of your school of tuna in your
ocean. It is because they have a
particular type of relationship much to
some degree similar to what you would
have with what you call a dog or a cat.
Oh, understand? Yeah. So, just as your
animals, your dogs, your cats serve to
reflect to you certain ideas in your
human form level of reality, your tuna
fish serves the same function to some
degree for the dolphins, although it is
slightly different.
So you are simply recognizing now that
because you are associating more with
the dolphin energy that you have a wider
range of pets
a wider range of reflective guides in
what you call the animal kingdom that
serve to reflect different ideas of
information you can receive about
yourself on many different levels
understand. Yeah, I guess so. There's
nothing real specific that these things
were telling me besides that. I mean,
there was no there may be some
specifically intertwined messages, but
they will all come out if you simply act
like the overall blended being. You now
are beginning to recognize that you are.
We simply lay the foundation down for
you that allows you to recognize the
momentum of the particular direction in
which you can move and bring all the
specifics bubbling to the surface in
your own good timing. We are not here to
delineate all the specifics. All the
wiring that you are creating yourself to
be just the general
conductivity move in that direction and
all of the reasons for all the specific
wiring will make themselves
plain. Understand? Yeah. Thank you very
much. Thanks. Shing. [Applause]
[Applause]
Hi. And to you good day. Uh I have a
question on uh reincarnation. All right.
And a lot of it has to do with your um
policy of like looking for what excites
you. All right. Our policy. Yes. Yes.
That's right. And I was wondering about
if the whole policy behind reincarnation
is is progressing and expanding and
doing things that maybe you did not have
a chance to do or for some reason didn't
complete in a previous existence. It can
be used that way. Yes. Then uh wouldn't
it follow somewhat that we are put here
for challenges to be put in positions to
expand ourselves in a sense but you are
not put here you put yourselves okay
that's okay if we put ourselves in so
then that uh policy of doing whatever
excites you seems to be somewhat
counterproductive. Oh no no no no no no
no no no you will still discover you
will still grow and the idea in a sense
of the overall challenge of your reality
is in coming through the idea of
limitation and learning how to transform
limitation into unlimited expression
even as strong a limitation as you have
created upon your planet that's the
overall challenge well shouldn't we be
looking for limitations and challenges
in order to progress
faster. The things that you can use in
that way that are representative of
limitations that you can blend within
you are representative of your growth of
your expansion. Transforming a
limitation into something that is no
longer a limitation is the whole idea of
growth and expansion. The idea is simply
now that you have been using your
limitations for many thousands of years.
You are running out of them.
You are at the end of the cycle of that
particular type of challenge. You are
now going on to something that can be
looked at as a challenge if you wish it
to be. And perhaps it is this for many
of you. Since a lot of you think that
peace will be very boring, your
challenge is to understand that it can
be very exciting and to create it to be
so. Well, I was thinking more in terms
of like if you're in a relationship with
someone and if the relationship
is not going well, then do you uh look
upon it as a way
to do something that you haven't been
able to do in a previous existence? You
can look at it that way. Yes. It doesn't
have to be looked at that way and it
isn't always connected to another
existence. But if you wish to look at it
that way, you can. Okay. Well, then how
do you know if if you're looking at it
as a way of expanding something that
happened in a previous existence or
you're looking at it as something that
should uh be an impediment to your future?
uh be an impediment to your future?
There is no thing that should be an
impediment to your future.
The idea of whether it is a stem from a
previous existence or
not has really nothing to do with the
idea that if you see a limitation in
your life that you don't prefer that the
idea is if you want to to change it into
something that is not a limitation. No
matter where it originated from no
matter what the momentum is connected
to. The whole idea is that if you prefer
it not to be a limitation then learn how
to transform it. I see. Well, what is
the value then of knowing say a past
life? Then it can have some value to
certain individuals. But one of the
reasons we are always relatively
hesitant to delve into the idea of past
lives is because from our perspective,
you really don't need to know anything
about a past life to fully live the life
you are living now. Because you have all
the things you need in any given life to
live that life to the fullest.
Sometimes maybe because of the way you
have set yourself up, it might serve
your memory, your reflections, your
guidance to be aware of an idea that you
call a past life notion. But you don't
have to be because remember you are
speaking linearly and all these lives
are going on simultaneously anyway. They
are not truly in the past. They are
simply different ways you have of
perceiving the being that you are. They
are in a sense cross references going on
right now. Again, much in the same way
that all the programs on your radio
device all exist coexist with each other
simultaneously. And you can switch your
dial back and forth perhaps gleaning a
bit of this program, a bit of this
program, a bit of this program, and put
it all together in whatever way you want
to. But for many of the things you wish
to do in this particular life, all the
information you really need is on the
setting your dial is tuned to now. Any
bleedth through that needs to be there
from any other life is automatically
there. Not necessarily in ways that
allow you to think it comes from another
life, but in ways that is translated in
terms you can use in the present. You
may not recognize it as bleed through.
You don't have to recognize it as
bleedthrough. That's why you don't
necessarily have to be aware of the
information as specifically coming from
another life. The information from any
other life you need to live this life is
already with you. But maybe in terms
that make sense in the present life, not
necessarily making sense from the idea
of a past or future life. There may be
many things you are aware of that you're
aware of because of other lives, but it
seems that you are aware of the
information now because it comes in the
terminology that serves you now. Well,
um I was thinking in terms of uh if you
established some kind of a pattern in
this life. Yes. Um that if you went and
you looked at what happened in your past
life, it might explain what the pattern
is in this life. Yes. But remember that
when you establish a pattern in this
life, you are creating the past life.
You will discover to reinforce the idea
of the pattern you established in the
present. And then there there'd be no
need to I understand that. But uh then
there'd be no need. You really can just
look for what excites you the most. You
don't need to. Absolutely.
It's all there is to it. You really can.
Okay. Thank you. Thanks.
Shing. Good evening, Bashar. And to you, good
Good evening, Bashar. And to you, good
day. Thank you. Well, I didn't know I
was going to get picked. I just put my
name in the box and I got picked. So,
well, you must have had an ID. I have.
You know, I've been meaning to ask you.
Uh you were about a few months ago you
were talking about the cacina that you
were exploring the cachacina idea and I
wondered if there is any kind of a
correlation but somehow we can use their
energy or something to help us so we
don't have another big
earthquake. I don't know if there's some
kind of a correlation there between them
but I feel like you know that there to
some degree in a sense there is. Is
there Well, could you tell me what it
is? Go and discuss with your American
Indian culture some of the ideas of what
their energy can be used for. Okay?
Relate to the earth. Talk to the earth.
Become aware of the consciousness of the
earth. And then you will understand why
the earth is doing what it is doing and
when it will do it.
Really? Yes. And you can understand how much of
Yes. And you can understand how much of
that energy can be redirected in other
ways. That's sounds good. It is up to
you. Okay. Remember that no matter what
happens, whatever vibration you are will
determine what of what happens you
experience. Understand? Your fear will attract you
Understand? Your fear will attract you
to a negative circumstance because your
fear says I believe the most likely
reality that can happen to me is a
negative one. If you simply understand
you have no need for that particular
type of experience or that if you do go
through it, you will use it in a
positive way, then you will always be
able to get out of it something that you
will be able to use in a positive way
and you will go through it in a positive
way and it won't affect you negatively.
Great. Well, that makes me feel a heck
of a lot better. It is not really per se
for that purpose that I have said this.
The idea simply is
to allow you, as you say, to get a
handle on what you choose, on what you
decide is the reality vibration you are
because you cannot
experience any physical event that is
not the frequency you are on. Period.
Okay. Does that serve you? Yes, it does.
Well, thank you very much. The people on
your planet that you call the hopey can
tell you much about kacina energy. Okay.
Thank you Bashar. Well, thank you very
much. Pleasant dreams.
Sharing. Good evening, Bashar. And will you good
Good evening, Bashar. And will you good
day? Um, I wanted to ask you a question
that um I asked my parents but um I
didn't get a very good answer about.
Well, you obviously got an appropriate
one. However, yeah. That's true. Um, and
it was about sex. All right. And, um, I
wanted to ask you, aside from
procreation, um, what was the what is the purpose of,
um, what was the what is the purpose of,
um, sex on this planet and the alignment
of energy points within you? Accessing
consciousness, different levels of
consciousness, including the physical
level in a different way, in one of the
ways it can be done. It is one of the
ways you can align all levels of your
energy of your consciousness. Okay. So
why is there so much um guilt and um so
much disease and so much upset around
the sexual issue? Why is it a mass?
That's what I would like to know.
Well, it is mostly because of some of
the fears that your society generated.
Certain ideas, certain perspectives of
limitation and being out of control and
fearing to discover portions of
yourself, fearing to love yourself,
believing you don't deserve the love.
All these ideas and many more issues all
have intertwined to create all the
things that your society has been going
through recently and for many thousands
of years with regard to respecting its
own intimacy.
Understand? Yes, many different ideas
that are simply a product of the
definitions of limitation you have
placed upon yourself. The denial of
different portions of yourself as you
have created these portions to
exist. The ability to forget that you
can function as a whole being. And then
when individuals stopped functioning as whole
individuals stopped functioning as whole
beings, the
idea of guilt of
jealousy created the notions you call
laws and moral perspectives that would
then forbid anyone else from feeling
that way because some individuals feared
it so much they couldn't even stand to
see anyone else getting in touch with
it. It became bad, wrong, evil.
Understand? Yeah, that's my parents. So
that sounds very
familiar. All
right. But generally speaking, it is
simply aside from the idea of what you
call procreation, one of the ways beings
can express the connection to all the
different levels, all the different
polarities of the energy that they are,
including the physical level. Because
the physical level cannot be denied. It
is obviously just as valid as any other
level or it wouldn't
exist. But it can be used with integrity
and without
it. Anything can be used with integrity
and without it. Just being a thing, just
the fact that something exists in and of
itself doesn't mean that it is
inherently positive or inherently
negative. The existence of the thing
doesn't determine that one way or
another. How you use it, how you view it
does. So individuals in that
sense that fear it on many levels then
are basically reflecting a belief within
themsel that they in certain
circumstances would reflect it
negatively without integrity. They are
not necessarily seeing the full
integrity of their own being.
Understand? Yes. Does that answer your
question sufficiently? Uh yeah, I just
had one tiny more question. Uh all
right. Uh it was about um sex in the
future. I mean is you're our future
selves in a sense? I mean is the sexual
act I mean the exchange of sexual
energy. Is there a different way of
doing it where you're from? Uh is there
in our
society it is similar to your own
although in your terms it has evolved
into more of an energy act. There is
still the idea to some degree of what
you would call physiological proximity.
But the idea now is that it is more of
an energy act. It is more an exchange
directly and an activation of the
cellular structures within the body.
That is due to the actual flash exchange
of energy more than what you would
typify as a physiological act of
procreation. It becomes less and less
physical. And in a sense on many ways
when you blend the physical and the
non-physical together, it becomes less
of a
distinction. It becomes both the same
thing. All one act, all one idea of
blending. So in a
So in a
sense, not meaning this to sound strange
to your
ears, but in a sense because of what our
society is, any such exchange in our
society between any individuals on some
level is actually felt by the whole
society and that adds to our overall
ecstasy and sense of joy.
Understand? Yeah, that sounds good.
Yeah. Thank you. Well, thank you. Thank
you. All
right. Thanks a lot. Sharing.
Good day, Bashar. And to you, good day.
I've just learned about um some things
that have been excavated in South
America, there are life-sized figure of
a man, a woman, and a little boy that
are made out of pure quartz crystal. And
I've also just learned that in the
Wyoming, Montana area of our country,
they're uncovering um a crystal skull
that is 9 ft in diameter and weighs
1,000 lbs.
Are beginning now to discover many of
the ideas that were understood by
civilizations on your planet, by all of
you in those civilizations on your
planet in your past. You are now
regaining and remembering the idea of
who many of you have been and many of
the things you have all created. Many of
the things you knew then are what you
are rediscovering now. Many of the
aspects that represented the blending
and the balancing and the vitality and
the conviction of the society you were
then in touch with the natural elements
themselves. Now that you are rediscovering these
Now that you are rediscovering these
things archaeologically speaking, you
are now able to understand the
principles upon which they were created
and apply those principles in what you
call your contemporary society.
Can you uh give me some idea of what
your origin of these are? Are they from
our planet or they Yes, they are from
Atlantean or Lammorian? Some of them.
Yes. Both. Yes. The idea in general is
that the knowledge was shared by many of
those civilizations and manifested by
many specific cultures around your
world, especially what you call your
American Indian cultures. The idea
simply is is because they did not allow
themselves to lose touch as quickly with
the idea of the natural communication
with other dimensions of consciousness
and your planetary consciousness. These
crystallin objects basically contain
within them energy patterns in the
crystal that represent the ability if
you mimic the energy pattern in the
crystal within your own consciousness
the ability to transcend to different
dimensional planes. They are keys in
that way. Understand is this relates to
the Mayan experience we discussed
previously. Yes. These are more
accelerated and more ancient versions of
these ideas, higher power, which shows now
ideas, higher power, which shows now
that your consciousness as a society is
beginning to blend sufficiently to be
able to take advantage of these larger
powered artifacts. Understand? Yes. So
identification, what you may call
meditation upon identification with
these crystallin forms can allow many
crystallizations to take place within
your consciousness that will accelerate
the impact of your individual
consciousness around the world, your
planet many times and throughout
universal reality. They are signals,
signposts, beacons, mirrors,
reflections, amplifiers of your
consciousness. amplifiers of the crystallin
amplifiers of the crystallin
consciousness you are all
becoming. You can use them that way if
you wish and enter new dimensions of
yourself. Understand? Yes. Can you
discuss the legend about the little boy
figurine? They the Indians say that if
he's removed from the mountain that he's
buried in that their village or their
area will be destroyed.
Basically, not that that has to happen
in that way, but basically what is being
understood is that if they are energy
gates, they do have a certain relation
to the energy fields of your planet.
Where they are is for a reason. They
amplify the energy in the most
harmonious way. to move them out of
alignment to some degree would be
analogous to having one of your machines
running on high speed and taking a part
of it away in the middle of the
operation. What do you think would
happen? Understand? Yes. So the idea simply is
Understand? Yes. So the idea simply is
that the balance of the energy includes
those figurines because their vibration
has been matched to that area. They
amplify the magnetic vortex of that
area. to remove them would be in a sense
to set the machine a skill. How does
that relate to the Mayan skulls that
have been discovered and removed to
museums or to private collection? To
some degree they are a little more
portable. They are in a sense what you
would call remote aspects being only
what you would call the skull, the head
of a whole
figurine. So they are the eyes, the
remote probes, the remote units that can
be moved in a sense to many different
loces. Now, they are all each keyed to
specific local, but they can be
rekeyed. Understand? Yes. And I just
want to ask if this um if these new
discoveries are a part of the crystal
skulls that have been discovered
supposedly when all the artifacts have
been uncovered, there will be great
information for all of our universe when
they're all brought together. In a
sense, yes. If any individual in any
local sits down with any one of those
skulls, they can communicate not only
with different dimensions of experience.
If they are clear enough, they can
communicate with anyone else who has a
skull anywhere.
Understand? But do they have more power
when they're all brought together in one
location? They can be amplified
logarithmically in that way. Yes. They
will have a different purpose then, a
different function. They will then be
able to literally produce the combined
magnetic vortex that can be literally
physically felt to be a gate, a
dimension of experience. At this time,
not meaning to instill fear in any of
you, I would be cautious about doing
that because it will cause a type of
acceleration that will force anyone
present in that area to really face all
the aspects of their
consciousness. All of them.
Thank you very much, Bashar. Thank you
for your willingness to now develop
crystal clarity.
Am still creating patterns of
relationships in which I feel
unsatisfied and in which I have
conflict. Are you assigning the same old
meanings to things that may simply on
the surface appear to be the same old
patterns? Just because it looks the same doesn't
Just because it looks the same doesn't
mean it means the same. If you know you
are a new person every moment of time,
have you given yourself the opportunity
to assign a new meaning to what may
appear to be an old pattern, but doesn't
have to create the effect of an old
pattern if you give a new meaning to it?
Thank you. I I see that I have grown
through my patterns. It's not the same
pattern. What's the same to me? What
disturbs me and uh what I wish to move
forward from is the is having conflict
and having dissatisfaction as if I'm
always searching for something different
than what I have and All right. May I
ask you a question? Yes. Do you create a
particular expectation about the idea of
what a relationship ought to be? Yes.
Why?
What do you know it can be? And if you
know it can be, why create a specific
expectation on how it should be?
Why not assume that you will simply
attract even though the manifestation
may come in expected ways what it can be
and that it will serve you in a positive
way rather than necessarily narrowing
down the specific definitions of what
you think it should be. Only allowing
those specific definitions to represent
to you the things you want rather than
allowing unexpected spontaneous things
to also represent what you want.
In many ways my current relationship I
have done that in order to be in this
relationship I have totally different
what I'm getting out of it is different
than what I thought I was looking for a
relationship as me about it is
different. All right and yet the sense
of and yet I am again in conflict. All
right. But again, also, if I may
interrupt you for a moment,
remember if you always at the same time
are recognizing that a circumstance and a
recognizing that a circumstance and a
situation is really not representative
of what you prefer in the overall sense.
The idea is to realize that it all
begins with the relationship to yourself
and that when you allow that to be
complete on every level that you can
imagine exists within your consciousness
then it isn't that you need a
relationship to feel complete and if
what you have as a relationship is not
reflective of your preference you don't
have to be physically in it.
Yes. Could you suggest to me what it is
that I have not completed in myself that
Well, can you answer the following
question? Do you need to have a
relationship? No. All right. Why?
No. All right. Why?
Well, I'm
self-sufficient the way I am. I don't
need it, but I certainly want to have a
relationship. Why? I want to be close,
to be intimate, to share, to have that
the depth that you can have in a
one-on-one uh seemingly more more depth than in
uh seemingly more more depth than in
having a one-on-one many. Um I want I
said seemingly I know it's all right.
And yet that's the way it seems. And I
want to uh
have a family. May I ask you another
question? Be as honest as you care to be. Okay. Do
Be as honest as you care to be. Okay. Do
you really express yourself in life as
boldly as you really want to in all
things? Yes. All things. Very bold. Very
bold. Very bold. All right. Very bold.
Is that
expression something that is within
integrity or are there times when it is
invalidational or judgmental? Yes, I'm
judgmental. Definitely judgmental.
Definitely the thing that I think I need
to work on the most about myself that I
think is the most obstructive to Why are
you choosing to be judgmental?
How does it serve you to be judgmental?
I have the sense that it's a way I have
of protecting myself that protecting
from what I'm not sure that's why I'm
asking but I see that I use the
judgmentalness it causes distance part
seeks tremendous depth and as I get
close to it I seem to be seeking
distance I'm being judgmental all right
I could also say well I learned it from
my parents I could say all those things
but I really would like to I'm really
seeking in this conversation
an awareness that will allow me to move
away from being so judgmental. So if you
know or if you believe that the idea of
being judgmental is what supplies the
difference and perhaps what supplies
what you have called the repetition of
patterns of relationships. Then if you
simply continue to assimilate the
reasons for why you would choose to be
judgmental, you will then integrate
yourself completely and will attract
relationships accordingly. Until you cease to be
accordingly. Until you cease to be
judgmental in that way, probably you
will still attract relationships that
will give you a sparkling opportunity to
continue to be judgmental. Right?
So remember also that when you say well
a part of me wishes depth, it is either
all of you or it is not at any given
moment. Remember that you are not a
collection of parts. And if you stop
thinking of yourself that way, maybe you
will stop thinking of other people that
way. Understand? Yes. Thank you. Does that
Understand? Yes. Thank you. Does that
assist you? Yes, it does. Thank you,
Bashar. Thank you very much. All my love
to you and to
you. Sharing.
Hi, Bashar. Goodbye to you. I have been
using the Robert Monroe Hemisync tapes
to um explore other dimensions and to
communicate and to explore more of my
total self. And while I'm using these
tapes, I have had um these experiences
where I feel a lot of joy and
understanding and later on. Yes. I feel
that I forget what it was and that I
don't understand anymore. Oh no, no, no.
And you have assimilated. You are using
it. You don't have to maintain
analytical awareness of all the memories
to simply know that it has sunk in and
that you are using it. The idea is to be
spontaneous with it, not to in a sense
cram your memory full of facts.
Understand? Mhm. Well, I think it's more
the feeling that I miss. Sort of like
the feeling of Oh, but one moment one
moment. One moment. Your definition of
what is happening is the only thing
creating a sense of loss. Remember once
again that because your society is used
to recognizing things by their
differences that when you match the
frequency of something and you don't
feel the difference between you and that
as strongly. Your first assumption is
that it has gone away rather than
understanding that you have simply
matched its frequency. So you don't
notice as much of a difference anymore
because you have become that
vibration. Understand? It hasn't gone
anywhere. You've become it. That's why
you don't notice the difference as
strongly as you used to. You have
elevated yourself to another level where
then something else can come in. To sit
there and assume that you have lost it
or it has diminished is to simply take
the old definitional point of view that
once you don't feel a difference, it
must be because it's gone somewhere
rather than you having assimilated to
that level. So there isn't any
difference between you anymore. It's
simply because your society is used to
measuring things or recognizing the
existence of energy by the differences
between you rather than the
similarities. Understand? Yes. Are you sure? I don't
Understand? Yes. Are you sure? I don't
feel that that's it. All right. because
uh some of these understandings what I
do remember of them you know one of the
things is that I'm uh this understanding
is that there is no negativity and that
oh one moment one moment there is
positive and negative energy there
always will be as a polarity expression
it is simply that you do not have to
choose negative
manifestation in your experiential life
but the more you become aware of more of
yourself, the more you're going to
become aware that there will always be
positive and
negative. Understand? Yes. Negativity in
that sense exists. It's a part of
creation. You don't have to choose it.
But becoming more aware of yourself
means you will be more aware of more
ways you could choose to be negative
because you are becoming more aware of
everything. So, you're going to become
more aware of that, too. Doesn't mean
you have to choose it, but you're going
to become more aware that you could
choose it. Understand? Yes.
Now, if there is a particular
feeling you sometimes think you may have
lost and wish to
recapture, well then feel it. Invent it
again. Create it right now. Remember
that anytime you quote unquote remember
what it was like as you are remembering
it, you're creating it in the present.
Right? Then only your assumption that it
is a memory of something that's not
happening now causes the separation that
doesn't allow you to feel it now because
all you're saying is I remember what it
used to feel like then. But in having
the memory, you're actually creating
that vibration in the present. If you
recognize that your memory is being
created in the present, you will feel
the same way now while you're having the
memory. Understand? Yes. Are you sure? Well, I'm
Understand? Yes. Are you sure? Well, I'm
wondering because I don't want to just
keep on repeating myself. Seems like you
never can. I don't have conscious
control over these experiences. It seems
like they just happen.
Many things you may wish to happen
automatically, seemingly, spontaneously,
seemingly outside of yourself in order
for you to have a spontaneous
occurrence. The idea is not always to be
analytically aware of the fact that you
are choosing it because then you don't
necessarily have physical spontaneous
occurrences and events in your life.
Understand? You're not going to have
analytical awareness of everything you
choose in physical reality because then
if you quote unquote knew every single
step you would ever take, you wouldn't
have to take them and you wouldn't get
anything out of them by going through
them spontaneously. Understand?
spontaneously. Understand?
Yeah. So like my goal is to be able to
use this perspective all the time and to
integrate it into my physical life
instead of having Well, go ahead. Well,
it's it's not integrating because I
don't seem to What makes you think it's
not? Why are you defining that it's not
integrating? Why are you choosing to believe it's
Why are you choosing to believe it's
not? Because I feel very elated when I'm
uh using these tapes and the rest of the
time I'm usually depressed. Why would
you choose that? I don't know. What is
the belief system within you that makes
you think there's a difference between
those two times?
Well, that's what I'm exploring because
it seems like when I'm
uh in that elated state, I'm just
delighted with everything that's going
on in my life. Yes. Yes. And the rest of
the time I don't like it. All right. But
remember, as we have discussed, a
feeling is a reaction to a belief. So if
you feel the idea is that you are not
elated, then you believe for some reason
that there's enough of a difference
between those two times that you can
feel that differently. Also do remember
that we have discussed the idea of
depression as only being meditation that
you judge to be
negative. So many times all you may be
doing is be in a meditated state and
assimilate what you have learned in the
tapes but you're judging it to be
depression. Understand? It may only be
meditation, the assimilation of the
information in a calm and balanced
state. But because you do not feel the
elation in the way you're used to
feeling it or in the way you think you
ought to, all of a sudden you
automatically apply a negative label to
the idea of what you're going through
rather than assuming it's a part of the
natural positive process as
well. Just because you don't feel the
same doesn't mean it can't be
positive. Many times you will feel a
certain energy in a certain way and then
you won't feel it that way anymore
because it's now up to you to apply it
in your life and generate the feeling
through your actions.
understand? Yes. Is this helping you?
Well, I'll listen to the tape later.
Listen to the tape
now. The tape in your consciousness. The
tape you are right now. Remember, you
are the tape. You are the information.
And if even it will or can work as a
suggestion for you, as a technique for
you, as a process, as a ritual for you,
if you pretend you're listening to the
tape now, do you feel excited? Well,
Well,
yeah. Well, then
pretend you're listening to the tape
anytime. Just because you're not physically doing
Just because you're not physically doing
it doesn't mean you can't do it. And
that's what it's all about anyway is
allowing you to start relying more on
yourself and less on the external
tools. In many of the interactions that
we are having now with individuals on
your planet in what you would call
private sessions, and many of you will
attest to this, your tape recorders
don't function because it allows you to focus
function because it allows you to focus
on the information as you. It allows you
to start relying on yourself, not on the
external tool. So if that's the feeling you want
tool. So if that's the feeling you want
to generate when you are walking down
your street, generate it because you
want to, not because you need the tape
to do it, because you want to. Because
the tape may represent your ability to
do it. If the tape simply represents
your ability to generate that feeling,
remember the tape isn't giving you that
feeling. you are. So if you can give
yourself that feeling when you're
listening to a tape, why can't you give
yourself that feeling when you're doing
anything else? You don't need the tape to
else? You don't need the tape to
generate the feeling. The tape has shown
you you can generate the feeling. So
generate it anytime you want to
understand. Yes. Does that serve you?
Yes. So I'm wondering why can't I
remember though? I I still have to be
able to remember some of these
experiences. How do you know you had them if you
How do you know you had them if you
can't remember them?
Because I remember a little bit of it.
Oh, a little bit. Then use that little
bit as all you need to
know. Again, you are creating an
expectation on what you think you should
retain analytically. Whatever you
retain, that's what you need. Does it
not give you joy to have the perspective
that if all you need to remember to have
ecstasy is just a little bit, then
doesn't that mean you're a lot farther
along than you thought?
Well, I don't know. I sort of think of
it as going, you know, to Japan and then
coming back and having forgotten half of
Japan. You never forget anything in the
way you need to remember it again. Trust
in the way you are.
The way you remember it is the way you
need to use it. When you use it, you
will then know anything else you need to
know. The only reason you seem to be
blocking the idea is because you're not
using what you are being shown you can
use. You are insisting on the whole
picture before you will use what you are
getting. calling what you're getting a
part of the picture rather than
recognizing that what you're getting is
in and of itself a whole
picture. Understand? Stop calling what
you're remembering a part. It is a whole
idea. Function that way. Use it as a
whole and you will understand that it is
all you need. You will remember
everything else you need to remember
when you need to.
This is your opportunity and your
ability to learn to label things in a
different way to understand that every
single component is in and of itself a
whole idea. This is your way of
discovering the holographic structure of
creation. Every part contains the
information of the
whole. Here's an analogy for all of you.
Imagine what you call a grid laid out to
infinity. Lines go this way, lines go
this way, creating what you call little
squares and blocks laid out flat
two-dimensionally as you say. Got the
picture? Place anywhere anywhere on that grid a
Place anywhere anywhere on that grid a
mirrored reflective ball
bearing. And notice in the surface of
that ball bearing even though it is
warped into a sphere is the picture of
the entire
grid. All the information of the grid is
in that one spot. You don't have to walk
to infinity to the end of the grid in
order to see it all in order to know you
have it all. It's all in that one spot.
All the information you
need. Understand? Yes. So anything you
get that you think is a piece is
actually in and of itself the whole
idea. Use it that way and you will get
all the information you need to out of
it. If you
insist on having to have it in the
format of the grid all laid out, it will
take you more time to walk the perimeter
of the
grid to get all of the
intersections. It is up to you. All
right. Yes. Thank you. Thank you very
much. Sharing.
Hello. I'm sorry. And to you, good day.
You adjust the mic. Oh,
okay. I would like to know. Speak up. Speak up
I would like to know. Speak up. Speak up
so that all may share. I would like to
know what I should do, what I can do to
discipline myself to to accomplish what
I came here to do. Writing. What did you
come here? Writing. Writing. I'm a
writer and I feel very I feel like
there's all this time slipping me by and
I'm not accomplishing. There it goes.
Here it comes again. There it
goes. Right between your fingers.
Now, are you a writer? Yes. Does it
excite you? Yes. Are you writing? Not as
much as I want to. Why not?
Uh, my energies are focused in other
areas right now. And I Are they as
exciting as being a writer? No. Why are
you doing them?
Because I need to make money right now.
Why can you not make money as a writer?
I feel I can. It's just that it You feel
you can when I
When is it that time
again? Is it that time? Time for the
threshold of believability.
Do you wish to play?
Yes. No. Maybe. Do I wish to play? Do
you wish to play? Yes. All
right. Here we go.
Have you taken the threshold of
believability meter before? Yes. Do you
want to take it again? Yes. Are you
sure? Yes. All
right. Get centered. Take a deep breath.
All of you can play along with your own
idea. Focus on the thing that excites
you the most. for you the writer.
Got it? Yes. Now, be very honest.
Very honest. It's all right. Don't worry
about it. Be very
honest. Beyond a shadow of a doubt, with
absolutely no hesitation, do you believe
that it will be absolutely no problem,
absolutely possible for you to be a
successful writer in 20 of your years?
Will you be a successful writer by then?
Yes. No problem. No problem. 10 years.
Yes. Absolutely. Absolutely. You can see
yourself doing it. Yes. Absolutely. 10
years. more than enough time to become
the writer I prefer to be. Yes. Yes.
Five years. It's very possible. Very
possible. Okay. Okay. Not absolute, not
certain, but all very possible. I know
that it is. I just still have these
doubts. All right. That's all right.
This is the first step in getting in
touch with the doubts so you can
transform the doubts. This is how you do
it. Being honest with yourself about how
long you really believe right now with
all the doubts you think it will take to
be what you want. That at least will put
you squarely in touch with what your
belief system is, what your doubts are.
Now you have something to deal with. Now
you know, all right, I have beliefs
within me that make it only just very
possible that I will be a writer in five
years. Why would I believe? What would I
have to believe in order for it to take
5 years? Examine your beliefs. Examine
your doubts. Get in touch with the
definition of them. Discover which ones
you prefer to keep. Discover which ones
you prefer to change. Change the ones
you prefer. Rewrite them. Find out what
the old definition is. Rewrite it.
Create a new definition. Then take the
threshold meter again and see if it is
now less time. Now that you have changed
some of the definitions, see if it will
take less time. Understand? Yes. Now you
can do this as soon as you really
believe you can be that idea. Nothing
will stop it. Nothing will stop the
opportunities from coming into your life
to allow you to be the idea it excites
you the most to
be. But it is up to you in your
definitions. If you don't believe that
it will support you, if you don't
believe it will be effortless, if you
really don't believe you can be that
person now, you won't
be. It's as simple as that. I know that.
All right. So get in touch with your
definitions, get in touch with your
belief systems and treat that as a part
of the idea you are excited about
being. Do not see it as a block, as an
interruption. It isn't. It is a part of
who you are. Own it so you can change
it. Don't deny it as being in your
way, as taking a long time, as wasting
time. If you invalidate it, you make it
take longer to be what you prefer to be.
Use the process as it occurs. And that's
how you accelerate the idea more
quickly because what you are doing,
whatever you're going through, is a part
of the idea. It excites you to be the
things that come up are coming up for
the purpose of giving you an opportunity
to deal with what you have to deal with
in order to be the idea that it excites
you to be. They are not things you have
to get out of the way in order to be
that thing. They are a part of the being
of that thing. Use them. Don't deny
them. Who knows?
All the things you are experiencing now
may make a wonderful
book. May give you the material you can
write about. We'll give you the different
about. We'll give you the different
perspectives and points of view I would
assume you would need to be the writer
you want to
be. Life for a writer is all
material. Understand? Yes. Is this
assisting you very much? And always
remember that your imagination is the
key. If you have a way you prefer to be
that you believe you're
not, envision the you you prefer to be.
Watch what that you does, how it acts
because if it isn't who you are, it will
act differently. Watch its attitudes,
its actions. Watch how it handles the
actions. Watch how it handles the
situations and circumstances in its
life. Hand it the circumstances in your life
Hand it the circumstances in your life
and watch how it handles them. Handle
them the same way, you'll get the same
effect. That's what your imagination is
for. That's the tool that it is. It's
that simple. It's the template, the
blueprint. Feel what it would be like to
be that person and you will be that
person. Put all your senses into it. See
the writer. See whatever you wish to be.
See how the writer acts. See how the
writer thinks. Feel how the writer
feels. Have the tastes, the sights, the
smells, the
touches. Hear what the writer hears. And
you will be the writer. And have the
lifestyle of the writer in your
imagination. Get into it with all your
senses. Be excited. Because if you
really believe that that writer in your
imagination is you, you'd be excited
about it.
Be excited. The vibration of excitement
will elevate you into that reality, will
attract that reality, that lifestyle to
you. Understand? Yes. Thank you. Is this
exciting you? Yes.
Thank you. Believe that you can function
as a writer. Attract opportunities into
your life. Let yourself attract
opportunities that you can act upon that
will show you that you can make a living
as a writer. Trust yourself. You can do
it. You are a writer. If you really
believe that, act like one.
Understand? Yes. Thank you. It's all a
matter of your attitude.
Thank you very much. You're welcome. Sharing.
Sharing.
Hello, Kash. And to you, good day. Uh
this is my first time here. I'm getting
a lot out of it. My friends brought me.
It's wonderful. All right. Remember that
every time is the first time. So it's
the first time for me too.
Thank you for sharing with me. My first
time. My first time.
This goes for all of
you. Do proceed and share with all.
There was someone in my life a long time
ago. Some a man I was very close to. All
right. I'd like to know. I am trying to
find this person now after many years.
What I find I have a connection with him
over many years. Yes, you still do. Yes.
Why are you in this sense trying to find
him? I have a need to know what happened
to him. Why?
I have to tell him how important he was
in my life. Do you not think you have
already done so? Yes. And I need I want
to confirm. I have hired people to find
out what happened. All right. And what I
am told is that he was killed in
Vietnam. All right. And then I am told
he is he was a soldier missing in
action. All right.
I feel he was killed. I'd like to know
what happened. He is not his name is not
on the Vietnam memorial.
Name Gilbert. Full name Gilbert Rantana.
Age in your terminology?
20.
Whether this may be valid in your time
track or not, our strongest perception
is that this individual is what you
would call a little boy of approximately
seven or
eight in your terms
reincarnated. In dream reality, you
always interact with this individual and
have done so many times.
deliver your message there. Send your
unconditional love. The child will get
out of it what they need
to. They may remember you in their
dreams and may apply you in whatever way
they need to, the memory of your love in
their new
life. But you always have the capacity
of interacting in your dream reality.
And you have already many
times. But he cannot be as focused upon
you at this time because of the new life
that is being lived. At least according
to our perception of this energy.
Understand? Yes. Is this a child I know?
It is not our perception that you do. At
least not yet.
Is the spirit that was Gil still with
me? Even though the physical plane he's
a child
in one sense as the oversoul. Yes. But
not in the direct sense you would mean
it. I understand.
One moment. One moment.
The time flow on this at this point for
us is what you would call relatively
foggy. You may know of the child. It is
our stronger perception that you do
not. It seems at least for now in the
way we perceive your energy that you may
have a stronger opportunity to know the
child when the child in your terms is 15
to 17 years of age.
May I ask you a question? Mhm.
Are you a teacher? I'm a writer.
Our strongest perception is that the
most likely, at least for now, this can
change, most likely circumstance in
which you may re-encounter this being at
approximately the age of 15 to 17 will
be in what you would call a class
situation where you will be lecturing or
teaching something to them.
And that's how I would recognize him. s
you will recognize the
energy. This is all we are allowed to
share at this time. Okay. Thank you very
much. We thank you and simply always
remind you these are the perceptions of
my consciousness through my time track.
There may be
variances as they apply to your time
track. We have given you what is the
strongest perception we can receive at
this time. Remember that all things are
fluid, but we have given you the
strongest momentum we can perceive at
this moment. Remember that you always
have the stronger access to things that
happen on your world because you are of
your world. Use your dream reality and
be in contact with this
individual. Be aware of the
communication you can have and are
having and have had. I will. Thank you
very much. sharing.
Hi, Bashar. And to you, good day. And
I'm excited to talk to you. Why? Because
makes me excited. All right. I'm very
ecartic to talk to you. Thank you. Oh,
you're welcome. I want to briefly tell
you about four years ago, I had a real
startling experience. Oh. All right. I
was at an amusement park and I was
sitting drinking a cup of coffee and
somebody came by and they were pushing a
baby stroller and in it was a little
baby and I hardly know what the little
baby looked like other than it was a
female child but the child's eyes locked
on me. I'm totally riveted to my eyes
and I just know that I knew those eyes
from somewhere. The experience just
almost demolished me for that day. I
spent the whole rest of the day looking
for that child and I couldn't find it.
Can you give me some insight in
that? But a strong past life
connection to some degree a counterpart
of the same soul you are, the oversoul
that you are. A reflection, a brief
encounter as a timing device, as a
signpost to awaken within you certain
ideas has been a very strong teacher for
you in the past and only needed to touch
you briefly to remind you of many
agreements you have made in this life to
kick off, I shall say, your momentum in
certain ways. It was a fulfillment of
one agreement you made within timing
with others you have known that have
been very close to you.
Um I'm a little confused. Are you saying
it was a part of me or are you saying it
was another uh another separate soul
that I didn't It is another individual
that you have interacted with in many
different lifetimes that to some degree
is also an aspect of the oversoul you
are also an extension of. Mhm. Yeah, I I
Yeah, I understand that. Do you have any
way of knowing who it might be if I told
you a person's name? Could you tell me
yes or no? Maybe. Maybe.
Okay. Okay. Try the name Adele Stfield.
Okay. Try the name Adele Stfield.
No. No. Okay. Thank you. Thank you.
More often than not, you knew that
individual as a
male in other lives.
some attachment of what you would call
Tibetan, some attachment of what you
would call
Atlantean. There are others, many
others, but those are some of the
strongest bells between you.
Shooting. Good afternoon, Bashar. Good day to you.
Good afternoon, Bashar. Good day to you.
Good day to you. Speak up. Speak up so
that all may share. Be bold. I have run
across some things that are so exciting,
I had to come up and share them with
everybody. All right, by all means.
Um, I wanted to go and find where the
dolphins are, and my husband wanted to
go and live in Arizona. All right. And
yesterday, listen, listen. Um, listen. Yesterday,
listen, listen. Um, listen. Yesterday,
a friend of mine sent me a folder in the
mail and lo and behold, it low and
behold. Yes. Synchronicity. It says
desert dolphins. Yes.
What has happened is that this lady
called Mary Carolyn Meadows has designed
what she's calling the Carefree
rejuvenation product which she is going
to put in an area that is north of
Phoenix. And it is going to be a big
dolphin center as well as a big healing
center. and she has been having uh
visions through some of the rebirththing
sessions she's been having and the
dolphins have been giving her the
visions of how this should be
constructed. All right. Part of it is
going to be
underground. Uh it's going to be just a
fantastic project. They're connecting up
with some other group that is going to
help them uh provide the seawater. The
things that they're going to do at the
center is people swimming with the
dolphins after being prepared through
various ways. Uh they're going to work
with handicapped children. Yes. They're
going to be couples um working with them
for conscious conception, pregnancy, and
birth, water birth. Yes, dolphins are
very good at both of those.
And it says the desert the desert
dolphins will be a major focus of the
health and rejuvenation center which
will offer a firstofits-kind series of
programs. It will be a synthesis of the
latest and most ancient healing
methodologies. In addition, they will have a Desert
In addition, they will have a Desert
Dolphin Academy, which is a creative
learning from preschool to university
level, and an interglobal interspecies
think tank. Nice. Isn't that exciting?
Yes. uh their
first their first international press
conference is going to be on November
25th and at the present time they have
the preliminary
uh write up called the business plan
done on it but now they're looking for
seed money in order to actually begin
putting it together but I I called
Arizona and talked to this lady today. I
had to talk to her personally. Hi. And
she said that they were planning on
putting their first baby dolphins from a
Florida dolphin center in their first
tank beginning in April. That's what
their um time schedule is. Many many
many of the interactions you will be
having will also be the product of the
creation of what you would call centers
on your sea coast to allow the dolphins
to come and go. However, a few dolphins
for the purpose of these interactions
will be willing for a time to be within
what you call some of your tanks for the
purpose of those
interactions. Do not worry about the
idea of some of those that will
volunteer for this in terms of what you
would call captivity. Some of them in
that sense are willing to do that and
they know what they are doing. You are
simply providing an environment for them
to come and visit you in that sense as
what you call specialists.
So anyway, next week I'm going out to
Arizona and see this wonderful lady. And
I told her that I would bring along some
of the tapes that Daryl has done in
Channeling the Dolphins and she is
ecstatic about that. All right. Thank
you for creating the excitement in your
life. Thank you for recognizing that
wherever you go, you are always in touch
with all levels of consciousness and you
can manifest and
materialize in the most unexpected
ways. Thank you. Thank you. We leap for
joy. Me too.
At this timing, you may all enjoy a
short break. will resume contact in
approximately 10 to 15 of your minutes. [Applause]
I will say continue.
Hi Bashar. Goodbye to you. Thank you.
Good day to you, too. Well, I have a
dilemma. A what? A dilemma. A dilemma.
Oh, yeah. Exciting. Exciting dilemma.
Right. All right. Okay. A little
background. I'll be as brief as I can
be. Background. Background.
Okay. In the since I've come back to Los
Angeles in the last 5 months, I've had
some really great things happen and
spiritualistic growth and everything.
Oh, everything. All right. Yeah.
And and yes, not but and and um I've
I've had incredible amount of disasters.
I mean lifethreatening situations. Oh
my. Very exciting. Very exciting. Yes. I
have been trapped in elevators after
earthquakes. I've been saved a man's
life who got attacked. I've had my
little kitty fly out the window and fall
five floors.
And one thing keeps happening after
another. The the greatest thing that's
coming out of all this is that
unlike anything before I've come to see
you especially
um these disasters right in the face of
it all I I always feel a connection with
you and a thought stream comes through
my head that has three words to it and
it just goes not this time guys and at
that point the disaster
entirely resolves. Yes. Yeah. So now
Yes. So So now I'm getting some good
positive things out of all this. Right.
Then they're not disastrous, are they?
Well, no. They get a averted, right?
Yes. Well, now do you remember what the
nomenclature what the definition what
the ancient meaning of your word
disaster is? No. Disaster separated from
the stars.
Wow, that's really interesting.
Always you are connected and when you
know you're connected, you're never
separated and it isn't a disaster.
It's always transformable.
It does. It just turns right around.
Yes. Okay. So now, yes, my husband
after all these seeming disasters,
after all these exciting events, Yes.
He wants to leave Los Angeles and go
back to Canada. Oh, I'd be going back to
Canada. He'd be going to Canada. And um
he's very insistent on it. And I'm not
all too sure that I want to leave. Why
the insistence?
He believes he he um can have a new
beginning there. He's from El Salvador
and has been all right. persecuted in is
the decision in that sense therefore
made because it is representative of
what the individual really desires to do
or is it representative of the
individual running from something what
he really wants to do he really wants
that and he wanted to do that before he
met me as a matter all right and so and
so here I am going well I don't know do
I want to leave Los Angeles now or or
what I'm faced with this decision. Do
you? Well, I'd like to leave Los Angeles, but
Well, I'd like to leave Los Angeles, but
I didn't want to leave right now. Oh,
all right. When will you leave?
Well, there was some things I wanted to
prepare first, such as such as um more
money. More money? Why? Uh to um to live
on when I first get back to Toronto. Why
not simply attract what you need when
you get there?
Yeah, I thought of that.
Yes. Well, okay, that sounds good. It is
up to you if you're willing to trust it.
Yes, I do. I could trust that because if
that's one of the reasons in that sense,
then that doesn't necessarily say you
don't want to move. It simply says that
you are hesitant about it because of
your belief system. Mhm. I see.
Understand? Yes, I do. Anything else?
Well, one other thing that's kind of
keeping me here, and that is I I was
talking to you before, I was telling you
about the band I had gotten together.
Well, now it's really going well. Oh,
all right. And I'd have to separate
myself out from that. I see. Uhhuh. Why
do you have to? Well, because if I go to
Canada, they're staying here. Oh, all
right. Uh-huh. So, I feel like Which
excites you more?
heavy side. Yeah.
Uh well, I guess it's just because I
know what I have here already. Well, all
right. You know, but which excites you
more?
Does it excite you to go to your Canada?
Yeah. Why? I really like it there. You
really like it there? Yeah. I like the
seasons. I I like everything about it.
All right. What is it that excites you
about your band?
Music. Music. Yes. The creation of it.
The possibilities of All right. Does it
have to be that music or can it be just
as exciting with other expressions,
other connections?
You mean another band? Yes. Yeah. I know
some real good musicians in Canada. Oh,
really? Yeah. Yeah. It could be that exciting
Yeah. Yeah. It could be that exciting
there. All right. If you really believed
that you could bring it all together in
your Canada as easily as you have it now,
Canada as easily as you have it now,
would that make a difference in your
decision? Yes. Would it be easier for
you to go? Yes. Well, then okay. If
that's the only thing standing in your
way, then allow yourself to trust that
you can bring it together just as
easily. In other words, it may not be
specifically that you do not want to
leave this band because you think it
can't happen anywhere else. If you
really believe it can happen in the
place that it excites you most to be,
then you won't necessarily have to hold
on to something that you don't
necessarily need to hold on to. I see
you understand. Yes, I do. Well, that
does it. I'm going all right. I'm going
to get to see you. Remember remember
remember. Okay. You are always connected
to everything. And many times, as we
have perceived on your planet, when you
make a move that quote unquote
physiologically separates you from
something you have been with for a long
time, sometimes in certain cases, you
actually wind up interacting with those
things more often than when you were
physically together. Yes. Just different
ways. And again, it is an understanding,
an opportunity for you to realize that
physical distance isn't all that
critical that you will be able to be
connected to whatever you really need to
connect to no matter where and when you
are. If you are where it really excites
you most to be understand. Yes. You'll
be able to connect to anything anywhere
anytime in the way you really need to.
Even you. Why not? I understand. I am
not in your Los Angeles area anyway. I know.
I know.
But remember true remember remember
remember. The idea is not to need me. The idea is
The idea is not to need me. The idea is
you have you. Yeah. Well, I don't need
you. It's just I love the the the
exchange. I love you as well. You know,
but the idea of having a real equal
exchange with us is going and doing what
it excites you the most to do.
Understand? That's how you speak to us
as an equal. Okay. So, thank you. Thank
you. And I'd like to thank you also for
the connection I had when these things
did occur. I definitely felt the
connection and the assistance. Our total
vibration and the vibration of all
within the association is always being
beamed to your planet. Simply remember
that when you tap into it, you are
tapping into your version of that
energy. Okay? You may recognize the
flavor of our consciousness because you
are familiar with the idea of placing
that energy within our power rather than
within yours. It will come with a flavor
simply to remind you that what's going
on is that you are now operating for
yourself on the same level you perceive
we operate on. Yes, I did feel a
blending there that it was. Thank you
very much. Thank you, Bashar. Bye-bye.
Enjoy your new elevator ride.
Ching. Yeah. Good day, Bashar. Good day
to you. Uh, you might be interested in
knowing that quite a few of us who come
to visit you are called Basharites.
Why? God knows. Because your name is
Bashar and we're right. I guess you're
coming here. I just made that up.
Anyways, my name is not Bashar, but
thank you. That's true. That's true. Uh,
anyway, I'd like to ask you my question
after I ask you a question. Uh, many
moons ago, there was a lady who was
standing here asking you about her
mother who had cancer. I believe it was
her mother. And uh without going into
everything, you mentioned something that
I could never get an answer from most
people is you
said get a disease that's a good
disease. And the closest thing I can
think of and said a cancer is maybe a
24-hour flu, but I number of people I
asked just couldn't get the concept of
what a good disease would be. That is
not a direct quote. Well, it's close
enough for government work, isn't it?
No. No. Okay.
The idea that we are in that sense
expressing is that sometimes individuals
will create disease for a positive
reason. And the idea is that they can
sometimes also create a disease that in
your nomenclature is not as negatively
severe in order to serve the same
purpose. Those are the ideas that were
being expressed. Okay, that's I like
that much better. Anyway, what I wanted
to ask you was um this question of
integrity. Now, if I go to the grocery
store and I stick my hand in the peanut
jar and I take some and eat them and
then I go eat a couple of grapes before
I buy them, does this mean I I ain't got
no integrity?
If you let the people know that you did
that, then you have Well, one day there
was a sign there and it says, "Do not
sample." And the guy came over me, says,
"You're not supposed to sample." I said,
"I'm not sampling. I'm stealing." So, he
looks at me, says, "Okay." And walked
away. Uh, all right. An opportunity to
discuss definitions. Yeah. Okay. But the
thing I I guess I really do not have a
good understanding of the word
integrity. Could you just give a
synopsis on this?
And basically the
idea follows suit into what you
generally think of as being honest and
open and
communicative and in that sense
respecting other points of view and
basic agreements that have been set up
between you. And before you change those
agreements, allowing all individuals
that would be involved in that change to
understand what's going
on. That is basically one foundational
expression or explanation or definition
of integrity. Functioning as a whole,
the whole event that you are in being
interconnected with everyone
else. And the idea of trusting that
whatever it is you really need, you will
be supplied with one way or another. In
other words, you don't have to quote
unquote bend or break what you have
already agreed with someone else is a
particular agreement or rule.
In order to allow that idea to
transform, you can simply attract to
yourself an opportunity to get what you
need in a way that quote unquote
naturally circumvents what may have been
previous agreements without necessarily
doing it in lie of their knowledge of
it in lie of their knowledge of
it in opposition to their knowledge of
the change.
To put it on very simple terms, in order
for something to change as an agreement
you have made, you don't have to be
sneaky. You can be out in the open and
allow something you really need to be
changed automatically with the agreement
of all connected in the event. Now, to
some degree, what you did to some degree
is representative of one way to do it.
Since if you were very blatant about it
and attracted an individual that noticed
what you were doing and had a very open
discussion about what was going on and
they allowed it truly allowed it to be
something that was representative of a
fulfillment of their integrity and their
definitions and their agreements, then
that's one thing. But if there was the
attraction of the idea that you were
doing something that you knew beyond a
shadow of a doubt other individuals were
presenting to you as in the consensus
reality a lack of integrity then that
can be representative of a lack of
integrity. The idea is simply that it
can be approached from many different
ways. It depends on what the
overall interaction is, what the
agreements are that are arranged or
rearranged between all the individuals
that must be involved in creating that
interaction and whether it serves the
best for all concerned in a positive
way. Understand? I believe it sounds
like you're saying it's the greatest
good for the greatest number basically.
Okay. Now not to mean that an individual
cannot receive specific benefit of the
idea as well but also it invokes clarity
of communication and honesty about why
what is happening is
happening. Now in other words let us
examine briefly what were your reasons for doing
briefly what were your reasons for doing
what you did? Me personally, you
personally I'm a games player and I like
to play games. All right. But what were
your reasons? Specifically
entertainment. Did you have within you the recognition
Did you have within you the recognition
or the agreement of a recognition that
what you call stealing usually
represents a lack of
integrity? In other words, were you
aware that many of the other individuals
that might have encountered what you
were doing would see it as a lack of
integrity?
Sometimes yes and sometimes no. It
depends on what the case is. Yes, as we
have said, it always depends on what the
circumstances are and what the
interaction is. Simply put, it can be
recognized this way. It is not so much
the idea that what you call the end
idea that what you call the end
justifies the means or the means
justifies the end. They are inseparable.
The means is the end. The end is the
means. They are one idea. One
idea. One idea. So the way you act, the
way you present yourself will determine
the outflow, the basic interaction that
is the result of your particular
participation in it. Now, sometimes
things can be done that would seem to go
against what you call society's rules
that can be used to shake things up a
little bit.
and doesn't really cause the idea of
what you call harm and isn't really
necessarily a representation of lack of
integrity. But it will depend upon the
level. It will depend upon the approach.
It will depend upon the attitudes, the
circumstances, the agreements, and
basically your primary intention as
well. Well, I'm sure glad I didn't tell
you. It excites me to steal those
peanuts.
I've said I'm glad I didn't tell you
this. All right. But thank you for
telling me what you did about it. Thank
you. Okay. Does that serve you? Yes, it
does. Thank you very much. Thank you
again. Do remember that whether you
think it can happen this way or not,
sometimes an individual who simply walks
up and says, "Do you mind if I take a
few of those peanuts without paying for
them?" Will very often find that an
individual may say, "Sure, go
ahead. Understand?
I understand. Thank you. Thanks again.
Sharing. Hi, Bashar. And to you, good day. It's
Hi, Bashar. And to you, good day. It's
wonderful to talk to you again. And you
as well. Um, I have recently
uh I guess not developed, but increased
my interest in geometry. Oh, all right.
And specifically, I'm drawn to the shape
called a tetrahedra or a three-sided
pyramid. It is the primary geometric
foundation building block of all
physical reality. It is the smallest
what you call regular solid shape and
therefore represents the basic template
equation in geometric terms that can be
used to define and describe any
equation, any perception, any variation,
any description of physiological reality
at all. It is the key shape, the key
format that can explain all ideas of any
event or physiological action in your
dimension of experience. Yes. Um I would
like to ask you two things about it.
First of all, speak up. Speak up so that
all may share. First of all,
um in looking around on our earth, uh I
find four-sided pyramids every place.
Yes. And I don't see as many tetrahedral
shapes. They serve a particular function
in a certain way. Well, what I'm asking
you is
uh the function that the tetrahedrin
serves as opposed to the foresight of
pyramid. It will be more
specifically a type of electromagnetic
focus that has to do with prime
mentality rather than the idea of a step
removed from that the focusing of the
electromagnetic field as the four-sided
pyramids do. Ah it will be the literal
gate three-sided gate between
physicality and non-physicality.
The four-sided ones do this as well, but
in a different way that aligns more with
the different layers of electromagnetic
energy that you have defined are
representative immediately of different
layers and levels of physical awareness.
Whereas the three-sided one will
actually bring you back to the center of
the void itself out of which all energy
and physical manifestation of energy
comes from to begin with. It is more of
a primal key. Whereas the four-sided
type uses the energy that is already
manifested as physical energy.
Understand? I see. Yes, that makes a lot
of sense to me. Um, do you have anything
to share with me about why it is that
I'm drawn specifically to that shape?
Well, many of you now will simply begin
to recognize through the melding of what
you call your metaphysics and physics.
the idea of exactly how the building
blocks of your reality are formed, how
they connect together, and it can allow
you more conscious recognition of how to
create the realities you prefer. It can
simply be a focus, a crystallizing tool
for you to reflect to your ability to
manifest the idea of physical reality
from what you call the void
itself. You are to some degree similar
in vibrational wavelength to some of our
society. And therefore the three-sided
idea attracts you even as it attracts
us. Yes, that makes a lot of sense to
me. Thank you. Well, thank you very
much. Sharing.
Hello, Bashar. And to you, goodbye. Very
happy to be here. Um I'm a school
teacher. I've just moved here. Um and
just started teaching at what we call um
quote unquote inner city schools, quote
unquote. All right. Um this is a new
experience. I've never taught at a
school like this before. Oh, exciting
for you. Yes, it is. Um, but it poses
some really unusual challenges. Wonder
if you had any information or advice
that you could give me about how to
motivate or reach kids that don't really
understand um maybe as to some degree it is a
um maybe as to some degree it is a
matter of retraining as you say.
Remember that by this time in your
society they have already been fed many
definitions that they are now quote
unquote locked into holding on to
because they do not know there is any
other way to be the primary fundamental
idea that you can begin to
retrain anyone with sharing with them
this idea. The opposite of what you have
all been taught up to this point is a
everyone everyone everyone is already in
control of their
reality. The control does not come
externally. It comes internally.
Everyone is as powerful as they need to
be to create any reality they desire
without having to hurt anyone else or
themselves in order to create it. You
can begin to teach them that what they
are experiencing in life is the product
of how they define life. Get them to
explore different
definitions. Approach it from a
different point of view, a different
angle. A point of view changes the
reality. Teach them about the idea that
point of view is what they are. That the
personality they consider themselves to
be is only a set of definitions. They
can change those definitions. In
changing the definitions, they will
change the people that they are
literally not figuratively. Remind them
you are not talking philosophy. You are
talking physics,
mechanics. Any change in your beliefs,
any change in your thoughts, any change
in your emotions changes the person you
are. Allow them to learn to act out the
different people they desire to be, the
way they prefer to be. Get them to use
that imagination. Remind them their
imagination is not something nebulous.
It's not something intangible. It is who
they are. It is what they can be. It is
real. It is a vibration. If they can
feel it, if they can get excited about
it, it is who they are. And they will
manifest that life. Remind them of these
things. Give them back their power. Let
them know they're in control. Let them
know they are co-creating the reality
with you. I think that would be very
helpful to know. I was I felt drawn to
this particular school and I don't
exactly know why but I feel like there's
maybe some specific messages I can bring
them to my Thank you very much. I think
that remember also and remind them of
this all teachers are learners. All
learners are teachers. So true. Yeah.
Thank you. Thank you. It will have an
impact on who it needs to. Thank you
Bisha. Thank you.
Shedding. Hello, Vashar. And to you, good day. Hi.
Hello, Vashar. And to you, good day. Hi.
I have a question on aging. Aging? Yes.
This weekend at the whole life expo, I
come across a friend at one of the
booths. They were doing some
diagnostics. Nice. With infrared. Nice.
So, I did it and I was amazed at the
accuracy of their diagnosis. All right.
But the premise of this was they use a
infrared scanner to to get spots on the face. I
scanner to to get spots on the face. I
think it corresponds to AC acupressure
points that goes to organs in the body.
Some of it. Yes. Well, this goes into a
computer that prints out a set of
numbers. But the whole premise of this
is that the fact that the they say the
aging process is based on uh they call
it the body the normal body on our
planet has a
25,000 or 2500 25,000 sun day
lifespan. And it has to do with
radiation. how much
radiation uh each organ the thymus gland
being the first one that's most affected
by radiation gets a number one. All
right. To some degree this is so but
only at the frequency that you exist at
now or have existed at. The more you
elevate your frequency by living in the
moment, the more you match the vibration
of what you call that stellar radiation
and the less it affects you in a
negative way.
The idea that is why living in the
moment, doing what excites you makes you
ageless, timeless because you are living
more in the now and you create less
time. When you accelerate your energy on
that level, you match the frequency of
that stellar radiation. You become more
of a light being, a light body. And then
the idea of the so-called difference
between the old you and the stellar
radiation isn't so dramatic. you are on
the same level and the idea is that
aging in that sense is
suspended. The things that are affected
in that way by the radiation only become
affected because you are operating on a
much lower frequency than the stellar
radiation. And so the difference is
created to cause what you call a
friction, a wearing down because of the
interaction of a higher energy and a
slower energy. The more you match the
frequency, the less friction there is,
the less wearing down there is.
Understand? I see that comes from living
in the moment and doing what excites
you. Elevating and accelerating your
energy level, becoming a stellar body
yourself. Understand? I understand that. Does that
Understand? I understand that. Does that
serve you? It does. One of the things
that they they on the diagnosis, they
said that I had never thought of this
that it could affect the body, but their
diagnosis showed up. I had moved around
the country a lot. They say like living
in different parts of the country
changing position in the space in which
it doesn't affect the body because you
are a different vibration in a different
local. A different local is a different
vibration. Different magnetic flux and
gravitational flux takes place and you
are constantly redefining the
gravitational and energetic matrix that
you are by moving around in different
loces. That's what moving around is
redefining the gravitational and
electromagnetic flux that you are.
Okay, I got that. Thank you. Thank you
very much. at this timing. Allow us to
remind each and every one of you that on
what you call the
interaction we will be having with you
on your 29th day of your present month,
in honor of your Halloween, we will
share with you our version of a ghost
story. [Music]
[Music]
On the 22nd day of your month, we will
share with you another story which will
be labeled the
sound. Next week of your time, who
knows? We will discover our interaction
next week of your time together at the
same time. At this timing, we extend to
you our deepest appreciation for the
co-creation of this interaction for
being willing to discover different
facets of the multi-dimensional crystal
that you are. Remember in that sense
yourself, all that you are, the
consensus reality is each and every one
of you. Each and every portion contains
the whole. Be what you prefer to be
energetically, boldly, with conviction
and unconditional love. We thank you for
the gift of your sharing. Our love to
you, exciting dream life and life
dreams. A fond and loving good day.
[Music] [Applause]
How did it go? Very well.
Thank you all for being here tonight.
Thanks for coming. We'll be here again,
of course, next Thursday and the next
Thursday and next Thursday.