Oh, thank how are you all this evening
of your time? Great. Great. Are you all
alive? Yes. Thank you. Allow us to begin
this interaction, this evening of your
time with a few ideas of the reasons for
our interaction with your society at
this time in your history.
Your civilization as we have perceived
it has existed for thousands of your
years in relative degrees of
awareness. Awareness of self. Awareness
of the realities all around you. You
have existed in more or less what may be
termed a sleepwalk state.
limited, segregated, separated in
various ways. Highly
focused into certain daily routines and
patterns and habitual rituals which have
created patterns and cycles of
repetition in your
society that on some levels may be
negative and that you may no longer
prefer to experience in your society.
Now we have perceived for a few of your
decades your society not just
individuals within it but on mass has
begun to explore the idea of
consciousness itself has begun to expand
its definitions and with it its horizon
into the exploration of what you are as
a being. What you are as a
spirit. With this new attitude, with
this new
perspective, with the diverting of your
energy in this new
direction, several things occur
simultaneously. An expansion of your
awareness begins to take place. You
begin to consider things that your
society as a whole has not allowed
itself to consider for quite some time.
You begin to become aware of the
possibility of other consciousness
within what you call your universe. You
begin to seriously consider that
interaction with not only the other
consciousness that may be in the
universe might be possible, but that you
begin to discover that interaction with
different levels of your own
consciousness is also possible and that
you have in fact more levels to your
consciousness than you originally
thought. All of these things as you say
are part and parcel of the expansion of
awareness of yourself that is now going
on on your planet that you have termed
the transformational age or the new age
if you wish. It is that
selfexamination self
exploration. And when you do that, when
any civilization begins to expand in the
ways you are expanding now, begins to
explore the things you are exploring
now, you change your vibration, your
frequency, your radiation. And this
radiation is picked up, if you will,
sensed by other civilizations, by other
levels of consciousness, by other
dimensionality that are already
exploring or have explored some of the
levels you are now beginning to explore.
When this radiation is sensed, then in
that sense we approach very cautiously,
very slowly the civilization that is
undergoing the change so as to not in
your terms upset the balance of their
progress at the rate they have
determined is appropriate for them. But
bit by bit, we sense that there may be
individuals and groups of individuals
that are willing to consider new points
of view, perhaps new approaches to life,
and willing to consider that they can
create and have every right to create
and deserve to create the realities upon
your planet that you desire to
experience. Rather than continuing your
age-old habit of assuming that physical
reality is somehow separate from you,
that you really have no dominion or
control over it, and that you have to,
as you say, take what is dished out, you
are beginning to recognize that you, as
some of your ancient literature
suggests, are truly made in the image of
the infinite creation. And what that
simply means is that every being is made
in the image of the infinite creator.
And what that means is that every being
is a reflection of the infinite
creation. A mirror, a model, if you
will, of the infinite creation. And what
that means is that you are actually the
creator of the
experiential reality that you have. In
other words, yes, the universe exists.
All creation exists and in that sense
you can say was created by the initial
creator. But all the experiences
personally that you have within that
universe are your doing are the doing of
each and every individual that has the
experience. These are some of the things
we can explore in this interaction this
evening of your time. Our primary
purpose in interacting with your
civilization at this time is to reflect
back to you certain things that have
been buried within your unconscious
mind, your subconscious mind for a long
time. to reflect back to you the things
you really do know that you have
forgotten that you know so that you can
remember that you are made in the image
of the infinite creator and act like it
and know that you have dominion over
your physiological experiential reality
and created to be the way you wish it to
be. We have the purpose of interacting
with you to discuss the mechanics of how
this may be so of how you may allow
yourself to accomplish a realization
that you always have been are now and
always will be in control of your
experiential reality whether you have
remembered that or not. These are the
things we are here to assist you in. To
give you back the power that you for
thousands of years have given away to
other individuals to ideas that you hold
above yourselves. You have as a society made
yourselves. You have as a society made
less of yourselves. Many times it is now
time to reclaim your integrity. Take
back your power. Take back your
responsibility. And that is why in every
interaction that we have with your
society, we remind you first and
foremost, you are not expected to
believe anything we say simply because
it is us saying you are equal to us in
every way, shape and form. As far as we
are concerned, yes, our civilizations
are different. Yes, some civilizations
may have a more expanded point of view,
be less limited in your terminology
socially, technologically, if you will.
That does not make you less. It simply
makes you
different. You can choose to expand and
to grow, to learn, to share, to create
peace, harmony, love upon your world.
You can learn to do these things. But we
are not here to force you into that
modality. We are here to love you, to
reflect to you your ability to create
that modality if if if you desire. So we
are here to share what works for us and
we can guarantee it will work for you if
you desire to use it. If you don't, we
will love you no less. And we still
appreciate that each and every
individual in creation is their own
unique way that the infinite creator has
of expressing itself.
No matter what comes out of any
interaction with you, to us that is a
gift because it allows us to see all the
different ways that creation can
manifest itself through all the
different beings that you are. We thank
you for that interaction and in return
for the gift you have given us, I simply
ask you now
how may I serve you?
Yes. Uh thank you uh for sharing and
co-creating with us tonight. And you as
well. And I I also want to thank you.
It's uh so
exciting sharing with you and your
reflections have made it
wonderfully possible for me, let's say,
to to really realize the abundance and
the excitement that's all around in
mine. And and it's
uh it's been wonderful. every all the
time. I I think about the the wonderful
times, but I also experience the times
and uh that was reflected in in the the
drive up here from where we came as it's
a roughly about a 10-hour drive, 8 to 10
hour drive. And I can actually remember
driving for about an hour
and it was wonderful because it I just
went from idea to idea. I thought there
were a lot of got a very strong sense of
space brothers and sisters all around.
In fact, there was one time when over
the crest of a hill, I sneak this one in
on you. Over the crest of a hill where
there were no trains or highways, I saw
some very bright shining rotating lights
reflecting up over the hill. And I just
wanted to ask you, no, it was not
actually. That's that's what I thought.
I just want to know if you concern any
of that. Uh, but it was in your
terminology, if you will, maneuvers by
factions of your own military. Yeah. Oh,
unadvertised too. I would say that's
great. We thank you for your sharing at this
We thank you for your sharing at this
time for allows us to point out one idea
that we would like to share with all of
you that we have shared many times. This
notion of where time goes when you are
having fun. Absolutely. Now you all say
well time flies well you know it doesn't
really fly we understand the expression in your
fly we understand the expression in your
language I but what is really happening
is the
following when you are focused on
something that you really love to do
when you are completely
absorbed by that idea you are living in
the moment truly in the moment the now
eternal moment you see time and
space is your creation, is your
projection, is your illusion. It is real
while you are in it, but it is an
illusion nonetheless. It is a
convenience. It is a definition, the
definition you require to be able to
exist in the format you call
physiological reality. Without the
notion, without the idea of time and
space, you could not play, if you will,
the game of physiological reality.
Not to the extent of the limited way I
have played. It has served a purpose
being played out that way and we can
discuss this later. But the notion for
now is that time is very malleable, very
flexible. And what is actually happening
when you are living in the moment, when
you are doing something that absorbs you
so much, so much of your excitement goes
into it that you do not feel the passage
of time. And then you look up and say,
"Oh my, well, three hours or so have
passed. Perhaps only felt like, oh, say
15 minutes to me." Well, let me tell you
something. Whatever you have actually
experienced in terms of the amount of
time, whatever amount of time you
actually feel has passed is the amount
of time and only the amount of time you
have physically ate. You simply
reconnect yourself into the agreed upon
majority time flow to keep pace with
everyone so that you can recognize that
3 hours has passed for everyone else.
But it is not that you have ignored it.
It is that you didn't create it. And if
you do not feel the 3 hours, you have
not lived 3 hours. You have only lived
the 15 minutes experientially. And you
have only aged the 15 minutes
experientially. This is why your lifespans are getting
This is why your lifespans are getting
longer and longer and longer. Because
the more you live in the moment, the
more you gather yourself back together
in the present rather than the past or
the future, you've then become in the now
future, you've then become in the now
moment more timeless, more ageless.
You recognize your eternalness, your
infinitess. And therefore, an hour, a
day, a week, a month, a year, a 100
years can go. As you say, in the
twinkling of an eye, you look up and
say, "Oh, an hour has passed." Well,
seems like a 100 years have come and
gone. Where did the time go? It didn't
go anywhere. You simply didn't create
it. It
It
is an actuality in terms of physical
mechanics that we are discussing. We are
not discussing just an attitude. We are
not discussing just the philosophy. We
are discussing physics and
mechanics. The experience you have of
time determines the actual amount of
time you spend in any particular
reality. And it will show upon you. And
the more you learn to live in the
moment, no matter how much time you have
created, you can actually reverse that
process and go back to a physiological
state that is more conducive of the
style in which you are living. No, you
all fall.
Yes. Sure.
Sure. You want elaborate or explain
define integrity? Integrity totally.
Integrity is usually back which is
referred to as simply the utilization of
positive energy for positive purpose,
positive meaning. But integrity in that
sense from your own root word signifies
that you are integrated that you are
gathering all that you have segregated
and bringing it back together. Integrity
in a sense is literally pulling yourself
together. Functioning as a unified
whole, not as a collection of parts, if
you will.
Integrity involves
trust, love, harmony,
willingness, and action. It means
functioning as a whole being, knowing
you are connected to all the things you
need to be connected to and living the
life that you know represents who you
are. Acting outside of integrity means lack
Acting outside of integrity means lack
of trust. Unwillingness to believe you
are in
control. Attempts at gaining control in
an exterior way. Domination,
force, that is lack of integrity because
you do not feel integrated and a part of
the whole. That is a basic definition of
whole. That is a basic definition of
integrity. Will that suffice? Thank you.
Thank you very much. Sharing for sure.
Yes. What is your concept of God or all that
What is your concept of God or all that
is? God, God is all that is. It is.
Thank you. In a sense, you have already
defined it. When you say all that is, it
is literally to us that all that is.
Nothing is left out of that definition.
When we say all that is, we mean it. In
other words, anything we can conceive
of, any being, any place, any situation,
any circumstance, any object, any
dimension, any universe is God. It is
all God. In a sense, our concept is a
literal interpretation of the phrase all
that is. We recognize that while your
word god can signify the infinite
creation, the infinite creator in a way
that allows you to know it is self-aware
which it is as a single identity which
it is. It is also aware of itself as the
combination of all identities within the
creation that it is. So to us it is not
so much that God is separate from the
creation. It is that God is its
creations. You, us, all things are made
of God. That is our definition of God.
Does that apply? Uh, no. But, uh, it it
needs more elaboration. All right. In
what direction?
In the direction of different levels of
uh existence or consciousness up to
where does it go? Is there an to where?
No, there is no end. It is absolutely
self-contained. There is no beginning.
There is no end and there is no outside.
So your definition is limited.
Your definition of a limitless being is
necessarily limited in a sense. Yes, if
we have to use
terminology. But the idea to us simply
is that God is all that is. Anything you
can imagine is God. God is that. It is a
part of God. It is contained within God.
God is everything. Everywhere, everyone,
every when anything you can imagine must
be within. and made of God because there
is no outside or you couldn't imagine it
if there
was. Is this making any more sense? A
little more. How about energies? The
different kinds of energies. But these
are all simply different vibrations
within God. Different levels within God
and they can be used for positive or
negative. Absolutely.
Everything can be used either positively
with integrity or negatively without
integrity because God is all energy and
therefore by definition must contain the
polarities of positive and negative. One
last question. What is your concept of
evil or the devil? Thank you. We
recognize what you call evil simply as a
lack of integrity. the use of negative
energy or energy in a negative way. To
us, the terms in your language, good and
evil, right and wrong, well, we
understand what you generally mean by
them. But many times we find that your
society doesn't understand even what you
mean by them because the terms good and
evil, right and wrong, are very
subjective value judgments. And you
know, if you simply think about it for a
moment, that you have witnessed upon
your planet times and situations where
something may be going on that you know
is an expression of integrity. And
certain individuals can say that's evil,
that's wrong. And you know, you have
seen circumstances where individuals are
expressing negativity and yet someone
may be judging that to be good and
right. So to us the terms positive
energy or integrity, negative energy or
lack of integrity are more precisely
descriptive of the energies you usually
refer to and the actions you usually
refer to as right, wrong, good, evil.
The devil concept to us is simply the
collective consciousness again
self-aware because all consciousness can
be self-aware but the collective
consciousness of your entire
civilization on the negative side. So
this spirit this being you call a devil
is simply part and parcel of your
civilization. Not that there are not
beings throughout the universe that may
choose to express themselves negatively
because there are. But the one that you
most often refer to as the devil or
Satan is simply the combination of all
the negativity in your consciousness on
your planet. And because all
consciousness is alive, it is alive and
self-aware. But its power and its
existence is only derived from the
support it gets from your civilization
as an idea. In other words, fear in and
of itself is a negative vibration. Fear
generates the existence and maintains
the existence of the consciousness form
you call the devil. In and of itself, it
really is quite empty and cannot derive
sustenance or support without the fear
in your
society. This is our perspective of the
being and the consciousness you call the
devil. Is this clear or is there some
specification we need to make? I don't
want to take the the floor all the time.
I thank you for for your interaction.
Thank you. We thank you. Feel free to
interact anytime. Everyone can realize
that they can learn from anything anyone
has to say. Chem.
Hey, I'd like to ask you a number of
questions. All right. Could you identify
exactly the
galactic location of your planet? Yes.
In your terminology, it is approximately
500 of your light years in the direction
of the constellation you call Orion. But
we are in another dimensional plane from
you. Our star is not visible to you in
our normal dimension. Your star is not
visible to us unless we make a
vibrational shift. Does that answer the question?
shift. Does that answer the question?
It's not visible. He said, so in other
words, it is physical but not in your
vibratory dimension. It is in a parallel
dimension. In other words, we cannot
observe it astronomically through our
telescopes or our or uh radio uh radio
astronomy. Not from your dimensional
point of view. If an individual on your
planet were to change his or her
vibrational frequency and then look
through one of your telescopes, yes,
then you could see it. But from your
typical dimensional vibrational
frequency, no, you cannot.
Yes. Are you familiar with the Ashtar
command? We are to some degree familiar
with what you call the Ashtar command.
Yes. Although to us it has slightly
different connotations than the ones
that have circulated upon your planet.
It is representative to us of a
gathering, a grouping of consciousness
that is involved as we are with your
planet in terms of uplifting and
elevating your consciousness, reflecting
to you the ideas that you are, the
godhood, the goddesshood that you are so
that you can then create the world of
harmony and love and peace that you
desire. It is assisting you in much the
same way. Although they are of a
different frequency and therefore
different individuals will be attracted
to them, different individuals will be
attracted to us and vice
versa. Does that answer the question? In
other words, you are not working under
the so-called intergalactic federation.
Yes, we term it the
association. That is our terminology for
what you call a federation. We simply
prefer the term association rather than
federation because the term in your
language federation has as you say
governmental connotations which actually
do not exist as a structure in our
association. But yes, they are a part of
that association. We are a part of that
association. So are many other
civilizations, especially the ones from
Plleades, Sirius, Reticulum, and many
others at this time that are interacting
with your world to be of assistance in
whatever way, shape or form we can
unobtrusively. Another question. Hey, uh do you have a
Another question. Hey, uh do you have a
b a bodily uh form? Yes, it is in your
terms approximately of average 5 ft in
height. White whitish gray skin
coloration, very wide upturned eye.
Males have no hair. Females have hair.
We are very slender in appearance. The
closest approximation you may care to
make. To any racial type you are
familiar with would be something similar
to what you would call Mongolian upon
your planet, but not identical. Similar.
Our eyes are much larger, much further
upswept. Our features are a little more
in that sense refined, not quite so
structured, very small in the nose, the
mouth, the ears, very large in the
eyes. Has anybody of your planet ever
been incarnate on our planet? Yes, many
times. Many, many, many times. The
physical channel before you is my only
incarnation that I have had upon your
world. Thank you. Thank you very much. Cherry
Thank you. Thank you very much. Cherry
Bishop.
Um, well, I just also want to welcome
you to being here. This is wonderful to
be here with you in the San Francisco
area for lots of reasons. for me. Um,
and I want to talk about that a little,
but I wanted to ask you about a dream
that I had that was so vivid and
intense. I wrote it down in purple ink
and then purple ink purple ink and uh
thought constantly about asking you
about this dream and then left what I
had written I think back at the other
hotel. So I think probably all that's
important today and I'll go through the
dream next next channeling with you is
what I remember of it from synchronicity
with it and that is that somebody in the
dream was loudly whispering throughout
the dream the number 47 over and over
and over again like an overlay to the
dream. And the dream had to do with me
being in a room that I have dreamt of
before that seems like I've seen I think
in cowboy movies just an old house
cowboy movies. Cowboy movies with a
screen door that squeaks when it opens
and very poppy string kind of thing.
Nothing that I can really relate to
other than that's all I only place I
ever remember seeing something like
this. And there are these beds that
aren't really exactly made up just with
sheets on them. And I'm sitting there
and there's some discussion about
whether or not I'm to have this baby and
it then as we have said the decision has
not been
finalized not by you not by them right
but it solidified and it feels like it's
getting closer. Um, and then the um,
anyway that the 47 and I was just going
to mix that with another dream that I
had the week before where I was giving
birth and I had on this white night gown
with ruffles and stuff. The kind of
night gown that I'm very fond of right
now that is sold on the particular
chain. Um, and but I didn't hear the
baby cry at all when the birthing
process was going on. No pain, no shock,
no trauma, only support, only energy,
only love. For many of the new births,
remembering that some of these new
births are about yourselves, not
literally about children, but even for
the literal children. No more pain, no
more suffering, no more shock, no more
trauma. I see. Okay. Cuz I had
interpreted it differently than Gohead.
Well, I had inter well someone that the
next day in a meditation group said I
think it was a stillborn that may have
been why you didn't hear the crying and
I wasn't trying to relate to that. Um
okay it is quite alive and quite
active simply is at peace.
So I'm used to that state is your
society that generally you make the
assumption that for something to be that
peaceful it must be dead.
Okay. Well all right. when I I feel good
about myself not not trusting that. And
um so when I when I woke up and I was
telling my husband about the dream, he
among the things he says to me, he
listened and then he jokingly said,
"Well, if they said 47 and that was
around the time that the first spaceship
landing was now all they have to say
crashing." Oh, crashing. Okay. He said,
"Now all they have It's not what we
would call a landing, per se.
Well, I wasn't sure what the number
meant." He jokingly said, "Now all you
have to do is have them whisper 19 and
you've got it." But we were just joking
at that point. It does have reference to
your year
1,947. It also has reference to the idea
of the timing of 47 years of which you
have already experienced 40 from 47 to
your 87. Seven more years generally is all
87. Seven more years generally is all
that is required. It is the average span
of time required for the majority of you
and in this case you in particular to be
experiencing more and more a high degree
of percentage more of the type of
reality you truly desire.
Okay, that that makes it also in your
terms of numerology combines into the
idea of 11 the power number the first
transitional gate
is so that's where I'm at at going to or
am at experience right now. There is
more to it than that but for now that is
what we can share. Okay. Cuz the the
whole week things were happening which I
felt was synchronistic. Um everything is
synchronistic whether you pay attention
to that or not is another thing. But
everything is synchronistic. Everything
is connected to everything else and
everything happens for a reason.
Everything. Everything. Oh everything.
Well yes everything.
No exceptions at all. No exceptions at
all. No, I I want to join one. No, not
even one. Not even one. No, not at all.
Okay. Uh, so the next day we were
invited to a an art gallery opening in
the town where we went somebody that we
didn't know very well. And she said,
"Why don't you stop by between 6:00 and
9:00, preferably around 6:00." And that
was my plan. And then all day long,
something kept telling me, "Go later in
the evening, make other plans, rearrange
things, and go around 8:00." And so
that's what I finally did. and somebody
who had been there for a few minutes at
8:00. I started talking to them and she
began telling me about um having an
adopt just adopted a child as and so we
began she was well we began speaking and
she gave me information the next day uh
I was able to start the papers rolling
for an adoption procedure
and the woman said to me you you're
probably going to have to wait about 10
days two weeks before you get all the
information and I said something like oh
probably not because it's something I
want very much and the Next day the
information was in the mail as um
manipulation of time. Mhm. And is
brought about by intensity of intention.
Okay. Because my feeling is just
basically what I want to share with you
is it felt so right to receive that
information from this lawyer that um
that is something we're going to pursue
through the 10day period you were quoted
in that sense is simply a symbolic
format to let you know that the idea has
old Orion
connections. The form you call adoption
is an Orion trait in the incarnations of
Orions upon your
planet. Not that others cannot do it,
but those with linkages to that stellar
system in times past will more or less,
more often than not, adopt rather than
bear what you call living children.
Because there are so many that are
incarnated already that you can only
form the families you need to form by
allowing yourself to come through into
incarnation whenever you can and then
finding each other in whatever way you
can. Through adoption is one way.
Thank you. Okay. Thank you. Pleasant
green. Thank you. Sure. Yes. Uh could
you elaborate on the meaning of uh the
number 11 and further on that if there's
any additional meanings of the number
111? S. Thank you. Recognize that 11 as
any symbolic mathematical relationship
is representative vibrational
frequencies, vibrational equations if
you will, which go into making up what
you perceive to be the physiological
universe. Certain frequencies will
represent overlapping of these
vibrations of the primal fundamental
energy of creation in certain ways.
These certain ways reinforce themselves
when the waves overlap creating specific
concepts, specific energy gates,
specific flow of energy. What you call
11 in that sense is the
selfreflecting symbol of the prime one.
In that sense, it is a mirror image. It
is in that sense the first
representation of a higher polarity. It
is the gate to another dimensional
realm. And it is also the first step out
of what you recognize as your
physiological universe which is 10
dimension. It is 11 the first
representation of the next level of
dimensionality of universes. And every
11 after that 22 33 is an especially
strong one. That is why many transitions
in your lives take place on or around
the age of 33. It is a triad of 11s and
the triad the triangle is the basic
constituent of all physiological
reality. All things are medded out in
threes. Polarity two and then the third
principle that allows them to move into
action into realization into
manifestation. So 11s mark certain
patterns of energy, patterns of
frequency that describe how different
universes are interconnected and at the
same time actually function as a
mathematical description of the gate,
the doorway if you will, through which
you can align your vibrations to
accelerate you through those gate,
through those levels of awareness, those
levels of consciousness to bring
yourself into closer realization and
manifestability within the reality.
qualities that you desire upon your
planet. Is any of this making some sense
somewhat? Is this serving you? Is there
a particular aspect you wish to focus
on? Well, I'm actually more interested
in the number 111 itself, not as not as
a doubled 11 to 22, but rather as 11s
that stand side by side. It's a number
that uh uh appears to me constantly, be
it uh in time. Well, you are simply
observing your own synchronicity. Many
individuals upon your planet will
observe specific numbers that represent
awareness of synchronicity. It is also 1
2 3 4 the fourth density that you are
going into the fourth dimensionality one
one. It is a gate of a specific type
that represents the awareness and
recognition of
interconnectedness synchronicity. Many
individuals in your society use the same
number 111.
There are also those that use 1010 but
that's a very specific frequency with a
very specific connection. Others will
use 44 but again it is similar to the
idea of the four ones and is
representative of the fourth dimension
into which you are proceeding. It is
your key your signal consciously to tune
into when things are aligned
harmoniously and so you can see that so
you can move in that direction. It is
your signpost to let you know you are
following the course of events
harmoniously that you need to follow or
that you can be made aware of the
harmonious line that you can prefer to
follow if you're not doing so. It is
your signpost in that sense. You follow
me? Yes. Does that assist you? Yes, very
much. Thank you very much. Sure. Mr.
Sure. You and then you. I wanted to ask
you a question. All right. Go right
ahead. Speak up. Okay. If someone that
you love has died recently. Yes. Is it
possible to feel that person's
vibration? Oh, absolutely. Why not?
Nothing ever really dies. Nothing ever
really disappears. Energy is all here and now.
disappears. Energy is all here and now.
Look at the radio analogy. Your device
upon your planet you call radio. You'll
have that. Yes. One moment. I'm about
finished. Do you think that that was a
sufficient answer for you? It was kind
of Oh, all right. But let's look at it
this way. We wish you to understand the
mechanics so that anytime anywhere you
have a similar question, you can apply
the understanding to it and answer the
question yourself. All right. Yes. No.
Maybe like it. You have a device you
call a radio. Yes. I do. You know that
no matter whether or not you are getting
one program at a time, you know that if
you switch the dial and get another
program, that doesn't mean the other
program is still not there, does it?
It means all the programs are there all
at once and you can receive any of them
you want to depending upon where your
dial is
too. So you can always receive any
energy that has ever existed in any form
whatsoever. Just tune your dial, your
thoughts to that frequency. Picturing it
if you will, that's one way. Feeling it,
that's another way. And that will tune
you into that frequency. And you will
receive communication and connection in
whatever way is representative of what
serves you and them best.
Does that serve you? Yes, it does. So
when I'm thinking of that person, they
are receiving and so are you. Now they
may be aware of it in different ways.
You may be aware of it on different
levels. It may not always come as you
say as a loud and audible conversation,
but it will be received and the energy
will be used in whatever way benefits
that individual best for the state in
which they now exist. You will receive
the information in the same way in the
format and the state that benefits
whatever you need to know at this time
that serves you best. Follow me? Yes.
What else? I I think what I was trying
to feel is just that person's presence.
Yes. Well, you can is very simple.
Remember that memory is created in the
present. Memory is not really of the
past in that sense. It is in the
present. And as soon as you remember,
you are
recreating in a very real way. In a very
real way. Maybe not in the same format,
but it is nonetheless a very real
connection and a very real
creation. So feel it. It is real always.
You cannot imagine
non-existence. Unreality. Anything you
imagine is somewhere, somehow, somewhere
a reality. Does that serve you? Yes, it
does. What else? I wanted to ask you,
you were saying earlier that there are
no accidents. No. Um, but we plan what
comes into our lives. Basically, some of
it you allow to be spontaneous. You do
not necessarily plan out every single
moment of every single day but generally
yes you propel yourself in specified
directions and the results can only be
the result of the directions you have
propelled yourselves in. So in that
sense yes you plan sometimes
specifically but more often than not
generally. What about suicide? That is
the one exception in a sense, conscious
suicide. For do remember that all death
in that sense is suicide since you do
plan it out quote unquote. But what you
are referring to as conscious
suicide is an attempt to escape.
Usually the agreements and the formats
and the plans you originally laid out
for your life because you have created
out of the decisions in that light a
belief that your life is not under your
control that you do not think you can
transform it in ways that are positive.
So individuals that feel so trapped so
powerless usually think that the only
way out is to remove themselves from the
original agreement.
99.9% of the time you will find that
when an individual consciously suicides
for a negative reason, they will almost
automatically reinject themselves back
into a new incarnation, go through the
life all over again, get to that point
all over again, and still have to face
the same things because they ran from
them the first
time. Follow me? So, does that answer
your question? Would that person be
reincarnated immediately or can be
usually depends upon the degree of
negativity experienced in the
transition? Sometimes there can be a
great deal of confusion. Sometimes those
individuals may not even know they are
physically dead. That is what you refer
to as your hauntings. Sometimes violent
or confusing deaths that do not allow
the individual to know they are actually
dead. It may take them some time to
adjust. They will have assistance on the
other side as you say to help them
adjust. But if they are not willing to
pay attention, if they do not believe
that there is any need to pay attention
to, they will continue to quote unquote
wander in a state of
confusion. Follow me? So it depends upon
the belief system of the individual
first and foremost about what they
thought might happen to them upon
physical death. Because remember this,
when you are no longer physical, you are
a thought form in a world of thought
form. There is no timeline between what
you think and what you experience. So
your strongest belief always creates
your experiential reality both in
physical reality and non-physical
reality. But in non-physical reality
there's no time lag. So if you're locked
into a morose belief, then you will
experience an instantaneous
manifestation of that type of reality
and remain locked into it for as long as
you hold that belief. Follow me? That is
the original purpose to the individuals
on your planet you call
exorcists. They are quote unquote spirit
psychologists. Recognizing that a spirit
may still be focused even though it is
dead towards the physical dimension and
so may pay more attention to physical
beings than the non-physical ones who
are trying to get their attention to let
them know they're dead. So the exorcist,
the spirit psychologist says after
getting the spirit's attention, you are
dead. Go on your way. Everything is all
right. Be who you wish to [Music]
be. Now remember that as an oversoul you
have many lines, many aspects, many
dimensions of a being. You can feel a
person's energy and not necessarily be
actually consciously in communication
with the singular aspect you used to
label as that soul, that energy. A
portion of them can be often involved
doing many other things, but you can
still feel their energy because
everyone's energy is everywhere, all
right, here and now. And you will tap
into whatever aspect of it represents
your desire, your manifestation, your
attempt at communication that you need
to perceive. And it is a real contact,
but it may be with a portion that is
aware of the contact and not necessarily
with a portion that's not. Does that
answer the question? Thank you very
much. Yes, other
can you explain the higher self and how
we can choose to understand our own
higher self? Thank you very much.
Now this notion of higher self all right
well very exciting but remember what you
call levels of consciousness and we know
we have used that terminology and we do
not mean it to be negatively confusing
in your term but such as your language
the notion of level is also an illusion
so many individuals when they think oh
yes I wish to be in touch with my higher
self basically will continue to maintain
a separation between their quote unquote
lower self and the higher self not
realizing that in a sense they are one
and the same thing. However, the higher
self we usually refer to simply being
represented by that portion if you will
of your whole spirit your whole soul
that extends beyond physicality into
non-physicality as well and is actually
where most of you is contained.
But the idea the easiest way or I shall
say one of the easiest ways to get in
touch with your higher self in a
conscious way is to do the following.
First of all, allow yourself to be very
relaxed and allow yourself to know that
the separation is an
illusion. Then imagine imagine imagine a
precious thing your imagination. Many of
you do not even know what it is for.
It is the access key to any reality you
desire to experience. Use your
imagination. Imagine the idea of the
higher self. What you pictured it to be.
What you imagine it to be. Imagine how
it would feel to be the higher self if
you were the higher self. If you had an
opportunity to be that higher self, how
would you feel? How would you act? How
would you think? What would you do that
is different than what you are doing now
if you were the higher self? Picture all
these things. Imagine all these things.
Examine, explore all these
things. Then realize the simple understanding of
Then realize the simple understanding of
the following. If you start to act that
way, you will be the higher self in
physical terms.
And you will have absolute close
communication with the higher self
because you will be the higher self in
physical terms. Remember
this in a sense we know that because of
the separation your world has created
you tend to that your spirit actually
inhabits your body. It doesn't. Your
body is your spirit in physical terms.
So you are the higher self, but the
higher self is powerful enough to create
the illusion within itself that it has a
higher and a lower counterpart that
somehow does not have access to the
information and the knowledge that the
so-called higher self
does. All you need to do is imagine,
feel, play it out what it would be like
to be the higher self. Or if you wait to
put it this way, what it would be like
to be in contact with the higher self.
And as you imagine it, it is so. It is
so because. Because your imagination is
real. Real. Absolutely real. And it is
the tool, the gate that is specifically
key to your vibration to allow you to
accomplish what you want to accomplish.
That's what it's for.
Is this making some sense? Yes. Does
that serve you? Thank you. Thank you
very much. One moment. One moment. You
are there. The other
there. The other
way and other way. If I may. To truly
know you are in harmonious
synchronization with or as the higher
self is to do, to
act, to be in your life. the thing with
integrity that excites you the most
because excitement is the physical translation
excitement is the physical translation
of the vibratory energy that represents
the path you chose to be in this life.
That's what excitement
is. When you are doing the things that
excite you the most, that's when you're
being the most you. That's what
excitement is for, to tell you this is
you. This is what you're all about. So
do it. Excitement tells you three
things. It tells you A, this is you. B,
because it is you, is the thing you can
do most effortlessly. And C, because it
is the thing you can do most
effortlessly and is the thing that you
are, is the thing that will allow you to
be the most abundant in your life and
continue to support you in order to be
able to continue to do the thing that
you are. So when you do what excites you
the most, that vibration, that
frequency, that excitement is the
vibration of your higher self. is the
vibration of you being the higher self
in physical reality. Does that make
sense? Thank you. Yes, it does. Thank
you very much. Yes. Something completely
different. There has been reports of abductions of
There has been reports of abductions of
human beings by extraterrestrials. Yes.
For for experimentation. Yes. Yes. Yes.
Now, what right do they have? Oh, one
moment. I will answer you. I will answer
you. Thank you.
First of all,
remember many many many things about
your consciousness are relegated to the
consciousness are relegated to the
unconscious levels rather than the
conscious level. Nothing
level. Nothing
absolutely nothing happens in your
experiential reality without your prior
agreement and or
belief. But the majority of the
agreements that have been made between
your people and those extraterrestrials,
as you call
them, those agreements remain relatively
unconscious within the majority of you.
And you don't remember them many times
until way after those interactions take
place. Because one of the reasons for
those interactions is to invoke those
memories within you to bring up the fear
that have suppressed those memories of
those agreements within you. Allow you
to play those fears out so that you can
get over being fearful. That's why there
is so much fear in those abduction
cases. Now, if I may, if I may, you can
use the same word if you want. It does
not bother me. However, I would like to
simply suggest that rather than the term
abduction, we simply use the term
detainment because that is basically all
that is happening. And abduction per se
usually implies that an individual is
never returned.
The idea is that individuals make
agreements, make contracts to meet at
certain times in certain places with
those beings whether they remember they
have or not to undergo certain
interactions that will bring out fear
within them. Now this does not mean that
they are actually being harmed. Nor does
it mean that the things that the
extraterrestrials do are in that sense
truly fear-causing. The fear that those
individuals feel are simply the buried
ideas, the buried fears within them that
are brought out in the presence of
beings that are wholly integrated
because that was a natural result of the
interaction of a wholly integrated
energy and one that is not. The wholly
integrated energy has a tendency to
overwhelm the one that is not forcing
all the things that have been suppressed
up to the surface when an individual in
that sense then must face them no matter
how fearful they are. But recognize this
all the individuals that have undergone
those detainments have been on the
detainments have been on the
verge of removing fear from their lives
completely. The only individuals that
that happens to on your planet are
individuals that have a very small
amount of fear left to deal with. We
leave individuals who have a greater
amount of fear alone. For they are not
ready for that interaction to bring them
up through the final levels of facing
who they are, integrating those pieces
of themselves they have segregated from
themselves for so very long and become
whole beings that can then be equals to
us. so that we can day by day, bit by
bit interact more and more blatantly,
openly with your society as equals so
you will not fear us.
Is this making some sense to me? Yes, it
is partially an answer. There has been
cases of nasty things happening or at least
of nasty things happening or at least
reported between all right
extraterrestrial and humans. as one
other thing. First of all,
recognize some of the things reported
quote unquote literally happened. Many
of them have not. Some of the things
reported may seem real but are created
out of the fear of the individual and
manifested as an experience they believe
has actually happened when in fact all
that happened went on in their mind and
not physically.
Sometimes there odd physical marks, but
even that does not always mean that it
was in your terms a literal physical act
because you and your mind control the
matter of your body. And if you really
believe that something actually
physically happened, even you can create
the mark on your body to show that some
of those marks are real. But in no way,
shape or form has anything ever been
done that is in your terms truly
damaging or truly painful to the
individual. The fear of the individual
causes all the pain. And there have been
individuals that have simply also been
asked if they are willing to have the
pain suspended which has also been done
for many of them. But the things that
are being done are being done for many
reasons and they are being done whether
your individuals know or not with your
permission. That is what gives them the
right because they have asked and you
have said yes whether you remember it or
not. And all that is being done is in
assistance to the changes going on on
your planet to assist in the
transformation so that you will be able
to function as the beings you need to be
in order to create the planet of peace
and harmony that you say you desire. I
know a lot of it doesn't make sense at
this time. But the more that you
integrate and the more that you trust
that you are also co-creators with us in
these interactions, the more you will
understand there is no need for fear and
the less you fear, the more pleasant the
interactions will be. But to have agreed
to them and we are only in that sense
abiding by those agreements.
Most of those types of interactions are
carried on by a specific group that
comes from the stellar system you refer
to as zeta
reticulum. Those are the beings of
average 3 ft of your height, sometimes
four, very wide, large black eye. Skin
coloration can vary from whitish gray to
pale beige to dark beige to dark gray
green. There are three types as you call
them racial types of zeter
reticulum. Does this answer your
question? Yes. Then in this case if there is the
Yes. Then in this case if there is the
agreement of the person uh then it is
within the cosmic law and all is well.
Oh yes yes yes. I was uh wondering if
some beings are acting besides the
cosmic law in disagreement with the
cosmic law. As far as those experiences
are concerned it has happened from time
to time but it is actually relatively
rare. Most of the negativity simply
comes from your own
fears. But your vibration as a planet
has changed greatly since those times.
And when your vibration, one of harmony,
love, and peace, no longer matches the
vibration of fear, then any being that
chooses to interact with you negatively
will no longer be able to even find you
because you will not exist in the same
vibratory plane any longer. So those
types of interactions are becoming more
and more and more
rare. Understand?
Your explanation is is very fulfilling
for me. Thank you. Thank you very much
for being a part of the fulfillment of
your planet. I understand more now than
ever before about this particular situ.
Your understanding will make a
difference in the ability of your entire
planet to understand them as well. We
thank you. Sherry, you and then you.
First of all, I'd like to thank you for
being here. I'm so excited to share. We
thank you for being there. Um, a couple
questions I want to ask. All right.
Number one, speak up. Speak up. First of
all, I realize you're on a totally
another dimension and we're on this
dimension. And we're all part of the all
that is. Yes. And um my spiritual
awareness I'm going to call it started
about six months ago. And I realize now
that I have uh created my reality and I
have made um these choices
and may I interrupt you for one moment?
Sure. Thank you very much.
Understand all of you that when we say
there are no accidents and that can
create your reality
utterly realize that many of the things
that happen to you in your lives that
are or you would label negative in
nature are created usually from some of
these unconscious beliefs unconscious
fears that you have. We are not saying
that when you create your reality you
are consciously choosing the negativity
that happens in your life. We are saying
that you unconsciously choose it because
you may fear that such a reality is the
most likely reality that will happen to
you. So the idea of the whole process of
getting in touch and becoming
consciously aware of all levels of
yourself will put you squarely in
conscious control of the fact that you
have always created your own reality.
And now that you know that you can
create the reality you prefer
consciously rather than realities you
don't prefer unconsciously. That is what
we mean when we say there are no
accidents. continue which is really exciting to me
continue which is really exciting to me
exciting to us as well always has been
about 13 years ago a sister who died and
uh I believe you know I'm in contact
with her and I realized that she is
supportive in developing and assisting
in the person that I'm becoming yes um
which is wonderful and one of the things
I wanted to ask is I'm on this dimension
now and I realized that she's a totally
another dimension and so are you. Are we
all to experience those different
dimensions? You already exist on every
level there is to exist upon and you can
experience any number of them as you
desire in any way, shape or format you
desire or any order you desire or any
degree you desire.
Then where will this all lead us to lead
you to? Um there is no ending. It is
forever. Ecstasy forever.
Ecstasy forever.
Do you believe that we are equal to you?
Yes. You are simply different. Using
your energy in a different way. Even a
being that uses its energy negatively is
still equal to a being that uses it
positively because they are using the
same energy. They are simply doing it in
different ways. Perhaps one with
integrity, one without. But they are
still equal in their power, in their
potential, in their manifestability. Are
they not?
Yes. So yes, you are equal. No matter what
So yes, you are equal. No matter what
you choose to do with your energy, to
us, you are still equal. We may have in
a sense a broader perspective in a more
positive nature than your general
planet, but that doesn't mean you're not
equal. It simply means you are choosing
to limit yourselves rather than expand
yourself. Okay. So we're in this process
right now of becoming whole. Yes. Yes.
Okay. Do you feel that you've reached
that point? Yes. I will always grow. I
will always change. I will always learn
more. I will always expand. But I know I
am whole. And even you are whole. No
matter what the definition or
arrangement or aortionment of your
energy, you're still
whole. Understand?
Yes. Am I to experience your dimension?
Do you want to?
Sure. Well, then you can. And stop.
Stop. Stop. You have. Yes. Or let's put it
Stop. You have. Yes. Or let's put it
this way. Let me fit this answer into
your time trap. You
will. At the same time, I can still say
you have. Does that make sense to you?
have. Does that make sense to you?
It may make more sense if I tell you
that we consider ourselves to be in what
you would call your future.
So, in that sense, you will. But because
all things are simultaneous and time is
an illusion and because in your dream
state you are far more flexible than you
allow yourself to be in physical
reality. You already have visited many
times.
Does that serve? Yes.
One moment.
The counterpart of your energy in our
dimension that we aren't aware of has
something to do with
botany with living things specifically
of what you would call the vegetation
kingdom a natural gardener if you
will. Does that serve you?
I'm not quite. All right. Do you
understand that you have many different
lives? Then what may be called the counterpart,
Then what may be called the counterpart,
the life you have in our dimension that
we are aware of is a being that is
involved in the idea of natural biology
in that sense or botany if you will.
Okay, understand
yes you are next. I had a question about
your question. You weren't too late for
that somewhat. Go ahead. Go ahead. Decide
somewhat. Go ahead. Go ahead. Decide
among your gohead. Okay. Uh I just
wanted to know if you could share more
clarity about the harmonic convergence.
All we will say at this time is that the
harmonic convergence as you call it upon
your planet represents the literal
midpoint overlap between an old cycle of
energy and a new cycle of energy. The
old third density vibration and the new
fourth density vibration. the old
vibration of limitation, the new
vibration of integration. That is what
it represents. The actual shifting
point, although it has been going on for
quite some time and will continue for
quite some time afterwards, that
represents the actual fulcrum point, if
you will. There will be many linkages of
will. There will be many linkages of
energy dates upon your planet on that
date and there will be much energy sent
to your world from other civilizations
on that date. Not that it is not being
sent all the time, but it will be
extremely focused and powerful on that
day. Especially with regard to the three
energy centers on your planet you call
Mount Shasta, Mount Fuji and Hawaii.
They will form the triangle, the doorway
through which the energy from our
association of worlds will funnel into
your world to make use of in whatever
way, shape or form your energy so
desires. All of them. Yes. Uh I I think
that answered my next question. Um you
Thank you, Michelle. Someone to I know
the dates are the 16th, 17th and 18th of
August and someone had suggested that uh
my husband and I leave a meditation by
the ocean in La Hoya and place called La
Hoya Cove which is considered to be a
high energy. Oh, I have a good time. You
don't need to ask me anything about and
to that the highest intensity would be
at dawn. And I just want to clarify
before I get up at 5:' in the morning.
What excites you? I want to ask you. The
idea of doing this excites me a lot to
get people together to meditate. When
does it excite you to do it?
Um the 16th comes to mind strongly. All
right. At what time? 6:00 in the
morning. Thank you. Have a good time.
Trust your imagination because it will
provide you with the appropriate
frequency that is correct for you. Okay.
You follow me? Right? Remember, it all
occurs simultaneously anyway. You will
overlap with other individuals in other
parts of your world to whom 6:00 in the
morning is not your 6:00 in the morning
anyway. But you will overlap with them
nonetheless. So, pick the one that feels
correct for you. Pick a time in which
you feel comfortable because if you're
not comfortable, you're not going to do
your best.
You follow me? I might make it later
then. Examine why. And if you find yourself
Examine why. And if you find yourself
automatically popping awake, say 3:00 in
the morning, then trust it. Put yourself
on your own automatic timer and say,
"Awaken me when it is the appropriate
time for me." Trust that if it does
awaken you in that way, you will not be
sleepy. So you won't care what time it
is because you'll have the energy
because it is the appropriate timing.
You follow?
Does that serve me? Yeah. Well, what I
will do is uh in line with that I will
go into meditation and ask that I know
the time in to assist other people to
come there to ask them to be there at
that time and I think that that power
spot feel that feels perfect to me
outdoors have a good time and thank you
for your participating. Okay. Thank you.
Yes, Bashara. This is the first
experience I've ever had. Me too.
Remember that every time is the first
time with this. Okay. I don't
understand. um when you're speaking
about dimensions and all right let's
look at it simply first before we go on
may I
thank you do you understand the idea
that everything is made of
energy what you call solid matter is
simply a form of energy correct you
understand the idea of different colors
of light being simply different
frequencies of the same energy correct
Then understand dimensions in the same
way. They are whole realities unto
themselves even as you understand your
physical universe all around you. But
they are of a different frequency. So
they overlap interlink with your
dimension. But your senses more often
than not don't perceive them because
they're on a different frequency. Much
in the same way that your eyes generally
don't perceive ultraviolet light even
though it's all around you because it is
of a frequency that is not germanine to
your particular dimension of
experience in the sensory mode. So there
are many an infinite number of parallel
dimensions going on if you wish all
around you all throughout. In a sense,
you are walking through other people all
the time. They are walking through you,
but you don't see them. They don't see
you because you're on a different
frequency. Now, does that explain dimensions to you
Now, does that explain dimensions to you
sufficiently? Somewhat. All right. And
then my other question is, how do you
achieve or how do you get to these other
dimensions? All right. Thank you. First
of all, remember again, you already
exist as a total being on every
dimension. Now sometimes meditation centering
Now sometimes meditation centering
within yourself and bringing yourself to
a neutral state with regard to all
dimensions can allow you then to lock
into any one that you care to imagine.
Remember that your imagination is real
and whatever you imagine is
representative of some dimension of
reality. So, the ones that excite and
entice you the most, the ones that have
the strongest vibrational meaning for
you are the ones that you will most
likely begin to experience when you put
yourself in a neutral, centered,
balanced state of meditation. I've never
been able to achieve that type of state.
How do you get to your Do you sleep?
Yes. Well, then what is that?
I'm uncon I'm not consciously aware of
Oh, but you are. Okay. Tell yourself
perhaps this suggestion. When I go to
sleep this night of my time, I know I am
still active. I know I am still involved
and participating in many dimensions of
experience. Allow
Allow
yourself to allow to grant permission to
yourself to slowly but surely at
whatever rate you are comfortable to
begin to recall while you are doing it
that you are having these experiences.
In other words, create the format you
call lucid
dreaming. Do you remember any of your
dreams ever at all? Yes. Then understand
that those dreams are symbolically
representative of activity in other
dimensions of experience. Now they may
be symbolic more or less. Sometimes they
are more literal, sometimes more
symbolic. Depends upon what type of
reality you are in and whether or not
your physical reality has enough symbols
to represent that reality when you wake
up to allow you to remember the
experience. Dreams many times are simply
representative of an experience and not
literal. Sometimes they're literal. So
remember first of all that your
so-called dream is a real experience in
a very real reality but not the physical
one you are used to follow. Yeah. Allow
yourself to tell yourself when you are
dreaming to let yourself know you are
dreaming while you're doing it. Have you
ever done that?
Not that I can remember. All right. You
can allow yourself to do so. It is
called lucid dreaming in your
terminology. You awaken in the dream and
when you awaken in the dream all of a
sudden you realize you are in another
dimension of experience. Now some of you
may find this frightening and so you
will prevent yourself from doing that
until it is no longer frightening.
But tell yourself you can do this at
whatever rate is comfortable for you.
And bit by bit you will find first of
all probably that your dreams whatever
dreams you do remember will first of all
become more
vivid. And then bit by bit you may allow
yourself to snap awake in the dream and
realize that the dream is an illusion in
a sense and that you are in a dimension
of experience and that you can create
that dimension of experience to be
whatever you wish it to be. And then you
can control that. And when you control
that, when you come back into your
physical dimension and awaken into your
physical dream, because physical reality is a
dream, because physical reality is a
dream, then you can remember what you
did in the dream reality. And you can
learn how to wake up in the physical
reality. Remove the limitation of the
focus of solidity and separation of this
physical dream. Expand the definition
and begin to see into other dimensions
of experience. That's one way. Does that
appeal to you? Yes. Um we should should
we not fear?
Um well, I'm not going to tell you what
you should or should not fear. If you
want to fear, you can.
Do we create our own fear if we go to
another dimension? Absolutely. So if you
know, if you know, if you know, if you
choose to trust that you are completely
self-empowered and that there is
absolutely nothing you could ever
discover in any dimension or within
yourself that can't be applied in a
positive way, if you are willing to
trust and know that, then there is
nothing to fear and your lack of fear
will create all experiences to be
positive. It is only the fear itself
that creates the experience to be
negative. Not a wiser word was ever uttered on
Not a wiser word was ever uttered on
your planet when someone said the only
thing you have to fear is fear itself
because it is only the fear itself that
creates the negative effect. No
circumstance and no situation has built
in
fear. No circumstance and no situation
means anything inherently. They are all
neutral props. You decide what they
mean. And when you decide what they
mean, that's the effect you get out of
it. The effect you put in, the effect
you get out. Positive meaning in,
positive effect out, negative meaning
in, negative effect out. Simple physics,
simple mechanics, action, reaction. So
if you find yourself fearing, then what
that means is you have been taught to
believe this circumstance is fearful.
Re-examine the belief. Discover why you
would believe that. Discover why you
might decide you don't want to believe
that. If you prefer to believe something
else, redefine the old belief. As soon
as you redefine the old belief and you
recognize it doesn't have to be fearful.
I can learn a lot from this. You will
transform it into a positive experience.
And then there will be nothing to fear.
It is automatic. Understand? Yes. Thank
you. Does that serve you? Yes. Then most
exciting and pleasant dreams too.
You know, we are going through very
intense times on the planet. Oh yes,
we're all aware of that. And the the old
ways and the old imageries and the old
designs are fading away for me. Yes. As
well as for many other people, I'm sure.
Bit by bit, it is changing. Yes. And I
am finding myself with new in a sort of
it's not a limbo but it's a it's an in
between time. Very good. Yes. This is a
typical symptom now of this particular
point in the transition the limbo state.
We have referred to it by that term
ourselves very often. It is giving you a
chance to shift your gears to be aware
of all the probable realities there are
to choose from so that you can choose
the ones you prefer most strongly.
Re-engage those gears and head off in
that direction. But for now, I guess
many of you are floating in what appears
to be a limbo state to give you the
opportunity to choose which realities
you wish to re-engage. Well, the reality
in which I want to re-engage uh involves
uh wealth as abundance. Abundance. Yes.
But not having to work and struggle for
it. To struggle and to have a little
job. Yes. You don't have to just to make
money, but to have a lot of fun. Yes,
that's the whole idea is that it is very
simple. As we have already said, when
you do what excites you the most, you
will automatically draw whatever type of
abundance into your life you need to
allow you to continue to do the things
that excite you the most. Recognize I
said type of abundance, but there are
many ways abundance can manifest. It
doesn't always have to be by the way you
have been taught to think. Abundance
needs to be represented in your life.
definition. Abundance, the ability to do
what you need to do when you need to do
it. Period. That's all abundance is. The
ability to do what you need to do when
you need to do it. Now, sometimes that
can be in the form you call your money.
It can also come in many other ways,
however, and many of the reasons why
many of you don't allow yourselves to be
as abundant as you could be is because
you refuse to believe abundance can come
in any other way other than the way your
society says it must come or you won't
be abundant. So, individuals who insist
that it has to come through a particular
narrow doorway will then force
themselves into struggling situations in
order to create the abundance in the way
they have always been taught it has to
happen. But if you do what excites you
the most and act upon whatever
opportunities are presented in your life
that represent what excites you the most
with your integrity at any given moment,
you will always attract the necessary
abundance in whatever form it has to be
there to get you to the next level of
excitement. Always, always, always. It
always works. I guarantee it 100%. There
are no exceptions. Not even
you. So, is there something that excites you
So, is there something that excites you
above and beyond anything else that you
are not doing?
Uh, that's a good question. Oh, thank
you very much.
Let me think about it. You are catching
me off guard there. Oh, all right. you
enjoy I I enjoy uh writing and I enjoy
Well, can you could you help me because
I am a little bit in limbo. I don't know
exactly what direction to go to create
that abundant the one that excites you
the most at any given moment out of all
the things you are aware of that are
available to you. Which things that you
can do something about that you can act
on in some way excite you the most?
Well, it's in the area of writing I
would say. Then write be a writer. Do
not be one moment. Pay attention to the
definitions of your belief. Do not be
someone trying to become a writer
because that will only bring you a life
of trying to be a writer. Be a
writer. Examine your imagination what it
means to you to be a writer. If you
picture yourself being a writer, look at
the picture. Is that you, that picture
of you acting differently than the you
you are now? And if so, then act that
way. And you will be a writer and
attract a writer's life. The
circumstances coincidentally,
automatically, synchronistically will
fall into your lap.
The opportunities will knock on your
door and they will be the opportunities
that come to someone who knows, thinks,
breathes, eats, sleeps, acts, lives like
a writer. But first, you must be the
idea before you can have the lifestyle
of that
being. Understand? That is total trust.
If an individual says, "Well, yes, I'd
like to be this." But I have to have
something to fall back on just in
case, that doesn't sound like someone
who really believes they are this thing.
Because someone who is that thing
doesn't have those thoughts that they
need to fall back on something. They're
a writer. They don't have to think about
that idea. They're a writer. What do you
mean fall back on something? What is
there to fall back on? I'm a writer. I
don't need anything to fall back on just
in case. I'm a writer. That's who I am.
That's what I am. That's what my life is
all about. An individual who says, "All
right, well, I'd like to be this, but
just in case, I'll hang on to this."
Let's say
30%. Then you cannot possibly expect to
be what you really want to be any more
than 70%. Because you're only a 100%
being. So as long as you hang on 30% to
something you don't want, you can only
get what you do want
70%. When you trust that you will always
get what your intention is and that the
opportunities will automatically fall
into your lap and you can act upon them,
then you can trust that you can be what
you want to be 100%. And as soon as you
are it
100%, you will have that life 100%.
Does that make some sense? It makes a
lot of sense. Yes. Uh my situation is
that maybe I I don't believe I can be a
writer and and and create immediate
wealth to sustain myself. Ah but again
remember recognize how you are defining
wealth. You will create whatever form of
abundance you need to be a writer in the
way you really want to be. Let's put it
this way. Let's say you finally decide
all right all right I'm a writer and you
start acting like it along comes someone
perhaps looking over your shoulder
seeing what you are doing say that's
very interesting what are you writing
and you say oh so and so say you know I
was just talking to a friend of mine who
wishes to publish a whole series of
works just on that subject well you know
this environment you're in well it
doesn't look very conducive to writing
this stuff will you say well yes I know
but you see I'm a writer It's all right
anyway no matter what environment I in.
So they say, "Well, how would you like a
better environment for this whole idea
to inspire you?" This publisher will
actually put you up in a glorious
mansion for you to write in so you can
be properly inspired to come out with
the type of work that he wants to
publish or she wants to publish. And you
say it's a deal. Now you have lived in a
mansion without ever having to earn a
dollar to pay for it. That is also
abundance. having what you need to do
what you need to do no matter how it
comes. It might come as a gift. You
don't know that. Let it come in whatever
way represents the path of least
resistance. Because many times needing
the money to get what you want may take
longer than somebody coming along and
saying, "Hey, take this please because
you will be helping me if you let me
help you." So that's why you don't need
to insist that wealth has to come in a
certain format. It will come in whatever
way it needs to come to allow you to be
whoever you are really being to whatever
level you are willing to be it. I
promise it always works. Never doesn't
work because the universe supports all
of its creations. When they are willing
to function as the fullest creation they
know themselves to be, then the universe
can support you as fully as you're
willing to be. But the universe, even if
it supports you always, can only support
you to the degree you are willing to
believe you are that being. No more, but
no less
either. Always exactly precisely to the
degree you are willing to believe you
are the idea. So set your
intention. Everything else, all the
details will automatically take care of
themselves. You don't have to focus on
how do I get there? What are all the
specific processes? Oh yes, they are
valid. They can work. They can give you
great insight into yourself. We are not
discounting them. Every tool is valid.
If it works for you, use it. If it
doesn't, don't. But the idea is that
when you set your intention, when you
know what you are, this is the thing
that excites me the most. and you act
like it and move in that direction,
acting upon whatever opportunity
presents itself to you that carries the
same degree of excitement, you will then
automatically pull in all the
circumstances you need to do what you
need to do. And if you're not
immediately capable of doing some
specific portion of the whole idea that
excites you, do whatever you can that
excites you the most. And that will lead
you whether it appears to be connected
or not into the circumstances you need
to be led in to give you the ability to
attract the circumstances to do the
other things you were not capable of
doing before. All excitement is a thread
and it leads to all other excitement.
Always guaranteed no exceptions not even
you. Does that help me? Yes. You know
you are such an interesting uh being to
to talk with. I would love for example
to inter to have the the capacity to to
interact with beings like yourself for
example. But you do. Yes. Okay. But in
in such an interesting way that the book
would would help uh the readers to to
have exciting and wonderful new ideas
coming up and and accepting also other
civilization. Well, you're capable of
doing that. Let your imagination fly
more easily. Is it possible to have
dialogues with somebody like you for
writing sometimes, but we will not tell
you what to write. That will be up to
you. No, but there must be
remember that you you you you have
access to all levels of information. We
are here to remind you that you have
access to all the same levels of
information that we do. Where are they?
Where are those levels of information
within you? Within your trust that you
have access to them. Without the trust,
you have no access. If you have the
trust that you do, you will get the
information in whatever way, shape, or
form it needs to come. It will come
along the path of least resistance. It
may not come in a dialogue like all of a
sudden the sky opens up and there are
the words printed on the clouds. It
might. It can. It has happened before.
But it may simply come in the actions
that manifest in your life. Open
yourself up to your desire to your
intention and let the information come
in whatever way it needs to. Who knows?
Maybe you will simply be walking down
your street and you will overhear
something that comes from someone else,
one of your own people, and it will be
the very line you need to hear to
inspire you in exactly the direction you
need to go. You don't have to go
searching the stars for that information
if you're looking for conversations to
have. Your people can help you right
here on your own
planet. Attract yourself into whatever
circumstance you need to to acquire the
information you require to be who you
are. You will get it. Don't place an
expectation on how you think it must
come. Just let it come. You will always
recognize it when it gets there.
Understand? Yes, I understand. Thank you
very much. One moment. One moment. One
moment.
What is your timing?
9:15. It's good time for a break. Uh, I
would say I'm I'm I'm getting energies
from here that it's time to take a
break. So, I always I always just trust
you'll know. You'll pick up that energy.
But there are about three or four people
who for some reason want Well, the
physical channel said he'd like to know
that. Okay. Okay. Yes. Physical channel
wanted to know at 9:15 around 9:00. You
may all then enjoy a short break and we
will resume contact in approximately 15
of your
I don't say continue.
You talked about existing in all
dimensions at the same time. Yes. And I
was wondering what determines what
dimension we incarnate on or do we
incarnate on all dimensions
simultaneous? You can incarnate on many.
Not all dimensions require physical
incarnation though. You can still exist
in those dimensions in whatever is the
representative format of consciousness
in that dimensional
plane. Understand?
It is simply that you can look at it as
if you are incarnated on all of them.
But that this focus in this light
because of the definition of what this
dimension is does not necessarily give
you an awareness of all the other
incarnations if you will you are having
at the same time. Some other dimensions
this is not so you have more ability to
be more aware of all the incarnations
you have going on at the same time. And
this is one of the traits that your
dimension now is also beginning to
develop. You follow me? Does that answer
your question? Yes, it does. So, in a
sense, this dimension has its limits.
They're not It has its definitional
limits. It has not as many limits.
However, as you experience within it,
you can impose upon yourself and have
more limits than simply those limits
that are required to define the
dimension. The limits that are required
to define the dimension in which you
exist. compared to the limits you have
placed upon yourselves for thousands of
years are far far less extreme than you
think. You have many more capabilities
even as a physical being than you have
been thought to think you
have. You are now becoming more and more
unlimited. And even within physical
reality, there are many things you can
do. Even if you are still a physical
being that you have not allowed yourself
to do simply because of the assumed
limits you have placed upon yourselves
through habits, beliefs and ideas you
follow. Does that answer the question?
Yes, it does. Thank you very much.
You male back there. Yes. Thank you.
I've got two questions. Yes. Um the
first is that in my day-to-day quest for
self fulfillment, I find that I have a
choice to either live a life based on
spiritual principles or live in fear and
pain. Oh, right. Yes. Your choice. And
as life as my life proceeds, I choose to
live in fear and pain less and less.
Yes. I live more a life based on
spiritual principles. However, in my
dreams, I find that fear seems to exist
in a different way. I'm wondering why my
dreams are embodying more fear for me.
Well, you are, let's say,
shoveling some of the stuff that you may
still have to work out within your
consciousness into your dream reality
where it can be played out without harm
to your physical
self. Understand? So you are shoveling
it out of your physical reality into
your dream reality where you know it can
be dissipated
harmlessly. Many of you are doing this
now. Am I playing with it in a sense?
Yes. In a sense you are examining things
learning all the things you need to
learn from it but without having to go
through the rigors of playing it out in
the physical reality which takes more
time. So you are accelerated. One of the
first things many of you will do in your
acceleration will be to shuffle some of
the things you still have to deal with
into a dream reality where it can be
processed much more quickly. So process
that you still will but you'll do it in
a way that will allow you to accelerate
in your physical reality much more
rapidly. Congratulations.
Second question. Thanks. Does the number
12 have any special meaning? All things
have significance. All
things 12 for us coincidentally and
paradoxically and not accidentally
enough is what our ancient numerical
system is actually based on. Not 10, 12.
To us it
represents all forms of vibrational
expression before the number you call
13, which to us is a very
transformational number, very magical as
you say number. Now you recognize it as
well, but you recognize that idea in a
very fearful way in what you call your
negative superstition. 13 is a vibration that has
superstition. 13 is a vibration that has
to do with getting in touch with all
levels of consciousness. It is in of
itself the limbo vibration we referred
to earlier. So 12 to us has meaning in
that it represents all the steps
necessary before it culminates in that
completely integral
transformationational gate of
13 in our ancient language shakashimi
13. Does that assist you? Yes. Thank you
very much. Sharing for sure. Yes. Uh
couple of questions uh to back up to the
um multi-dimensional existences for lack
of a better term. We'll do I'm unclear
on how uh in our terminology you can
kind of be be in more than one place at
one time. All right. Let's look at it
this way with another analogy. You have
a hand. Yes. Yes. Has fingers. Yes. Yes.
All right. Imagine a row of boxes into
which you can place one of your fingers
in each box. You follow me? Yes. Now,
they all lead back to your hand, do they
not? Yes. So, the hand represents the
oversoul that you are, the combined
energy that you are. The finger
represents a fragment, an extension of
that whole idea. In the same way that
each light you have represents a
fragment or an extension of the whole
energy that you are. So you can extend a
finger as a life into a particular time
frame as many as you wish in any
particular time frame in as many time
frames as you care to. But they all
connect back into the one whole being
that has quote unquote spread itself out
over the different dimensional plains of
space and time. You follow me? Yes. But
I'm aware of all my fingers in the
different boxes while they're in there
as the oversoul. Yes. But not
necessarily as the fragment depending
upon the definition of the box you have
placed that finger in. If there are
separations in those boxes that does not
allow one finger to see the other
finger, that can symbolize the
forgetting and the limitations that each
finger or fragment may experience that
does not allow it to know that other
fingers exist.
Okay. But to clarify a little further,
you you have stated that these lives
exist all at the same moment. Basically
basically yet you referred um to someone
else here before in a prior question
that her counterpart existed uh as a
botonist in your dimension for example.
Now is that a future life or is that it
is considered in your colloquial
timeframe analogy a future life. We
refer to it in the colloquial way to
allow it to make sense to her in the
time frame that you are used to using.
But all lives exist now. So let's put it
this way. To her it is a future life. To
me it's a contemporary. How's that?
Where does the integrity exist then
within the the energy? Now you use the
word counterpart. Yes. That's all energy
that exists at the same time. But yet
counterpart is a specific term.
Counterpart refers to another life that
is going on usually literally in the
same time frame in which you exist. I
use the term counterpart in this sense
because it exists contemporarily with me
and we are referring to someone that
exists contemporarily with you. But
counterpart generally is used to refer
to an aspect of the whole soul that you
are that typically would be called a
past or future life but it exists at the
same time in what you recognize as
another person. That is a spark if you
will same part of same soul. So
therefore there's integrity existing
there although to us it may seem
fragmented in time. Oh yes there is an
underlying template of integrity that
connects all fragments.
Okay. Does that assist you? Yes. Thank
you very much. Uh the second question to
back up again. Uh you've talked
repeatedly about how we create exactly
what is in our existence, although
perhaps not every single thing that
happens. Oh, every
every single thing that happens. Okay.
But you said there's a differentiation
between conscious and unconscious that
some things are created consciously and
some things are created unconsciously.
Okay. My question then is how does one
work towards
um getting or becoming aware of the
unconscious drives? Well, we have
discussed that already to some degree.
By doing what excites you the most, you
focus your consciousness more in the
surface and focusing it more in the
surface dissolves the barriers between
your unconscious and conscious mind and
allows you to be aware of more of what
you are and what beliefs you have. Okay,
that wasn't clear on that.
Thank you very much. There are other
ways you can do meditations and get in
touch with different aspects and
portions of yourself in that sense.
Mostly an easy way to do it is to look
around and see what's happening in your
physical reality because your physical
reality must be a reflection of what you
believe to be most probable. So if
what's happening is something you don't
prefer then first of all take
responsibility for it and own it by
saying if this is what is happening it
must be reflective of what I believe is
the most likely reality to happen. Now
do I prefer it? Yes or no? If no then
what would I have to believe in order to
have this kind of reality? Once you get
a handle on the definition, change the
definition into a belief you prefer.
Once you change the definition that you
believe you prefer and start acting as
if that is the belief you now hold to be
true, your physical reality has no
choice but to follow suit because it is
simply the shadow of your soul.
Understand? Yes. So that's another way.
Does this frighten very much? For sure.
For sure. You and then you. Okay.
Following up young man over there was
just talking about leads into some of
the questions I've had about some things
that have happened the past couple
months in my life that are confusing me.
Oh, all right. Remember first of all
that confusion intrinsically is not
negative. It is similar to the limbo
state confusion coion fusion with more
of
yourself. Continue.
Um, last week a number of things
happened, but all in one day I had um a
new friend of mine. Um, call me and say
that she just been picked up uh for
drinking while intoxicated. And would I
come down and help her get out of jail?
And I beg you a pardon. Did you mean
driving while intoxicated? Yes. Oh, I
say drinking.
Um then about three hours later, someone
called me and said, uh they needed some
money. Could I send them $1,000? Yes.
And then um all during this period of
time, a person that I've known for a
long time was a house guest who has
recently been diagnosed with cancer and
is on chemotherapy. Now, I looked at all
of these things and I was thinking if
these, you know, that these
things don't seem to be reflecting
anything in my life. One, I don't drink.
Oh, one moment. One moment. One moment.
Oh, all right. I want to tell you what
my confusion is. So, I was saying I
don't drink. I don't have problems with,
you know, needing money. I don't have
cancer. I I'm not careful. And then, and
I kept thinking these are kind of
negative things. And I kept thinking
there's so many positive things going on
here, but I couldn't put my hands on it.
I couldn't see the symbology. So that's
what I wanted. That's one thing I wanted
to help on. I know that's what I was
about to say. Okay. Understand that just
because individuals are in your life
doesn't mean that what they're doing is
a
onetoone reflection of what you're
doing. But they are in your life because
you believe for some reason that you
need to interact with them. Perhaps it
may simply be to be of assistance, but
that's representative of your belief. It
doesn't mean that when we say you create
your reality with your beliefs that you
create a reality that always reflects
back to you exactly verbatim one to one
something you are actually doing as an
active state. It means that you create
your reality with your beliefs by
drawing into your reality individuals
and circumstances that you believe you
need to interact with for whatever
reason. You following? Okay. See the
difference? I see the difference. Could
you help me? Well, how can you be of
assistance to those individuals? That's
that's fine. Okay, that makes sense.
Thank you. Okay. Along the same lines,
um, by the time the house guest left, I
was um I thought of myself throughout
the week having these thoughts that were
really very foreign to me. Things like
being very concerned about catching a
cold and and having ill health and and
Just some other things that were going
on. I realized that that that happens
oftenimes not only with the house
guests, but you'll be sitting next to
someone and you're in a perfectly good
mood and then 5 minutes later you you
are empathic. Yes. Okay. Um that's not
something I prefer to do. I would rather
Yes, it is something you prefer to do or
you wouldn't be doing it. Okay. However,
you don't have to do it in a negative
way. recognize that you want to be
empathic so you can identify with what
they're doing, what they're going
through, so you can help them. The only
difference is you don't have to take it
upon yourself in a negative way. You
don't have to match the identification
all the way to the point of creating
yourself to be in the same negative
mood. You can recognize it, but you can
also recognize it in a detached and
compassionate way. You don't have to
experience it just because you're being
empathic, but you do want to be
empathic. So you can help them because
if you can't identify with them, if you
can't be empathic, you won't know enough
about who they are to be able to help
them anyway. Okay, fair enough. Then can
is there any sort of technology or
something that would help me not slip
into that as much because I don't find
that comfortable to first of all
recognize that what you have been
experiencing has simply been from the
assumption that you have to pick it up
all the way. Now that you know you
don't, that in and of itself can make
enough of a difference. But here's a
suggestion. Anytime you begin to feel
it, allow yourself to breathe. Breathe
deeply, calmly, evenly and take the
energization and oxygenation that occurs
in your electromagnetic field and allow
yourself to modulate the energy so it
simply becomes something you are
observing and not something you are
experiencing. Give yourself the ability to simply know
Give yourself the ability to simply know
what you need to know in a very quick
and telepathic manner and then once you
know it dispense with the formalities of
the symbology find what I am saying to make
symbology find what I am saying to make
sense. Yeah.
No no no suggesting that
just slow and easy and it doesn't have
to go on for very long. Three breaths
are enough to even it out. Three
breaths. Okay. And and and you have automatically
Okay. And and and you have automatically
provided your own answer for another
suggestion. Do what you just did. Laugh.
Because that lightens everything up.
Okay. One last question. I think is
associated with it. All right. I've
recently moved from Southern California
to a town about 73 miles north of San
Francisco. It's beautiful up there. I
like it very much. But when I get into
my apartment, I find a very definite
shift in energy. Yes. I feel rather
cohesive and directed when I'm outside
and and doing things. I get into the
apartment and I feel dispersed. Yes. And
I find myself wanting to do nothing but
read metaphysical books and sleep. So
and then well then I think well I kind
of do these other things and I more or
less invalidate myself and then
sometimes I get into bad moods and I
also sometimes feel that I'm picking up
something in the environment. Anyway,
it's a mess and I want it is only your
safety valve. That is all is the place
where you can explore all those things
in the safety of your own privacy
knowing that you will have dealt with
whatever you need to deal with and then
when you leave the apartment you will be
able to be of assistance in the focused
way you need to be having already
processed all the things you need to
process. It is your place of processing.
That is all. It's your womb.
Okay. Where you are being reborn
constantly. It is your place of
self-discovery. Interesting.
There is it is your think tank, your
isolation chamber.
Okay. There's one one kind of I don't
know. It seems like there's an energy
there though too that is there is energy
and consciousness and some of it has to
do with some of your past lives and
associations with the
area and some of it has to do with
things that have yet to happen.
Okay, some of it I find myself depressed
and all right remember that depression
is only meditation that is negatively
judged. Remember that depression is
simply going within to find the answers
you know do not exist outside yourself.
Do not judge it negatively and it will
not have a negative feeling to it. That
is all depression is
for. It is for you to reconstruct the
idea that you are as a person so that
when you emerge from the meditation you
are a different person. The person you
need to
be. That's what it's for. Don't judge it
and it will be more of an enjoyable
experience. All right. The way you say it sounds
All right. The way you say it sounds
great, but why do I judge it then? I
mean, why? Simply out of the habitual
rituals that your society has always
taught you. Okay. Oh, what's the matter?
And and the life going within,
withdrawing, retreating. What's wrong
with you? Why can't you buck up, be
strong, face
lifeike? Those things create the idea of
that self-meditation to be very, very
depressing. very negative because your
society takes it as a sign that you
can't handle life when in fact it is
exactly the way to handle it to go
within to search for the answers that
you know you need to live the life you
know you
love. It is simply a habitual ritual.
That is all. Get over it now by
redefining it and you'll never
experience it that way again.
Sometimes the
depressive energy, the depressive
attitude is a buffer as well. You
surround yourself with a type of buffer
so you can do the processing in a way
you believe is safe without feeling like
a raw exposed
nerve. So you depress yourself, compress
yourself, go through the change and then
expand. It is a way to integrate in a sense it
It is a way to integrate in a sense it
is compression more than
depression. Understand?
Yeah. So if you agree with my
definitions, make them your definitions.
And when you make them your definitions,
you will have a different experience
when you create
that. Remember that no matter how you
have experienced anything in the past,
as soon as you redefine it, you'll never
experience it that way again. And it
doesn't matter how you used to
experience something. When you change
the idea, it changes in that moment. No
matter how it used to be, because you
create the past from the
present, not the other way around.
Got it. Yeah. Does that help you? One
last question. There's a voice that says
failure, failure, failure. I don't think
that's me. I don't know how it's coming
from another something that's different
from me.
First of all, it always has to be you,
even if you are receiving information
from another source.
It is again you, but it is the one we
refer to as some of the past life
phenomena. So, it sounds like it's
coming from someone else because you
don't consider that you to still be the
you you are now. It is old memories and
old habits that you are
assimilating. Tell it you love it. Tell
it to hush up.
Tell it that you are integrating. You
know you're not a failure. And remind
it, remind it because this is the most
important thing. It is not a failure
either because the ones that scream
failure the loudest are usually the ones
that believe it about
themselves because then they don't want
to see anyone else succeed out of sour
grapes. You follow me? Yeah. So that old
portion of you is simply not wanting to
lose your company because you know what
you say about misery and company.
So remind the old you that it is not a
failure, that you love it, that it can
expand, and therefore once it knows its
potential, it will not have to remind
you of what it believes itself to be.
Understand? Work the past from the present. Thank
Work the past from the present. Thank
you.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
Work it out among yourselves.
Yes. I I have been delighting in some areas
I I have been delighting in some areas
of my life, I think, in in
self-sabotage. Oh, all right. Many of
you find it very exciting. Yes. And I
polarized myself with a lot of ideas of
things I could do. And I could do them.
Yes. But I don't choose to do any one of
them. And I use doing the other ones to
keep me from doing the one. Oh, right. I
must be delighting in it because I've
been doing it for a while. Yes. Having a
wonderful life. Yes.
When it no longer serves you, you will
no longer do it. It's frustrating me and
I guess I like your comments. Oh, all
right. What it takes to Well, let's ask
a question if I may. May I? May I? Thank
you. Thank you.
If if if if let's play we know how many
of you love to play here.
If you did do one of those things you
say you do not do, what would happen?
or what do you fear might happen if you
would do one of those things?
I think I'm afraid that if I do all of
them, which is what I'm Yeah. driving
forward. Yeah. That I will run out of
things to do I'll be consumed by the
Yes. By doing them all by the activity
and expectations and demand.
All right. Fair enough. Very good. Why
do you believe
that? Oh, I don't know. That's do why
why do you believe that would be the
natural result as opposed to any other
result? I think the way that I've done
similar things in the past have put me
in that position. Not like I', you know,
run. We understand the connection that
many of you have to the idea of what
happened before means it's going to
happen again. But that's not the way it
works. What happens now is what you
decide will happen now regardless of
whatever has happened in the past. Do
you believe that?
I think I'm afraid to believe that.
Why? Why would you be afraid to be
completely in control? Does the
responsibility scare you?
I think I don't I think I don't trust
that that person that I was is not still
there. And oh, the person you were will
always exist. Always. You are never going to
exist. Always. You are never going to
get rid of anything because there's
nowhere to get rid of anything too.
However, no, no, no. You see, you don't have to
no, no, no. You see, you don't have to
be afraid of that. You will always by
definition as an integrated being you
always must retain connection to
everything you have ever been or you're
not integrated. It's how you use it.
That's the whole point. It's what you
prefer to be in terms of the overall
direction that you use all the other use
as. So you can allow the old you to
exist but simply no. You choose to
not let that old you decide how things
will be
run. Understand? Yes. You are deciding
what you prefer. This is your now. Your
now. Not its now. Your
now. Its now is then. Your now is now.
So while you may rely on it for past
experience because it has brought you to
where you are. So don't invalidate it.
By all means don't invalidate it.
Validation is the key. If you invalidate
something you have been that firmly
anchors you to that spot and that's why
you don't get ahead because you're not
willing to allow that portion of
yourself to be valid. And if you don't
allow that portion of yourself to be
valid, you can't get past that point.
Because each point is a stepping stone
in the direction you want to go. Let
that portion of yourself be valid. It
has served a purpose, if only to show
you what you no longer prefer to be. But
if something has shown you what you no
longer prefer to be, that gives you a
clearer idea of what you do wish to be
and therefore has served you in a
positive way. Everything can be used in
a positive way if you look at it in that
way. You understand?
So let the way you used to be that you
no longer prefer to be have served you
to bring you to a point where now you
are aware of what you prefer to be. And
assume assume trust that your awareness
pay attention your
awareness in and of itself of where you
prefer to be is enough to allow you to
know you have made the decision of who
you are now. And then you will have the
lifestyle of that. You
understand? Your awareness of who you
want to be is your intention of who you
want to be. If that is your intention,
act like
it. There will always be more than
enough time to do all the things you
want to do. If there wasn't, what would
be the point? The universe does not do
pointless things. Never gives you more than you
things. Never gives you more than you
are ready to really handle. Never. And
if there are two things in life that you
really need to do, two things that you
really must do to be who you are, then
the time will arrange itself for those
two things to be done. Because if there
wasn't enough time for both, the
universe would not be allowing you to be
who you are. And that doesn't happen. So
you will always have enough time.
Always. Everything will fit into place,
fall into place in perfect timing when
you relax your grip on trying to make
sure you are controlling everything.
That's tiring. You're trying to juggle
your life around. You don't have to do
that. Everything already has a niche.
Everything already fits in a slot. Let
it allow it to. You don't have to make
it. You don't have to force it. Allow it
by acting upon the opportunities that
present themselves to you most strongly
that excite you the
most. And that will allow everything
else to fall into place naturally.
Remember, the whole transformation is
about learning to be
natural, not Normal
Normal
understand the natural you you are not
the normal you you have all taught
yourselves to
be. So
relax do what really excites you because
it will allow everything else that
excites you to fall into place and take
its turn.
There will be no demands, no stress, no
strain. That is counter to the
definition of everything
fitting. Understand? Does this serve you?
Understand? Does this serve you?
Well, thank you very much for your
willingness to expand in that direction.
You and then you.
Maybe you. I'm very interested to know a
you. I'm very interested to know a
little bit more about uh yourself and
the people. Well, I do not want to jab
it on all night. What do you wish to
know specifically? Okay. Uh from what
I've learned or understand there the
different dimensions, the physical,
astral, causal, mental, levels. Yes.
What level? Well, we call it levels, but
we're not saying up or down, but what
dimension would you say you're Oh, one
moment. One moment. What you are
referring to now are in a sense levels
and dimensions but it is not the same
kind of a dimension we are referring to.
We are referring to something that in
your terminology would be more of a
parallel dimension that also has its own
portion of the astral, the etheric, the
causal and so on. Yes, it is a parallel
idea. Another type of vibrational
physicality. We are fourth density
physical moving into fifth which means
non-physical altogether. You are third
density physical going into fourth
density physical where we are at now.
But those changes are taking place
within and the astral and aetheric and
causal and all the other planes in that
sense overlap and are a part of the
parallel dimensions in which you and I
exist. We are two different ways of
doing the same thing. Would you say that
the other Okay, we're in a parallel
dimension, but the other
uh levels are of a higher vibratory rate
than where we come from. The astral
dimension in that sense is the
non-physical fourth density. You are
becoming physical fourth density. We are
already physical fourth density. The
astral plane is non-physical form and it
basically goes up from there until you
reach the octave and then you go into
other dimensional universes, other
tones, other vibrations.
And in order to achieve that astral
level, we can leave this physical body.
There's that astral body by using the
astral body or the soul. Yes, you can if
you wish. Now remember again that even
though we know how it appears to you,
the idea of astral projection and astral
travel is more of an expansion of your
consciousness than a literal quote
unquote leaving of the body. All you're
doing is changing the focus of your
consciousness to a wider being. You
follow me? So it's not a movement of the
body leaving the body. Not literally,
literally, literally because nothing
ever really moves or goes anywhere. It's
all here, right? But it is an expansion
as if it were a bubble expanding and
your consciousness was on the skin of
that bubble. So while you are physical,
it is a tight bubble. When you expand
astrally, it becomes a bigger bubble and
the body exists inside that bubble and
on and on and on and on and on.
So the idea to remember is that it is
not that consciousness exists within
your body. It is that your body exists
within your consciousness. So as you
change your focus, you are simply
expanding the definition of your
consciousness and seeing things in a
more expanded way like a bubble growing
inside. And then that bubble of course
by definition will contain everything it
has ever been.
understand? I think so. Does that answer
the question? Yes. Is there something
else you wish to know about our
civilization? Uh yes, there is a friend of mine who is
Uh yes, there is a friend of mine who is
in touch also with extraterrestrials and
they mentioned something about the zone
zone. The zone is that a level of
existence? Yes, there is many references
to many different types of zone. The one
we perceive that is being made reference
to here is the fact that there is a
transitional zone if you will that
represents going from one dimension to
your dimension represented by all the
different levels let us say of fitness
around your world representing all the
different spiritual levels outside all
those immediate levels associated with
your world there is a zone that allows
you to shift gears and go into another
dimensional series of levels down to the
core of that
civilization. There are many
inhabitants, many levels and different
forms of consciousness even within what
you call the zone which can be
considered the actual framework of all
that you and I may consider to be
universes unto themselves. Understand?
themselves. Understand?
Pretty vast.
Um, it would be as
if there were in your terms writings on
a page and writings on a page would be
one civilization. Flip the page,
writings on the other side, another
civilization. But the page itself is a
zone of consciousness unlike that on the
surface but very real in its own way and
gives definition to the fact that you
can even experience the other two pages
simply because the page itself exists.
That is what is being referred to as the
zone following the structure that gives
definition to all that you and I
consider real realities. But in and of
itself it is its own real reality. very
different very different very different
but there is consciousness contacting
your world from that area
there I assume I know that there are
many on planet earth as well walking
amongst us as walk-ins or as they also
have been seated here many eons ago yes
but remember remember in a sense none of
you are original to your planet anyway
right and some of what you call walk-ins
are not walk-ins in the literal sense
Although some are some of them are
simply ascensions from one level of
consciousness into another level of the
same consciousness. It will change the
personality completely and make it seem
as if it is a completely different
consciousness but it
isn't. Now in our ancient language zone
translates out
to in our particular solar system there
is an area just to illuminate you on our
particular area called Babar the zone.
And it is called such because the planet
in that orbit does not orbit within the
plane of the ecliptic of the solar
system. It goes up above the plane down
below the plane creating in a sense a
zone where there should be a planet. You
follow me?
Does this suffice?
Yes. Oh, thank you very
much. Sure. I've been working with one.
Yes.
I have two questions. Oh, what? When
someone you love very much and who loves
you very much dies. Yes. A parent for
instance. Nice. Who has provided
guidance on your life? Can that guidance
continue? Of course. But remember, even
though we know what you mean by
guidance, you have been providing your
own guidance based upon what you have
accepted of their
guidance. Understand? So you can still
accept what you
wish and there are many who will assist
you but you still choose what you
determine is your guidance. So you are
actually guiding yourself.
But can they become a part? Yes, they
can be spirit guides. Yes.
Okay, that doesn't Yes, it does. And
yes, they are. My second question
is for myself, there's an area that I
visit every year where I find myself
more spiritually aware. Is that common
or is is there a reason for me feeling
that way in this particular place?
You perceive it has a high degree of
association for you with regard to the
original reason you have incarnated upon
earth to begin with. So in a sense you
pay a visit to
home what you consider to be more home
than where you are for shall we say
refreshment and
assessment. Understand? Yes, that makes
sense. Thank you. Thank you. Yes.
Thank you. Thank you. Yes.
I've been working with people uh in
helping them integrate the energy. Yes.
Thank you very much. On a spiritual,
mental, physical level. Yes. And uh I
need some assistance in working with
people with AIDS. Oh, all right.
Remember this. We will be brief because
we have discussed this many times and
the literature and information is
available. The idea of AIDS is a specific symbol to
The idea of AIDS is a specific symbol to
represent the denial in your society for
a long
time. The denial of the blending of the
masculine and the feminine energies
within each and every
individual. This denial and the
continuence of this denial and the
placing upon this continuence of this
denial of
invalidation, judgment, negativity and
fear has now created a
disease disease that represents the lack of
disease that represents the lack of
willingness the fear to blend and
integrate the masculine and feminine
energies within each and every
individual into a balanced state.
So when individuals can balance and
blend that energy within themselves
equally, there will be no
disease. None of any form
None of any form
whatsoever. Think of an individual as an
energy being and allow them to begin to
see themselves as homogeneous, a blue
white electromagnetic light without any
particular variation. Let them rec
crystallize their bodies out of that
homogeneous blue white light and know
that the new body is representative of
the new idea of blending and balancing
day by day, bit by bit. More and more
they can transform
themselves into a balancing and a blame.
Now certain individuals may not believe
they can do that and they may in your
terms take themselves out of physical
existence before they will bring
themselves back in if they choose to to
examine and blend and balance the ideas
that they have chosen to explore in that
life. But individuals can also blend and
balance that energy in the present life.
They do not have to die physically in
order to do that.
So talk about the ideas and be of the
systems and the ideas of the blending
and the balancing of the masculine and
feminine energies within each and every
individual and it can alleviate the
disease. Does that assist you? Yes.
Thank you very much. There will be in
your terms but a few moments remaining
for this interaction this evening of
your time. Are there any further
sharings? Yes.
There has been a lot of doom and gloom
philosophy going on. Yes. Doom and
gloom. Doom and gloom. Um, one
particular channel has been instilling
fear into people's mind that about what
is going to happen
catastrophes to what is going to happen
to California. Yes. And literally
hundreds of families have fled to other
parts of the country in fear. Yes.
Uh what is the credibility that you can
give to Thank you. Let us address the
situation this
way. Remember
this. There is no such thing as a
prediction of the future. Prediction is
as follows. It is a sensing of the
energy that may be most likely to
manifest if it doesn't change. And that
sensing takes place at the time the
prediction is made. That's the energy
that exists at the time the prediction
is made. However, realize that once an
individual knows where the momentum and where the
knows where the momentum and where the
energy may be and what idea it is
behind, if they do not prefer that
manifestation, their awareness of the
prediction can render the prediction
obsolete. Nothing is chiseled in steel.
Now certain prediction may pick up on
events or
probabilities that have a great deal of
momentum behind them and may seem very
likely. seeming as if nothing could
possibly divert it because the energy is
so strong but anything can always be
transformed and so we will say this
about the whole idea of the
transformation. You are going through a
transformation changes there will be but
you can decide what reality you prefer.
You can decide whether you wish to
experience the transformation in a
negative way or a positive one and that
will determine how you experience any
type of shift at
all. Be the full loving being of service
you can be to be of aid and assistance
and live the life you live to the
fullest. Then you will not have to place
yourself in an area that will shake you
away. So individuals will simply find
So individuals will simply find
themselves automatically without even
planning to being where they need to be
to be in the type of reality that
represents the way they choose to go
through the transformation positive or
negative. Now there may still be a few
sporadic occurrences of transformational shifts
occurrences of transformational shifts
in a negative fashion in a catastrophic
fashion but you have already as a
society as far as we perceive your
energy done much to transform that
energy in a positive way because you are
willing to wake up. And so even as few
as 10 of your years ago, there were many
more likelihoods of negative
catastrophic transformations than there
are now. You have
alleviated the whole area will siphon
that energy off, transform it in a
positive way and use it in other ways
and will not have to have a negative
catastrophic transformation. Changes
there are and the electromagnetic field
of your world is shifting all the time.
But these pressures and changes and
shifts can be released positively as
well as negatively. So anytime you hear
such a prediction that you feel is
negative and fear inducing, recognize
you're not really being lied to, but you
are being given an opportunity. Take it
as an opportunity. Take it as an
opportunity to say, "All right, I have
heard what you say. I know you may be
sensing the mass consciousness of this
particular area at that time but I
choose I choose because I know I can
choose a different way to manifest that
reality. Say, I thank you for giving me the
Say, I thank you for giving me the
opportunity to decide whether or not I
prefer the reality you are defining
because now I know the reality you are
defining as the most probable reality is
not the reality I will experience and
you have given us all an opportunity to
transform that energy in a positive way.
So take any such prediction as an
opportunity not as something chiseled in
steel. You follow me? Absolutely. Does
that assist you? Oh absolutely. Thank
you very much. We thank each
And every one of you individually and
collectively this moment of your time
remember please remember each and every
individual makes a
difference. You all have impact and any
change in a positive direction you
create within your life. Any change in a
positive direction you
allow to happen in your
life will make a difference in the
ability of your entire civilization to
choose the positive reality. It will
make it that much more easy because you
are adding that much more positive
energy by your own actions, by your own
choices. It tips the scale and it will
accelerate in that direction if that's
what you prefer. Remember above and
beyond all anything you can imagine that
all anything you can imagine that
represents the positive reality you
deserve is deserved by you is deserved
just because you can imagine it. You
don't need another reason. You don't
need a stronger reason to have a life of
ecstasy other than the reason that you
can imagine it and you choose
it. Just because you say so is
enough. You are exercising the free will
that the infinite creator gave you. Your
choices and decisions will stick. Just
because you say so. It's enough. It's
that simple. It is that simple. Nothing,
nothing, nothing is too good to be true.
Nothing. We extend to each and every one
of you our appreciation once again and
our unconditional love in allowing us to
experience the gift that you are. Our
energy and our love when we bid you
exciting dream lives and life dreams.
Wake up and live your dreams. You
deserve it. We thank you for acting as
ambassadors of your world. And I thank
you for allowing me to act as an
ambassador of mine so that we may one
day more and more share the same dreams
and explore all of creation in joy and
ecstasy. We thank you for allowing us to
play with you. Good day. Amen. Amen. [Music] Everyone
go as I was going into the world that I
guess there's really no way that I can
get out of that.
Not want to.
hung down invitation.
The um the woman that I saw went down
before me because there was other people
involved too. The woman that I saw being
sucked down before me had a little bit
of panic on her face too. But then as
she was going into the whirlpool and
being sucked down all of a sudden there
was ecstasy. In
In
whirlpool all energy gate all vorticy in
whirlpool energy
whirlpool you
remember in whirlpool. You
remember all of you in whirlpool.
Oh, my last thought is I was going into this
my last thought is I was going into this
school and thought, "Okay, I'll enjoy
it, but I wonder how my mother will
think yawn." And I was sad for her.
yawn." And I was sad for her.
At bottom of whirlpool, all is
there. No one is gone. Everyone is in
whirlpool when you at bottom.
All come
together. E space term black
E space term black
hole. Oh, reality at bottom of
whirlpool. All is there. No one is a
part. Spain. Hey,
spirit guides of
specific nature for people human form
who still dream
alive. Dreamers on land live dreams in
and out through doorways. Walk and see
white spirit. Spirit is human. Spirit is dolphin. Spirit
dolphin. Spirit
is extra
tyrria. Spirit is energy light of world special
Spirit is energy light of world special
dolphin. Special dreams. Special humans.
Natural nature spirit.
Thank you. I I have one more question. I
I have been on the guided tour of Lion's
Path. Can you tell me where are you
going? Similar, Orca Path, Samurai of Sea,
Similar, Orca Path, Samurai of Sea,
Sorcerer of Sea, Orca, Black White,
Polarity to Swim. Orca path, lion path.
To live
bold, to live on edge of sorrow, to cut
through water, to cut through energy, to
cut through reality.
Bold expression, sharp and quick. No turning
expression, sharp and quick. No turning
back. Strong energy. All reality, no
constant foundation, no sea floor, bottomless
foundation, no sea floor, bottomless
depth of all eternity is lion's path.
Ancient dragon dream, dragon of sea,
dragon of air is lion's path. Orca be
dragon green dragon
dragon. Ancient wisdom be green
transformation emerald be of arts. arts.
We
sh dream
energy pod be all slumber play tonight your
pod be all slumber play tonight your
time. Swim and
shine. We play physical physical come
into water. Play. We swim. We touch.
Play. Our world. Your world. One world.
Bait. You. You.
I.
We. One world. Brother sister. B. And
one world, other world we
be, we love, we sand, we share.
All right. All set. Allow us to
continue.
Do I ask about um on Easter Sunday I was
out on a sailboat around and I was sure
there were nearly close to a thousand I
don't think I'm exaggerating white
Pacific dolphin. Okay. And I was going
to
ask some other significance to
that if there was a movement of energy
or why that was that large a grouping.
I've never seen anything like it before.
It was more and more the more you
collect of yourself together. The more
you create yourself to be a pod, the
more pods you will interact with.
Single interactions alone will no longer
suffice to represent the gathering
together of all the levels of the
consciousness that you
are. You will be in the midst of an
explosion of their ecstasy.
Yes. Use the energy. Let it accelerate you.
Use the energy. Let it accelerate you.
Ride upon the wave.
Beautiful. I see.
I see.
Thank you.
you. Thank you. I have two questions.
Number one,
first question is,
what is the specific nature and purpose
of the
pink Amazon River dolphins?
Some of this has been to some degree
relayed by Dreamer in the sense that
they represent nature spirit. They are
particularly reflective of what you
might call indigenous natives that still
live half in your third density reality
and half in fourth density reality. They
are the comingings and goings and
reflections in your reality terms of
different levels of consciousness that
communicate with the indigenous natives
in those areas.
Second question. I had a dream recently where I
question. I had a dream recently where I
was conducted to a place underwater on
the sea
floor and there was a
civilization extent there
um
biped beings humanoids if you will and uh they
beings humanoids if you will and uh they
were very busy. They had a a complex
organized society, very clean and very
efficient. And my question is, is this common on
And my question is, is this common on
our planet? Because I was told that this
was upon our planet and that those who
dwell under the
waves have not been in contact with
those who dwell upon the land.
It is not, let us say, uncommon.
However, simply recognize that those
dwellings do not specifically exist
within the exact dimensional frequency
you would call your own and therefore
they are not findable unless you are in
their frequency range. They are not
visible. They are not in your third
dimension specifically. Contact that has occurred
specifically. Contact that has occurred
has occurred in the same way you have
just described that manner in dream
reality. Since you bridge all levels of
frequency range, you can go where and
when you will.
One last question in regards to that
civilization. Do they have
interdimensional craft? Yes. Thank you.
Thank you.
Um first of all, I want to thank you for
the workshop that we co-created last
week. Well, thank you for co-creating it
with us. Um my consciousness has kind of
been like the best way I can explain it
is a strobe. Oh what wherein one moment
I will be aware of that I am third
density and then the next moment I'll
realize that maybe half the day is gone.
Hey already.
Hey you are sensing the flashes of the
creation of momentary time.
Um about the dreamer uh I sense that
this consciousness is strongly connected
to Neptune.
or in a sense. Well, I mean, it's the
same vibratory.
Yes. Although some of that vibratory
frequency perhaps would be more
appropriately felt through many of what
you would call the whales.
I'd also like to share a dream with you.
All right.
Um, obviously I enjoy astrology in the
dream state as much as I do waking
state. I had a dream where I was
receiving all different forms of
astrology that I was totally unfamiliar
with. Okay. But I I just accepted that I
understood it in the dream state. Um and
at the end of the dream, I saw uh I
became very lucid and I saw a craft, an
extraterrestrial craft, right? That um
had it was translucent. It was the same
ship that I interacted with in the green
state at 12, 11 and 12. And as it as it
passed over me, it was translucent and
it was there was a
rotating circular objects on the bottom,
right? And I synchronistically the next
day I went into a bookstore and I saw
the exact same craft on a book and the
author had stated that it was a
reticulum consciousness.
You are seeing overlays one level
reticulum but a stronger level
arurus. Okay. Is that is that connected
to my astrological information in any
way? Arcturus specifically. Okay. Thank you
Arcturus specifically. Okay. Thank you
very much. Thank you.
We thank you very much for being there.
Um, you were talking about polarity in
black and white. Exactly. And I have in
my in my astrological configurations, I
have a polarity of
Saturn opposing Uranus and the sun
opposing Neptune. And um, I'm I'm a singer and I
Neptune. And um, I'm I'm a singer and I
want to tune
into the frequencies to be a channel for
healing. All right. and I'd like to know
where I can say the science that I need
to the science.
May I ask you a
question? When you say you wish to be a
healer, how do you picture yourself
doing it?
By bringing the weight under I mean
physically, how do you picture in your
mind yourself doing it? When you say I
wish to be a healer, is there a picture
that comes up? Do you see yourself in
the act of healing? And if so, how are
you doing it? Describe the picture
literally in physical terms.
Communication of what
nature and writing. All
right. That is what excites you then.
Then do
it. There is nothing else you really
need to know unless you wish to create
another process.
which you can do. All right. Then use
your imagination for your imagination is
the key. What way do you believe would
be the most exciting way to go about
learning what you need to
learn? If you had a preference, if you
had the option, which you do have by the
way, but which perhaps I can play like I
am giving you right now.
And I say, "All right, there are things
you wish to learn right now at this
moment. You have the unlimited option of
choosing any way, shape, or form that
you think would be fun to learn the
things you need to learn." What would
you choose?
Anything at all.
Anything. Use that imagination.
Anything. You are now being given the
proverbial three wishes.
[Music]
to network with lifelines that I I might
not know now and I might know now. Done.
[Laughter] Look around. to to
to to
travel through all time to receive the
information that I can bring out. Done.
You have been other places before you
have been here and you will be other
places after you leave and everything
will bring to you exactly the
information you require at that moment.
No sooner, no later.
And to know what is necessary to know
what is
necessary. What is necessary to be a
healer is to act like you already are a
healer and then you will live the life
of a healer and experience all the
things that a healer experiences. So if
you wish to be a healer then now use
your ability to be a healer in whatever
way you can use it. That is the most
exciting way that is now available to
you. That will bring you into
circumstances and situations that will
give you whatever else you need to be a
healer and a channeler in any other way
you desire to be it. Using what you have
now lures you into circumstances that
gives you what you need for
later. You follow me? Everything is
connected. Everything plays a part.
There are no extraneous events in your
life. None. Staggering, isn't it? [Music]
[Music]
Everything is connected to everything
else because everything is the same one
thing manifesting in all the
simultaneous multi-dimensional ways it
can. So when you act upon whatever
manifestation, whatever representation,
representation it gives you at any given
moment that you can act upon. It will
always gently guide you into the
necessary circumstance to infuse you
with whatever else you need to do any
other level of what you want to do.
You follow me? So relax and look around
and examine what opportunities are
already available to you in your life
that you may not yet be acting upon
because you may think it has nothing to
do with getting you where you want to
go. You follow me? Do what excites you.
Thank you.
You
sure? Why I was at the workshop last
Sunday? Yes. And when you were asked to
go to our favorite place, your place of
perfect peace. Oh yes. I had two of them
at the beginning.
Nice balance. Now
there was a person actually two people.
Hi. In um the first I went between two
of them at the beginning and there were
two people in in the first one. All
right. And then I would go to the
mountaintop and then I would go back to
this other scene and then I eventually
stay in the
mountaintop and then I would come back
to the room because the room had so much
beautiful energy with it. But anyways, I
was wondering if you could help me
understand the significance of putting
um two people in um my perfect place
like this. Were they male and female? Uh
there was a male and I don't know the
death of the other one. All right.
It will do to represent it as feminine
if you wish and simply recognize it as
your opportunity to blend and marry the
relationship of the feminine and
masculine energy within you so that it
becomes one being you.
All right. Very good.
Yes. Well, the marrying of that
relationship within you will always
create a birth.
Will that assist you? Yes. Well, thank
you very much.
Hey, I have a specific question. How
specific can I be? Well, let's
see. How specific can you be? [Music]
[Music]
A question was asked earlier about the
lion's path. Hi,
there are three of us involved in in the
lion's path right now. What are your
feelings about the direction that is taken
taken
perhaps meaning to be
derogatory? There could
be a little more
boldness. There could be a little more
trust that it truly is a lion's path.
Does the lion stop to
worry or does the lion
live? Are the plains yours to
roam wherever you wish or are you on a
preserve and restricted
which? Those are the things perhaps that
we perceive you may wish to
consider. Is the world your
home or are you isolated within the idea
of
yourself? When you expand the idea of
who and what you are, all your ability
of communication will expand
accordingly. You will
contain everything else. And therefore,
any message that needs to be delivered
will automatically be delivered because
who you're delivering it to is no
farther away than you
are. And nothing is truly separate. The
lion does not really think itself
separate from the
savannah. The lion knows it is the
savannah. The savannah knows it is the
lion. Animals understand themselves as
the relationship they are in, not
separate from it.
How about that?
Does that serve you?
Do you wish to be more specific in a
particular
direction? Do you think that uh the
individuals involved in this lion's
path because they are
together? Do you think that's the
strongest creation creative point to
where we're going as far as being
together? What if I said no? Would you
believe me?
I would listen to you. All right. What
do you feel? All right. We are playing
this out at a certain pace for a reason.
If I said
yes, would you be more likely to believe
me than if I said
no? And if I may phrase it another way,
which one do you prefer to believe, the
yes or the no?
You've answered my question. Oh, thank
you. Yay.
Yay.
Oh, all right. Time's up. Okay.
You have to be quicker than that.
You tell me. I was telling you that
quick. Oh, yeah. When you say quickie,
we take you literally.
This is not even my question. I have a
question for two friends. All right.
Semiquicky. Okay.
Sorry. You You've been talking about
electromagnetic forces tonight a lot.
realizes and some question came up as to
whether or not it we know this whole
country with microwave mania. Um is it
safe to use microwaves? There are people
who do use them, people who don't use
them. Um what are your thoughts about
why all of a sudden microwaves have
become this microwave energy has the
specific characteristic whether it is used in
characteristic whether it is used in
certain directions or not to literally
alter the structure of
the structure of
material. This can be a causation and it
can be an effect as well of the
alteration of material.
Microwave energy represents the
manipulation of a particular spectrum of
light. That does have to do with your
ability to tunnel through, shall I say,
extremely colloquially
put, from one dimension of reality into
another. Microwave energy
represents the
ability to manipulate the structure of
matter. Represents the level of energy
upon which the structure of matter
begins to slide and slip and break down
and destructurize. This can be beneficial
destructurize. This can be beneficial
destructurization or it can be
destruction depending upon how it is
utilized. So when you say is it safe, it
depends upon the attitudes, beliefs,
scenarios and realities that have been
created by the individual utilizing it
for any particular specific purpose and
whatever other individuals buy into that
belief system and whatever other
individuals do
not. You as a being, as an
electromagnetic being always have the opportunity to
being always have the opportunity to
recognize that whatever vibratory
frequency your particular bubble happens
to be will determine what effect the
general electromagnetic spectrum in your
society has upon you. Whether you accept
it in or whether in your terms you let
it slide around your bubble.
You follow me? Yes. It is up to you. you
will find that there is a high degree of
recognizable microwave frequency in
connection with many of our spacecraft.
This is an effect from the stepping up
of the light energy that we use to power
the craft and is given off as a field
around the ship. Because that microwave
field is the isolation bubble that
allows our ships to unlock from one
universal reality and lock into any
other universal reality, allowing us to
redefine and relocate ourselves
instantaneously without having to have
traveled through space. Mhm.
You follow me? Yes. So, in the microwave
energy field, all universal realities
break down and can be rearranged in whatever
down and can be rearranged in whatever
pattern we impose upon it with our
vibratory resonance frequencies within the craft.
resonance frequencies within the craft.
We
melt, very colloquial, very colloial. We
melt the universe around us and
resolidify it where and when we want to
be. You understand? Yes. Yes. So the
choice of vibration vibratory pattern is
up to the individual.
Nice. Thank you. Thank you. Yes. And
then you Yes. Um, I have been
communicating with my bird for a while
now and lately speak up.
In what way?
Inside of you. How? like what he wants
to say. Uh it's it's like um he's
reflect I'm reflecting something in
myself and he's reflecting back. Yes.
Well, that goes on between anybody in
any relationship.
So if I'm reflect if I have something
that needs to be clear or he wants to
bring out, he reflects it back to me.
Yes. And you can take the reflection at
whatever rate you are comfortable in
taking it. No one is forcing anything
upon you. And simply remember that since
you are all mirrors and all reflecting
to each other, then nothing really has
the ability to actually get inside of
you and crawl around. All it can do is
reflect to you and you can let it bounce
off of your reflective surface or you
can accept the image in the surface of
the mirror you are, but you have to
choose to accept it in order for it to
be inside of you. No one can place it in
there without you creating your version
of it to exist within you. You follow
me?
Any individuals that interact are
mirrors for each other.
They reflect at any given moment certain
ideas and aspects that you have
attracted yourself to them to allow them
to reflect to you. Now this does not
always mean that when you see an
individual acting in a certain way that
they have to be an absolute one to one
representation of what you are doing in
life. But you still attract them to
reflect certain ideas and opportunities
to you so that you can reflect in return
certain ideas that they may need to
explore about themselves in that given
moment. You understand?
So simply take anything you are offered
simply as that an
offering not a forcing an offering.
Whatever vibratory frequency you choose
to be will determine which aspects and
how much of that offering you decide to
incorporate within your reality
structure. Anything that you do not
believe belongs there simply say thank
you for your offering but no thank you.
You follow me. Does that assist you? Oh,
thank you very much. One moment. The
female. Um, I had a dream two nights
before the workshop last week about
going up and down an elevator and huge
waves coming over it. And when I came
down at the bottom, I had pictures of
people that were on the beach and the
thought that came to me was I wasn't in
an elevator. I was in a craft and I was
taking pictures and this is what I was
bringing back as proof. Can you give me
any ideas of what was really taking
place here? At this timing, for now, let
us let it lie. There is more to this
understanding that will play itself out
in your dream
realities. Do not worry about it. Enjoy
it. Enjoy the ride. Enjoy the
solidification and reinforcement of the
reality. Enjoy dipping into the past and enjoy
Enjoy dipping into the past and enjoy
realizing that you are now where you
truly wish to be and that this is the
life you have been waiting for for
thousands and thousands of years. All of
you. For now, we will allow you to
continue to push the buttons on that
elevator and go where you will.
For now, for now, right now is the
timing for us to extend to each and
every one of you once again our deepest
appreciation, our deepest love and our
deepest joy at your willingness to share
and interact with
us. Exciting dream lives and life dreams
to you all. Wake up and live your
dreams. We bid you all a fond and
unconditionally loving good night.
Good night.
How'd it go? M
thank you all very much for being here
tonight. Thank you. And also