all right I'll say how are you all this
day of your time as you create time to
exist allow us to begin with an
interaction on the idea of Miracles you
may use that as your title if you
wish in this way recognize that what you
often consider in your civilization to
be Miracles you consider to be out of
the ordinary above and beyond the
mainstream reality that you are used to
experiencing in your day-to-day world
but recognize what typically call a
miracle is in actual fact a recognition
of the fundamental workings of the
universe it is a recognition of when
reality physical reality the experience
of physical reality as you have come to
know it is actually working in
synchronous harmony with all other
levels of reality and thus a miracle is
actually representative of when the
universe is working most naturally
physical reality the day-to-day events
that you typically experience that seem
to be different from what you call
miraculous that in a sense is even more
of a miracle than a typical Miracle as
you call it for a typical Miracle is an
indication of the natural state of the
universe when everything works hand in
hand absolutely flawlessly and can
create whatever manifestation is
indicative of the way the minds and the
hearts and the beliefs of the individual
involved in that circumstance wish it to
be whereas what you call your day-to-day
life is the product of Divergence many
times from the so-called natural
awareness or natural state of creation
natural state of reality and in that
sense the things that you most often
take for granted are actually the
exception to the nor in that sense the
way you have structured your reality all
of the different
diversifications separations and
specific Endeavors that you create in
your day-to-day lives those are the
miraculous manifestations of the
foundational energy your daily life is
therefore miraculous and when you see in
your life's what you normally call a
miracle when all of the normal what you
think of as normal activities that go on
are for a moment seemingly suspended to
allow this so-called Miracle to occur in
actual fact what you are seeing there
for is the very
fundamentals the homogeneous balanced
Natural Energy that everything in your
daily lives is Created from you follow
along therefore recognize that your
lives at any given moment are made of
magic if you will are miraculous in that
way and that what you typically call a
miracle is not something that is an
interruption in what you think is the
natural or normal way that life exists
but it is actually a manifestation of
naturalness a manifestation of the basic
root foundational energy out of which
all of the divergences in your daily
life are created a miracle is a calm
spot the eye of the hurricane as you say
wherein you allow all the different
energies the homogeneous energy of the
foundational creation itself to Simply
work in its purest form when you know in
that state that everything does fit in
with everything else everything does
work in life and a miracle is simply
your willingness to allow on all levels
all at once life and the universe to
work in the way it was designed to work
so if you wish your life to become as
you think more miraculous and for life
to become more and more effortless
expression of that level of creativity
then all you need to do is allow your
life to revert back to its natural state
to the zero rest balance point to allow
the things in your life to be there that
need to be there rather than thinking
you must make or force or push those
ideas into creation desire
determination those are tools that can
allow you to allow your reality to work
but desire and determination do not have
to be expressed in a struggle type type
of mode desire is the activation key
that will bring to you anything you
believe to be possible to experience in
your life and when you allow your desire
your excitement which is your indication
of your connection to the Primal energy
out of which all is created when you
allow your desire to bring those things
into your life then your life will be
effortless will be miraculous day to day
to day you follow along
at this time
therefore we will communicate in the
mode we call sharing
F ELC thank you very much I have a
couple of questions they're not exactly
on the subject you're talking on but
does not have to be never has to be all
right good uh it has been predicted by
Leah that in March of 87 there will be a
profound change in our economy do you
agree and is this change for the better
or for the worst the idea of what you
would call approximately March 15th to
March 17th will be a very strong energy
gate wherein many Transformations can
take place some aspects of what you call
your sociological structures your
economic societies may discover new
principles that will allow different
manifestations of inter relationships to
begin to be laid down upon your planet
any transformation can be experienced
and expressed in a positive and or a
negative way which way that manifests
depends upon the attitudes and
perspectives of the individuals involved
so it is up to you as to how it will
manifest but that time frame is a very
strong transformational energy gate
guys thank you the other question is
we're doing this documentary for public
public awareness do you have anything to
say regarding this first of all that you
are also doing it because of the public
awareness that already exists so
recognize that anything you find
manifesting in your reality not only
goes towards reinforcing the ideas that
you can do but is also a reflection of
the ideas you have already become so
first and foremost what we will say is
to extend from us an appreciation and a
thank you to your civilization for being
willing to come to the point in its
conscious conception of itself wherein
it is willing to discuss these ideas and
expand in many different ways the
exploration of your Consciousness will
be discovered to be the key to any idea
you wish to understand within the living
of your life and that fundamentally what
we will share with you is that the only
fundamental process truly necessary for
you to understand any anything you wish
to understand about life is to Simply
live the life you are living and in that
true and full living and expressing
yourself according to the tress of what
you know to be representative of the
energy each and every one of you are you
will in living that life discover
everything you need to know about the
life you are living for again the
universe does not do extraneous and
pointless things everything works and
there is a reason for everything explore
and expand your Cur osity become
fascinated with the interplay of all
ideas as they interact and interrelate
and you will discover that everything is
an orchestration and a Flawless one at
that Bashar thank you very much we thank
you for your Endeavor we thank you for
your sharing and your willingness to
participate and create an opportunity
for others to participate in the growing
expansion of awareness of remembering
that you are all made in the image of
the infinite Creator and what that means
is you are all infinite creators we
thank you all right
sh B hey a couple of weeks ago in the
times there was a article that the
scientist had found two giant ARS could
you care to
comment could you care to comment on
tell us a little bit about that we can
disperse but a little bit of
information what you are perceiving as
the ARs
are specific compactions of the
gravitational Dynamic tensor fields of
the physical universe that have
undergone what you would call vast
implosive energy you are seeing the
spin-off or cast off remnants from the
implosion of one portion of this
physical into and through a Gateway of
another physical
Universe thus the energies released are
quite a bit higher in magnitude than
anything you have discovered around your
localized area for in that area
therefore you are seeing let us say to
be colloquial in your language the
breach the gate the doorway from one
Universe to another and the after
effects of that implosion of the
creation of that gate a very powerful
gate these arcs therefore are
representative of how SpaceTime itself
has become as you say warped or Twisted
representative of the motion or the edge
or the currents now involved in that
particular doorway or Gateway you follow
me thank you thank you another question
last week you gave us some beautiful
information on
limitation is there anything you care to
tell us in regards to denial
denial denial in this way is again the
belief the inherent ingrained belief
that there might be something in your
life that you might come across that
would not be able to serve you but when
you recognize that everything happens
for a reason then you will know that
anything that happens in your life can
be used to add to the overall
understanding of yourself in a positive
way and allow you to expand and
accelerate in growth therefore denial is
simply the belief in your lack of
completeness in your lack of ability to
utilize in a positive way any that could
occur in your life it is a fear that
there is something within you that is
beyond your control that may get out of
hand as you say it is only a fear it is
only the result of the fact that your
Society has been taught that you are not
in control of your life therefore you do
not allow yourselves to be aware of why
the things that occur in your life do
occur and so because you think that to
learn more about them will actually
place you in greater lack of control you
many times will refuse to explore them
feeling safe and secure just where you
are not realizing that the more you
explore those things the more you will
have to add to your overall
understanding of yourself and the more
stable you will actually
become does that assist you yes very
much thank you very much thank you
sharing M hey in working with the uh
Lazarus tape that you uh mentioned to us
some a couple of months
secrets of manifesting what you want uh
in cleaning up the tools to use for
manifestation I find it uh I find it
difficult to find out what my payoffs
are and my blocks are quite large I if
you say
so I wonder if you can shed some light
on what why do you believe your blocks
are large and first and foremost what is
your definition of a
block the denial that uh I have a payoff
for a negative uh action in my life
denial that you have a payoff for a
negative action would you clarify that
please okay I'm um exhibiting lack you
are exhibiting lack yes I I don't have
the kind of car that I want and the
money that I want to do the things that
I want and I don't know he says find out
what your payoff is and I can't imagine
why I want to do this all right perhaps
one suggestion only a
suggestion to allow you to discontinue
looking at it as a lack and focus on the
things you already have so that you know
you already are abundant in one way and
that you can be abundant in other ways
rather than assuming that you lack
anything because if you are approaching
it from that end that point of view then
you are only reinforcing the idea that
you are not abundant that you lack
something approach it from the point of
view that you already are abundant in
whatever ways you have needed to be
abundant and that you can be abundant in
other ways more expanded ways rather
than assuming that just because you are
not right now abundant in a particular
way means that you lack abundance at all
you follow me so examine the other end
of your
tool as
well now it also does not necessarily
have to be that
complex it may be as simple as you
simply have the habit of generating that
particular type of scenario whether or
not there is any particular quote
unquote payoff whether you actually have
an ingrained belief that you need to
suffer you may simply be in the habit of
generating the reality the way you are
generating it so allow yourself to know
that you are in the process of creating
new habits now and that it is not
necessarily so that you have to dig and
scrape for this deep dark secret you are
holding from yourself beautiful you
follow me thank you yes I do if it is
that difficult to find a payoff maybe
that's an indication that there really
isn't one I love it
okay thank you yes thank you so lighten
up upon yourself and when you use the
tools that the tapes gests in order to
sculpt a new reality use a light touch
as well it is only the novice that
applies undo pressure and very often
snaps the tool you follow me yes I do
you do not have to dig quite so hard
okay thank you thank you Bashar
sharing hi Bashar hi um I I bought a
little toy today it's a tuning fork and
um like the way it moves you oh very
exciting very very very exciting and uh
I bought a little pitch pipe too and
just while I was sitting here I was
thinking um if there was different notes
cuz now I'm interested in using it to
heal possibly yes then you can simply
ask any other individual to stop you
when you hit the note that moves them
and that's the vibration you can work
with them on you follow me yeah whatever
strikes a cord within them will be the
key that unlocks them from the reality
that they have lived in before and will
allow them to now manifest the reality
they prefer so simply test it out with
any individual you are interacting with
which one do you like this one this one
this one oh that one all right then that
will be the key one when you hear this
therefore if this is the one that truly
strikes a cord within you you will know
that when we play this note you will be
at your absolute
most malleable most open most receptive
most willing to create the reality you
desire this will be your support field
and a support field it literally will be
you will generate the tonality and that
tonality the vibrations themselves will
function in much the same way as the
energy fields around our spacecraft and
will in a sense isolate that individual
from all of the reality habits that they
have previously been man esting and will
give them the opportunity to lock into
new ideas you follow me yes it is like
suspending them in a type of fluid
surrounding them with that
sound okay so there's not one or any
different note that's good for a certain
uh the individuals will let you know for
whatever it is whatever note hey every
individual is different and they are
different at different times can I use
this like over a body and said of just
by the ears yes oh yes especially over
the solar plexus
especially okay thank you thank you
chatting Bashar hey um I talked to you
the first time I talked to you was about
headaches I was getting hey they're more
consistent now they're about every other
day and you said it had something to do
with gravitational shifts on the planet
to some degree your sensitivity to
electromagnetic shifts okay I was just
curious about that the other thing was
when I was about three um I was playing
with a ball in our living room and the
ball rolled under our couch and I got
our maid to get the ball for me and
while she was I happened to look behind
me and through the curtain appeared a
figure a very tall stop
okay are you doing in your life what you
wish to be
doing I think on one hand I am and on
yes I'm which is researching more
into um myself in what way
spiritually bodywise how it all how will
you use this knowledge
physically probably to improve myself
and my life and those around me
how what me methodology is most exciting
to you I don't know I'm researching
quite a few different ones all right
which one has already been most exciting
to you which one stands out the
strongest now so far that has has helped
me the most the one you wish to
exemplify the way you wish to put into
action what you have learned how do you
wish to share what you are
learning how do you wish to be of
service I don't know yes you do I do yes
okay when you allow yourself to know
that you do many of these headaches will
cease entirely for you are receiving
entirely for you are receiving
communication I know I am yes and and
I'm aware that I have been all right I
dream all the time yes and and as a
matter of fact I had a dream about you
last night yes going to Germany I think
it is by the way do you plan to go to
Germany I plan
nothing okay
now the idea is that you are highly
receptive as we have said to these
electromagnetic pulses right and they
are being used to communicate with you
okay but the idea of the headache only
comes because you are to some
degree hesitating and resisting letting
yourself express it in the way you know
would be most joyous you are analyzing
the ways a little bit
so strongly that you are not truly
allowing yourself to give full fruition
full embodiment and full expression to
the way you truly do desire to express
it because you want to be very careful
in your mind you are being cautious but
to some degree you are being overly
cautious and this resistance and this
hesitation is allowing this energy
communication to back up within you and
creating the sense of pressure oh when
you are more willing to let it out let
it through trust your instincts rather
than having to rely so much on your
analysis process then you will allow
like a vow some of the steam
out you follow me I think so I'm I'm
just not certain when
it when it will be
correct there I go again right
yes now right right now let's use your
imagination right now okay let's open
those gateways up a little bit don't
worry it won't
hurt allow yourself now to imagine even
if your conscious mind thinks this is
only a game that's all right play along
imagine right now at least one way it
does not have to be the absolute
idealized ultimate and end all be all
way you could ever come up with right
now imagine one way that you would feel
happy in expressing what you are
learning one way that you would feel
most light and joyous in sharing and
being of service with what you are
learning one way one
idea speaking with others all right are
you already doing this yes to what
extent a little all right when you find
individuals in other words who are
interested you simply share ideas with
them yes yes all
yes yes all
right the knowledge you are learning how
else do you imagine it can be
applied other than speaking with I don't
know that's that's where I don't know at
this point that's not what's arrived yet
I don't know all right
when it does arrive how do you imagine
it will
arrive I'll know yes you
will now is it all right for you to know
that when it happens yes is it all right
for you to not necessarily consciously
know it
now yes are you
sure I maybe I may at the point where
it's about ready to arrive and I and I
sense it and all right the
regulation of the patterns to some
degree is an indication of a cohesion of
a
crystallization okay so yes you are on a
threshold right now
right will you do me a favor okay well
thank you will you take three slow deep
breaths not fast slow
okay in so doing did any even the most
abstract type of image come to you at
all just me just you just me just you
very good you unto
good you unto
yourself are absolutely
self-contained and all of the knowledge
you are discovering already exists
within you all of the
communication you are
having whether or not it is connecting
to what you might typically call other
Consciousness or not also comes from
you allow yourself to recognize
therefore that right now you are
complete and whatever definition of that
completeness you choose to have will
determine the rate and timing in which
you will manifest your unique expression
of that completeness
you yourself is all you
need you yourself in that sense is all
you have but it is all you need so in your
have but it is all you need so in your
search in your reearch
allow yourself to recognize
that there was you at the beginning and
no matter what or whom you connect up to
or with in your research there will only
be you at the end so to speak the
end and when instead of a
search it becomes an
expression then the energy will
flow for reearch is creating an
echo inwardly and the innocent headache
are a reflection of that
Echo when you let it
out then you will be channeling through
yourself rather than allowing it to
bottle up and channel back into yourself
constantly rearching for that part of yourself you
rearching for that part of yourself you
think you do not yet contain you contain
it when you let it out that is when you
will Discover it has been there all
along and you will no longer need to
search and research
you follow me yes you know what you need
to know when you need to know it yes and
at the same time everything you need to
know to be anything you wish to be you
know right now anything that you can
conceive of being at all right now
because you have the ability to conceive
of being that idea even the slightest
notion of that idea you contain all the
tools necessary right now to be that
idea because having that idea is an
indication that you do have the tools
for that level already
right thank you thank you very much more
and continuous pleasant dreams to you
thank you and the breathing the breathing will
you and the breathing the breathing will
also energize balance and alleviate a
great deal of the
pressure so breathe meditate breathe
slowly fully all right thank you thank
you yes good evening bishar to
you my question is in regards to
experiences that I have had on
spaceships all right were they fun oh
they were wonderful oh thank
you they were quite interesting guys I
feel that a time has come for me
to be more open about these experiences
and I have I have come to you to ask
suggestions and directions in how to go
forth to do
this recognize first of all that your
willingness to do what you are doing now
and share what you are sharing now is in
and of itself a first step for now you
are allowing yourself to let it be all
right for other individuals in your
Society to know how you believe you are
connected up in this Society you follow
me yes you have many many many
literature books that speak of many many
different kinds of
encounters physiological encounters
mental encounters and so forth the
physical Channel made you aware of a new
one this evening of your
time perhaps in reading
synchronistically of that account it
will allow you more understanding of how
to come forth with your own for it is in
that way written by individuals who have
that experience and those individuals do
form connections to other individuals
that have similar experiences and wish
to explore the entire
idea also whatever it is you have learned in
also whatever it is you have learned in
these experiences you can simply share
the information therein in a general
sense the principles apply what you have
learned the principles of what you have
learned in a general way to your Society
by sharing the ideas in ways that
individuals in your Society can make use
of so that they can get them to work for
themselves whether or not you define The
Source or label it is not important the
ideas the essence the tools it is what
is workable that is what is important so
simply whether or not you have to tell
anyone where you think the information
was learned share the information then
you will be acting as an example a
reflection for other individual to see
within you how this information works in
your life so that if they choose to
believe it can work in their lives they
can live it too they do not necessarily
have to know where it came from in that
sense for again fundamentally since it
was a co-creation it still always comes
from you I see you follow me yes I do so put
you I see you follow me yes I do so put
into action in whatever way excites you
the most the information share that with
people put it into action how you wish
to be of service in sharing this
information will be exactly the correct
way for you to share it and will be the
reason for why you were contacted I see
okay you follow me yes I do we also
thank you for playing your part in the
expansion of awareness in the
civilization into which you have chosen
to be born thank you could I have one
more question please that was it that
was it just
kidding you do not have to ask if you
can
ask go ahead I'd like to know why I'm
plagued with health problems plagued you
did play interesting
experiencing one idea is very strongly
connected to what you might call some
past life scenarios wherein you had an
inherent weakness
belief you have carried that inherent
weakness belief into this life to some
degree one of the main reasons was to
allow you to focus focus on the mental
attributes that have now brought you to
where you are and given you the ability
to form the communications you have
formed you no longer need that as a tool
for the communications have been
fulfilled in that sense they are now
ongoing you are doing what you need to
do in that sense you are on track and
therefore you can allow yourself to
realiz real eyes that you can be sound
of Mind and Body simultaneously and one
of the ways to realize that most
succinctly and most quickly is to
recognize that your mind and your body
truly not really are separate
things I see now let me share with you
one idea we have shared with many of you
of
late whether or not this makes
mechanical sense to your outer aware
Consciousness this will sink in on one
level and you may find that in your
dream realities or the way your life
plays itself out you will realize more
profound deeper understanding of what we
are about to say than it may appear on
the surface at this
time listen are you listening yes I am thank
listen are you listening yes I am thank
you
Consciousness does not
exist in the
body the body exists within your
Consciousness do you understand the
difference yes
then learn to feel the
difference learn to allow the
understanding of that difference to be
absolutely real for you for if your body
exists within your Consciousness then
your body is only the product of the
ideas and the beliefs at any given
moment that you are creating your
Consciousness to
be ask yourself
how does having the idea of imbalanced
Health serve
you if it no longer serves you then
recognize the only reason you may be
holding on to it is because of
habit because of the way you have been
taught to think now that you have formed
the connections that you have formed one
of the reasons for those connections is
to allow you to know that you are the
creator of your reality and that your
physical experience is the product of
what you believe to be true and if you
have a physical experience that you no
longer need then the only way that
physical experience can continue is if
the beliefs continue if the beliefs
continue it is usually only the product
that you are used to those beliefs being
the only beliefs you are familiar with
redefine the belief if the idea of ill
health no longer serves you then allow
yourself to say I will now receive and I
make the conscious decision now to now
receive any information I need to
receive in the easiest possible way
along the path of least
resistance and therefore I will not have
to create scenarios in my life that now
force me to look at things that I am
refusing to look at because I will not
allow the information to come subtly
when you do not allow the information
that comes to you to come subtly then
your body and your Consciousness will do
whatever it has to do to get you to pay
attention attention to the area the
aspect and the fragment of yourself that
you have created the message to come
from many times this will take the
manifestation of
disease because then you are absolutely
beyond the shadow of a doubt focused on
the idea that you are living at that
moment you are paying attention to the
totality of yourself when you can pay
attention to the totality of yourself
without needing the disease you will not
have it so the idea is to H iiz yourself and
it so the idea is to H iiz yourself and
recognize that body and mind are one
idea one
idea do not separate them any longer and
as strong as you find your mind to be
your body will follow suit you follow
yes now how do you
imagine yourself to be in what you call
an idealized state
how would you imagine you would be in
what you call perfect
health can you feel what it quote
unquote would be like yes I you have a
good strong feeling of what it would be
like yes I do all right feel it for a
moment let it completely wash through
your body feel what it would be like to
be
absolutely perfectly in health you do
know what it is like so feel it
absolutely experience it let that
sensation sink into every cell every
molecule every atom the spaces between
the atoms let it Infuse itself in the
energy field the electromagnetic field
that you are you know that matter is
energy and energy is matter yes yes yes
I do then allow yourself to think of
yourself for now if you believe you are
an outof balance material State then
revert yourself back to a homogeneous
energy state where no one part has the
ability to stand out from any other part
as soon as you allow yourself to melt
back into energy in your imagination
then you will be realigning the
definition of yourself you will be
defining the ideal blueprint of yourself
and then as you allow your body to
recrystallize from that energy State
allow it to recrystallize more along the
pattern of what you are now holding to
be the idea of what it feels like to be
in perfect heal in other words in your
imagination imagine yourself to become
the homogeneous blue white
electromagnetic energy that your
material is Created from in your
imagination float in that state be that
state see yourself as the blue white
sphere of transparent energy then in
that state impose upon that energy the
vibration of what you know it feels like
to be in perfect health then let your
body recrystallize along the new template
recrystallize along the new template
that you have imposed upon the energy
that you are and bit by bit as many
times as you need to do it but
absolutely definitely bit by bit you
will then reconstruct yourself according
to that idea that you know represents
your idealized state you follow me
yes enjoy thank you this is one of the
ideas that we will also be taking many
of you through within the workshop that
has been announced the idea of what you
call this Workshop will be as you name
it a self-empowerment
workshop and we'll focus on four primary
aspects all geared in building your own
understanding of self- creativity and
empowerment one will be bodily
alignment the second will be psychic
sensitivity the third will be creativity
and abundance and the fourth will be the
idea of Awakening and transformation
and manifestation into your life of the
ideas you know you
are these four ideas combined
together will allow you to experience an
a concentrated
form a time
frame that completely takes you out of
your typical preconceived notions of a
daytoday existence and allows you to
begin to rely upon what we have
discussed to be the miraculous
Foundation of creation
itself so these ideas we will assist you
with go through you with in terms you
call technique and
exercise and it will be in a highly
concentrated form but we
form but we
guarantee that your own imagination
always has the ability
to give you what you need if you are
willing to rely upon it and at the same
time when you are willing to let
yourself transform in these ways changes
will occur in your life at whatever rate
you are comfortable in allowing them to
change we thank you thank you enjoy the
meditation be vibratory energy for
everything is
simply that
sharing good evening Miss from
Miss from
Canada understand the idea is that we
are not speaking your language at all we
are only capable of using the vocabulary
inherent who the
who the
channel is Yes the channel not me
mer do you understand
us the channel I understand the channel
I understand the channel speaks English
your language English I am
speaking I am speaking of the higher
power we understand okay but you also
have definitions that you have been
taught yes I have been taught now I am
speaking to
you on one
onone I'm asking a question
ask all right I'm going to a new Venture
I commercial
advertising and product placement
in entertainment industry guys that's it
guys I'm asking that's it
what is my Venture going to end up with
or what will
I what are
my are you frightened yes why I don't
know that's why I'm asking you are
frightened because you do not know that
you have the ability to create the
reality you desire yes but recognize
that you do and that
therefore anything at all that excites
you the most is what you will be most
successful at if you put 100% of your
trust into it you see excitement is your
sign excitement is the energy of
creation and therefore when you discover
something that excites you the most that
is your sign that that is the thing in
life you actually can be most successful
at all you need to do is trust it and
act upon it and follow the excitement at
any given moment follow where the
excitement goes and you will always be
completely successful and abundant
excitement is the physical translation
of the connection to Infinite
Creation so if it excites you do it and
you will be successful if you find at
any given time within any Venture that a
certain aspect of it no longer excites
you then discover where the excitement
does lie follow it and even though it
may not seem on the surface to be
connected to what you think it should
connect to it is the excitement within
that scenario that lets you know
ultimately it is connected maybe not in
the way you have been taught to think
maybe in an unexpected route but if you
always follow with 100% faith and trust
and unconditional love whatever it is
that excites you the most all all things
that excite you will be able to be
accomplished in your life because
excitement is a thread that leads
through everything you need to do to
fully live the life you have chosen to live son
of sharing good evening bishar good
evening I've been coming to see you for
SE I've been coming to see you for
several months now and I haven't spoken
before this because I'm terrified of
speaking in front of groups all right
you are not alone in your Society did
you know something What that particular
fear is the number one fear in your
Society I would believe it so you are in
marvelous company in fact I've created it so well
company in fact I've created it so well
that I thought if I do not not get up
here and get through this
then I'm never going to get through this
fear so I'm here oh thank you very much
thank you for allowing us all of
us to be what reflects your own trust in
yourself to you we thank you for
showering us with such a beautiful gift
as your willingness to share for the
fear you have and the fear that any of
you would have about the idea of
speaking with other individuals or in
front of other individuals is only the
fear that what you have to say is not
worthwhile but you are a unique facet of
Infinite Creation and therefore because
you exist everything you have to say is
just as much an equal gift as anything
anyone has to say so we thank you for
showering us with the gift that you
are thank you and if it wasn't for the
boldness and the courage of so many
other people that have gotten up here
and done this then I wouldn't have been
able to listen to all the wonderful
tapes that I've listened to over the
last few months and caught up on your
last year and learned so much from all
of you and I just want to thank you very
much we thank you and allow us to remind
you of one
thing the you you used to be you no
longer are thank you
enjoy hi he my mother recently had a
contact a voice came very clear in her
head Alana I am your space brother and
she's been very upset ever since because
she doesn't know how to establish
contact and that was the only
communication that she got and she was
kind of nervous at the time all right
the nervousness therefore in a sense is an
nervousness therefore in a sense is an
indicat of the rate that will be let us
say most conducive for the next contact
however not all contacts are going to
come in that
method understand once again that no
matter what form a guide takes many
Communications will simply play
themselves out in your physical life in
other words walking down your street
overhearing a certain
conversation seeing a printed sentence
that makes sense to you walking up to
your bookshelf and seeing the one book
that gives you the information you now
need those are all forms of
communication from many different levels
you follow me yes so simply suggest that
she stop trying to pay attention to the
way it came before and simply get on
with the living of the life it is as we
have said the living of the life that
will allow any individual to know
everything they need to know to continue
living that life and the idea once again
and why many of these contacts are
sporadic in that sense is once they have
been let us say kicked into action the
idea is to realize that you do not need
those contacts to live the life they
then lure you to looking to searching to
exploring with your curiosity so that
you discover for yourselves that you
have the empowerment to continue the
acceleration and you don't need the
other individual to do it for you guides
are very tricky in that way they lure
you into more of
yourself you follow me yes so allow the
individual to learn to live in the
moment live in the now enjoy the life
they are in living that life to the
fullest everything they need to know
they will find out one way or another
one way or another it is simply the
opening of synchronicity in their life
the opening of the awareness that
everything in life is synchronicity and
that simply means that everything is
always in the right place at the right
time interacting with exactly the
correct individuals that need to be
interacted with to show you at any given
moment what the idea is you believe in
the strongest from time to time the guides
strongest from time to time the guides
will give a small hint a small
interjection in the most subtle of way
it may seem to be startling to you just
because it came in an unexpected fashion
but allow yourself to recognize that the
momentum has been set off and that if
that individual simply allows their life
to unfold and lives it that the momentum
will carry them uniring to the places
they need to go and if and when they
need Communication in that fashion again
it will be
there thank you thank you very
much hello Bashar
hello uh first I'd like to say uh I
experience great joy and excitement in
hearing the word from you we experience
ecstatic joy and excitement in
interacting with all of you thank you um
my question is I'd like you to discuss
an antidote or remedy for getting for
getting in the way of the true self
because of the personality we have
already done this to some degree yes
following what excites you the most is
what allows you to be the true self mhm
okay the medicine so to speak is that
simple all you need to do is take
it
right now first of all what may be quote
unquote getting in your way also is the
assumption that the personality has to
get in the
way personality is not who or what you
are it is an artificial construct and
therefore it is your artificial
construct what do you wish it to be
Define it and that's what it will be
Define the idea you prefer to be and you
are most excited about being at any
given moment and the Persona has
absolutely no choice but to become a
reflection a representation of the idea
you believe most strongly in you know is
you so the idea is to control the
personality as as opposed to the
personality controlling well in sense
but control may lead to conflict you do
not have to control it in a sense it is
already under your control it is your
creation MH you are already controlling
it you have never lost control your
personality at any given moment is
absolutely always a perfect reflection
of what you believe if most likely can
be it is always under your control and
has never been out of your control ever
H always it is a reflection of what you
believe most strongly that is why when
you see situations occurring in your
physical reality when you see ideas
occurring in your physical personality
it is not there to show you that you're
out of control it is not there to show
you you have failed it is not there to
show you you are stuck it is there to
show you what you believe and if you
don't prefer it change it your
personality will change accordingly to
whatever idea you know is who you are
but you have to truly know it and act
like you know it and trust that you know
it then your persona can change to show
you beyond a shadow of a doubt that you
do in fact know who you
are okay but you are never out of
control M even when you create the
illusion that you
are mhm you follow me yeah so first and
foremost lighten up on yourself lighten
up on your
personality it is simply a prism your
personality is a prism it has three
corners belief emotion and
thought those three corners form your
physical Persona the idea you are at any given
Persona the idea you are at any given
moment is the white light of your
homogeneous Consciousness it comes
through the prism and breaks down into
whatever type of spectrum you have
defined the prism to be so examine your
beliefs your feelings and your thoughts
and when you allow yourself to Simply
know that you wish to have certain
beliefs in a certain way then that will
Define your feelings that will Define
your thoughts that will describe the
prism of your personality and therefore
that will be the way the white light of
your homogeneous Consciousness breaks
down into the Spectrum you see as your
physical reality MH you follow me yes um
but but
uh I'm not sure what you mean by beliefs
all right beliefs is a patterned system
of perspectives of the situation you are
creating yourself to be in your
relationship to that situation where you
think you quote unquote stand relative
to any particular concept or notion how
you relate to it how it relates to you
those are your beliefs mhm
I
believe in the
idea of
disease I believe that if therefore I do
such and such it will result in such and
such and so it does you are setting up
the equation beliefs are simply
equations they are cause and effect
equations that is what your beliefs are
you simply say if a happens B Will
Follow That is a belief mhm you can
allow A and B to be any definition you
wish and when you redefine What A and B
are it changes the entire event you
follow me mhm and in many scenarios a
can go into the b space and B can go
into the a space it does not have to be
linear mhm cause and effect are single
event and one does not necessarily have
to come first if you create a strong
enough effect nature not allowing there
to be a vacuum in creation will supply
the cause to support the effect you have
created so that is why in life many
individuals as we have used this analogy
before will go through life absolutely
refusing to be happy until they find a
good enough reason to be happy a good
enough cause to be
happy if they would allow themselves to
perhaps come from the point of view that
they really don't have a reason to not
be happy and allow themselves to Simply
create the effect of Happiness then
nature will supply all of the causes to
support the happiness so act as if
actually yes
mhm that is it thank you it is believing
is seeing not seeing is
believing MH thank you very much yeah thank
you hello Bashar hello how are you
perfect and you fine you are perfect as
well whether you know it or not in your
own way you do not have to
try um my question is let me tell you a
little bit about
myself I'll be brief I'm just getting
into while learning about um New Age
awareness and I speak little louder okay
I'll speak up I can't help but be a
little skeptical that is all right we do
not care for you understand in your
Society it is the habit of the way you
think to think that anytime anyone has
something to share they share it because
they wish to prove something and we have
absolutely nothing to prove well I want
to find my inner light I want to find
myself and I want to spread my knowledge
to other people you go right ahead but
how do I know that that the people let's
see on my venture to find myself are
real real everything is in the sense of
people not faking something if you know
what I mean let me put it this way they
are quote unquote faking it or not if
what they share with you works for you
it doesn't matter who they
are and that is actually the whole idea
take what works for you no matter where
it comes from if it doesn't work don't
use it if it works use
it that's all there is to it you follow
me yes I do that is why why we are
coming now in the manner we are coming
because this way you don't have to
believe we are who we say we are and the
message itself is what is more important
not the
messenger because it has been the habit
of your Society to lock onto the
messenger and ignore the
message so take the message for whatever
it means to you use it if it work Works
find what works use it that's the idea
that's all there is to it that is what
is real what works for you is what for
you is most real what doesn't work you
don't need to think about it right now
if it works for you later you'll think
about it
then you follow me yes I do now also
allow me to point out one thing what you
call skepticism many individuals in your
skepticism many individuals in your
Society think all right I'm going to be
very scientific I will be
skeptical skepticism is not a scientific
attitude objectivity is skepticism is a prebuilt bias
bias
objectivity is balanced objectivity says
all right here's the
concept how does this apply how can can
this be applied what can I learn of it
one way or another what in this concept
will work or won't work for me
skepticism says this is
hogwash I will therefore go in exploring
this with resistance already rather than
an open balanced objective point of view
nothing is truly ever truly objective
everything is always subjective but you
can create subjectively an objective
attitude but skepticism is not
scientific and any true quote unquote
scientist will be the first to
understand that because if skepticism
were a scientific tool there would be
very few things you would ever
discover so when many times individual
in your Society say that they are
skeptical many times it is simply a
misinterpretation many times they are
being truly objective but many times
when individuals think they are being
objective they are actually being
skeptical which means they already have
a builtin belief about what it is they
are approaching you follow me yes I do
thank you and also allow us to remind
you that because skepticism is a
built-in belief then quite often
skepticism will only be able to manifest
in life the result of that belief in
other words I Told You So and when you
get the manifestation that lets the
individual say see I told you so that's
an indication that the only reason they
got that manifestation is because they
to begin with believed that they were
going to be able to say I told you so so
it is a self-perpetuating
prophecy thank you for your sharing you
are the path you need to be do not
forget a path is not what you are on a
path is what you are you cannot be off
of
yourself enjoy the path you have created
yourself to be we thank you for sharing
that idea with us at this timing we will
suggest that you all enjoy a short break thank
break thank
you hi how's everything [Applause]
going all right I'll see sharing
hi and different things but I still feel
that I'm not going to make it can you
help me make it in what I don't know the
purpose for me is wa learning something
here and I you are learning by anything
that you do everything is a valid tool
everything if you are going through life
perhaps simply looking for a few
specific things you may Overlook the
fact that everything that happens in
your life is there for a reason
everything even though you may have
created specific manifestations that you
desire to unveil in this particular life
the living of this life in the fullest
way you possibly can is the actual
fundamental purpose of this life because
whether or not you have ever lived
before whether or not you will ever live
again you are a reincarnational being
but you will only be this you
once so in that sense you do you do only
have one life to live as this you
therefore living this life to the
fullest is the purpose of this life
within that life there may be many
things you truly desire to do therefore
many individuals when they go through
life looking for a specific thing that
would seem like the purpose of their
lives create difficulty in finding that
thing because they don't recognize it's
up to them to decide what that thing
is anything that excites you the most is
the purpose that you will decide to do
and you will be there for fulfilling the
purpose of your life because you will be
living it as you say to the
hilt so what excites you the most what
do you want to
do anything that you have experience
will simply add to your ability and
knowledge to let you do the things that
excite you the most so whether you are
exploring as you have said macrobiotics
or yoga or eing or astrology or science
or religion or economics or politics or
any of these ideas they are all tools
they are all different ways to learn
more and more about yourself the
fundamental reason being to do what you
wish to do learn learn about yourself in
all these different ways so you can do
the thing that excites you the most in
the best way that you can so you must
make the conscious decision as to what
the quote unquote fulfillment and
purpose in your life will
be you follow me yeah what excites
you sailing and sailing and sailing and
sailing and sailing and sailing and
sailing all
right then why not
sale I'm just taking a
break do understand that you can be of
service to other individuals even while
you are enjoying sailing you could be
teaching them how to sail you could be
sailing them places they wish to go you
can be of service to many individuals by
doing what it is that excites you the
most and making a living at it just
because something in life excites you
beyond anything else it doesn't doesn't
mean it's not a valid way to make a
living so follow what excites you the
most when you know you are fulfilling
the person that you are within integrity
and are willing to be of service to
those that may require your service then
you will be able to fulfill in service
to other individuals and in turn the
individuals that need your service will
only need the service that will allow
you to be who it is you are and you will
not be expected to be anything
else so do what excites you the most and
at any given moment act upon whatever
opportunity comes to your life that
represents what excites you the most
that you are capable of acting
upon that's it that's all you need to do
and you will be supported in complete
and total
abundance you follow me yeah that makes
sense thank you thank you sail away
Sherry good evening Bashar good
evening uh this is my first time to hear
channeling such as this is my first time
here welcome thank you it is um a great
pleasure and very exciting to hear the
simple questions turned into very deep
and philosophical and wondrous
answers I have a extremely simple
question I would like to uh contact fact
um an ancestor of mine a great great
great grandfather is such a thing
possible such a thing is possible
however first of all recognize that many
individuals that in your terms have
physically died some time ago may
already be reincarnated and physically
alive again also many times even if they are
again also many times even if they are
still non-physical there will be many
things that they will be learning in
their own Realms and in a sense they are
not focused in the same way that they
used to be towards the Physical Realm so
contact between you may not necessarily
be as blatant as you may think it has to
be or as blatant as you think it should
be however no matter what state any
particular portion of an individual is
experiencing at this time one portion is
always contactable for every single IND
individual whether you can understand
this technically or not is existent
within every other single individual so
that portion that represents that
ancestor to you exists within you and it
is quite possible to have dialogues with
it and it will be just as real as
talking to the original idea because
everything is simultaneous you see when
you think well I have to talk to this
person and to do so I must reach back
into the deep dark recesses of time
break through these barriers stretch
myself across the fabric of these guls
and chasms in order to reach them then
you are not understanding that linear
time is your illusion and that all lives
exist now but are simply in different
orientations so that one life may not be
aware of another
life one
moment what is the time frame of that
individual the time frame of what is he
was born in
1763 may I tell you slight about
him not yet all right he was he lived
until
1840 what is your present age
61 are you discovering something
something now within your life that has
to do with either trade or what you
would colloquially call
Magic I have been reading uh books uh
that would
be based in uh psychic phenomena
lately uh trade magic I'm not sure all
right what is the idea of psychic phenomena to
what is the idea of psychic phenomena to
you what does it mean to be
psychic there are things that are known
that uh that I don't consciously
know when uh when someone can express or
accomplish uh something in a realm that
I don't consciously understand I
consider that a psychic phenomenon now
you have described an effect yes but
what is
it what is it to function psychically to
psychically to
uh I don't know all right what is the feeling all
feeling all
right functioning psychically is simply
empathy identification with another individual
identification with another individual
it is in fact a type of being in
love now when you are in love in that
way and identifying fully with another
individual you adopt a similar pattern
of vibratory frequency that similar
pattern of vibratory frequency allows
you to interpret the energy of the
universe in the same or a similar way
that they interpret it so you create in
your mind similar thought
patterns it is not that you're actually
reading their minds you are in a sense
mimicking their minds to know what they
think that is how psychicness
functions when you create a
link with any other individual no matter
when they physically
live then you are identifying not just
with them but as them and conversely
many times individuals that you find yourself
times individuals that you find yourself
drawn to will many times be an
indication of an extension of the same
energy you are already identifying as
that individual now to some degree not
absolutely 100% a literal continuation
of on every level but on many levels we
are perceiving that your energy is a
continuation of the energy you have
describ in other words you are The
Reincarnation you follow
me I believe I heard
you will that suffice for
now yes thank you therefore if you wish
to have a conversation with that
individual will talk to
yourself talk to that aspect of your
mind that represents that vibratory
identity and you will be in communion if
you will with that identity thank you sh
Bashar yay why in this present day uh are the
yay why in this present day uh are the
Arabs experiencing so many difficulties
and why do they seem to be so maligned
in this country
there are many many sociological
structures that they have created for
themselves to mold themselves into many
many reasons for which you do not have
what you call the time for us to go into
in great detail but basically you will
find much of their energy in many past
incarnations has been put towards the
idea of
warfare and in this way therefore they
are jostling to understand themselves as
a different expression learning that
they can express the power and the
energy that they feel so naturally
connected with in terms of the earth
they can express it now in more positive
ways they are learning the
balance many and this is one of the
reasons now we are not saying this is
absolutely exclusively so but one of the
reasons for part of the physical channel
background being Arabic is because that
particular manifestation played a in past lives
manifestation played a in past lives
with much of that culture in that area
as to how the original Orion Energy on
Earth was assimilated into your
culture a very very strong Orion
Incarnation was the historical
individual you call Sargon of
akad this individual is recognized in
your history as being responsible for
the creation of the Arabic
Empire there for it is founded on many
Orion principles in that way therefore they
principles in that way therefore they
are struggling simply because they
believe as the Orion did in those times
that to struggle was the only way to
express and understand the self and do
it through the idea of conflict they are
now beginning to assimilate into many
other cultures that allow them the
opportunity to recognize they can blend
and balance that energy in a positive
way and it does not have to be a
struggle or a conflict of ID ideologies
and that the blending of all ideologies
is what will actually paradoxically
allow them to express their own ideology
the easiest is this making any sense very
easiest is this making any sense very
interesting thank you thank you very
much you didn't answer the second part
continue why are they then why are they
so maligned in this
country maligned again is only the idea
that individuals are placing judgments
upon other individuals which is the same
thing as saying they are placing
judgments upon aspects of themselves
they do instinctively represent many
ideas of that conflict and many times
individuals may sense this and may Place
upon those individuals as a scapegoat so
to speak the aspects of themselves that
they are also in conflict with you
follow me yes I do so the assimilation
of the cultures in an equalizing way
will allow them to express themselves
and allow your or culture to express
Itself by recognizing that any Unity you
wish to experience upon your planet will
be the result of granting equality and
validity to the infinite diversity of
the different cultures upon your planet
relative to the way they choose to
expresss and their understanding of
their relationship to Infinite
Creation assimilation of culture would
you explain the blending the sharing of
Concepts from one culture to another so
that one culture culture does not have
to continue to think that their way is
the only way to understand creation and
that there are many different valid
tools that are existent in other
cultures that can be learned from and
that you are all connected on that level
as one culture
anyway you follow me good thank you very
much thank
you hi velle one moment s
you had a very empathic and strong
incarnation in that culture perhaps more
than one but one that we are perceiving
as what you might call a
princess in the Arabic
culture many of your years ago and that
may have something to do with some of
the connections you are perceiving
within yourself now and it may lead you
into expressing those aspects of yourself
continue on the last day of uh 1986 I
was in a metaphysical bookstore and I
saw a man that I seemed to recognize
very strongly and he had the same
feeling about me and so he many times
this is an indication of past life
connection I figured that was something
to do with that um
now last weekend I was due to meet this
this person um at a local convention but
it turned out that the person who was
going to can you speak a little louder
certainly okay um the person who was
going to give me a ride to this
convention uh her car I guess
conveniently broke down all right and so
we didn't get to meet and I went to see
a movie instead the movie I saw was
called Vagabond it was about a French
girl hitchhiking around France and in a
sense it was a movie about someone
searching for total freedom but in a
sense creating out of it total
loneliness now the movie really struck a
cord within me because I'm about to make
a journey soon myself and I've
experienced similar things when I've
traveled before then it has strengthened
you by giving you an opportunity to
recognize that now that you have seen
how one individual may have translated
the idea of of being alone into a
negative aspect you now know that you do
not have to prefer that and you can gain
powerment from the idea of your
aloneness definitely this is what I was
feeling as I left the movie house on the
way home I created an interesting symbol
that I feel was an instant demonstration
of this um
douch I was walking down the street and
a car pulled over and a man wound his
window down about an inch and he said
I'd like to ask you a hypothetical
question so I wondered what's Happening
Here what am I doing and so I said would
you wind your window down a little bit
more so I can hear you and he wound it
down a little bit more not very much and
he then said I would like you to get in
the car and drive around the corner and
he pointed to a a around the corner
where it was dark
and assist me in mentally torturing
myself and giving me ideas of how to
physically torture myself all right
something on that level basically nice
and I got kind of you know my first
impression was well this is interesting
and um do I want to pursue this or not
and I chose not to pursue
it um
however however as I was walking away I
realized that if I had made the choice
to go there or even invite I had the
feeling that maybe I could have invited
him to my house and talked with his
being and and shared some of the ideas
that I have about or that I have
experienced to do with struggle and pain
all right now I'm changing my own ideas
all right um in thinking about this it's
right um in thinking about this it's
reflected to me this is my version I'd
like you to share whatever you feel all
right about it um you were speaking to a
fragment of yourself continue I I felt
that I was seeing a myself before so to
speak and the the window was in my
opinion was representative of the old
aspect of myself only wanted to open the
window a little bit but I wanted the
window all the way down very good and so
that I could reflect to the old portion
of myself and unify the old portion with
the new portion your trust in
vulnerability as strength not as
weakness that's what I was thinking
thank you we thank you for such a loving
conversation with yourself and the
opportunity for the future self you have
now become to send information to the
Past self you were to allow them to
harmonize with
you we thank you for your creation of
simultaneous synchronicity in your life
rather than facing yourself along a
linear track thank you there are more
track thank you there are more
convolutions and pliable manifestations
of time that many of you may encounter
from this point
forward where you can meet yourself
coming and
going in all the reflective ways that
you need to to be the fullest possible
manifestation of the being you now know
yourself to be in this present
reality
sh hello um I'm tomorrow I have to
decide whether or not to quit AC School
One Moment One
Moment tomorrow you what have to if I
want to get you have to
nothing now what do you want want to do
tomorrow I'm not sure I'm I'm not sure
what excites me the most in life all
right what are your
options well I oh let me phrase it this
way is there any one thing that excites
you the most that you are more capable
of doing than any of the other things
that excite you the most or are there an
equal number of things that excite you
that you are also equally capable of
acting upon right now
well which one is more accessible to you
in terms of the tools you already
have um I'm not I don't know what I'm
good at doing really that's not the
question I asked
you you are good at doing whatever
excites you the most or it wouldn't
excite you as we have said when you feel
excited it is the excitement that lets
you know this is what you are good at
doing that's what excit excitement is
for So when you say well this excite me
but I don't know if I'm any good at it
it's a contradiction it's an
impossibility the thing that you are
good at is what excites
you if you weren't it
wouldn't well um nothing much excites me
right now this is another
contradiction you have just said there
were several things that excited
you no I I didn't say that I don't did
she say
that you said you had several choices
well I can quit school um if I do I'm
not sure what I'll do what would you
like to
do the only thing I can think of is just
to yes yes yes quit school and just see
what comes up all right if that's what
you find exciting do
it I was just hoping that you could
hoping hoping is not knowing hoping is
despairing hoping is I'd like to but I'm
not sure that's hope I hope I hope well
it would be nice if but that's hope
knowing is knowing this is what moves me
therefore this is what I am therefore
that is how I will act therefore this is
what I will
do now even if you create in your life
and unknowingness of the thing that does
excite you if you at least know what
does not excite you then you can start
there by ceasing to do that thing and
when you cease to do the thing that
doesn't excite you you will then make
room for the thing that does and then
you will know what it
is okay I think I'll try that you will
what
um I'll change my vocabulary first all
right understand your vocabulary many
times is an indication of the way you
believe and it is no accident that you
choose the words and phrases that you
did yes so either you will do that or
you will do
trying which do you
prefer I think doing it all right then
you don't need to try do it
okay or do something else well thanks
for the encouragement well thank you but
you see the idea is that whether you
choose to or not we believe in you
utterly beyond the shadow of a doubt
because we know you create your own
reality beyond a shadow of a
doubt therefore it is no effort for us
to encourage you because that
encouragement is only a reflection of
what we we know you're already capable
of you follow me yes thank you very much
to allow us to reflect back to you what
you do already know thank you enjoy all
right thanks
shoting Bashar hey I have been impressed
with your wisdom tonight mine it's yours
thank you it's ours
together I am the mother of two very
fine teenage girls all right and I would
like very much to hear your views on
parenting all of
them as many as we have time
for all right first of all do remember
and recognize that you do make
agreements to be in the families you are
in the children agree to be born to you
you agree to have them born to you and
so on and so forth so they are there
again for a reason no accidents no
accidents and the familyes that you are
closest to in any one particular life
you have been closest to in many
different lifetimes perhaps taking turns
being the parent being the child being
the cousins being the relatives you
follow me of course being the friends
being the business
relations in this way therefore allow
yourself to recognize that at any given
moment if you simply allow yourself to
be the fullest possible being you know
you are you will then be fulfilling in
the best possible way your part of the
agreement you will be being the person
they agreed to be born
to and then you will show them in no
uncertain terms as an example as a
reflection that they can also be the
individuals that agreed to be born to
you and you don't have to play the idea
of any games of definition you can
simply trust unconditionally and
implicitly that what you will reflect to
them will allow them to be who they are
what they reflect to you will allow you
to be who you are and together who you
are naturally will blend and work and
mesh and will not create conflict you
follow me I do does that assist you
certainly does anything else no thank
you very much oh thank you very
much hi Bashar strawberry how you
doing uh been having a lot of fun lately
um I find that the drives for specific
manifestations in my life have been
Vanishing I no longer have any great
drive to fly on carpets around the world
and uh there no why not I don't know
it's it's sort of like all there's a
blending of all of all it is in
Universal love this all right but you do
have an overall Drive oh yes a very
strong one oh you remember that
one uh did you want to comment on that
one no except that perhaps all of the
individual idiz drives are consolidating
and backing that
one you are pulling in some of the
expectations and allowing them all to
become
expectancy that's nice thank you thank
you Bard
um is
it I don't want to use the word
necessary let me see the way is all
right all right we'll use the
word to Encompass the reality of of of
all of the people in love in order for
us to start flying around on carpets
again in brooms at Halloween and and
goodies of this sort to actually
manifest these in our culture it does
not require the entire culture or even
the majority of a percent for do
recognize that there are single
individuals that have allowed themselves
to be capable of those
manifestations but since this is the
transformational life and since by
definition you do wish everyone to share
in the understanding of their ability to
create their reality then it may take a
percentage of A Sort but this is
changing this is growing and that
appropriate percentage is being
approached wherein you will allow your
lives to be miraculous and magical but
again as much of an example as you are
willing to be that you can be at any
given moment will increase
let us say the odds got you how do you
see the momentum in in actually being
able to manifest some of those sorts of
things as we would measure it in linear
time there appears as we perceive the
energy now now
15 to
24 of your years from now will see see a
large increase in expansion in things
that were formerly considered
impossible from that point forward there
will be geometric or logarithmic
expansions accordingly lovely delightful to talk to
accordingly lovely delightful to talk to
you the again and you B
you B
hey I chose to experience something to
learn something very specifically and
consciously well how wonderful yes
um perhaps not perhaps not Perhaps
Perhaps I didn't need to do it because
it didn't really excite it doesn't
excite me necessarily the most now but
any perhaps you needed to do it to find
out it doesn't excite you I
[Music] know all right but but the point is I
know all right but but the point is I
would like I'm not even sure I would
like I just want to know if it's
possible to do what to for example I was
supposed to do something and supposed to
no no no I was going to all right and
because I felt that my beliefs were not
in a place that were real capable of
attracting the money that I wanted from
this big game show I decided to postpone
it all right by calling in sick all
right so what kind up for me is this issue of
so what kind up for me is this issue of
integrity and for some reason it's very
it's a biggie for me a biggie a biggie
for me for you for me Y and what I
thought this what I thought was tanino
it's you have it too much it's it's just
a little bit too rigid for you you're
too free let go of it so much you know
let loose da da da lie every once in a
blue moon you know do this every once in
a while big deal and yet going
back getting to be on the show now guys
what I'm afraid of is that I might be on
the show and in the back of my mind or
whatever wonder whether it was sincerely
something that is for me or if I should
let it go do you know what I'm saying
because of that lack of
Integrity all right will you do me a
favor mhm will you recognize now that
you have taught yourself that you prefer
to manifest Integrity yes you now know
beyond a shadow of a doubt that you
prefer Integrity over lack of Integrity
yes
um it was a lot of fun but yes all right
yes it is your choice yes all right when
you allow yourself to come to the
realization that choosing lack of
Integrity has now allowed you to
understand that you prefer Integrity if
that's what you truly
are then when you make that realiz
ation there is nothing to
forgive continue from that point as if
that were
zero and everything that comes after
will be based upon your new
understanding regardless of anything you
have ever done if you use what you have
done in a positive integrated way
understood thank you
um okay one other Quicky on that subject
on um oh Quicky after a biggie after a
biggie um well let me the fear fear the
fear not well the fear that I have is
that I don't want to be righteous then
don't but still be within Integrity well
yes of course just because it feels good
inside it's not about being righteous
self-righteousness is simply the
assumption that what you have to say is
better than what anyone else has to say
so in other words being Integrity is
equal to being out of Integrity it's a
matter of preference Integrity is
knowing that what you have to say is
worth sharing but that no one else has
to
listen you follow me yeah that
everyone's point of view is equal to
your own everyone has their own way of
doing it you can share when you attract
into your life a situation that makes it
obvious that someone wants you to share
what you have to say but simply
understand that that is simply to give
them an opportunity to decide for
themselves what is best for them and
therefore you are being a service to
them self-righteousness is the
assumption that what you have to say is
the only way that they will learn what
they need to learn okay it is your
way it is not necessarily a way they
will want to share with you but
paradoxically when you allow what you
have to say to be equal to what they
have to say more often than not you will
find yourselves heading toward the
synchronous Harmony
anyway you follow me it's not really but
it's okay all right I mean sort of in
other words the more Integrity you allow
the more Integrity you are allowed to
express so you will wind up finding
yourselves thinking the same thoughts
anyway ultimately because when you allow
ultimately because when you allow
Integrity on your part and allow
Integrity on their part then the view
point of Integrity is by definition a
coming together a
blending so when you allow each and
every person to have their separate
point of
view then you create the Paradox of
attracting those individuals to you and
saying I like the way you let me be who
I am and by paradoxically letting me be
who I am I find that we actually think a
lot alike you follow me yeah but I don't are
alike you follow me yeah but I don't are
you saying anything specifically that
I'm not catching to me do you know what
I'm saying this is not a game
show there are no hidden answer I am
being both specific and general and as
simple as I need to be there is nothing
hidden in this message that's it okay
thank you for playing thank
you do come again
by the way you already have the biggest
possible prize
you all right thank you sharing hello
Bashar hello um voice channeling came to
me rather quickly and without quote um
human instruction right I'm wondering if
there is something that I can do to
enable Spirit to come through me more
easily for them and also possibly so
that I would not filter as I feel that I
sometimes do the more you use it the
more you will allow an ACC climatization
to take place that will allow you to be
of service so be of service use it apply
it
knowledge does not really serve until it
is
applied you follow me yes so serve use
what you already know in service and you
will create the conditions necessary for
you to blend and for them to blend with
you in an easier manner you will set up
the atmosphere that is conducive to more
blending by being of service you channel
the energy through into your reality and
change the atmosphere of your reality to
one that is more conductive of the
channeling to become more sped
up it is a self-perpetuating
system you follow
yes that is it thank you be of service
in whatever way excites you the most you
will simply attract into your life an
opportunity to allow you to be of
service if that's what you decide you
want to do it will be
obvious thank you thank
you chatting hello hello when you create
chatting hello hello when you create
your isolation fi around your spacecraft
and redefine the SpaceTime coordinates
to relocate to another u space time
coordinate very good right um can you
Define the SpaceTime coordinates in such
a way to transport back to what we call
our past or our future that is can you
move to planet Earth in 15th century or
SpaceTime is one thing traveling in
space is traveling in time traveling in
time is traveling in space it is one
thing however recognize that everything
will still fit in place even from the
apparent linear point of view and that
any so-called change ches that may
appear to take place within any previous
Time Track that you came from will
actually not be taking place in that
Literal time trck but in one parallel to
it you follow
me so exactly what do you experience the
same thing that you would the effect is
basically the same in other words you
could step into your craft go back in
time do something if you are assuming
that you wish to quote unquote change
the way something happen happens then
when you make that change if you go back
to the exact same time trck where you
left off there will be no apparent
change because the change that was made
was not in your time trck by definition
because that's not what happened in your
time trck the change so to speak is not
a change it is a part of the normal
history of a parallel Time Track so if
you wish to see the effect of the
so-called change you must go to the
future or go back to the present of the
parallel Time Track that you made the
change in you follow me is this making any
in you follow me is this making any
sense so what I will have to listen to
the tape you have time track a Time Track B
tape you have time track a Time Track B
time track a is your time track let us
say all right your history all right yes
no maybe yes all right time track b is
another history all together
everything is occurring
simultaneously therefore let us say time
track a and Time Track B are very
similar very
similar the idea in this way is that if
you leaving this point in your time
track a go back to the supposed
past you are actually going into the
idea of another time trck and being a
part of its history in a natural
Progressive Way you cannot actually
literally change your own past in the
same linear coordinate system when you
quote unquote change your paast you are
simply shifting gears into another time
trck that contains that ability to
change so you will have the experience
of that change in your new
present you cannot change
history you alter yourself to another
history that is appropriately
representative of the change you desired
to
make more correctly and the same applies
to moving to the Future yes how exactly
do you create the isolation field it is
a microwave energy effect that as an
alteration of light stepped up many
magnitudes above what you typically
think of as an electrical discharge it
is dispersed through the whole of the
craft through various devices after the
lightest stepped up by other various
devices one of which we call the flash
Matrix which incorporates many different
elements the isolation field will be
seen to be a microwave effect microwave
generation at that high rate of speed
will disconnect any object within the
bubble from the universe in which it
existed because you in that sense match
the vibrational frequency in a very
highly condensed way of the speed of
light itself the speed of life being the
barrier limit that represents physical
dimensionality when you create around
your craft a wall a shell made of the
very substance of the physical Universe
light then you with in that shell have
created a bubble a hole in that
Universe you follow me you are
redirecting the light out of which
everything is made around you rather
than through you you are now sustained
by the Primal template Universe which
exists on a completely different
frequency far above and beyond the
frequency of
light therefore in that Universe you
literally are everywhere at once so you
can be anywhere and any when you want to
be can this be done with our technology
now yes how do you do it have a piece of
matter bombarded with microwaves no you
will find that many individuals are
working on this idea now listen to your
media listen to your literature many
individuals are beginning to explore an
experiment and they will come out with
what you call public notification of
many of these ideas basically it
involves the idea of counter rotational
masses that are highly magnetically
charged that will generate the field of
which we are speaking in a fundamental
way fundamental enough to allow the
isolation to take place more
sophisticated control will come from the
generation of these fields through more
highly conductive
materials thank you thank
you there will
be but a few moments remaining for these
interactions this evening of your time
continue hello Bashar hello I want to
reconnect with you at the wizard level
yay uh I'd like to get some input from
you or share with you anything that you
might want to offer on my my journey
with the
wizard it's your turn to do the offering
now that is what we will share with you
if you are connecting with us on the
wizard level offer as a wizard okay um I
had this um uh channeling experience in
which there appears on a stage a an
entity which is a seems like a
combination of a potbellied stove and an
individual like a living guys do
understand that one of the things you
have been manifesting as the wizard is
to be in touch with many different
definitions and many different aspects
of your own overall Collective
Consciousness personality you are
becoming familiar with many of the
different symbolic ways in which your
own higher Consciousness can be
interpreted in your Physical Realm so
that when you know that your
Consciousness can manifest in any type
of symbolic form then you will know that
any type of form is Manifest in your
physical reality because everything in
your physical reality is only the
product of your Consciousness once again
it is an analogy to the idea that
Consciousness does not exist within your
body your body and all physical matter
you experience in life exists within
your Consciousness so now you are
playing the track in your consciousness
of all the different ways different
portions of yourself of your higher
Consciousness can take form can take
shape you are Lear learning malleability
and in learning malleability then once
the understanding is inherent within you
you will be able to express that
understanding outside of you in your
physical reality and allow many of these
so-called inner symbols to actually
literally physically take form in your
outer reality and that is when you will
function physically as a
wizard that sounds good yes okay at this
uh as this is going on off to the left
there appears to be an intense energy
source and it's so intense that it's
covered over with a Darkness to protect
all in the room who were uh present at
the time that is all right it is simply
the white light of your Collective
knowingness your connection to all that
is and to Infinite Creation and your
recognition of perhaps what you still
believe to be the necessary filters that
will allow you to take that white light
and break it down into the components
you need to explore so it does not all
come rushing in all at once and in that
sense you won't be able to make too much
physical sense of it you are simply now
recognizing that you have set up a
device through which that white light
can come in a manageable way so that you
can explore at your
leure you follow me yes I do thank you
thank you very
much good evening B good evening I'm
suffering medically problems all
right back pains all
right for how
long they come and go periodically come
and go yes for how long have they been
coming and going two days at a
time for how long 6 months now six
months upper or lower lower
what are you doing in
life I don't understand what you're
saying Ian are you doing in life the
things that excite you the
most obviously not does not have to be
quite so
obvious do you think you are or do you
you think you are not I am not why not
you know we do not mean in your terms to
seem redundant or repetitive but you
will find that many times many of the
pains and diseases you create in your
reality usually stem from many of the
same reasons that you will simply not
allow the knowing ecstasy that you are
to move you and when you hold
back then many times you create strain
and pressure because you are fighting
what you know is your natural
self if you continue to believe you must
support that weight it will cause a
strain in you physically it's not an
ailment not specifically it is more
attention it can manifest as an ailment
but to us there is really no difference
between an ailment and attention dis
ease understand the breakdown in your
language disase is literally that dis
ease no matter what the idea of the
physical carrier of the so-called
disease it is always generated and
attracted into your life because of
disease with yourself all pain physical
pain emotional pain mental pain and
spiritual pain is the result of the
cutting off of a portion of yourself
from the rest of all that you are so
that that portion is not deriving the
nourishment from the total whole are you
relating it to unhappiness in a sense
thank you so in this way allow yourself
to begin to recognize that you are
attracting into your life the situations
in your life for a reason accept and
acknowledge that you are choosing to
experience the manifestations in your
life in the way they are coming for a
reason allow yourself to delve into why
you would wish to experience it in this
way what are you learning learning from
it what is it forcing you to face and do
I need it you do not need it if you are
willing to allow yourself to face the
messages that it
delivers for the only reason many
individuals create nagging pain is
because they will not pay attention to
the messages when they are delivered in
subtle forms and when they ignore those
messages then the messages and the
Messenger will have to be delivered in a
nagging way so that you will pay
attention once you pay attention very good
once you pay attention very good
laughter will Center you and release you
very good your laughter is an indication
that you are willing to trust yourself
trust that whatever comes to you is
there for a reason and as soon as you
allow yourself to begin to pay more
attention to what you know within your
heart is true for you then you will open
up you will listen you will allow the
energy to flow through you and not
become blocked up within you because
you're not willing to trust
it what in life excites you what do you
or have you always wished you could
do what if you do it in life will allow
you to be the happiest you could be
what anything I chose to be I guess what
happy what do you want to do in life succeed
what do you want to do in life succeed
at
what H you are already a success at
life how do you wish to express it and
share and apply your success in physical
terms well success is nothing unless you
have someone to share it with
wrong thank you and that is the only
time I will ever say wrong for there
really is no right and wrong however in
one sense you are also correct but you
may be approaching it let us say
backwards the idea of
needing another individual to share it
with before you will allow it to be
something you will enjoy is what usually
prevents you from attracting anyone in
your life to share it
with because you are saying I am not not
complete I am not enjoyable as I am and
if that's the message you're giving
who's going to want to come and share
that when you say I am complete as I was
created at any given moment the things
that move me in life are just as valid
and equal and as important as anything
else that moves anyone else and when you
know you have the ability ability to be
the relationship unto yourself that you
have been created to be you will shine
as a complete reflection and that
shining and Radiance is what will
attract into your light like a beacon
individuals who will wish to share your
Radiance by reflecting it back to you
but until you shine as you are no one
has anything to reflect and share with
you of that radiance
I thank you very much I thank
you at this
timing allow us to extend to each and
every one of you our
appreciation for the opportunity to
share in the Consciousness you have
created yourselves to be open up in your
dream times and many other
Communications will be found to be
ongoing there all the time
we will therefore once again remind you
that within your physical reality wake
up and
dream because this is your dream created
to be what you prefer it to
be we thank you and extend to you a fond
and unconditionally loving and
ecstatic good
night night
how did everything