Okay. What this is for me, what I think it is,
What this is for me, what I think it is,
how it happened for me, which is uh will
lay down some structure um that will
probably be talked about a little bit
later on in terms of some of the
principles that are going on here. Uh
for well, what I'm about yeah, what I'm
about to say to some degree is
consolidated on these blue sheets. So if
if you want a transcription of uh the
general series of occurrences that
brought this about, they are available
right over here on the table um which
you can pick up after the session.
Um, basically my understanding of most
channelings is that they're the product
of an agreement or an arrangement that
is made prior to the physical life
itself between the person that's going
to become the channel and the
consciousness that you're going to be in
touch with or whatever aspect of
consciousness you're going to uh be in
touch with or have agreed to allow to
come through you. A lot of that
preparation or agreement itself is
actually done prior to the physical
life. Not that it has to be. You can
make that agreement at any point. Just
depends on your desire. But when you do
make such an agreement, especially if it
is something that that was made before
the life, then the circumstances in your
life usually take on whatever kind of
arrangement they need to to steer you
and guide you into learning the things
you need to learn to prepare yourself
for the fulfillment of that agreement.
So, of course, how everyone gets there
will be different depending upon the
lifestyle that they're living and what
it is they need to learn.
For me, the biggest turning point was
about 14 years ago on two different
occasions within the span of the same
week with four friends present with me
the first time and two friends present
with me the second time, we had very
close physical broad daylight sightings
of Bashar spacecraft over Los Angeles
here. What I didn't understand then,
aside from having seen what everyone was
calling a UFO, and what I understand
now, is that that sighting of his craft
was his way of tapping me in the
subconscious memory to start really
learning the things I needed to learn in
a more accelerated way. Spurred on by
that sighting, I began delving into more
research in metaphysical and UFO issues
and found a lot of them to be quite
intermixed. Um eventually I learned about mediumship
Um eventually I learned about mediumship
just by reading books and some at some
point somebody introduced me to several
mediums who were practicing at the time.
One of the entities coming through one
of those mediums offered to teach
mediumship for whoever was interested
because several people were. I took them
up on the offer not even then thinking
that this was something I was going to
wind up doing. I just wanted to learn
more about it because I had read all the
books I could get my hands on and there
weren't anymore at the time because this
was uh about four or five years ago.
When I was in that class, however, in a
receptive state under the guidance of
the other entity through the other
medium is when Bashar and his people
made the telepathic connection with me.
As soon as they did, the memory of
having made the agreement came back. Who
they were, who I was to them, what the
ship sighting had been about, dream
conversations I had had with them for
years that I totally blocked out of my
mind up to that point, all came flooding
back into that one memory. What came
with it was their first real time
telepathic message which was now that
you remember that you made such an
agreement now is the time to fulfill it
if you still want to. Do you still want
to? So obviously I said yes because it
is a choice. It's never something that's
pushed upon you. And that was about 4
years ago and I've been doing it since
then. Now Bashar presents himself as a
member of an extraterrestrial community.
They do have a physicality of sorts and
some of that is described in the sheet.
Um the word itself Bashar is not
literally his name in their society.
They're pretty much telepathic and they
do not have names as such anymore. Uh
they do not even use their language that
much anymore. But he chose it because he
knows we use names to refer to people.
It makes our conversations a little bit
easier. And the word is actually an
Arabic word which is partly my
background which is why he chose it. I
had no idea what it meant or that it was
a word at all when he did choose it. But
it has several meanings and all the
meanings basically apply to who and what
he is and what he's doing. One meaning
is that it is commander which is
something similar to what he is in his
society. Another is simply the man or
the being. A broader definition of the
term is the human race. And the fourth
meaning that I'm aware of is that in
Armenian the word Bashar means
messenger. So even though it's not his
name, it obviously applies to what it is
that he's doing. Now, one thing I like
to stress, especially to new people, is
that I have my own validation and my own
sequence of events that led up to me
believing that this is what it says it
is. That's the easiest way for me to let
it do what it does is by flowing with
whatever the information is. it comes
out about about itself and how it
presents itself. But what I like to
stress is that there's absolutely
nothing in this interaction whatsoever
that insists that you have to believe
that it is what we say it is because
right now we can't prove it to you
anyway. Bashar has said that in time,
maybe within the next 10 or 20 years,
there might be an opportunity as our
society changes for their societies to
be able to literally interact with us
more and more blatantly face to face.
But right now, they're doing it this way
for a lot of good reasons. And one of
the the primary ones is that they have
noticed in our society that we usually
at least in the past have a tendency to
lock on to the messenger and not hear
the message. So they're remaining
unobtrusive in the background. So you're
not forced to believe that they are who
they say they are. So you can decide for
yourself whether the information works
for you or it doesn't work for you. The
information is the most important thing.
And the basic gist of all this
information is to put you back in touch
with the power each and every one of you
have to create the reality you want, not
to hand your power over to him cuz he
doesn't want it. He's got enough of his
own. So, he's here to reflect to us the
idea of things that have worked for
them, things that give them joy and
perspectives that allow them to know
they are equal co-creators with the
infinite and to help reflect that back
to each and every one of us. But it's
not something that they, you know,
ultimately care whether you believe or
not. They're doing it as an offering, as
a service because it helps them as well.
So whatever you get out of it will be
what you put into it. And he's only
going to reflect just that. He's not
going to pull anything from you if he
feels you don't want to let you know,
share it in public or bring it out in
the open or deal with it at this time.
Whatever you put forth is what he's
going to deal with you on. Um if and
when questions come up in this
interaction uh two basic things to
Bashar there is no such thing as a silly
or a stupid question. So please don't
hold back just because you think you
might be wasting someone's time. Uh
everything serves everyone. It's a gift.
And if there is something he's talking
about especially today because I think
he's going to be talking about a lot of
concepts in specific terms. If there's
something for some reason you're just
not getting because it's new to you or
the words are coming out strange, um,
don't let it slide. Say, Bashar, wait a
second. Could you back up? Could you use
an analogy? Could you explain it another
way? He wants to know that you're
getting out of this what you want to get
out of this. So, by all means, make sure
that this is your time and you get out
of it what you want. Um, basically the
way that's done is just very informally
just say out loud, Bashar. If two or
more people say that at the same time,
he'll call on you in the order that he
has perceived that you've called out. Uh
so it's a very informal and uh direct
interaction in that sense.
When uh I'm going into the trance or the
altered state, basically what I will ask
you is to just remain silent um when I'm
going in and when I'm coming out. And
when he says goodbye, don't all start
talking all at once cuz I'm there's
nothing tiring or depleting about this.
It's actually quite energizing for me,
but it's very disorienting. I'm not
focused as the persona I normally am at
all. I can't think in the trance, so I
don't really hear the words. Um, but I
do feel the interactions. I am conscious
that there is an interaction going on. I
see pictures which are mostly abstract,
and I feel energy and emotion. And it's
it's sort of like having just this giant
stream of electrical energy running
through you constantly with all the
variations and fluctuations that are
represented by whatever type of
interaction he's having with you. For
me, it's more like listening to music um
in the sense that you shut your eyes and
you let it overwhelm you. But um
when he says goodbye, if you would just
remain quiet until I reconnect and
reorient and refocus, it'll just help me
a little bit with the silence. It's a
little bit jarring if everyone starts
talking as soon as he says goodbye
because it's like trying to wake up in
the morning in your own bedroom and
having a whole bunch of people shouting
at you in your face. So, just give me a
second. I'll let you know when I'm back
and then you can do whatever you want to
do.
No, no, no. When when I mean when he
says goodbye at the end of the entire
thing that then he's gone. Any chance
anything you want to ask by all means
ask during the thing. Yes. He's gone.
It's too late.
That's okay. Um,
okay. Also, um, see, I don't know if
there's anything else that really needs
saying at this particular point before
we start. Are there any questions about
procedure or anything you need to know
before we begin? Yeah. Sure.
Growing out of the back of your head.
Oh, okay. and become and become
different
from transmitting the information
because the fundamentals do stick and I
understand the basic mechanical
principles that he's talking about. Um
so I am radically different today than I
was four years ago. Uh my life I would
say in general is a lot simpler. things
happen in my life far more obviously,
more transparently, more coincidentally.
Um, I don't have I mean I'm always
growing and learning just as anyone
would, but I don't have, you know, like
real burning, mysterious, puzzling,
struggling type of questions, you know,
anymore. So, yeah, it's changed
drastically in that sense. Yeah. Where
are you originally from? You mean where
was I born here? Yeah. Did he uh do you
know that? Has that been said? In other
words, are you from
Oh, Esasani. Yeah. Okay. Um, Bashar can
explain the idea about origins to him.
The idea of giving yourself an origin or
recognizing a particular origin point is
not always something that that can be as
as literal as we may think. However, um
my basic understanding of the agreement
I have with him is that it does have to
do with connections I have to some
ancient systems in the Orion
constellation. Now, Essasani in a sense
has they have called themselves our
future selves and Bashar literally has
called himself directly my future self.
So, that's a connection to the same soul
in the same way as well. I don't know if
it's a literal thing that can be
interpreted directly, but one way to
look at it would be as if I have a
future incarnation as him which has the
ability to come back in time and speak
through its past self. It can get a
little mechanically weird to think about
it that way, but that's one way to look
at it. So, he lives in a different time.
He's in a different dimensional plane
and time for them is not exactly what it
is for us. Uh so there's a little bit of
difference in terms of how they relate
to our time zone. So no it's not it's
not direct but he can sometimes
understand what the flow of time is
that's going on here just because of he
has because he has access through my
consciousness. Yeah. Do you think that
uh then you and he would you pursue as
one? Yes. On one level because I was
going to ask his comprehension of a
physical body. Yes. Well, he has a
physical body, but the thing yeah, this
is a telepathic connection as I
understand it. But what he has said is
that because he is alien, if it if he
didn't have this past life in our
society, he wouldn't have a model
through which to understand us very
well. So a lot of times when
extraterrestrial consciousness does do
this kind of thing, they have had at
least one or more lives in that society
at some time. So they can at least have
a foundation through which to understand
otherwise he said we would be so
different and so alien in concept that
he wouldn't he wouldn't have any way to
help relate to what's you know going on
in that sense but even though I perceive
him to be an individual I know we're
aspects of the same oversoul so to speak
yeah no he senses he doesn't really see
no he senses he doesn't really see
directly he has said he senses us as a
series of relationships to each other
literally he defines an individual by
all the the ways you're connected to
everyone else. So he sees everyone sort
of like a crossroads of all the
different lines coming from everyone
else. So he can see how you're connected
in that sense. That's what he reads off
of. How about him?
Pardon me. If we have some sort of
connection with him or with somebody
from a lot of times he will see that.
But it's just a matter of him sort of
reading the energy and he will usually
only know what he needs to know in that
moment. So if he's actually put blocks
on himself to make sure that whatever
information he has access to is not
something that interferes with a process
that you're going through that he
doesn't want to spoil the surprise. In
other words, he doesn't want to spill
the beans. If there's something he feels
he shouldn't be telling you, he'll
automatically find that the information
will not be accessible to him.
Then the whole idea of this is not for
pop psychology, but it's really for
inner world. Oh, absolutely. All of us
realize that we can achieve something. I
mean, the new I sense the movement from
everyone I've worked with the last two
days. We're all we all channel. Yes. Oh,
everyone does. We're to awaken to the
fact that we can do it and no longer use
you. Yes. Absolutely. Matter of fact,
directly what Bashar has said is he's in
this job to put himself out of a job.
Exactly what he's doing. So, thank you.
Yeah, that's okay.
He can speak. He can speak generally. He
can speak specifically. It all depends
on what the interaction is that's going
on and what serves everyone the best.
Obviously, he has a better opportunity
to speak specifically if it's one-on-one
because he can get more intimate with an
individual on that level. in a group, he
will usually tailor for the group
anything that any specific individual
wants to know about so that everyone can
at least apply it however they need to.
Okay. All right. So is he married
only he has said in the sense that they
consider their entire civilization to be
married to everyone in their
civilization. It's not a it's not a
ritualistic thing. They are born into a
family which is their entire world. So
basically, so again, thank you and uh have a good
so again, thank you and uh have a good
time and I'll see you all later.
Have a nice trip here. Thank you. [Music]
[Music]
All right, I'll say how are you all this
day of your time as you create time to
exist.
Allow us to begin this interaction, this
day of your time
with the laying down of some more
foundations for what we will be
discussing within the interactions that
we always have had with you. The idea
basically fundamentally that we have
termed mechanics of metaphysics will be
outlined as follows.
We have recognized that many of you are
exploring different aspects of your own
consciousness, different ideas. You are
now realizing your consciousness to
always have been. You are rediscovering
things you have forgotten about
yourselves. In that sense, reawakening
in this what you call your
transformational or if you wish your new
age of awareness upon your Earth
civilization. Now these rediscoveries
Now these rediscoveries
have of course been rising within you
through the belief systems that you have
laid down through the patterns of
thought that you have laid down through
the definitions that you have laid down
for thousands of your years in the time
of forgetfulness. So many of the
terminologies you may now be using to define or
you may now be using to define or
represent the new discoveries you are
making sometimes in and of themselves
may not necessarily precisely define
what it is you are doing. You will avail
yourselves of the symbols that have
always worked best for you and will
apply the symbols you are familiar with
to the feelings and the experiences that
are new for you now to at least give you
some footing to at least have some
reference to these things that are
occurring to you. But many of these
older definitions sometimes bring with
them the older meaning you have given to
these definitions and many times do not
precisely describe the actual mechanism
of what it is you are now discovering
you are capable of experiencing within
yourself. Are you all following along so
far as this translating into your
language adequately?
Well, thank you. Now the idea therefore
will be to outline
some new definitions of things or to
rearrange, shall we say, some of the
older definitions in a new format that
can perhaps give you some new insight,
some new perspective on the definitions
that are representative of our
perception of the ideas you are now
experiencing on your planet. Allow me to
remind you what we are sharing with you
are our perspectives. They do not have
to be your perspectives. We have
invented in our interactions with each
and every one of you. A little motto as
you call it. It goes as follows. Do not
believe anything I say just because I
said it. Allow yourselves to listen to
the information
picking up on whatever vibration
represents what you believe is a tool, a
process, a technique, an idea that will
work best for you at any given moment.
As always, your imagination in itself is
the key and we will be talking about
that in a few moments as well. But
within this interaction, begin by
relaxing into your trust of yourselves.
relaxing into the understanding that you
will gain. You will receive anything you
truly need on whatever level you need to
receive it. You will not miss out on
anything that you truly need. There are
many levels of communication going on
within this interaction between
ourselves and yourself. Not just what
your ears are hearing constitutes the
entire interaction.
There will be vibratory feelings that
will pass through you. And let me remind
you, many of you have assumed that what
you are feeling is my energy. It isn't.
It's yours. We give you a mirror, a
template, a particular frequency which
we do radiate. But if you can feel it,
it means you are choosing to match it
with your own energy. So first and
foremost do remember that everything you
experience in this interaction it is
your choice and your creation to have
that experience because as far as we are
concerned you are all equal to us. We
are not better. We may have what you
call colloquially an expanded point of
view simply because of the differences
between our civilization, our
experiences, our history and your own.
But the idea does not mean that we are
not equal in our utilization of energy.
Every being is a 100% being. No more and
no less. And you are always using 100%
of yourself. even if you're using 90% of
it to make it seem as if you're only
using 10%.
Now, that to some degree is an analogy
of the definitional reality you have
been playing along with for several
thousand of your years. But it doesn't
mean that you are actually literally out
of control. Even though you may have
been able to create scenarios in which
it seemed you were, you are always in
control of an outofcontrol scenario. On
one level you are choosing it. Now when
we say you choose your reality, you are
creating your reality. We mean it
literally. But many times we have
perceived individuals in your society
because of the old definition that you
have of some of your words will say,
"What do you mean I choose everything
that happens in my reality? I would
never have chosen to get hit by a car.
Why would I choose to do that specific
thing? Now, sometimes it can be a
specific choice. But when we say you
choose your reality, we do not literally
mean necessarily that you specifically
choose a particular way in which it will
manifest. What we are talking about is
that your belief systems and whatever
emotions are strongest within you will
draw to you the type of physical
experience that most precisely
represents the basic idea or image or
belief you hold of yourself to be most
true. You may have a general definition
of yourself and you will simply attract
in specific physical terms in specific
physical experiences the one experience
that represents the path of least
resistance that is capable of fulfilling
or manifesting or reflecting to you the
general belief you have of yourself. It
is not that we are saying you
definitely, precisely, and specifically
desired to be struck by one of your
automobiles. But if an individual may be dealing with
But if an individual may be dealing with
ideas and issues perhaps of safety or
unsafety, of victimhood or nonvictimhood,
of victimhood or nonvictimhood,
of fear on many different levels, that
where they are is not a safe place to
be, then that fear in and of itself is
what will attract the most likely
occurrence to reflect to show in no
uncertain terms to that individual. that
they have that they harbor those type of
negative beliefs.
Situations that happen in your life,
circumstances that are the reflections
of your physical reality, they don't
happen to show you you're stuck. They
don't happen to show you you're a
failure in life. The circumstances that
happen in your life, the physical
experiences that you have happen to show
you what you believe so that if you
don't prefer it, you can change it. Your
physical reality is what you call your
feedback mechanism.
So that every single moment of your
existence as a physical being, you will
constantly be giving yourself an
opportunity to gauge and measure what
belief systems you are buying into
moment to moment to moment. You are not
lost in life. You are not out of
control. The things that happen in your
reality are the reflections of what you
believe about life. the quality you
believe life to be. So you are always
given by yourselves an opportunity
through the events in your life to
determine whether or not the beliefs you
have are the beliefs you want to have.
They're not there to show you you're
stuck with what you've got, nor that you
have failed in your life, but to show
you how free you actually are. Because
at every given moment you have the
opportunity to know precisely what your
strongest belief is because your
strongest belief must always be what
manifests around you in physiological
reality. You all follow along so far. It
is a very simple thing, very very
transparent are all of you to yourselves
if you would but allow your definitions
of life to be clear in that sense to
allow yourself to know.
There is absolutely nothing
you could ever experience, nothing you
could ever discover about yourself that
cannot be applied in a positive way.
Absolutely nothing.
Every circumstance,
every situation,
they are all fundamentally blank, all
fundamentally neutral,
devoid of meaning entirely.
No circumstance and no situation has
builtin meaning. They are props in a
sense, surface features in a sense.
You are taught to assign meaning to
them. So automatic does this process
become that you automatically believe
that when a circumstance occurs.
The meaning you immediately perceive is
the meaning that automatically comes
with it inherently. But it doesn't. It
is neutral when the circumstance occurs
and you automatically assign the meaning
that you have been taught to assign. The
meaning you assign to the neutral
situation is absolutely, totally and
utterly what determines the effect you
get out of it.
Positive meaning in, positive effect
out, negative meaning in, negative
effect out. We will use briefly an
analogy we have used with many of you
before. It is called your train station
analogy. You're all familiar basically with the
You're all familiar basically with the
device you have on your planet. You call
a train. Yes s
you are to the best of your ability and
fully within your intention and
integrity rushing to meet one of your
trains because you have a very important
meeting. This meeting will turn events around in
This meeting will turn events around in
your life in the direction you really
prefer. So you know you don't want to
miss that meeting.
So, you are doing your best to make sure
that you meet that train.
You arrive at the train station. You are
on your platform. You look down the
track and there goes the train.
Now, anything
anything
now decision number one, automatic
assignment number one, negative meaning.
I've missed my train. Oh no,
this is horrible. Terrible. A
catastrophe. Oh, miserable day. Now I will never make
Oh, miserable day. Now I will never make
that meeting. I will now never be able
to do what it is I really want to do.
That meeting was so important.
I am now going to be very angry that I
have missed that train. I am now going
to be judgmental about the whole
situation. I am now miserable. I am
furious. Depending upon the type of person you
Depending upon the type of person you
are, you will either hold it within
yourself and allow yourself the idea of
negativity simply within your own life,
or if you prefer company, you will stomp
off to the train station to complain,
making everyone else's day just as
miserable as your own.
Now, away you go. Stomp, stomp, stomp,
as you say.
Scenario number two. You arrive on the
platform. There goes the train. You're
not on it.
Neutral situation.
Now you say to yourself, second choice,
positive affirmation.
I know because I have chosen to know I
am a positively manifesting person.
Because I know that I also know there
really is no such thing as an
interruption in the path. I am.
Everything that occurs in my life
because of the decision I have made
about who and what I am must therefore
by definition be a part of the path I
chose to be not an interruption in it.
Therefore, this circumstance somehow,
even though I do not intellectually know
how, must serve me in a positive way. Oh
joy, oh joy, the unexpected has
happened. Now I am giving myself a wonderful
Now I am giving myself a wonderful
surprise. I wonder what it will be.
So as perhaps your demeanor being a
little more calm, a little more
ecstatic, decides to ponder all the
positive reasons for why you might have
missed the train, knowing that you did
your best to get there.
Because you are pondering, you stand on
the platform a little longer than you
might have had you gone stomping off in
anger. Standing there a little bit
longer allows you to feel a tap on your
shoulder. And you turn around and lo and
behold, a friend you have not seen
perhaps in 10 years who has just gotten
off the train was coming into town to
surprise. and they are somebody who actually
and they are somebody who actually
serves what you want to do better than
the person you were going to meet. Now I
understand why I miss the train so I
wouldn't miss you because you, my
friend, actually represent more
precisely and more realistically the
path I chose to be and the service that
I can provide in life and the service
you can provide to me. Too good to be
true? Oh, that's just a coincidence.
What a fairy tale. Life isn't like that.
Oh, yes it is. Life works that way
exactly when you let it because
everything is connected to everything
else. Synchronicity co-incident not accident
Synchronicity co-incident not accident
coincident.
a simultaneously manifesting incident.
Doesn't mean it's an accident.
It simply means they're parallel,
tandem, interactive.
You have
built into you, I shall say, all of the
vibrations of all the possible and
probable realities you could ever
experience in your life.
The vibration, the emotional vibration
you are at any given moment utterly
determines which of those probable
realities will be the one you manifest
into physical experience. You are
holographic in nature, holographic in
structure, which simply means every
point, every place contains the ability
to manifest any part of the whole at any
time, anywhere.
The vibration you are utterly determines
which aspect of the holographic hole you
experience to be your physical reality.
Positive in Positive out, negative in,
negative out.
Your imagination
is the template, the blueprint for all
the probable realities you could
manifest. Emotion
Emotion
is the activation switch. Emotion
energy motion is the activation switch
to the blueprint of your imagination.
Your imagination is the library of all
the things that could be and are in a
sense simultaneously existent with you
but simply are not being immediately
applied in your particular focus of
dimensional experience but could be.
Your emotion determines which of those
blueprints which of those templates will
be brought into manifestation.
If you have positive emotions,
excitement, joy, strong desire, and
ecstasy, you activate the positive
blueprints. If you have fear, doubt, guilt,
If you have fear, doubt, guilt,
judgment.
That's what activates the negative
blueprints. It is as simple as that. It is simple
It is as simple as that. It is simple
physics, simple mechanics. Whatever you
put out, that's what you get back. And
that's why because everything is a
matter of vibration.
Everything you call a different thing, a
different place, a different time is
simply a different frequency of the one
primal energy out of which all
dimensions of experience and all objects
within that dimension are created. There
is only one energy. There is only one
infinite creation.
Each and every one of you, each and
every one of us, all the different
objects in your life, all the different
circumstances in your life, all the
different planets, stars, galaxies,
universes are all the same one thing manifesting
are all the same one thing manifesting
itself in all the multi-dimensional,
simultaneous ways it can.
It's all one thing. So, it's all
connected. All the parts you have for so
long thought it to be are all connected
because they actually are different
manifestations of the same one energy.
You all understand? It is as simple as
that. You can never be isolated in that
sense. You can create the scenario of
seeming to be isolated, seeming to be
cut off. And it is those scenarios that
will create the effects
of pain, disease, loneliness,
depression, confusion in the negative
sense. But remember, all pain is the
product of the resistance of your
natural self. This transformational age
now is where you are all learning to be
natural, not normal.
You have been normal for thousands of
years. You are now through with being
normal. Now you are learning to be
natural, the you really are, the
fundamental you you chose to be in this
life. Because remember
the fundamental purpose so to speak as
you say purpose meaning of your life is
to live this life as fully as you can
because even though you are
reincarnational beings you have never
been this you before and you'll never be
this you again.
This is now. And in that sense the you
you are only does have one life to live.
This is it.
So living it to the fullest is the
fulfillment of the purpose and the
meaning of this life. How you want to go
about it that's up to you. The things
that many of you think of as the goals
and the purposes in your life are only
the methodologies
through which you simply desire to
express the purpose and the meaning of
the life you are. Many of you say, "Oh,
I want to build a spiritual center." All
right, but that's not the purpose per se
of your life. It is one of the
methodologies, perhaps the methodology
through which you can best express the
purpose of the life you are. But the
purpose itself is the fullest living of
that life. Because then
you are the fullest facet of the
multi-dimensional crystal of infinite
creation you can be. And when you are
the fullest facet you can be, you
function as a living reflective mirror
example for everyone else
to be able then to decide for themselves
whether or not they choose to share, to
match, to mimic, to mirror, to parallel
your energy or whether they choose
something else.
But the unity, all the unity that you
desire and seek upon your planet, all
the unity will be the result of the
granting of equality and validity to the
infinite diversity of expression within
your civilization.
Now, how do you go about doing that?
Living to the fullest.
That is very simple. Very simple.
To have a thing, it is called the
feeling. A feeling of excitement.
Excitement. What is excitement?
Many of you do not really know
mechanically speaking. What? It's when
I'm happy. Well, yes. All right. It's
when I feel good.
Yes. All right.
Energy. Yes. Excitement is energy.
Absolutely. Excitement
Excitement
is your physical translation
of a particular vibratory energy.
The particular vibratory energy being
the energy that is representative of the
path you chose to be in this life.
The things in your life that excite you
excite you for the reason that they are
most truly who you are that they are the
things that you can most effortlessly
and abundantly do in your life. That's
why certain things excite you because
excitement is the sign the signal that
many of you ask for when you say give me
a sign. What am I supposed to do in
life? Give me a sign, please.
The things in your life that excite you
the most is the sign. The excitement
vibration, the thing, as you say in your
language that turns you on, is the thing
that you are quote unquote supposed to
be doing. Now, you don't have to do it,
but it is the thing that you will be
able to do most effortlessly by
definition. You can struggle if you want to. You can
You can struggle if you want to. You can
suffer if you want to. That's up to you.
Your choice. You have free will. But the
thing that excites you is the natural
you. Do it. And you will automatically,
synchronistically, coincidentally
attract into your life all the
opportunities and circumstances to allow
you to live the life you say you prefer
to live.
But many of you have been taught out of
following what excites you because well,
let's list a few of the reasons that'll
never work.
That's too easy.
Everyone knows if you don't work hard
and suffer, then you will never earn
happiness. Oh, grow up. Stop acting like a child.
Oh, grow up. Stop acting like a child.
You're dreaming. What a daydreamer. How
naive. Here's our favorite. No pain, no gain.
All right, fair enough. And just as
valid a reality as any other reality.
However, it means that if you really
have a strong desire to gain and you
don't think it can come without the
pain, that's what you'll get because you
want to gain. So you will gain through
the manifestation of pain
because you will not believe because you
have been taught to not believe that the
thing that excites you is what will
support you. That the thing that excites
you is what will allow you to explore
and expand and grow effortlessly in joy.
It does work. It never doesn't work. And
there are no exceptions. Not any of you.
Because you create your reality now
through your strongest belief and
through your strongest emotion and
through your thought pattern.
We are not telling you to do something
different than you have ever done
before. When we talk about trusting the
thing that excites you and acting with
conviction on that thing even though you
may have been told it'll never work.
We are not talking about using a trust
that you have never used in your life.
Oh this trust thing. Oh something very
new. Have to get used to working with
this. Have never used trust before. Oh
yes you have. You have always used it.
Each and every one of you have created
everything in your lives with infinite
trust. It's simply a matter of whether
you trust in negativity or positivity
more. That's it. It's the same
mechanism. Trust is, if I may use this term
Trust is, if I may use this term
loosely, the machine that translates
what you believe most strongly in and
the definitions you have of life into
the manifestational physical experience.
So if you feed your trust machine with
joy and ecstasy,
and ecstasy,
you will get a physical manifestation of
joy and ecstasy of opportunity unlimited
expanding ecstatic. If you feed your
trust machine with doubt and negativity,
what else can you expect on the other
end? You can only get back what you feed
in. And very important, we know many of
you have this belief as well. There's
nothing hiding in the machine that has a
mind of its own.
To take your decision and sneakily
change it into one you don't want.
Nothing has a mind of its own, but you.
You decide. Your emotions don't have a
mind of their own. There is no such
thing really as I don't know why it I
just feel that way. I don't know. It's
just the feeling. It's there. I had
nothing to do with it. It happened to
me. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Life does not happen to you. It happens
through you.
Emotions. Emotions.
Emotions.
Emotions are one part, if I may use the
term, part of a threepart construction.
The three-part construction is as
follows. Belief, emotion, thought.
Belief, emotion, and thought are the
three sides of the prism you refer to as
your personality.
It is the beliefs, the emotions and the
thoughts that your consciousness created
itself to be that determines the person
you are. A person
is in a sense an artificial construct, a
projection of the overall consciousness
you are. It is one of the facets, one of
the faces your overall consciousness can
represent itself to be.
And it is constructed out of the
beliefs, the emotions and the thoughts
that you choose in your life.
As a prism does,
it will break down the white light of
your homogeneous consciousness into the
diversified spectrum of your
physiological differentiated reality.
As a prism does,
it will break down the white light of
your homogeneous consciousness into the
diversified spectrum of your
physiological differentiated reality.
That's what a persona does. It allows
the homogeneous you to be able to
experience itself as a series and a
collection of differences.
But the prism being constructed out of
belief, emotion and thought
will utterly determine the projection of
the reality based upon the clarity and
the proportion of equality in the three
sides of the prism.
If your belief systems are not in
balance with the idea
of your emotions and your thought
patterns, if they are focused along a
certain bias in a certain direction,
that will be the projected image, the
spectrum, the rainbow you get through
the prism of the persona you are.
So understand this very importantly
your persona while a valid extension of
you is always changing. It is not a
static thing
and we are talking about this literally.
I am not talking figuratively. I am not
talking philosophically.
Every time you change a thought, every
time you change an emotion, every time
you change a belief, you are not the
same person.
Literally. All right. All right. All right. You may
All right. All right. All right. You may
think you look the same. Well, of course
it's the same. I look in the mirror,
same face.
That's your convenience.
That is the way you have chosen to
represent yourself to create a
continuity of physical experience so
everyone else can key off of that and
recognize the overall energy that you
are. We are however aware of a society
wherein when they change their beliefs,
emotions and thoughts they actually
change the way they physically look
utterly. You simply have not chosen to do that.
You simply have not chosen to do that.
You maintain an outward continuity
because of the idea of continuity. you
have chosen to be. You are literally,
however, literally a different person
when you change any one of those facets
of the prism your persona is because a
persona is an artificial construct.
Doesn't mean it isn't natural. But
simply, we are using your term
artificial to allow you to understand it
is a presentation that is very
changeable and actually changes every
single moment.
The people that you were when we began
this interaction are not the people you
are now. Nor will the people you are now
be the people you will be when you leave
this interaction. Literally. Literally.
Literally. Does he really mean
literally? Yes, he does.
I am not speaking by analogy. You are
literally not the same people.
Therefore, if you can, as you say, get a handle on
if you can, as you say, get a handle on
this understanding,
you will then begin to realize, well,
wait a minute. Are you telling me that
if I change my thought and I change my
emotion, I change my belief, any one of
those, I am so different a person, that
I literally don't relate to anything the
old me actually used to be. Yes, that's
what I mean.
You don't have the same past anymore.
You don't have the same future anymore.
Whatever you define yourself to be in
the now changes everything
because the past and the future are
created from the present. What
everyone knows? You have to have
something happen first before something
else can happen. The past determines
what's happening now.
No, you create the illusion of linear time.
you create the illusion of linear time.
It is real while you're in it, but it's
an illusion nonetheless. All things
exist simultaneously. Again, hearkening
back to what you call the holographic
structure of all that is. This is where
we use what is called the radio analogy.
You all are familiar with the device you
call a radio upon your planet. Yes.
Now you know all the programs you could
receive on that radio. They're all there
being beamed to that radio device all at
the same time, but you only get the one
you're tuned to at any given moment.
You could by analogy assume
that the program you were listening to a
moment ago is the past. The program you
might listen to in the next moment is
the future. And the program you're
listening to now is the present. Doesn't
mean that the program you were listening
to or the program you're going to be
listening to aren't there right now.
They are. You don't receive them because
your dial is set up linearly. Before,
now, after. Click, click, click,
beginning, middle, end.
But it is because of the definition of
your dial. In other words, your
perceptions of your definitions of
physical reality that makes it seem as
if the past is way back there. The
future is way out there and the present
is simply just here.
Now is the only experiential time in
which you ever exist. But all things
coexist simultaneously with you. And
because now is the only point of power,
now is the only place the dial exists.
Then whatever is going on now utterly
determines the relationship of anything
that went on before. You are making a
comparison always from the now. So
whatever you define the now to be
utterly determines which probable pasts
you now bring into manifestation to
relate to the idea of what's going on
now and vice versa. The idea
yay. Yes.
Yes.
Well, let me remind you of this. You are
creating that memory. Now
that memory is not in the past. It may
be colloally of what you call of the
past, but you're creating the memory in
the present
right now. So what you call the past you
choose to remember is the one you are
creating to make the best sense of
supporting the present you have. If you
were to change now, we are not saying
you have to do this and we are not even
saying that it's necessarily likely that
you will because of the continuity
because of the definition you are
creating your life to be. You will
usually maintain the path you are
familiar with more or less. However,
changing it in subtle ways, but it can
be changed in very dramatic way. If you
were to change the definition of your
present sufficiently enough, your past
would also change radically,
radically. And you can even see it
reflected in other individuals. And many
of you may have actually had this
experience. Did that really happen that way? No, I
Did that really happen that way? No, I
think it was more like this, wasn't it?
Yes. Yes, I think it was. It may have
actually been the first way first, but
now that you have changed, now you're
all remembering a different way, and it
all seems to fit in. Yes, that must be
the way it was because, well, look where
you are now. Well, it had to happen that
way. Everyone knows that. It's obvious
because you see, when you change your
present, whatever past you then create
to fit and back up and reinforce the
present will always seem to be the past
you always had. By definition, you won't
necessarily allow yourself to know there
had been another past because that other
past won't necessarily reinforce where
you are right now. So when you change
your present and change your past, it
will seem absolutely obvious that the
past you remember is the past you always
remembered, but you don't necessarily
know that the past you're remembering
now is the one you actually remembered
three of your years ago. It may seem
that way but you don't really know that.
Understand?
Is it possible to piggy back in a sense?
However, what you call time travel if
you I shall say intersect your own
timeline will never be exactly the same
timeline. It will be maybe exact in
almost every way you can possibly
measure it but it will be a parallel
timeline and it can be explained simply
as follows. If you in growing up as a
child never in your childhood met your
future self and then when you grow up
your adult self travels back in time to
meet the child you were then obviously
it must be a different history. I'm
talking about
not meaning
but viewing the sequence of events as
you can always allow yourself to pull
from the holographic matrix whatever
sequence of events is representative of
the desire and the intention you have in
the present but it is simply one path of
many pasts that could be and if you
change your intention and change your
focus and change your perspective next
time you do that you might receive a
slightly different path
Yes. S
we thank you. Is that sufficient? You're well.
Hey, why? Yes, it can be.
the basic idea. Now, now not that every
single circumstance of that nature falls
into this category. There are many
different reasons at any given moment
for why many different things may be
happening and there are as many reasons
as there are individuals having that
experience. However, one of the things
that we generally perceive is happening
now in your society is that you are all
beginning to learn how to live more in
the now, in the present, in the moment.
As you do that, you break the connection
to specific ideas of having to remember
the past because you simply know what
you need to know when you need to know
it now. And you don't have to rely on
what you have always called memory of
the past. So many individuals will in
your terminology seem to forget huge
chunks of their past.
There's a bit missing from the tape at
this point.
That is another story. Generally
speaking, if you know it's not because
of fear, if you know you're not denying
the idea of discovering something about
yourself, then if you are forgetting, it
is usually because you want to try and
focus yourself in the present. You
follow me?
It is similar, if I may interrupt you
for a moment, to why many of you also
may not remember your dream realities.
Because the idea now is that you are
blending your non-physical dream reality
and your physical reality into one
thing. What you call a dream or a memory
is a bridge or a link, a convenient
symbol to remind you that there is a
connection between what you have been
calling two separate things. The
physical awake state, the present, the
dream reality, the past. So you have
what you call a memory or a dream to be
able to say, "Oh yes, I was doing that
then. That is something that happened in the
That is something that happened in the
past." But if you are now blending
everything into the now, then in a sense
you never really wake up from the dream.
So there's nothing to remember after
having gotten beyond it because you're
never beyond it and you are awake all
the time in that sense. Literally living
the dream, literally living the present.
You follow along? Does that answer your
question sufficiently? Yes. Yes.
I seem to
know instinctively are issues that I
need to integrate or issues that I need
to face.
Yes, you will always know what you need
to know when you need to know it to
reflect the idea you are willing to be
at any given moment.
An individual who is willing to allow
themselves full trust of that idea can
do things at any given moment they have
never done before.
That's why individuals can let us say
sit down perhaps at one of your musical
instruments even though they have never
played in their life. If they are
willing to be completely in the present
with the idea that they are now a
musician, absolutely beyond a shadow of
a doubt, they will access the
information a musician would access and
they will be able to channel the energy
through themselves and simply play
because in that moment they have utterly
defined themselves as a musician and
nothing else. When they get up from the
instrument, they may no longer need to
do that and may not have absolutely any
recall of how to play that instrument.
But that's because they don't need to.
If and when they have a desire to sit
down at it again, they'll know what they
need to know when they need to know it.
For sure. Yes. All right. About the past
again. Yes. Yes.
It can.
But again,
the reality you have created for now
because of the degree of continuity you
all rely on may not necessarily always
manifest blatantly in the changes that
occur. But yes, it has occurred that way
and it can occur because remember any
physical object is just a projection of
your consciousness anyway. They don't
empirically exist solidly apart from
you. And that's the basic definition of
the whole idea we are discussing with
all of you. The reason you can create
any reality you desire is because there
is no empirically existing physical
reality apart from the definitions
themselves. The definitions you have
been taught to believe in are the
physical reality you experience.
Physical reality is only constructed of
definitions. That's it. You have added
in one important definition that allows
physical reality to seem to be something
separate from you. And that's the
definition that it is separate from you
and that's it.
Yes. In a sense, but karma is completely
In a sense, but karma is completely
self-imposed. Karma is basically the
fundamental idea of what we have been
talking about in terms of the fact that
everything is vibration and whatever
vibration you put out is automatically
the vibration you get back. That doesn't
necessarily mean that everything has to
be an absolute one to one mirror
reflection of everything you have ever
done. There are many ways to create a
balance in the momentum, a balance in
the energy that you have generated at
any one point in your life. For example,
let us say an individual does commit
what you call a murder, an act of lack
of integrity in one life. Now, even
though many of you have done it this
way, you don't necessarily have to be
murdered in the next life in order to
balance that equation of energy out. The
idea can be balanced out perhaps by
being willing or to talk someone else
out of committing a murder in the next
life to share with them the idea of
their self-empowering and balance the
energy out that way. Karma is completely
self-imposed. It is not a judgment
placed upon you from outside. There is
no outside in that sense. It is simply
what you may call a tally sheet of the
balance of energy at any given moment. A
momentum begun and allowed to be
completed at any point holographically
speaking anywhere along the timeline.
And also remember this, something you
may do in what you call a present life
can actually be balanced out in a past
life. Because the idea is that when you are
Because the idea is that when you are
choosing lives, it's not done
necessarily linearly and you can
actually choose what you colloquially
call a past life after a present one.
Understand? No. All right.
No. All right.
One moment. One moment. A little
clarification for now. The idea again
perhaps that will assist best by analogy
will be what is called the film strip
analogy. Now you are familiar with what you call
Now you are familiar with what you call
a strip of your film with many frames.
Yes. Each of these frames is analogous to a
Each of these frames is analogous to a
different life.
Each frame knows only the life it is
living. But you the projectionist
you know the whole film exists all at
once. Do you not? You see all the frames
laid out before you on your table.
The analogy is the consciousness you are
as a physical being while it is
physically focused may think like the
frame that that is the only frame there
is and that one has to follow the other
in order to make sense out of the
picture. But the projectionist, the
oversoul you are in between lives, the
non-physical part of your consciousness
can at any given moment point to any
frame on that film in any order.
Continuity does not have to stick for
it. It can decide to look at a frame 30
frames ago before it looks at a frame in
the middle. or it can decide to look at
a frame 30 frames ahead before it looks
at the frame in the middle. It doesn't
matter. It can be anywhere in those
frames it wants to be at any given
moment, hopping back and forth over what
you would perceive to be the barriers
that separate one life from another or
one moment from another. It is two
completely different states of
perspective. And the non-physical state
does not adhere to what you call linear
time at all. The non-physical
perspective has the ability to transcend
the idea of linear time and view any
life in any order or live any life in
any order. You follow me?
Big one. Oh, the big one.
Are you afraid?
Why? I just don't want to be. There is other
I just don't want to be. There is other
places you could be. Very well said. Now
remember this first of all and here is a
foundation of the mechanics of
metaphysics that we will get into next.
There is no such thing as a prediction
of the future.
There are sensings of the most probable
reality, the reality that might have the
highest degree of energy or likelihood
to manifest at any given moment. But the
prediction is a sensing of the energy
that exists at the time the prediction
is made.
If in the very next second the energy
changes, you can take that prediction
and fold it up very small and toss it
out the window. It is obsolete.
Now remember that we said your strongest
remember that we said your strongest
emotion attracts you into the reality.
So if your strongest emotion is fear,
guess where you will be.
If you understand,
if you understand
that transformation is simply change and
does not have to be felt in a negative
way, then you can play your part in
changing the vibratory energy of your
planet and making it not necessary to
have what you call the big one, but
allowing all the ideas of pressure to be
released in a series of moderate ones,
if necessary at all.
and or if there is an area where the
majority of the consensus reality has
determined that they will experience the
idea of transformation in a negative way
in a catastrophic way. If that's not
your vibration, then automatically
synchronistically whether you plan to or
not you will not be there if and when it
occurs. If it's not your vibration, you can't
If it's not your vibration, you can't
experience it. You cannot have an
experience in your life that you are not
the vibration of. To fear something is
to be the vibration of what you fear and
to attract yourself squarely into the
area that it has the highest degree of
likelihood of occurring within.
Understand? Beautiful.
Allow yourself to remember, treat these
ideas, these predictions, no matter from
whom they come, not as something
chiseled in steel, but as an opportunity
to decide, is this the reality I prefer?
Do I believe I need that experience? If
I were to go through that experience,
what would I learn about myself? How
would it serve me to go through the
experience in a negative way? If you can
determine what it is you'd get out of it
if you went through it that way and
allow yourself to get those lessons now,
then you won't have to have that
manifestation, will you? So, the idea is
that if you wake up now, you won't have
to shake yourself awake.
Many individuals on your planet here and
there may still create in isolated
pockets the idea of catastrophe simply
because they will not allow themselves
to believe there is any other way to go
through the transformation other than a
trial by fire because that's the way
they've always been taught. You have to
suffer. You have to suffer. You have to
suffer. No, you don't. No, you don't.
No, you don't.
You can. You can. You can. But you don't
have to. It's up to you. And it's all a
matter of how you define it. What your
clearest definition is for why you would
have to experience it. If you know why
you would choose to experience something
negative and you get the lesson out of
it now, then the symbol doesn't have to
occur that way. You can, as you say, cut
it off at the past.
Understand? I have an object here. I'd like to know
I have an object here. I'd like to know
what it means to
how he feels about it.
Tetrahedral structure in this way will
represent the basic foundation of all
creation in terms of the smallest unit
that can be manifested as a material
form. Everything that you call physical
reality is based upon the triangular and
tetrahedral structure. The tetrahedral
structure also is the symbol of our
mentality in terms of a vibratory
frequency. The idea basically is as
follows. It is the smallest geometric
form that can exist and therefore most
representative of the materialization
that is just one step away from
non-physicality altogether. Such a
crystallin form basically represents the
formula, the template, the matrix that
can be used to outline any physical
property at all scientifically speaking.
As an example,
you have the idea of what you call
subatomic particles. Now, this is a
notion. The idea of this notion,
however, has been expressed on what you
call quantum level that you can neither
know both the momentum and the position
of a subatomic particle simultaneously.
Either one or the other. You can know
where it is, but not how fast it's
going. or you can know how fast it's
going but not where it is. This is
called your uncertainty principle in
what you call quantum physics. The
tetrahedral structure can point out
exactly why this is the case. If you
allow yourself to assign to three of
these points the idea of the x y z
coordinates that give you physical local
and the one coordinate of time that
gives you the when of it. Then you will
understand that from your perspective at
any given moment you only have the
capacity in physical reality to measure
completely any one face at any one time.
You cannot see the whole
fourthdimensional structure at once
because you live in a third-dimensional
reality. So if you take the face that
represents the XYZ coordinates, you have
the totality of position. you know
exactly where it is, but you have a very
fuzzy idea of when because the time
coordinate doesn't fit into this plane.
If you measure any one of the other
faces, you have two of the coordinates
of the physicality, x and y perhaps, and
the total coordinate of time. So you
know when it is precisely, but you have
a very fuzzy representation of exactly
where it is because you don't have the
third coordinate of the physical
reality. This tetrahedral structure is
the simplest form in a sense that can
physically materialize and is the
template is the shape of the basic
template upon which all physical
materiality is based. Therefore, the
tetrahedral pyramidal structure as a
crystallin form, if you use it perhaps
as a trigger, as a catalyst for your
meditations of consciousness, can put
you in touch with the prime frequency,
the actual carryover point, the
transition point itself from
non-physicality into physicality, from
physicality back into non-physicality.
It is the transformational gate
structure, the doorway if you focus on
it in your meditations, through which
you can perceive all of the primal
energy and unlock physical reality, melt
it back down into the liquid light out
of which all physical material objects
are created and then recristallize it
into the solid form you prefer to
crystallize it into. That is one way you
can use such a structure. But remember
all of these structures, all of these
ideas, all of these crystals are
catalysts. They are representations and
reflections of the master crystal of
consciousness. You are in and of
themselves. They are representative of
energy and of course power. But the
power for manifestation is not in them.
It is in you. These are triggers. They
are catalysts to awaken and unlock the
power of manifestation within each and
every one of you. Does that serve to
answer your question sufficiently? Thank
you very much. Yes. Why is it?
Oh, thank you very much.
Because your definition of a pattern is
something that repeats itself. Now,
Now,
here is something that is a very simple
idea mechanically speaking.
Habit pattern. something that you do
that you don't know you're doing. Once
you know you have a habit, once you know
you are doing a pattern, you don't have
it anymore because you have to be beyond
it in order to know you had it. So if
you can recognize you have a habit, you
really don't have it anymore. It is only
your assumption
that it will automatically remember mind
of its own keep repeating that you keep
getting the experience that it keeps
repeating. It doesn't have a mind of its
own. It's not automatic in that sense.
It is your description of it, your
definition of it that makes the
assumption that a pattern keeps
repeating that allows it to seem to keep
repeating. One way to break this idea is
to understand that if every now is a
different now, then no matter how it
appears on the surface, it can't really
be truly a repetition, can it? It must
always be new. Understand?
Now, the idea therefore is to understand
that if you recognize you have a habit,
if you recognize you had a pattern and
you say, "All right, now I recognize it.
What do I have to do? What process do I
have to go through in order to allow
myself to alleviate this pattern and how
long will it take? You are generating
right then and there the idea of needing
a massive amount of time before you will
allow yourself to believe that you have
transformed that habit. If you need such
a process, it is valid. We are not
condemning it. It is very creative if
that's what you believe you need.
However, if you can understand that your
if you can understand that your
recognition that you had a habit is the
sessation of it and you start acting in
the manner you prefer to act now as if
you really no longer have the habit, you
will then simply see beyond a shadow of
a doubt by the circumstances that occur
in your life that you really don't have
it anymore.
In other words, here's where your
imagination comes in. This is what your
imagination is for.
If you recognize there was something
that you used to do that you no longer
prefer to do. You see that in your
imagination. All right, there it is.
This is how I used to be. This is the
old definition.
Then clean your blackboard
and create an image, a visualization of
the you you prefer to be. See the you
you prefer to be without the old habit.
See the new habits you prefer.
Understand the thought.
When you then visualize this new you,
feel it. Feel it with all your senses.
See it. Taste it. Smell it. Touch it. Be
it. Feel what it would be like to be
that new you. If this you you are
defining your imagination is someone you
really say you want to be, I would think
you'd be very excited about being that
new you, wouldn't you? So get excited
about it. Feel what it would be like to
be that new you. And as you stop and
think about it, if you are actually
feeling what it would be like, you're
actually feeling it as you are being it
in that moment.
See the new you.
See the difference between the new and
old you. Not in a judgmental way. Not
saying, "Oh, yes, this new you, bright,
shiny, wonderful, bad old you, e pooy."
No, no, no, no, no. The old you is what
brought you to where you are now. Don't
invalidate it. It's still a part of the
whole. If you invalidate any part of the
whole you are, you are what creates
yourself to be unable to move ahead
because you take energy from yourself by
invalidating a portion of it. Everything
you have ever done has brought you to
where you are. Don't invalidate it.
Simply recognize you no longer prefer to
be that way, but realize it has served
you in a positive way, and you will add
to the overall positive energy that will
make it that much easier for you to be
the new you you prefer to be. When you
have that new definition, that new image
of the new you acting in the way you
prefer to act,
take a circumstance and a situation you
have in your life that perhaps the old
you doesn't know how to handle and give
it to the new you. Hand it to the new
you. Then sit back in your meditation
and watch. Watch how the new you handles
the situation. Watch the success the new
you has. Pay very close attention to the
attitudes, the methodologies,
the way the new you goes about handling
a situation successfully.
Then copy it.
Mimic it, mirror it, and you'll get the
same result. That's what your
imagination is for. To generate the
template, the blueprint that if you
follow, you'll get the same result.
That's how to use your imagination.
Does that serve you? Thank you. Yes. And
then you
all right. In a sense, yes. However, we
will be brief about this idea because it
can get lost in labeling as you say.
Basically speaking, such a thing can
occur. But what is mechanically
happening? Remember how we talked about
the idea that a shift in your frequency
means you really are a different person.
Then simply remember that what is
happening is such a strong
identification is formed. That the
energy that used to be the old you is
the same energy that is used to create
such a radical shift that a completely
new persona, a completely new you takes
over from that point forward. In a
sense, you could say it has been an
ascension of the self. A walk-in can
seem to be someone else simply because
you are so used to thinking of your
persona as being who and what you are.
And so such a radical change in persona
means well it must be literally someone
else. And in a sense it is because any
change means you are literally a
different person. But it is still the
same energy in that sense simply having
shifted its frequency so drastically
that it presents itself with a
completely new perspective a completely
new point of view and in that sense is
truly radically a different person. You
understand? No. All right.
No. All right.
In a sense colloially it can be. But
remember what the definition of energy
is. Everything is the same one thing. So
even though an association of walk-in
shift may be made with what you call
another soul, the idea is that as soon
as the shift is made, all that has
happened is that you have redefined the
local through which any particular
format or concentration of persona is
presenting itself.
It is a shift in a sense. the person it
used to be may seem to go where the new
person was and vice versa, but all
you're doing is making a shift of the
dial in a certain way to allow what used
to be flowing out in one area to flow
out in this area and what used to be
flowing out in this area to flow out in
another area.
The same oversoul. It can be. It doesn't
have to be, but usually more often than
not, yes, it is connected through the
same oversoul structure.
Does that answer it for you?
Is there any limitations to that
imagination? Not how do you get used to
being How do you get used to there being
no limitations? Now, you may still
choose to impose some general
limitations on the idea of the reality
you experience simply because you do
want to play a particular game. So, you
will have what you call the general
consensus reality beyond which you may
not choose to go in this life. Just so
you will have something that basically
forms guidelines for the overall rules
of the general game you are playing. But
there is much leeway within that whole
idea. True unlimitedness in that sense
is something you will not have to get
used to because anytime you take your
energy or elevate or accelerate your
energy to a level where you will
experience more and more and more
unlimitedness or less and less and less
limitation. You will simply
automatically be adapted to that level
by definition. And whatever it is that
is going on on that level will seem
absolutely natural to you on that level.
You will not have to get used to it per
se. You follow me? One way, however, to
adapt to the changes of less limitation
that are going on on your reality, your
level now, is to assume that there are
no pointless nor extraneous events or
creations going on. And therefore if
something is coming to you at a certain
pace then by definition it must be the
pace you actually can handle otherwise
it wouldn't come to you that way.
Understand?
Ask yourself why you would assume it
needs to come faster
because many times it will only be your
definitions that will make it seem as if
it has to come faster than it is coming.
And in a sense, paradoxically, the way
you allow anything to accelerate is to
accept it completely for the way it is
now. Because when you live fully in the
moment and get out of the now,
everything you're supposed to get out of
the now, that's when you make room for
something else to come in. If you don't
use what's going on now with the
attitude that you're waiting for
something better to come along, then you
don't make room for anything else to
come along because you haven't used up
what's there for you in the now. Many
times the desire for something to come
faster is the result of impatience with
what's going on now. And that means
you're not using the now fully.
Remember, you don't really need patience
in one sense of the term because if you
are living in the now and you recognize
that everything that's happening now is
what needs to be happening for whatever
reason, then you will live in that now
fully and you won't need something
better to come along. You'll be having
such a good time living in the now that
you will then
make the room naturally for the flow of
anything else that will come up as you
say later. Also by living in the now
your focus is such that you create the
experience of less time and before you
know it it is later because you have not
been creating the experience of as much
time by being so focused in the idea of
enjoying what you are doing in the
moment. Understand? You all say time
flies when you're having fun. You know
it's not that it flies but the idea is
that simply you think you are ignoring
the passage of time but when you are
doing something that really focuses you
that you really enjoy and you're really
involved in that moment and you feel
that only one half of your hours has
passed and you look up and three of your
hours has passed. you whatever amount of
time you have literally felt
experientially to have passed is
literally all you have aged.
So when you live in the moment, you
become ageless, timeless. And the idea
is is that simply before you know it,
everything around you,
3 hours, 3 days, 3 weeks, 3 months, 3
years, 300 years, 3,000 years has come
and gone.
And everything accelerates into the now.
The less time you create, the less time
there is for things to happen in. So the
more you live in the now, you make it so
that everything that needs to happen in
your life only has now to happen in. So
it will accelerate to you. Remember, if
you don't live in the now, then the
things you want in life can't find you
because the now is the only place they
can find you. Understand?
Does that answer your question?
Working with them.
Do not make a task out of it.
Live in the now. Be in a childlike
manner. spontaneously,
spontaneously,
lovingly, joyfully, ecstatically,
because everything that is in your life
is there for a reason. Even if only to
give you an opportunity to decide that
what's going on is something you don't
prefer. But if you deny that it belongs
in your life, then you do not get to use
it for the reason it's there.
Yes. Yeah. Um, the Native American
sorcerers, they talk about waking up in
your dream. Yes. And then your dream
body brings you your body anywhere else.
Yes. Can you talk about that? Basically,
it is a simple analogy to the fact as we
have said that you create your physical
reality by what you imagine it to be, by
what you dream it to be. And that your
consciousness in and of itself is what
is projecting the dream of physical
reality. Let's put it this way.
Let's put it this way.
Your consciousness does not exist inside
your body. Your body exists within your
consciousness. Your physical reality exists within your
Your physical reality exists within your
consciousness. Wake up in the dream of
physical reality.
know you are dreaming right now and you
can create this dream to be anything you
want it to be in your dream reality.
Sometimes if you are allowed to wake up,
if you allow yourself to wake up in the
dream and know you are dreaming, then
you know you are actually generating not
only the non-physical reality but the
physical reality as well. And then that
allows you to understand there really is
no difference between physical and
non-physical reality excepting the
definitions you have given it. Once you
know you are dreaming right now and wake
up in this dream, you can create your
physical reality to be any dream you
prefer it to be. You will know it is
malleable. You will know that it is the
product of your thoughts and nothing
more. Understand? For sure. I have a question
Understand? For sure. I have a question
on the earthquake that we just had. Yes.
10 days prior to that, I dreamt the
exact situation I was in when the
earthquake happened. Many of you will be
sensitive to the idea of how energies
will be released. So, yes. Well, I just
want to I just want help in interpreting
that and getting more clear on Okay. So
I dreamt it before you.
You recognized
something that your collective consensus
reality had already decided was going to
have a a particular amount of momentum
behind and so therefore your perception
of it was picking up on the energy that
by that time had gathered enough
momentum that it would be unlikely to
divert. You simply became sensitized to when
You simply became sensitized to when
your consensus reality reached a certain
level of energization of a particular
manifestation. All of you are becoming
more sensitive to the consensus
agreements so that you can decide which portions of
so that you can decide which portions of
those agreements you prefer to
participate in and in what way you
prefer to participate in them.
Sure. You follow me? So I would have had
that dream to give myself a choice. Yes.
And to also understand that you are in
touch with everyone else, that you're
all deciding these things together.
And therefore, you and you and all of
you are a part of the board of decision
makers for your consensus reality and
you always are let in on what's going on
because you have a vote. Okay. Okay.
Now, at the point that I dreamt that if
I didn't like it turned out good in the
dream, so I wasn't worried. If it didn't
turn out good in my dream, do I have a
choice to change? Absolutely. The idea
of how it manifests in your dream
reality may simply be a reflection of
what the strongest beliefs are within
you to give you the opportunity to
decide whether you wish to let it
continue in a negative B or whether you
wish to allow it to be transformed in a
positive way. You follow me? You always
have a choice. bottom line.
You always have a choice. Always,
always, always. Yeah. Thank you. Um, do
you sleep? And if you sleep, no, you
don't sleep. Not in the classical sense
that you mean it. Okay. Less and less of
you are now needing the idea of having
to become unconscious in order to
connect into your higher selves. Now
that you are connecting into them in
awake states, you will then be able to
simply be active because you will allow
the connections to take place in an
aware and awake.
Always, always, always. Yes.
Do you sleep? And if you sleep, no
sleep. Not in the classical sense that
you mean it. Okay. less and less of you
are now needing the idea of having to
become unconscious in order to connect
into your higher self. Now that you are
connecting into them in awake states,
you will then be able to simply be
active because you will allow the
connections to take place in an aware
and awake state rather than needing to
be unconscious to perform those
connections. Understand?
Understand?
Are we relative and 99% absolute?
1% relative and 99% absolute.
As far as reality, as far as I am
concerned, it is all consciousness 100%.
But the idea is that you are your
version of the infinite.
To us, it is always both. Any reality
you generate with your consciousness is
for you a 100%
absolute and it is absolutely relative
to everyone else's absolute. In other
words, the truth is composed of all
truths. There is no one background
reality against which to measure all
other realities for their comparative
validity. They are all valid. The only
thing that is common for every being
within creation is the fact that you
exist and the idea of the active mechanism
and the idea of the active mechanism
that what you put out you get back.
Beyond that, it's your ball game.
It's your definition. It's your
perspective. It's your point of view.
Now, briefly
because we desire to provide a little
bit of an outline for some of these
ideas of what you call intuition,
psychic manifestation, telepathy, what
we call televate
some of these ideas
because you are now beginning to blend
consciously becoming more aware of the
fact that you always are in telepathic
connection with each
Allow yourself to recognize what
telepathy actually is. Many of you in
the old definitions have said, "Oh, it's
reading each other's mind." Well, in a
sense, yes, but not really. Mechanically
speaking, you don't literally read each
other's minds directly. The idea is that
teleathy is emotionally activated.
is emotionally activated.
Which means the more you identify with
an individual or an object or a
circumstance, the more you mimic its frequency. The
the more you mimic its frequency. The
more you operate on a similar
wavelength. If you operate on a very similar
If you operate on a very similar
wavelength to something else, it means
your prism, belief, emotion, thought
translates the homogeneous one energy
into the same type of thought patterns
as the other identity you are mirroring.
So, it's that you have the same type of
thoughts at the same time, not that
you're directly reading someone else's
mind. It's that you're mirroring them.
Therefore, the easiest way to generate
conscious telempathy in your reality is
to identify as strongly as you can with
everyone or anyone in it. And the way
you do that is through what?
unconditional love. Love is the prime
vibration, the prime chord of harmonic
in your reality. That's why individuals
in your society that you recognize as
being in love very often are the
individuals that very obviously know
what each other is thinking at any given
moment. Don't you all recognize that
lovers very often know each other's
thoughts? It's because they are on such
a similar wavelength that they have
similar thoughts at the same time. It
seems as if they're reading each other's
mind. They're just being absolute
reflections back to each other. So
unconditional love will allow your
society to know itself both individually
and collectively. will allow you more
and more of what you call psychic
intuition. Now we recognize that you
have generated many ideas you call
scientific notions on your planet and
this is all well and good and very
valid. The idea however now as it is
being applied to what you call psychic
phenomena is being a little bit
misunderstood. what you call old definitions of
what you call old definitions of
scientific thought are being applied to
something that you are not yet familiar
with in a conscious way. And it is being
assumed that the idea of psychic
manifestation must fit the old paradigms
of scientific investigation and it can
but not by the definitions that you have
created. Simply you are using old tests for
Simply you are using old tests for
something that does not fit those tests.
There are rules, so to speak, laws that
govern the idea of psychic
manifestation. There are reasons why it
works and reasons why sometimes it
doesn't work. But simply is that you are
still gathering together an
understanding of what those reasons are.
We will outline briefly a few of the
laws of psychic functioning. The idea
first and foremost is that we have
discussed that everything is one thing.
That is how you are able to be connected
to anything at all. And identification,
the matching of a frequency will put you
strongly in touch with that thing.
However, if certain conditions aren't
met, you will not get a manifestation of
psychic or telepathic functioning. One
of the prime manifestations, one of the
prime laws I shall say of this idea, one
of the prime definitions is as follows.
Just like electricity for it is very
similar in many ways. Psychic
functioning will always take the path of
least resistance. What does that mean?
It means as follows. Let's say you have
an individual that comes up to another
individual that says, "Yes, all right.
I'm psychic." Oh, yeah. Well, all right.
Let's prove it. You tell me what I'm
thinking. What did I have for breakfast
today? If you can't tell me, you're not
psychic. Now
the individual who is asking the
question looking for the proof already
knows the answer.
Why should the answer come to another
individual who doesn't know the answer
if one of the two individuals in the
interaction already has the information
they need? It shortcircuits the ability
of the other person many times to know
the information because the information
is already known within the collective
event. It's the path of least
resistance. Understand?
Understand?
The paramount idea is is the information
already accessible in an easier way.
Yes, it is. One person already knows the
answer. So that's it. the fulfillment of
the interaction. That's how it works.
Secondly, this can be to some degree
overcome by the second law, the great
need or desire to know the information.
If that person doesn't care what you had
for breakfast, if it doesn't excite them
to know what you had for breakfast, it
is unlikely they are going to be able to
generate an identical enough wavelength
of interest with you to care and know
what you had for breakfast. It all
depends on need and desire because that
activates the emotional engine, gets the
juices flowing.
If that isn't fulfilled then the idea in
that sense will not necessarily come
about. Third issue allowance spontaneity
confidence in other words many of the things you
in other words many of the things you
call psychic interactions will take
place quite spontaneously
without expectation in the daily normal
course of the interactions you have in
life. In other words, the laboratory in
which to search for these things is not
necessarily the laboratories your
scientists think, but the laboratory of
spontaneous life itself because it is
emotionally activated. It is not the dry
mental cerebral effect. Many of you have
been taught to think it is. An analogy
would be as follows. If someone pulled
someone into one of your laboratories
and wired them all up and they were very
nervous and uncomfortable, uncertain
about their surroundings and unfamiliar
and not feeling that the individuals
around them really cared for them one
way or another, nor did they really care
for what they were doing nor understand
what they were doing, then if one of
those scientists came up to them and
said, "All right, now on the count of
three, fall in love with me. And if you
don't fall in love, there is no such
thing as love. That is a more
appropriate analogy to the idea of why
psychic ability does and doesn't
function because it's empathic in
nature. And if the individual is not
confident, is not supported, is in that
sense faced with the idea of what you
call bias and or skepticism, if they are
not in that sense made comfortable nor
allowed to build their confidence, then
that is also going to shortcircuit the
idea of spontaneous interaction.
Fourth law, personal interpretation.
Many individuals even when they allow
themselves the ability to circumvent the
path of least resistance in that way
that do have a strong desire to function
in that sense that are confident enough
to do it may still not understand that
each and every individual has their own
set of definitions and may simply filter
the information through that set of
definitions. They will be getting the
correct and valid information, but it
may seem incorrect and invalid to the
individual doing the testing because it
doesn't come in the way they expect to
hear it as follows. Let us say you use
the idea again of your deck of cards.
Let us say the individual holding the
cards is holding the ace of spades.
Now, what the ace of spades means to
them may be what gets transmitted to the
other individual attempting to determine
what the card is. If the ace of spades
means to the individual holding the card
that it is a winning card, that they
have perhaps won a game with that card,
then that meaning that intention is what
will transmit to the other individual.
The other individual will pick up on the
idea winning card. If the individual has
played a different game and the winning
card for them was the queen of hearts,
the first impression they will get is
queen of hearts. No, you're wrong.
There's no such thing as psychic
functioning. But they did not stop to realize that
But they did not stop to realize that
what the individual was picking up on
was the basic intention, the basic
interpretation, the definition that was
being given to the idea of the card and
they translated the meaning of the card
personally accurately. Are you following
along what we are saying? The idea
simply is is that these basic rules do
exist and if this structure is adhered
to, then you can generate as many
repeatable cases of psychic
manifestation as you care to. If you
measure the event in the laboratory it
was designed to be measured within. You
cannot take measurements off of a cube
of ice if your laboratory is a furnace.
You must measure something within an
environment that is conducive to the
support of the thing you are measuring.
It is simply that your definitions of
psychic phenomena have not yet been
clarified to the point where you
understand what you're looking for and
what to measure. But these things are
changing in your reality. And this forms
some of the basic foundations of the
fundamentals of the mechanics of what
you call metaphysics. Now metaphysics in
that sense it is not something truly
extra to the physical reality. It is
simply different aspects that you have
not yet clearly defined in ways that are
applicable, workable in what you call
your daytoday life. But this is
changing. It's all a matter of how you
define it. Even what you call now some
of your leading edge physicists are
beginning to realize that your physical
reality is only what you define it to
be. So what you call the idea of
physical reality and what has been
called in the past metaphysical reality
is beginning to blend its definitions to
some degree. We perceive this will
continue to accelerate in your reality
until there is an understanding that
consciousness itself must be a part of
any scientific equation that you have
because your perspective utterly
determines the reality you get. You get
the result you design the experiment for
and that's all you get. Your perspective
to begin with, your bias to begin with
determines the outcome. A skeptic will
always be able to say, "I told you so."
Because that's what they believe going
in. Remember that skepticism is not a
scientific point of view. Openmindedness
is
skepticism even though we understand the
original root of the word means simply
to know. Skepticism in your society
generally now translates into a
preconceived bias in a particular direction that you
bias in a particular direction that you
want in a sense something else to
disprove rather than simply going into something
rather than simply going into something
with an open mind and saying is there
something in here that works for me or
not. It is not necessarily
representative of whether it must fit in
to those things you empirically think
you know to begin with or not. It all
does fit because there are no extraneous
creations. Each and every one of you
fits or you wouldn't exist.
Understand? Yes. Can you um tell us something about
Yes. Can you um tell us something about
your world? All right. How is our
timing? We will be brief.
We will be brief.
Our world in our ancient language is
called Esasani, which means place of
living light. It is not too unlike your
world. You would, with a slight
adjustment, be able to exist upon our
world that is slightly smaller than your
planet, very green, very park-like, no
large builtup structures. In that way,
at any given moment, the majority of our
society exists within spacecraft. Though
there are many beings upon the surface
of our world enjoying its naturalenness.
We have not as many ideas of season as
you do. It is mostly a moderate climate
in that sense. Not as many large land
masses. Most of it is ocean in that way
with a very slight axis tilt. So we do
not have the seasons that you do. We
have no moon whatsoever. The idea
basically is that our physiological
appearance is approximately 5t of
average height of yours. White whitish
gray skin coloration. Very slender. wide
and upturned of eye. The males have no
hair. The females have hair in this
sense. Usually tending to white.
We are in a different dimensional plane
than you and we have to make an
adjustment in order to see your star.
You would have to make an adjustment to
see our star. But if we were to overlap
in your reality, our star would fit into
your galactic coordinates. Approximately
500 of your light years in the direction
of the Orion constellation.
The idea is that we are simply a member
of the association of worlds of many
civilizations with whom we interact that
are now sending to you reflections of
unconditional love and joy so that you
may if you are willing to join us in
this association in the further
exploration and ecstasy of creation
itself. We thank you at this time for
your sharing. We thank you for
co-creating this interaction with us and
for choosing to function as ambassadors
of your world and allowing me to
function as an ambassador of mine. We
bid you exciting dream lives and life
dreams and remind you to wake up and
live the dream you prefer to be because
you are dreaming right now. We bid you a
fond and an unconditionally loving good
day.
How did it go?
[Music] [Applause]
Thank you all for being here today.
Thank you. Did you have a good time?
[Music] Let everybody know that we have live
Let everybody know that we have live
sessions every Thursday night at 7:30 in
We got the information on your way out.
Enlightening. Thank you. You're welcome.
My pleasure. Thank you.
Thank you very much. You're welcome.
Thanks for coming.
They decided to cut it off. [Music]