I don't say how are you all this evening
of your time as you create time to
exist. Allow us to begin this interaction this
Allow us to begin this interaction this
evening of your time with a
further expression another perspective
of the idea you call reincarnation and
this may be your entitlement if you
wish. Now you have those of you who have
Now you have those of you who have
considered the idea of the existence of
reincarnation. Even while considering
this idea because of the linear time
frame reference structure in which you
have existed for thousands of years of
your time generally have placed your
time generally have placed your
reincarnational understanding within
that time frame within that linear
structure. thinking therefore extrapolating
thinking therefore extrapolating
therefore that you have a life after
life after life and lives before lives
yet to
come. This is not necessarily
inaccurate but it is only the point of
view from within a linear time frame
dimension. Now realize the true
Now realize the true
multi-dimensionality of the being that
you are. How you are
are. How you are
extended in many dimensions of
experience at once simultaneously.
We have discussed with you many times
the notion that all of your so-called
past lives, future lives, and alternate
present lives are in a sense all going
on at the same time right now,
simultaneous, parallel, if you will.
The idea of
reincarnation is only considered
reincarnation because of the timeline
frame of reference. The idea of a
before, a middle, and an after. So if
something was and it becomes again, then
it must re
become in this way. Again, while this is
valid from within that frame of
reference, the notion that you call
reincarnation, perhaps we may now simply
begin to refer to as, if you wish, still
colloquial, but perhaps a little more
precise, as simply simultaneous multiple
incarnations. Simultaneous multiple
incarnations.
The idea of multiple
incarnations basically
occurs because you are eternal and
infinite. To put it more colloquially in
your frame of
reference. In a sense,
reincarnation must exist if you are in
fact eternal and
infinite. Because the idea, the idea,
the limited scope you are experiencing
yourself to be in what you call this
life is but a fragment of the total
being that you are if you truly are
eternal and
infinite in the true sense of what those
words mean. Therefore, if you are eternal and
mean. Therefore, if you are eternal and
infinite and yet you perceive that you
are only experiencing this limited idea
of one particular physical
reality. If
you see that you do not perhaps as this
consciousness consciously experience
yourself at the same time on the other
side of the universe as another being as
that infinite aspect of yourself.
Then you must
realize that you have created simply and
imposed upon yourself a
compartmentalization of the total being
that you are. And it is this
compartmentalization of the total being,
the total infinite and eternal being
that you are that gives rise to the
notion of multiple
incarnations. For if you are in a sense
truly everywhere, every when and you do
not experience that consciously, then
there must be other fragments of you
just as you consider the idea of
yourself to be a fragment or a limited
experience of the total being that you
are. All of these other
fragments in a sense are made to be
fragments are made to be experienced by
you in a compartmentalized
fashion so that you do not experience
them all at the same time all in the
same place. So you can experience this
particular reality or that particular
reality at any given moment. So that you
can create a
focus, an idea, a
specific idea. Without that
idea. Without that
ability, there would be no ongoing
creation. It would be static, stagnant.
The idea of transformation in and of
itself means that you are expressing
yourself in all the ways you possibly
can right now. Whether or not any one of
those ways is cognizant of all the other
ways does not matter. You are eternal
beings. By the definition, you are
infinite beings. And by that definition,
you must be everywhere everywhere that
there is to be right
now. Therefore, from whatever frame of
reference you create, that will
determine the terminology by which you
recognize your simultaneous multiple
existence. Now if you create a frame of
reference that talks about a linear
structure a before, a now and an after
then you will impose that frame of
reference upon the simultaneous multiple
existence of yourself. And you will say
I have past lives. I have future lives.
The past lives have already happened.
The future lives have not happened yet.
Those are all extreme
colloquialisms relative to the
neighborhood in which you
live. And that is
all. You are truly truly simultaneous
multi-dimensional being because you are
eternal. Because you are infinite. One
must follow the other.
The idea therefore of
reincarnation simply is a quote unquote
natural result of the fact that you are
eternal because now right now is the
only experiential time frame in which
you will ever perceive your
existence. Therefore, if you are doing
all of these other things, you create a
multiplicity of nows in which to do
them. But they all do occur right now. You
But they all do occur right now. You
simply have broken yourself up into
different frequencies, different
bandwidths. Again, the analogy of your
radio device. All the programs are there
at once. You only hear the one you are
tuned to at any given moment. But all
the programs are there.
You would not perhaps think for a moment
that it would be in any way, shape, or
form efficient to send the program one after
efficient to send the program one after
another. It would take an interminably
long amount of time to hear them all.
So, you do them all at once, all you can
imagine, and you give everyone a choice
as to which one they wish to listen
to. And you invent your recording
devices, so if they miss one, they can
get it later.
But the idea is still that they are all
available now and you make your
choices and whichever one you focus on
that is what you experience. And if
quote unquote later you wish to replay
your recording then you can have an
recording then you can have an
experience another experience another
life. And therefore remember that
because all lives are
simultaneous, you can in a sense have a
past life after quote unquote a present
one just as you can listen to your
recording after it has been
aired because now you are focused. Now
you are pointed in that direction. Now
that is what you want your consciousness
to be focused upon.
So re quote unquote replaying your tape
allows you to experience it as if it is
in fact for the first
time. And when you relate to someone
else, the experience of you watching
that tape, it still fits into the linear
time frame of your society. Oh yes. Oh,
you saw that too? Yes. Well, but that
was aired back
then. Yes. But I thought today for me it
was aired
today. But within the overall agreement
it was aired back
then. Therefore recognize with this
example as well symbolically many of the
devices that you are now creating in
your society are also assisting you to
in a sense fuzz out your concept of
time. For in many ways you can listen
and hear and experience something that
someone else has already heard and
listened to and experienced some time
ago. And for you it is the first time
even though for them it is a repeat in
your terminology. You can shift the focus of
terminology. You can shift the focus of
when anything can occur and you can
allow it to seem to be any time any
place. It is no accident that your technology
It is no accident that your technology
is reflecting this ability. That your
communication skills technologically are
now beginning to represent your
communication skills that you are
developing within yourself
telepathically and between each other
coming and going simultaneously of many
different messages on many different
levels. Your technology is now that way
because that is what you are all about.
the recognition of the coming and going
of many messages simultaneously on many
different levels and you can tune into
whichever one you prefer at any given
moment depending upon where your dial is
aimed. It is up to
you. Aim your dial where you
will. We thank each and every one of
you for choosing to
experience one at least of your multiple
incarnations with
us. And we now simply ask how may I
serve? Hello. Hello.
Hello. Hello.
Um, a friend of mine called me the other
day and his wife in Denver is dying. And
so he thought that if uh maybe you could
be of assistance to him, maybe I'll tell
you a little bit about her. Uh about 13
years ago, she had a surgery that was
supposed to take 45 minutes having to do
with the ovaries. It ended up taking 5
hours and she came out all bruised and
bit through her lips. And the only thing
the doctor said is it was touch and go.
And from that point on, she's had a
problem with her lungs.
Um then she had a son about three and a
half four years ago and then uh with the
birth of her son it really accelerated
to the point where they don't even have
a name for what it is that's happening
but what is actually going on is the
immune system is attacking her lungs as
if they're a transplant. Nice. And um
she would like to continue living now.
She has a wonderful son and husband and
and she's been to many doctors and flown
all over the country and nothing has
helped. She's on a lot of steroids right
now and
diuretics and uh it's still
progressing. And her name is uh Nancy
Gay Harris.
age. I think she's about 33, 36.
is the individual in your terminology
mobile barely with oxygen. She has to have
barely with oxygen. She has to have
oxygen around her all the time now. So,
but she's mainly bedridden now.
Are there three individuals in your
terminology close to her that can be
can be
willing to circle, if you will, this
individual one above the head when that
individual is lying down.
two to either
side at solar plexus
level. You understand? Yes.
These three
individuals, if they will close their
eyes and
place that
hand over solar
plexus, over third
eye, not touching physically the body,
and not touching physically each other's
hands, but layered as such. You follow
me? Mhm.
One hand of each individual over solar
plexus. One hand of each individual over
third eye. And in this
eye. And in this
mode with eyes closed and with deep
regular even
breathing to envision a bright blue
energy pouring into that individual,
pouring endlessly, relentlessly pouring
into that
individual for at least three of your
If possible, if they can maintain it for
at least 10 to 15 of your
minutes easily pouring that energy
in, they can perhaps be of assistance in
stabilizing the
body magnetically. Now that
Now that
individual can perhaps if such a
technology is available to you also over
what you call the lung area and solar
plexus area
area
plate a magnet. [Music]
There was for a moment for the channel
too much identification with the
individual. One moment while we bow. This
This
magnet placed with one side you would
call north facing the solar plexus.
Another magnet under the
individual the opposing
side can create through that area
magnetic stream which can aid and assist
in some alignment.
If in your terminology
electromagnetically those magnets can be
reversed in their polarity 7 and 1/2
times every
second that can create a
pulse that will align the individual's
electromagnetic field to the earth's
frequency which can also create a
stabilization within what you would call
the ionic exchange
process in the cellular structures of
the and would
and would
allow the
tissue to realign magnetically with the
rest of the cellular structure of the
body and not be considered invading
tissue. Can also strengthen the idea to
some degree of the immune system of the
individual at this
timing. For now, it is one of the
strongest things we can suggest. Okay.
It will be up to the
individual. But we do sense at this time
strongly within that particular
individual that they may be in their own
terms in her own
terms. They may be willing to create a
time of
transformation possibly physically out
of the body. It is very strong in their
energy. There is an opportunity
There is an opportunity
however for that individual and the
individuals which can be of assistance
to her to learn many
things. And if they learn certain things
along certain lines and if they all
agree that they can be served by
continuing to learn some of these things
and being of assistance to other
individuals by realigning that structure
then she may change her mind. Right now
it is our perception that in your
terminology it is 50/50.
She can go either
way. It will depend
upon the level of awakening and
activation that can occur within that
individual to allow her to know she can
align her system in that way and that
her friends can assist her. You follow
me? Yes. At this point, because it is in
your terminology teetering on the brink
of a
decision, this is all we are allowed to
do. Okay. Thank you. Thank
you. Sh.
Good evening, Bashar. I'm to you. My
name is Amy and I wanted to ask you a
question about an experience I had last
week. All right. Um, something occurred
here Thursday evening which was unusual
and the next morning when I went to
work, I was still in rather a reflective
frame of mind and aren't you always?
Yes. All right. All right. Thank you. I
um I went into the kitchen where I
worked to make some tea. The man I
worked for is a
composer and um for some reason he's
traveling. He's out of the country now
in a concert tour. So for some reason I
went into the room where his piano is
and I don't know why but I sat down at
his piano and lifted up the cover and
uncovered the
keyboard and I began to play nice
concert music. day.
I kept on playing and I heard applause
and I didn't look up. And then finally I
sense that there was someone next to me
and I looked up and it was a housekeeper
and she said that is beautiful. I didn't
know that you played. And you said and I
said neither did I.
Oh, you were there. You were there. So,
uh, I I still kind of my finger still
went over the keyboard. And she said,
"What was that you were playing?" And I
said, "Um, I'm not sure." And she said,
"Well, play that little song again
over." And I played a song and sang the
words and it was beautiful.
So, she said, "Wait, I'm going to go get
the tape recorder." She ran to go get
the tape recorder and she came back and
she said, "There's a business call." and
I had to stop and take the business call
and I rushed back to the piano and I sat
down again and I couldn't play
anymore. Now I my my employer is a very
talented man and a very good entertainer
and I was sitting at his piano. What I
was wondering is I have no doubt that he
channels a great deal of the music that
he gets. Oh yeah. Was I picking up
something that was meant for him or was
that for me?
Well, in a sense because you experienced
it, it was in that sense meant for you.
But in one sense, colloquially, you are
correct. You did allow yourself to sit
in the energy vortex in the area that is
conducive to that type of energy and you
were simply open enough to allow
yourself to use it in the same way.
I tried it again this morning and it
didn't work.
It will fluctuate from time to time, but
now you have built within yourself a
confidence question.
And that is why you are interrupting the
flow. I see. It is still there. It is.
Oh, yes. Again, remember that it ties in
very nicely also to what we were
previously talking about in terms of
multiple simultaneous incarnations. For
you have your own incarnations wherein
you are very musically inclined. And you
were simply allowing yourself in your
reflective mood to shift back and forth,
if you will, side to side if you will,
up and down if you will, across the idea
of the barriers of time and space. You
were simply more open, more willing to
be all the ideas you have been and allow
whatever energy was present in that area
to inspire you, literally inspire you at
that moment. You were simply sensitive.
Should I follow that excitement? I mean,
do you think it's
it is up to you. There are no shoulds.
However, it is our perception that in
general, it is not so much that you
necessarily have to continue to express
it in that way. Mhm. It can allow you to
know how open and malleable you are in
any type of endeavor. You may find
yourself walking into similar situations
of a different type and performing some
actions that you also didn't know you
knew how to perform other than music as
well. It is simply one way to let you
know that you are anything you wish to
be. And as we have said, at any given
moment when you are fully that idea, you
know what you need to know when you need
to know it. So in being the musician at
that moment, you knew everything you
needed to know to be a musician and it
was quite natural for you.
But you did allow yourself to
participate in that energy that is
present within that area.
Okay. Um then
uh I was going to say I I have
organizational skills and that's why I'm
there administratively. However, I feel
that there's another reason why I am
with this man at this time and I don't
think it just has to do with office
work. All right. Is there um is there
anything you can add to that? No. No.
Because you will find out when it
unfolds naturally as you have already
begun to do. Okay. One of the ideas as
we have already pointed out is to allow
you to understand a new form of
organizational expression, a flexibility
of
structure. That any idea at any moment
creates its own structure, but in no
way, shape or form does that mean you
are stuck or rigidized in that
structure. Ah, okay. That's good. If I
publish the music, do I have to give him
a
co-writing title? You may ask that
individual. Okay. All right. The other
thing I was um thank you for that. And
the other thing that I was going to
bring up was that um though I'm fairly
recent attendee here. I was having a
conversation uh earlier this week with
somebody that one moment. Yes. You were
quote unquote here quote unquote three
of your months before you were here
physically.
Oh, thank you. I knew I was
somewhere. Thank you very much. I
appreciate that. Um the other the other
uh question that I was going to bring up
was about vocabulary. I was speaking
with a friend that I had met here
coincidentally and uh in the course of
the conversation I said oh I'm sorry and
uh I was corrected by saying that that
was a negative term and I should not
use. Now before you go on, yes, many of
the ideas we have shared with you in
that way. Well, we have in many ways
been playing with you to just sort of as
you say knock you out a little bit of
the structures you have lived within. In
no way, shape or form do we mean to
force you to pay attention to every
single word you utter, for that is a
different type of structure and far more
limiting than the previous one.
All right. We do not mean that you have
to catch yourself at every single
phrase. If you know what you mean in
that sense, then just saying certain
words doesn't necessarily mean that you
are limiting yourself. I see. So words
like hope and I will try and sorry do
have a place in your vocabulary. They're
not necessarily a product of negative
thinking. Generally, some of them can be
Generally, some of them can be
representative of negative thinking. And
you may find yourself simply not using
those, but not necessarily to the
extreme that some of you may assume we
have been talking about.
Okay. Well, I don't see myself indulging
in self-pity. I'm in control of myself
and I then don't worry about many of the
vernacular that you use. If you know
what you mean, that's then simply
recognize that. Well, my friend isn't
here tonight, so I want to thank him and
thank you and
you. Thank you very much. Sure.
Bashar. Nice. In
um thinking on prosperity. Yes. Um I
came across an idea that I would like to
ask you about because I believe as you
have said in the fourth density that you
don't don't have money. I did not say
that. Oh, I never said that. Pay
attention. Good. I said that abundance
is the ability to do what you need to do
when you need to do it. Money is only
one tool of abundance. Now, you may find
that in fourth density further along,
you may choose to not necessarily need
that tool. I did not say it will not be
there. You follow me? Yes, I do. The
more you interact directly with each
other, exchange for exchange, service
for service, the less likelyhood there
will be for an intermediate symbol. Very
often your money supply that
intermediate symbol. So in that sense,
it is in all likelihood going to become
in your terms unnecessary. I did not say
that you had to get rid of it in order
to have fourth density. I see. Well,
that was what I was wanting to ask you
about was more of an understanding of of
that idea of exchange and how to because
I I find that when I remove the idea
that I have to have money for a certain
object and just believe that the object
that I'm bonded with it and it is mine
that it comes seems to come quicker when
I don't put the money in between. Simply
because many times money is not the path
of least resistance. That is all. If
there is a time when money is the path
of least resistance, then the money will
come. All we are saying is allow whatever
All we are saying is allow whatever
represents the path of least resistance
to be the symbol of abundance that comes
into your life. Don't resist other
symbols just because they aren't money
because many of them can bring you the
idea you desire more quickly than the
money can. But sometimes the money may
be the quickest way. But you will know
it obviously if it is because money will
be there before anything else. Mhm.
I see. One way or another. Okay. Okay.
The other question I had was um shedding
a little light on a dream that I had
that was rather funny. All right. I did
uh an Indian sweat lodge which is a
concentrated uh prayer in a sweat lodge
other people in the nude and uh it was a
wonderful experience for me and
afterwards I had a dream that I was in
my uh car which turned into a beautiful
new bright red car which it did within a
week. Nice. And uh and all the people
that were in the sweat lodge were with
me in the car. Uh not sexually or
anything, but just together having a
sort of a party, driving away in one
direction, and then the dream stopped.
And then we drove away in another
direction and then the dream stopped.
And we drove in all four directions
having a party in my beautiful red car.
What light do you need to shed on that?
Well, I think part of it was the the u
the symbology of the four directions was
more what I Well, it is symbolic
obviously of the migrational four
directions of what you call your native
Americans in that way. Simply the
representation of the four corners of
the earth.
You now cover the whole territory.
You face in all directions. You are
looking at all probabilities. You are
experiencing all life, all levels in
that way. And it is also a fourth
density symbol obviously. Oh, of course.
Think of that one. Okay. Thank you very
much. Well, thank you very much for
sweating it out.
But in a very real way, that is a very
strong technique. And the thing that
many individuals find themselves getting
squarely in touch with in placing
themselves in those meditative states is
that all of the so-called objects in
your reality are not out there. They are
in there.
And you can in many senses allow them
then to come out. Fabulous. Lots of love
to you and to you an infinite amount.
You will be around long enough to use it
all up. Shing.
Shing.
Good day to sh unto you. How are things
on Earth this time? Perfect. How are
things on Earth? We're perfect all the
time. No, thank you. Um, I've been
thinking about your question, how may I
serve you? For several weeks now, and I
keep coming back to thinking that
perhaps the answer is how may how may we
serve our
planet? And then last week, you
suggested some wonderful ideas. Yes.
Which we will discuss after the break
this evening of your time. Okay. Well,
I've come up with an idea I'd like to
share. All right. In fact, I've sent a
letter already to the editor of the Los
Angeles Times and uh explore the idea
with him of perhaps
allowing himself to print in the paper
more and more um information about
interactions with quote unquote
extraterrestrials. All right.
information about UFO sightings because
all right obviously more and more in our
society we are becoming aware of this
and I'm sure that even he knows that
perhaps um well if he reads my letter he
will I cited his book communion yes yes
I understand what you're saying uh and
also the fact that we have now have
movies and television shows about
extraterrestrials and I suggested that
um perhaps
The government would be interested in
knowing how many people truly would like
to know that and if he would ask for his
readers to send him a sampling of their
opinion that might be a good indication.
So I suggested perhaps a poll
interested could immediately write into
the paper and say yes I would like to
hear more about this. Well thank you
very much. This will be included in the
list of ideas that will go into creating
a program that you can share with your
government to allow them to share
information with you. Thank you. Um, I
have a question for my friend Sheila.
She and her husband Dino couldn't come
tonight, but last Thursday after being
here, they became aware of a presence.
Um, in fact, I believe she told me that
she had a dream in which she was talking
with the person who said that he comes
from the same place as Bashar. And
they've been aware of this for a week
now and had a certain amount of
communication with this being. And she
wanted me to ask you if you could tell
her more about it and how. All we can
say at this time is that it may
represent an
energy maybe that can be physically born onto
maybe that can be physically born onto
Earth.
Okay, I'll let her know that. Thank you.
Thank you. Someone from your world. That
is all we can say at this time.
Okay. Thank you. Um there's something
else I want to know. I showed Daryl a
couple of uh photographs this evening um
when he first got here that a friend of
mine had taken this summer, one in
Copenhagen and one later on in Florence,
Italy. And he wasn't sure whether it was
light coming into the camera from an
outside source that created this
smokelike effect or whether he had
actually captured an entity on film. It
is not colloally what you would call an
entity. Okay. Um, I'm sure it was no
accident. And I'll just allow him to
figure out what it means. It can be
self-reflective in many ways, but we
perceive it has particular meaning on
what you would call a very pragmatic and
physical level with regard to the idea
of what your friend himself sees in life
and what gets imprinted on the film of
his own mentality.
What is obscured and what is clear?
So perhaps he sees more than he's aware
of. Also, it may be an
Also, it may be an
example on a different level like
lightly of someone in a sense following
the light but perhaps allowing the light
to blind them a bit and obscure the
picture that they really need to see.
Mhm. Well, it'll be fascinating without All
Well, it'll be fascinating without All
right. Thank you very much, Michelle.
Thank you very much. simply remind that
individual this simply our perspective
is this simply our opinion. Yes. Thank
you. Good night. And do you
sure do you I wanted to thank you so
much for the workshop that we had on.
Well, thank you for cocreating it and it
really changed my life um quite a lot.
And I wanted to ask you I had the most
intense feeling of coming home.
Will you do me a favor before you
continue on? Yes. Will you restate your
last phrase for me? Instead of it has
changed my life, I have chosen to change
my life. I have chosen to change my life
and I've seen many changes that have
begun last two weeks. Incredible. Bloody
exciting. It is. I in conjunction with
that uh one of the things that donate
asked too was how we can be of service
in hoping to bring about this fourth
dimensional awareness. Okay. And I also
had a question in reference to a dream I
had two nights ago that was quite vivid
in reference to extraterrestrials and
wanting to know if this was just some
sort of a fantasy on my part or if
indeed this was an attempt at
communication. On one level it is true
communication. Do remember that all
imagination is real. on some level
somewhere, some when you follow me? Yes,
I do. It is up to you to determine
whether or not you wish to realize it
into your frequency or not. All fantasy
is potential reality in your
terminology. I
understand. Um, is there any way that you can tell
Um, is there any way that you can tell
me what uh in particular I would prefer
to do or if I what excites you the most?
I know. I've heard that before. Well,
you're right.
Okay, that was lightly what I had to
ask. That's all there is to it. It's
that easy. No big mystery. Thank you for
sure. No, thank you very much. Enjoy,
Jenny. I know for sure. I'm too easy.
Um, I spoke with you last week about a
pregnancy and I think I misunderstood
your response to me. Um you had talked
about a pregnancy on a parallel um level
and my interpretation of that was that I
was merely manif through through some
sort of connection. I was merely
manifesting the symptoms.
In one sense, yes. Although there is
from time to time in certain individuals
upon your planet a true what you would
call momentary temporary inhabitation
that comes in and goes out.
Well, um, well, okay. Well, now I'm now the
um, well, okay. Well, now I'm now the
test show that I am pregnant. Yeah. But
I'm I'm con I'm still confused. But it's
all right.
Many of these will come back in and
remain born in your reality. Some of
them will go out and be born quote
unquote on other
levels. It depends upon the agreements
you have made as to whether or not they
will stay in your frequency or be born
in another one. So the option right now
has to do with my determining whether I
will carry this two term or not. It has
to do with that and it has to do with
who you are and what you wish to do and
who the child is to you and what you
have done before together and what you
can learn from this child's ability to
go back and forth and back and forth.
Recognize again that the barriers are
breaking down between all the parallel
realities and all the alternate lives.
And in it sense the child quote unquote
child is
deciding along with you and all the
other use in the parallel realities
which one will be the focus of the
motherhood specifically. Oh it is still
up for
grabs. You are all the
mother but it will determine which one
will physically manifest the idea to
what you would call term.
Um and you may find that when enough
sharing and blending has
occurred, all of the parallel use may
come to term and that being coming into
your reality may come in with a
conscious recognition of all of its
twins in all the parallel lines.
You understand? Uh yes, I'm beginning
to. All right. There is no need to be
lost in the labeling. Go with what
happened. It is happening according to
agreement. Nothing is out of place.
All right. Um I I am having some uh
confusion in terms of just my physical
reality and the fact that I'm not in a
relationship or a situation. Um so
um I'm concerned about the idea of
having a child.
Why? Because I am single and um so
Because I am single and um so
well I it it seems to me to be a
difficult thing for a woman to raise a
It does not have to be. If you decide
that it's something you do not want,
then in all likelihood you will not have
it.
Um if I if I chose not to Yes. Would I
have an opportunity to allow this this
entity to come through me at another um
time? Yes.
Yes.
So it doesn't have to be right now. It
does not have to be. No. Although
recognize if it does then by definition
it must be the perfect time. And if you
take that to heart all of a sudden you
may realize you are quite capable of
handling it. It is up to you. It is all
paradoxical. No need for negative
confusion. Go with what occurs. What
occurs is your agreement. And if it is
by your agreement, you must be able to
handle it. You knew what you were doing. All
it. You knew what you were doing. All
you have to do is trust that you still
do. So whatever occurs, you know you
made the choice. And if you know you
made the choice, then obviously in
knowing what you were doing, you can
handle it. So relax. Mhm. All right.
Yeah. Yeah. All right. What I can do is
uh open up your dream communication with
this being. Talk with this being. Let
the being talk with you in your
imagination, in your dreams. Be
intimate. You are in a relationship with
that being. Talk with
it. Let it soothe you. Let it reassure
you that you are in control and that it
will do nothing against your will.
All right. Yeah. When you go to sleep,
relax. Talk with it as you drift off.
You will have
conversations. The more you relax about
this, the more you will remember the
conversation when you wake up. Do it as
many nights as it takes for you to
relax. All right.
Okay. Thank you. Thank you very
much. Sharing. Hello Bashar and to you.
It's very exciting to be talking to you
today. Very exciting to be talking to
you. Extremely exciting. Thank you. There's
Extremely exciting. Thank you. There's
two main things that I'd like to uh All
right. Number one. Number one is
sculpting. Sculpting. That's my
favorite. Good. In the past, you have
talked about sculpting with intention
and sculpting with light. Would you
expound on those those ideas? When you
begin to recognize and realize truly on
a physical level that you are made of
light and that everything is made of
light and when you blend in a sense the
separation between physical and
non-physical energy then you can
literally know you are able to gather
together out of the electromagnetic
aeromagnetic mentality in the air if you
wish a concentration of energy that will
begin to manifest as what may appear to
gaseous or liquid light and by your
thoughts you can shape it
literally to various degrees of
solidification and then let it
dissolve. You follow somewhat. All
right. Take me literally. All right. I
am talking about creating what you would
call sculptures out of thin air, out of
light, out of the energy inherent in
space and time itself. How can I work on
being able to do this myself? Use your
imagination. Thank you. That is what it
is for. And also recognize to begin with
that there is nothing invalid about
using the materials you have at hand
since everything is made of light. And
as you experiment with the various
materials you have, choose more and more
and more pliable ones, less and less and
less structured ones until all of a
sudden, bit by bit,
someday you will begin to
recognize that those things without form
will all of a sudden begin to manifest
form for you. and you will know you are
on the threshold of physical and
non-physical dreamlike reality. It will
take truly stepping into the dimension
of your dream imagination and not being
afraid not being afraid that you will
lose what you call your mind.
You follow me? Yes, I do. Thank you. The
idea also by beings upon our world is
that from time to time three of us will
get together and we will project in
between us a space an idea of that light
a medium if you will in which a
non-physical consciousness can take
embodiment temporarily. we sustain it and sustain
temporarily. we sustain it and sustain
its vibratory ability to manifest in our
frequency. That is another way you can
allow others of other levels to sculpt
in your medium when you allow that
medium to be concentrated enough and of
a particular vibratory frequency that
they can manipulate in that
sense. That is another
idea. All right. Okay. Um there is a
sculpture that has grown in my
imagination for some time. I see it very
clearly now but I feel as if the
materials are not yet available to me.
What does it look like? It the sculpture
or the material? Both. The sculpture is
if you were to take a a stellagmite
perhaps I don't know what they're
called. They're from the ground they
raise stagmite. Okay. Blackactite on the
ceiling. You take one of those, you
compress it so that you have an oval
shape all the way up and down. Then you
take and you spin that all the way up
and you have a spiral. My sculpture is a
series of those from approximately 7 ft
high down that one can walk through. The
material is made of something that when
one walks through it, it raises the
vibrational energy of the being through
the light waves. I see it as being
translucent. There is a whitish crystalline material.
There is a whitish crystalline material.
Yes, there's a sparkling element to it.
I there's part of me knows that this is
used in cities on I don't know if it's
your planet or other planets and I've
seen it and it's a but I don't know what
it is and I don't know how it's a
crystallin metallic if you
wish polymer fusion is it it's poured is
that correct it is grown it's grown okay
I' I' I've heard you talk about that
before that's a little beyond our
technology at the moment is it not
almost not okay good I I sense that the
time is not right for me to do this Yet
it has been growing and I but I sense it
at the time is it's a maybe 3 5 years.
You can if you wish because of your
excitement and your interests you can
attract yourself also to different as
you say disciplines upon your planet
that may allow you to gather all the
elements necessary. You can be
responsible for creating this material
if you wish.
You can begin to some degree with some
of the understanding of what you call
liquid crystal.
I have no understanding of that at the
moment. Go and find out.
Okay. Uh where would I do that?
Research your literature. There may be
individuals that are present with you
this night of your time that can point
you in a particular direction. Thank
you. Thank you. Thank you. That's the
first thing I wanted to talk about. The
second concern you're sharing tonight,
yes. Um, those of us who have some
memory of quote past lives, uh, we are
then what you're saying is that we
really have awareness of simultaneous
lives. Okay. That is why you do not have
to reach into the dim dark past or
stretch into the foggy future to have
awareness of these ideas because they
are right here right now. Okay. Um
though then what happens when we meet uh
individuals that we know we have known
before is it and not before is it in
other realities that we know them and we
are now interacting with them. Yes,
colloquially it can be before but now
that you understand it is all
simultaneous then obviously yes it is
ongoing right now. You are having an
interaction with them in another format
somewhere else somewhere else right now.
Okay. Um I have one last little
question. Oh boy.
Um we we are uh simultaneously uh
existing as are you I assume.
Absolutely. And therefore we're not just
on earth. We're on many planes and many
planets. Is that correct? Yes. Okay. We
have agreed for some reason to come into
this reality at this time and place and
experience the limitations that we have
agreed upon. And your expansion out of
them. Okay. That's what I wanted to ask
you. But what the benefit is then of
your coming in and helping us to change
this if we have we are a part of that
expansion. So then we are a part of you.
When we expand you expand and we can all
expand together. Yes. Thank you. It
makes it fun.
Thank you very much. Thank you very
much. Shannon.
Hello Bashar. Done to you. Um I'm going
to have a baby soon. All right. And I
was wondering
I hope so. I was wondering what you
could tell me about the agreement that's
been made between this child and the
father and myself. My my
my do you understand that the so-called
agreements we are referring to are
usually expressed in very general
thematic sweeping ideas. The specifics of how you
sweeping ideas. The specifics of how you
fulfill that agreement come moment to
moment to moment to moment in your
physical interaction. Yes.
One strong connection we can share with
you is that that particular individual
have a strong pension for what you would
call masonry or
architecture. We'll let you build upon
that. [Music]
[Music]
Okay. Thank you. There might be the
ability to have that individual together
with you lay a foundation for many many
many interactions that you have had are
having. But at this
time simply allow your life to unfold.
Everything you need to know will play
itself out in the life you allow to
unfold in a natural way by doing the
things that excite you the most. You
will allow yourself to be aware of all
the agreements you are
making. Remember again that when you say
agreements you have made, they are
agreements in the making right
now. So it is up to you. It is not for
us to tell you. It is up to you right
now. There are certain things we can
sense about the decisions you may have
made, but you may change those
tomorrow. But you are far more free to
decide than perhaps you think. That
might be one of the agreements you have
made to loosen up the parameters of
structure because that individual is
very familiar with
structure and can express an
understanding of how to loosen some of
that structure up with you. A more
expansive expression of the architecture
of your world.
All right. All right. Thank you. Thank
you. Sure.
Good evening. Unto you. I recently chose
to communicate with myself by means of a
a misalignment in my spine. I was
wondering if you could help clarify my
understanding of the the message
contained in the symbol. And at what
level? Um mentally is the misalignment.
Um physically at least. Yes. At what
level? Literally. physically uh on your
body at the vertebras that are named T10
and 11 right over the solar plexus and a
vertebrae named L5
um at or near the sacral center. Also, I
was wondering if you could help me
facilitate say something that would help
me facilitate communication with myself
in a more perfect way. A more perfect
way. A less painful way. All right.
At least less painful. For how long in
your terms of time have you created this
discomfort? Um, five
days. Much longer.
Um, without being active
though, have you allowed yourself to
avail yourself of any suggestions from
your own imagination, sir?
Yes, I think I have. But my
understanding is not clear on what uh
what I'm trying to communicate to myself
through the means of this event. But
perhaps you are looking at it too
analytically. Yeah, probably the idea
perhaps is to simply say well all right
I wish to communicate whatever I'm
communicating in a less negative way in
a more positive way. So imagination how
can I do this? Have you done that? Have
you ask your imagination to give you a
method, a ritual if you will, that will
allow you to experience the
communication in a more positive way,
which will allow you to open up and
understand what the communication is to
begin with. No, I haven't. Why not? Uh,
the thought didn't occur to me actually.
All right. Perhaps it couldn't get
there. Yeah. Now that it has occurred to you,
Yeah. Now that it has occurred to you,
now that we have bridged the short
circuit, allow yourself in that way to
begin considering, asking your own
imagination. And when you have the
spontaneous revelation in your own
mentality, that energy can shoot down
the spine, straighten it out, form the
connection, and allow the energy to rush
up the spine, that will then spark a new
revelation in you. And you can continue
that idea back and forth, back and forth
at a more accelerated pace to straighten
yourself out in that way.
Perhaps in a sense you have created the
blockage, the cutting off of
communication from yourself so that you
would not have to quote unquote listen
to what you have to say. There may be
something in what you will tell yourself
that you are not settled with. Something
you are not yet comfortable with about
relying upon your instinct and
intuition. So in allowing us to bridge that gap, we
So in allowing us to bridge that gap, we
now simply suggest that one of the
primary things you can do and begin to
learn to assist
yourself is to utilize your imagination
and simply ask your imagination for a
method that will work for you in
receiving the communication in a
positive way. Then trust what you get.
Act upon it.
Thank you very much. Thank you.
You are always connected to every part
of everything you need to be. Trust that
whatever comes along those lines of
communication will be something that you
can use in a positive
way. Also
remember absolute power does not corrupt
absolutely unless you absolutely believe
it. That is something that is very
That is something that is very
subconsciously
planted in many members of your society
about the idea of allowing yourself to
truly expand and experience the
unlimited aspect of your energy in a
painless
way. You do not have to suffer in order
to deserve ecstasy. Shedding.
Hello, Bashar. And to you. I think you
solved a mystery for me. Oh my. I've had
trouble all my life with a poor memory.
Like it didn't do me any good to learn
anything if I couldn't remember it. But
I but I'm looking back over my life when
I read something that really excited me.
Like 10 years ago, I read The Secret
Life of Plants and I still remember
everything in the book cuz it was it
really excited me. But uh
Dad I was curious about one of the
things in the secret life of plant that
thing that really excited me was
vibration a lot about vibration.
Everything is vibration. Okay. They they
got into this thing on the vibration
like the body was they use an angstrom
unit as a unit of measure. 6800 angstrom
units and every disease had a specific
vibratory rate. Yes. and live green
fruit and vegetables fresh had a
vibratory rate like 10,000 angstrom
units which would raise the body's
vibratory rate. That is why tonality can
be important in allowing an individual
to rebalance and recenter themselves.
For if you impose an atmosphere around
an individual of a certain frequency
that represents their ideal balanced
state then their cellular structure can
begin to identify with that rather than
continue to identify with the vibratory
state of the disease. I see that is why
the idea of chanting and tones play a
strong part in centering in meditation
and creating a state of health. I see
one of the mysteries they had in the
book was they they didn't understand why
the water at Lord's France was vibrating
at like 50,000 angstrom units. People
would go there and get in the water and
throw their cut crutches away. And yes,
it is because it is connected also to
another level of consciousness and
therefore represents an interface
between a higher vibratory frequency and
your I
see on one of the tapes you had said
that we would find in the future that a
microwave oven does something to water
that's beneficial. Would that be raising
the vibratory rate of water? Yes. I
see. Another thing I was curious about
is Elron Huard in his writings had
differentiated between recalling and
remembering. And I'd even tried what he
said on it. Like my 12-year-old niece
had to remember the last time she played
in the snow and had to recall the last
time she played in the snow. Okay. In
recalling, she just goes step by step
through the whole sequence. Yes. Could
you comment on that? Recalling is simply
living in the now, the incident which is
still going on. I see.
Okay. Thank you. Thank you very much.
Shout it.
Bashar, I have continually been creating
a um series of committing myself to do
something and then spontaneously not
wanting to do it when the time comes to
follow through with that commitment. All
right. May I ask you a question? Yes.
Why do you commit yourself to begin
with? Because the idea at the time that
I commit excites me that enough that I
want to do it. Will you answer a
question for me? Yes. Define commitment.
I'll wait. Thank you.
What is your definition of commitment?
Um, I'm not sure. All right. Then why
are you doing it?
Maybe. Then how do you know you are
doing it if you don't know what it is?
Well, it's something that I want to do
in the future. So
why you don't know what it is? How do
you know you want to do
it? If you know you want to do it, then
you must know what it is. What is it?
Well, what does it
mean? What is commitment?
It's following through on something.
Following through to whose parameters?
An agreed upon parameter. Agreed upon
parameter. even if it violates your integrity.
Well, it seems like that's what I've
been doing.
All right. But perhaps you have only
been structuring yourself beyond your
need. Perhaps you have only been
creating an assumption that if you do
not do it in such and such a manner,
then you will not have gotten out of it
what you need to get out of it. and you
will not have been of service in the way
you needed to be of service. Perhaps if
you will relax your definition, whatever
definition you might have within you
about what that is, then perhaps in that
way you will understand that you can
attract individuals into your life who
will simply interact and create
agreements with you that are already
representative of what you know to be
true of who you are. Rather than perhaps
creating agreements that may be
representative of what your society
thinks you should be.
And then you will always fulfill all the
commitments you make because all the
commitments you make will be gerine to
who you
are and there will be no problem in
fulfilling it because it will be a
natural act.
Okay. I'm not sure if I'm following you
correctly. So what I need to do is relax
the idea that I have that structure is
the commitment to some degree, but also
understand the definition of what you
are committing to because you may be
making a
commitment on something that you really
are not excited about doing to begin
with. You may be making that commitment
to appease other individuals and only
that. You may be making that commitment
not out of service but out of
servitude. Examine that the things you
are doing in your life are actually
reflective or not of who you are.
Because if you continue to make a
commitment on something that you are not
all about, it will be very difficult for you
about, it will be very difficult for you
to carry that through because you are
not you. Okay? So that's why I
continually experience getting up to the
moment and not wanting to follow through
with it to some degree. Okay. Some of
these ideas as they are experienced in
your society may also come from a lack
of trust that you have the capability of
doing so. Mhm. Perhaps again because you
place certain parameters of structure
upon yourself that tell you well you
have to do it this way in order to allow
that to be manifested or accomplished
and that is not always necessarily so.
So you may back off from the commitment
just because it looks like you have to
do it in a way that is not conducive of
who you are but that is not necessarily
so. Okay. Allow again your imagination
to stretch. There are many ways to do a
thing. Many ways. Thank you. When you
make your decision, your
choices, then allow yourself the
freedom to attract to you the things
that are representative of who you are
and therefore the things that will
naturally allow you to fulfill them.
Just because you'll be so excited about
them all the way through, it'll be over
with before you know it.
Okay. If you are able to pay that much
attention to every little step going on,
it doesn't sound like you're having a
very good time to begin with.
You follow me? Yes. Does that assist you
very much? Well, thank you very, very
much. Thank you.
Shanning. Hi, Bashar. And to you. One of the
Hi, Bashar. And to you. One of the
things that's been exciting me most
lately, especially since the workshop,
is uh establishing stronger
communication with my higher self. But
sometimes I think communication doesn't
always come through as clearly as it
can. All right. All right. A little bit
of redefinition. Once again, remember
that you are still thinking in a
segregationist manner. You are not truly
establishing communication with a
separate higher self. By acting upon the
things in life that excite you the most,
you are acting as the higher self in
physical terms. That is establishing
communication with the higher
self. Being the higher self, being what
you imagine the higher self would be if
the higher self were physical, which it
is. H
H
food for thought. Yes. If I were to ask
you, is there anything that my higher
self would want to communicate to me at
this time? What excites you the most? Do
it and you will be living as the higher
self and then you will know exactly what
the higher self is trying to tell you
because you will be the higher self in
physical terms and your thoughts will be
its thoughts. Its thoughts are your
thoughts. Okay, you will be one thing.
Okay, that makes sense. Then your
decisions, your conscious commandment,
your recognition of your excitement,
your recognition of your integrity will
be the same recognitions of the higher
self. You will be the higher self in
physical terms. Okay. It is that easy.
Good. I have one other question. A
couple weeks ago, you said that there
was an individual from another dimension
that I would be learning more about.
Yes. And I was just wondering, did I
have contact with this individual when I
was a child? Yes, I did. Okay. Can you
elaborate on that? Oh, heck. Be the
higher self. The higher self remembers
who it
is. So, the sooner you are the higher
self, the
clearer you will, the more obviously you
will attract to you the information and
you will recognize it. You will recall
it. Okay. Be the higher self because
that friend is on the same
friend is on the same
level as your higher self. So when you
are the higher self, you will be that
level and you will be able to interact
more immediately with your friend.
Okay. You follow? Yes, I do. Well, thank
you very much. You may all at this
timing take a show break and we will
resume contact. How's everything
going? in the room over here. Audio. [Music] All right. All right.
continue.
And do you? Uh, this week a crystal came
into my life and the moment I picked it
up, I could feel the power in the
crystal and knew that I was meant to
experience it. Remember that you are
only feeling your own power. Okay. Um,
the idea is that the crystal is of
course energy and there is power in that
idea, but it is also a reflective tool.
It is a trigger for the power you are.
So you're feeling your own
potentiality, your own vibrating
anticipated. Okay. Uh a friend of mine
who is very familiar with crystal told
me that it's the record keeper of
crystal. Um I have an idea of what I
think that means. I believe it's a store
of information. Um I was wondering if
you can tell me anything in particular I
can do during meditation to attune
myself to vibration and to knowledge.
Did you find the crystal? Uh, she set
some crystals in front of me and and I
picked up this one. Why?
I was attracted to it. Then you are
already attuned to it.
What do you mean? What do I have to do
to become attuned to it? You picked it
up. You're attuned to it.
That makes sense. All right.
I was just wondering in meditation if
there's anything particular um that I
can do to enhance what is already
there. Recall the idea of Atlantean times and
Recall the idea of Atlantean times and
also what you might term
extraterrestrial connection. From your
consciousness you can understand that
the crystallin lattice work has the
capability magnetically in your
terminology of storing information.
You can simply with your
imagination project that idea into the
crystal and you can in that sense use
the crystal as a symbol to transfer that
information from individual to
individual as a meditative tool as an
enhancement as an accelerator as a
multiplier for you. But basically what
it will do is bring you more and more
into the now moment. Because when you
are fully in the now moment, then you
know all you need to know about anything
you are doing at that particular
moment. Conversely, of course, you will
probably know very little about anything
else. But you will not need to.
You follow it? Yes, I do. Um, lately
I've been
aware through uh the dream state that my
spirit guide is probably a child. Um, a
small boy, I believe.
Um, I was wondering if he has any
messages for me.
Only that you learn to play with him.
Only that you learn to play as
him. Allow the child you are to come
out. The idea of what you are learning
as fourth density
beings is that you are learning the act
of play. You are learning to be the
children of the earth, the children of
the stars that you are. Understand
are. Understand
something. It is no
accident that many of what you
term extraterrestrial civilizations have an
extraterrestrial civilizations have an
embodiment form that you would probably
call very childlike instruction. [Music]
Take it from an [Music]
[Music]
expert. So simply learn to play with
that child as that child as the child
you are. It can be a wonderful guide by
simply reflecting to you the ultimate
and unlimited joy of spontaneous
discovery every single moment just like
a child.
Uh I also want to ask you one quick
question there. Um
I've experienced along with my roommate
uh a present an entity in our new home.
Um, the entity seems to be in the
woodwork and cabinets mostly. I was
wondering if the why the entity is
there. If it's connected to the house
more or to us,
both or you would not have found
yourself there. There is something you
can learn from this endeavor and simply
for now recognize that 99.9% of what you
will experience will be extensions of
your own consciousness expressing itself
in a seemingly exteriorized embodiment.
But there is other energy attached to
it. It is there for a reason, its own
reasons. And you are there for your own
reasons. And some of your reasons and
its reasons mesh.
Okay? Some of it has to do with things
you have
been. And it has to do with an
understanding you can impart to it even
at it understand itself and impart its
understanding to
you. There is something to
share. To some degree you are
experiencing a little bit, let us say a
thinning if you will, of the fabric that
usually exists
between one life and another life.
Okay, thank you. Thank you very much.
Happy homecoming.
Shanning. Yeah. Hello. And to you. Um
since uh quite an early age uh I had
been particularly attracted to certain
type of music right I find it
unbelievably attractive and uh whenever
I I get to listen to this um type of
music I
it's really internal tinglings and I'm
quite oblivious to anything else is is
anything more about it well our
particular perception of the tonality
would seem to invoke
strains upon the instrument you would
most often refer to as a harpsicord or a
clavacord in that way. Some of this idea
may no pun intended strike a chord
within you. The idea to some degree simply is
you. The idea to some degree simply is
once again reflective of a bleed through
of different aspects of yourself. Also
in this life you can put into pragmatic
use your understanding of tonality.
You're understanding that the reason it
moves you as it does is because the
vibratory harmonics represent certain
mathematical ratios that you can utilize
in this life now to express the creation
of spaces, shapes, and forms that can be
very conducive to placing other
individuals and yourself in states of
being that will allow them also to
connect into all the other aspects of
their being that are ongoing
simultaneously. Now when you say can utilize the the
Now when you say can utilize the the
harmonics in what in what way?
You can explore what you call the
mathematical ratios between the
different vibratory tones and there is a
way to translate that idea in what you
would call physical architecture,
physical shape.
Okay. Um second quick question. uh a
family with which I'm very friendly have
had uh one moment one
moment you can also very strongly attach
this idea of tonality to the vibratory
frequency of different crystallin
structures this is something you are
very I'll say you are very familiar with
in Atlantis
you are recognizing the power of sound
yes I get the sense of extreme power.
When this thing as your literature says,
in the beginning was the word.
All is vibration. It is the same
phrase. All is vibration. In the
beginning was the
word. It is the same phrase.
Please continue. Okay. Uh there was a
family um very friendly who had had
seemed to me more than their fair share
of illness. First the the father had
cancer and decided to apparently get
cured. Then their daughter had leukemia.
Um then the medical people gave her the
wrong injection and she became paralyzed
with it. Now the mother has had major
surgery because of a problem with the
ovaries. Um what what what might it be about
Um what what what might it be about
these people that uh allows them to
create all these apparent problems
because they they they may be simply
working many things out between
themselves sort of keeping it in the
family in that way. agreeing to be with
each other to reflect certain ideas back
and forth that they may be deciding to
work out perhaps through the ideas of
connections to other lives as well to
allow them to experience certain degrees
of excessive limitation now can be one
way for individuals to choose to
accelerate themselves more quickly
through it. Not that they have to
experience it in a negative way, but
many individuals in your society choose
extreme negative limitation so that they
will in a sense get all of the
limitation out of the way very quickly.
Um when I'm when I was with these people
at Christmas time uh I uh was explaining
our interaction uh with you and uh
trying to get over to them some some of
the concepts that we that we talk about
here and there was a great deal of
resistance. I was wondering is there any
particular way in which I can perhaps
express to them the idea that maybe they
they that it's not all negative what
they're going through and and they may
be able to find something. The easiest
way for you to do that is if you believe
in that lifestyle live it so that you
are a living example so that you can
allow them to see in you that it works
for you which then will give them the
best opportunity to choose to allow
themselves to know it can work for them
if they choose to. There is no other way
to force them, no other way to show
them. They must prove it to themselves.
The easiest way you can do so to help
them is by living it and proving it to
yourself so they can see you as a living
example. The idea of that type of
resistance is an indication of why they
are experiencing many of the energies
they are. For all disease is the product
of resisting one's own ecstasy. Okay.
Um, is this an appropriate time to
mention an idea for the uh communicating
with the government? Uh, on No, I don't
know. Mention it and let's see if it's
an appropriate time.
Well, I wasn't sure whether we up some
specific time for this. Okay. Okay. I
mentioned one moment. Three, two, one.
Now, [Music]
[Music]
are you ready? Well, uh, very very
briefly last week I mentioned I had the
idea of producing a um some kind of
movie that would perhaps uh warm the
people up to the general idea. I've
during the week I I've written some sort
of criteria by which this uh this movie
could come into um could be formed
around. I'm not a a writer or anything
like that. So I You're
not I haven't written any noses or
anything like that. But um anyway, I
have created this sort of general uh
list of requirements. All right. And uh
do share. Oh, if you want it will take a
minute or two. Will that be all right?
Mention a few of the ideas. Okay. Each
and every one of you that have your
ideas be writing them down, be compiling
them if you wish in this way also
because there will be facilitation and
organization through the physical
channel as well. Make copies if you will
bring them to these interactions. Leave
the copies and at the end of what you
now call your present month, there will
be compilation and discussion of all the
different ideas you deem will work most
smoothly and all of those ideas will be
placed into a format that will represent
the particular if you will petition that
will be sent.
Okay, very quickly then I've divided
this up into five little paragraphs. The
first one is a require only defines the
requirements then the a concept about
that then the need then the method and
an idea the requirement uh to create a
method or procedure which will assist
governments in informing the general
population of the existence of contact
between civilizations on earth and other
planets and which will alleviate any
fear they may have about releasing
information. And this was a general
thing I guess right the concept would be
ahead of any official disclosure allow
the general population to warm up to the
idea uh such that any extraterrestrial
contact would not seem unreasonable or
even unexpected to the majority of
people. This from the government's
perspective may minimize the fear of a
shock reaction and reduce the sense of
power that may be associated with the
concealment of the information. that now
I need um need a mechanism or medium
through which the idea of actual and
imminent direct interplanetary contact
can be brought comfortably into public
awareness or common understanding
showing the value of living and
participating in this transformational
age and showing the possibilities of a
new world order as being realistic
achievable and desirable. Now a method
would be something like to utilize a
familiar medium like a film uh which is
associated with entertainment, pleasure
and relaxation and which is accessible
to virtually all individuals in the
world, communication, satellite etc. The
product of the medium needs to be
attractive, exciting, stimulating and
positive. It should touch that point of
sort of knowingness that we have which
is often which we often keep suppressed
about things. Then I have given just a
few points about sort of what the movie
might look like um suitable for all
ages. It must include some tension or or
scary features to allow the viewers to
recognize in themselves the source of
their fear and belief cycles. Um to show
how all that is can be supportive and
not necessarily scary at all. Include
lots of written humans. That always
helps by all means.
by all means.
And and perhaps we could include some
political characters displaying
intelligence and vision.
Well, some of the real ones may may wish
to identify.
Okay. Do you work for Monty Python? Not yet.
Okay. Uh very different then. built to
maintain some kind some kind of
technological integrity as far as
possible such that it's obvious that the
plot takes place in something close to
our current time and the story line and
plot should be cohesive and fairly easy
to follow. Um those are just some broad
out. Thank you. I've printed these out.
I have 20 copies. And you say you're not
a writer.
Thank you. Thank you. All of this will
go into the pot.
Hi Var. And to you. How are you?
Perfect. And you? Perfect. Thank you.
Oh, thank you very much. I have so many
questions. I'm sure they'll be perfect questions.
I'm sure they'll be perfect questions.
Um, okay. humor with integrity of course
uh seems to play such an important part
in this earthly physical existence and I
was wondering if it is in fact a process
of vibrational acceleration itself. Yes.
Oh, do you have do you have humor um as
we understand it on Aasani or to some
degree? Yes. It is mostly spontaneous
and simply observant of the situations
and circumstances at hand. But all life
in that sense is joyful,
humorous, full of light, love, laughter.
Oh, I like
this. Um, thank
you. I have a little more hair, but
don't don't
worry. Um, okay. We have discussed the
power and knowledge of the individual
and that our society reflects perfectly
the manifestation of the level of the
belief of that empowerment in the
individual. Yes. In your society's total
understanding of this concept, is there
a need for a government or and in fact
is there any hierarchy of any sort such
as lawmakers in our society? No. There
is an embodiment which we call the
association which is of service in
providing what may be loosely termed a
connection point a switchboard if you
will for the coming and going of the
many communications from all the
different civilizations with whom we
interact. It may be a facilitator in
that way but it is not a ruling body.
It is a serving body by choice
and that's
and this planet civilization is is
approaching a time where we will start
to understand that and the idea of
government will eventually be phased out
as you understand it. Yes.
Good. [Music]
[Music]
Get rid of them.
Come on. Get rid of who? Just just
joking. If you humor
you are speaking about yourself, you
know what? Get rid of Okay. Yes. Because
it's a reflection. Yes. You are your
government. Yes. I understand. Is not
separate from you. Yes. No, I
understand. It's a process. And as long
as they know that we're moving in the
right direction, you are moving in a
positive direction regarding that idea.
That's right. Thank you. And last but
not least, this has to do with what
you're talking about tonight,
reincarnation. Yes. Um, is there a a um
Okay, hold on. Okay. Do beings uh
reincarnate quote unquote in groups
sometimes for a particular group? Oh,
very often. Okay, that is many times
what your physical families are all
about. Really now understand it is also
one of the strong reasons for what you
call the drive in your path to produce
offspring so that you can incarnate in
your same family
line. That is why you are producing less
offspring. Now in general you are
restructuring your need for that because
in a very short time you will not
require as many bodies because you will
not be reincarnating into your cycle any
longer. Um what about like for instance large
Um what about like for instance large
groups of people for instance I don't
know why and this may sound ridiculous
um but I've for some reason always
thought that the Nazis of Germany the SS
um which was a tumultuous period in our
history um that those people in
reflecting on their lives have come back
to learn uh the other side of that fence
and perhaps to come back as the
Ethiopians and these world some of them.
Although again remember to create a
balance does not require suffering in
return for suffering
comes a system can balance any idea of
perpetration. Simply being willing to
help to move in a positive direction can
create just as much of a balance.
You follow me? I'm not sure. In other
words, to put it very simply, just
because you murdered someone in one life
does not mean you have to be murdered in
the next. You can perhaps be of great
assistance to someone in a very positive
way and create the same balancing
effect. You follow me? I see. Yes. Now,
however, you have all murdered and been
murdered. Do we all have an ugly past or you all
Do we all have an ugly past or you all
have a so-called path that is the type
of path that has brought you to where
you are now? So in that sense in an
overall point of view it is not so ugly.
For it has allowed you to begin to learn
to prefer the
light and therefore it has served you in
a positive way. I see. I see. regardless
of how much negativity it has contained.
And who whomever you perpetrated your
crime quote unquote upon Yes. was there
and chose to help you learn this in in
one sense. Yes. Now many individuals
when they quote unquote choose to play
victim do not really choose it out of
conscious desire but they are
experiencing the idea of what happens
what kind of reality results when they
buy into the fear that they will be
victimized. And that is the same thing
as choosing to be a victim.
That makes sense. It may not be a
conscious choice as you understand that
term, but it is a choice nonetheless.
Okay. Thank you very much, Bashar. We'll
see you next week. Bye. Hold it just a
moment. Um, I want to question you.
Thank you. Hello, Bashar. And do you?
Yes. I've enjoyed over the many weeks
and months of this hearing and I have a
couple things I'd like to say. All
right. Um, a very close friend of mine
is going through what she considers to
be a bad time. All right. And I would
like some insight as to what to reflect
to her that would assist her in
learning. You have already reflected
some things.
This is true.
What has been your perception of the
so-called bad time?
She is creating
a sense of
being lost in misery. Lost in
misery. All right. you know, creating a
lot of negativity and feeling like
she's, you know, have you asked your
friend what she's getting out of it?
Not in so many words, but she I've
discussed with her some of the ideas
that we are creating our own reality and
she is doing this for a reason. And in
fact, one of her friends made got her
very angry because she reflected this in
in a in a way of saying, "Well, of
course you're creating it all and isn't
this wonderful?" And she got very upset
with her friend for, you know,
appreciating the fact that she was
feeling miserable. Yes. She was not
being given the company that misery
loves. This is recognized to some degree in
This is recognized to some degree in
your society. Support quote unquote and
love quote unquote are very often
reflected and represented in the format
you call
sympathy and that is not sympathetic in
the sense of true support or
love. The idea of true support and true
love is not that which reinforces
misery. Now you can in your terminology
Now you can in your terminology
empathize in the sense you can
appreciate that they are creating
something that for them is difficult.
You can appreciate that. That is all
well and good. But at the same
time those that truly believe in them
will not send the sympathy. And perhaps
an individual that believes they need
the sympathy to recognize what they
think is love may be angry when they
don't get it.
Now in a
sense they can also understand that the
opportunity to have experienced the
anger at least for that moment took them
out of misery. They were
burning
burning with a
centering, burning with
alignment. They perhaps did not allow
themselves to take it all the way. But
in the moment they were angered, they
were not in the same
way self depreciatively miserable. For
anger in that sense, in that format
implies an idea of
self-worth and at least it got her out
of the self-depreciation for a moment.
So all the individual truly needs to
realize is that someone reinforcing the
idea of the joy of the experience of
misery does not mean that they are
saying that you must be
miserable. They are simply saying you
have a choice as to whether or not you
can experience what you are going
through as a misery oriented expression
or not.
And that the second you
decide that you no longer wish to
experience it that way, then you
won't. Again, remember what may have
started this whole thing off is your
society's belief that what you typically
call depression is an inherently
negative state. And it isn't. Depression
again is only meditation, going inward
to find the answers you know don't exist
outside of you. It is a reentering of
yourself, a calling and a gathering
together of all the different aspects of
your persona, a board meeting, if you
will. You can take it both
ways. It is a reassessment of the
definition of your
life, a re-evaluation, a redefinition,
so that when you emerge from your
so-called depressive state, you are
literally a new person. You feel like a
new person. have new outlook, new
perspective, that is because you have
redefined yourself in the depressive
state. It is a natural
function. But when you say, well, what's
wrong with you? Can't handle your life.
You're retreating, you're withdrawing,
you create that to be a negative idea.
And then an individual may buy into that
and feel guilty and compound the idea of
their negative meditation, what you call
depression. Sometimes that can lead to
the type of escalated misery that your
friend may be going
through. Once begun, the cycle feeds
itself and escalates and accelerates in
an everex expanding negative
spiral. The easiest thing and at the
same time in your society perhaps the
most difficult thing, they are one and
the same. The easiest thing and the most
difficult thing in order for your friend
to just change what she is experiencing
is to simply change
it. It is that
simple. But this is all a lesson in the
learning of self-empowerment. A lesson
in the learning of giving the power
away, of giving your power over to the
circumstances and situations in your
life rather than recognizing that you
attracted them, you created them, you
control them.
Some individuals
perhaps enjoy a
vacation from believing they are in
control from time to
time. That may be all that your friend
is going through. But the power to
change it is right within her. It is
never anywhere else because there is
nowhere else for it to be. Nowhere else
for it to
be. Simply with whatever form of expressive
Simply with whatever form of expressive
love you
can just reflect even if it is in
attitude only and not in words your
belief in your friend in her
indestructibility her eternalness and
infinitess and that anything she is
going through no matter how miserable it
seems is ultimately only
temporary. Always remember that change is the only
Always remember that change is the only
constant and some of what your friend is
going through is a lesson for you as
well. Oh, I quite understand the fact
that the reason I am in this situation
with her is because there is something
that I am reflecting to myself as well.
All right. But again, the best service
as we were discussing with the other
individuals is to be a reflective
example of what works for you.
to at least then allow should that
individual someday decide to change to
at least allow that individual an
opportunity to see in someone else a
reflection of how it can be.
Yeah, she sees that part of it. She
doesn't quite understand the concept
that she's in control of her life, but
she's interested in what she can prove
it beyond the shadow of a doubt to
herself by simply acting upon what
excites her the most. It is not a risk.
It is not a risk. It is that simple. It
is not a
risk. And it will always prove to any
individual. You will always get the
feedback that proves it that what
excites you is what will continue in
your life. She can prove it to herself
tomorrow if she wishes. But she must
take the step of acting in that
direction or she will never see
it. It is that simple. And it may seem
to be difficult in your society, but
that's the way it
is. Because as simple as it is and as
difficult as it is, it's the same
act. Just taking the steps. As simple as
that. And for many, as difficult as
that, but that's it. She will get the
proof. We guarantee it. There is nothing
else we can do.
Oh, I agree. Well, thank you.
Thank you. Does that serve you? Yes.
Yes. Yes. We thank you and we thank you
for your continued participation in
functioning as facilitators for these
interactions and communication. Oh,
you're very welcome. I enjoy them all.
And we enjoy you a whole bunch.
Yes. Thank you, Paul. Sharing. Hello,
Bashar. Hello. Um, I have two ideas
about the government releasing
information, but I first want to ask
something about part of a dream.
Um, I understand to be in to some
extent. Um, it takes place in in the
desert in Egypt and um, I'm with a bunch
of people and one person suddenly kicks
away a few planks and there seems to be
nothing there but sand. This is not one
of the archaeological sites. into the
desert and I start to crash away a
little bit in the sand and I find some
sort of tablet guys about a leaf and it
has a little landscape on it three
little birds flying in the sky and it's
very pretty and I pointed out to this
person says well this is a beautiful
find uh hide it because this is something we
uh hide it because this is something we
want to keep to ourselves and you say I
didn't listen to that I continue to I
mean he turned away and I just continue
to dig and very good. This was sitting
on a on a shelf as it were. Nice. And
there was a shelf below it and on that
shelf I
found lots of little statuettes of um
little ivory statues of of little corpses like
ivory statues of of little corpses like
from the Yeah. And um this looks a
little weird. They are Atlantean
nobles. You are
discovering an untapped chamber from the
time of Atlantis. It is in your terms a
time capsule. Your interaction is now an
capsule. Your interaction is now an
indication that the time is approaching
when certain individuals may in
attempting to uncover that information
not see that it is right under them. But
other individuals that intuitively know
it is there will dig and will find it.
So that's an actual site. It is an
actual site. Well, you hear what I found
next. All right. Um, there are also
shelves above it. Yes. And I found all
these little Chinese.
And I was thinking myself, the Chinese
were in business. In a sense, that is
correct. In a sense. Yes. But it is also
an indication of what you might call an
extraterrestrial connection. Well, I was
thinking along the lines of finding my
past lives on those shelves. You will.
But they weren't in those figurations.
Not yet. Then there was also like this
was like turned out to be a whole
bookcase full of things. Yes. And then
on the top I sort of went to the right
and I found a new bookcase. The boots
were very different looking uh
sexualized piece. I hate to use the word
because it's a little judgmental but it
was almost a grotesque but don't imply
any negative. We understand
unusual and the first one was
spectacular. It was a little
um bigger of a mandarin Chinese mandarin
and um up to his neck. But then above
that he had a head like a cube. Okay.
And the cube has the whole star map
painted on.
That's the one actually that excited me
most. What does that mean? There is in
that chamber knowledge of the four
corners of the earth and of all the
heavens that was understood in Atlantean
times. It is in a sense incorporated into the
It is in a sense incorporated into the
structure of the figurine symbolically
and it can be translated and interpreted
by those who are sensitive to the
understanding. I felt about after heard
a lot about the whole universe being in
your mind. Yes. And it seemed to me that
that was the perfect Yes. depiction of
that. Yes.
And it is also an indication of the
universe rendered down into your
physiological format. Right. Confined in
the cube so to speak. But that that case
seems to have all a lot of strange
looking ones like that. Like some of
them have heads that go all the way up
and very long to years. Yes, you are
digging deeply into the recesses of your
soul of your true soul recall your true
soul memory and at the same time this is
to some degree truly representative of
an actual location on your planet.
So um you have to give me some
suggestions how I may use this or will
there be more games explaining that you
can in your meditative states re-enter
that and explore at your leisure. By the
time that is actually physically
discovered you may already understand
how to interpret many of the things that
will be surfaced. Do I explore? Oh yes.
You are back there and up
there down there and up there. But I
won't be part of this excavation. You
are part of it right now.
You are assisting in the ability of your
planet to discover it by bringing it
into your own consciousness. You are
channeling that knowledge into your
earth right now.
Thank you. And now these two ideas have
maybe off the
wall. I'll throw it out anyway. All
right. The first one I was this came to me last
The first one I was this came to me last
week actually after the session when I
went to bed. All right. And I was going
to ask for dream for ideas but nothing
came after that. That's all I have used
to and um first thing that came to mind
was that I heard a short while ago that
um you're spending $200 million a year
on a project called city search for
thresh. Yes. And we spend about $4
billion by
now scientists just sit there listening
and you don't hear anything. Okay. Is
because they are listening on radio
frequencies and that is not the majority
form of communication in the local
neighborhood. Why? Why? Okay. Uh why not make the
Why? Why? Okay. Uh why not make the
investment pay? Why? What I'm saying is
wouldn't this be usable as a means by which
this be usable as a means by which
to reach out to the the most skeptic
amongst them and why don't you guys
exist for
something. It is not up to us. Now do
remember again there have been actual
conversations between what you call extraterrestrial
between what you call extraterrestrial
civilizations and members of your
government. Yes. But not but what I'm
saying is that is not up to us.
They create a reality where they will
never hear anything. In a sense, yes, it
is up to them. Once they turn their ears
in a different direction, they will be
deafened by the amount of communication
that is going on. Well, it only cost 12
to come here, right? Um but you don't
see any way of to use that uh to create
that exchange in atmosphere. That mean
it is up to you first. You must make the
first shift. When you are listening on a
shift. When you are listening on a
certain frequency that is a frequency
that has nothing to do with us, you will
not find her. But the intention was
right or they want to they want to hear
something. I mean they may be somewhat
ignorant. Everything is proceeding at perfect
Everything is proceeding at perfect
pace. Understand that their lack of
reception is only an indication of the
blanket that your world has placed
around everyone.
That's unfortunate. It is neither
fortunate nor unfortunate. There is no
need to place a value judgment on it. It
is what it is and it is representative
of the frequency collectively they are
on. Period.
Um the other idea may just be that we're
along the same line for a while. All
right. Um at present uh the Voyager
spacecraft is sort of leaving our solar
system and uh it contains all sorts of
records and it's again something that
was intended
to to find the life out there or to make
contact but it's again in a very limited
sense of we
understand wouldn't there be a way in
which you people should have some
records from you are asking again for
direct intervention and we cannot do it.
Besides which, your civilization is most
likely going to be the ones who go out
and retrieve that message yourself.
Well, but it's an invitation, of course,
though, isn't
it? Understand
something. The
invitation has been
accepted over and over and over
again. and it has been
refused over and over and over again by
your world. So
So
um we have to really find a way then to
change the atmosphere of that's
it and are we doing that right here or
here in many places around your planet
and within each and every one of you it
is taking place. So have agreements. So
in a sense we can't do anything. You
know about the agreements and and we
just have
to what we call intervention. It's not I
mean we don't always know what is
intervention or not. You can know it is
a very simple thing to know. Basically
all you need to do is take
responsibility for your life and
communicate your preferences as to how
you desire your world to function.
And then it will be obvious that you
will create a type of society wherein we
can in fact
interact. Now I am going to put this
extremely colloquially and I do not mean
it in a derogatory
manner. But would you accept an
invitation into a war zone?
You would think twice about landing,
wouldn't you? Absolutely. Well, thank
you.
I'll do some more thinking. Thank you
very much. Thank you. And things have
been absolutely wonderful since the the
workshop. I mean, professionally and
life has become extremely exciting.
Thank you for creating it to be so for
it is all within your conscious
commandment. There will be in your
terminology but a few moments remaining
for this interaction this evening of
your time. Continue. Hello. And to you.
I'm happy to be here. I've been
listening to you on tape in St. Louis
for a long
time and I'd like to find out about for
three or more
years. I was experiencing a very deep
sense of grief and wanting to leave it.
Okay, that is a typical symptom of
individuals who begin to awaken into
their true expansiveness and the fact
that they exist on all levels at once.
It is a melancholy symptom that is still
allows you to experience the expansion
but leaves you half in half out on the
threshold of all the habitual ideas of
regret, guilt and remorse that you still
have created upon your planet. It is a
longing for the expansion and still an
ingrained belief that in order to have
it, you have to leave your plane in
order to create it. Now you are
discovering that you can actually create
it where you are and bring all of that
expansiveness to you so that you create
heaven on earth instead of having to
leave earth to go to heaven.
You follow me? It is a typical symptom
of the transitional
period. As soon as you recognize you are
fully in control of the reality you are
experiencing, then you will understand
that ecstasy is within you and can be
experienced anywhere, anywhere.
The feeling was before then. I think
you've pretty much answered it. I've
I've been feeling a lot of things
simultaneously.
Okay. Simply remember once again that
anything you ever feel is a reaction to
something you already believe to be
true. All feelings are
reactions to things you already
believe. So all the different things you
are feeling are all the different
beliefs you are now examining and
deciding if you prefer to take them with
you into fourth density.
I Yeah, I felt very strongly pulled like
someone was actually trying to pull me
over. Yes, you. Your future self saying,
"Come on, you made it. Come on. You're
doing fine. Come on. Come on. I'm right
here. You've already created me. I've
already created you. Come on. Trust it.
You follow me. I do. That is the lure. I
I've always wondered why 10 years ago I
went to the dying project, a week-l long
seminar of meditation on death is
transformation. And I loved it more than
anything I've ever experienced in my
life. Yes. Well, I have died many times.
Yes. I've been dying before you. Thank
you very much. Well, thank you for being
so
alluring. Thank you all for creating
your own allurement in that way and for
allowing all that is to manifest the
expression of its allurement which is
the feeling and the process and the
expression of the gathering together
into an integrated awareness that you
are now experiencing in your society. It
is attraction, allurement in that way.
The very same thing that attracts all
things to each
other. At this timing, we will thank
each and every one of you individually
and collectively for the cocreation of
this interaction this evening of your
time. We thank you for cocreating the
dream in which we are participating
together. Once again, simply
remember. Wake up and live your
dream. We thank you. Our unconditional
love, our deepest
appreciation, and a fond and loving good
night.
Um, how did everything go? [Applause]
[Applause]
Thank you. Thank you all for being here.
Would you flip that light on over there?