different level that contain that idea come into
ex the idea of ​​the
unbrokeness is not so much lerally it contains
act side by side cohesive
interaction with the polar you
experience it is simply one
thing that can create to
become different
are unes that unbrokeness of it
chesate in many other ways otherwise
positive and polar
this will have no frame of expression
for you does not have for
I but also break all
you all take a break all than
all than
Yes, I want to talk to you
about isemale energy that
number have two parts  number one is
I understand her at this point to be predomin serious fif energy is
don't have a lot of
information on that time is a timing to
find out anything more about you to
obvious about
I wish to be obvious as yes all
right then in the asking of the question
in one sense if that is the way you wish
to ask the question that is the answer
is it the timing to know more do you know more no that is the answer
okay now is
a new all right how have you created
yourself to be
now in your recognition I
'm allowing you  to be obvious
reflection of what
I pretty  sneaky. All right. St and
and
compensations as you could call
them to unlocking different aspects different
aspects different
propties can be the energy that comes
through your
solares the idea that you can function
as
of gateways andways
that reflect different
combinations of probabilities to
different individuals in that you will
can represent yourself as a
reflection with the idea of ​​and the
serious energy
as a in which a series of reflection can be
by
individual you can think of your asing your
as a
series of illian presentation intention
chrx your to perceive that the white of
your ending comes through it much the
take a  transparent
mostly in coming through that
chra yourself to view as
the reflective alaster surface of a in
which other individuals within the milky
substance and fluid can see reflected
from you all probabilities that they can
participate with you in that you are
constantly fluctuating the eye is as you
are presenting them of
quarties mass energy
conversions th always functioning as a
timing stroke in sense for individuals
and your to recognize the manyabili that
come with each Thank
One other thing you may have already um
included that with the idea of ​​the white light but
right now  I'm increasing
energy of allowing of allowing
her
female to come through more the emoality
to come through more enl back more this
is why we say the solar chra the chra of
intention and simply view yourself that
as the enery comes through you will
pour out of that area mirle you
are we going to be able to hear from
again soon soon can i ask to ask you ask you
question about my big
about my big
dog atted my little dog the new all and do
you remember what we shared Yes,
but I couldn't really figure out in
terms of well  he's done that with Jamie
once and from obvious point of view must his
dominance and I suppose it
has something to do with it has to do
with the idea of tradition tradition
tradition tradition
the now exporing is the tradition
some asely as you by indicating that you
may have reservations and allow the
traditional aspects the fundamental aspects of your
aspects the fundamental aspects of your
transformation
to conflict
Now in terms
of negative emos that we mentioned
earli when this happened I got very
scared obviously. los in and equitable withend thank
withend thank
you the questioned to that was that
when I got so scared I was comparing
that emo to those 50 seconds angular
kind of thing it
My heart was being real fast and it
wasn't the fear thing that we were
talking about earlier it was just a
reaction just like when you have the 15
second anger
but that energy accelerated you so
that you could form of those doties
so that your fear could be
channeled into the idea out
rather than you
much yes what is going on now that you theortun theortun
ofle ofe anding how much
different you have made
as you are not
asleep you are going where you need to be
going as you need to get
anything you at this [music]
I have of course of
course if you have a million you have
answer
for questions are onlywers that arearated from
your if you can even understand of the notion
it does not matter you concept
form is only having information
separate from
yourself to act as a reflection to show
you what you do contain as ainder
simply because you are used to
receiving  reflections fromingly
outside so you  create the information
with
consci un state of being creating that is a
form in recogn consciously a form
you will allow yourself to recogn it
consciously in a
question this does not me you cann ask
being before me
last confused about being being
[music] outside may
you what differ would make
well would make a of differ
because I feel better.  You would feel
better if I knew how to address this
person.  I impolite
impolite that is a concept in your
reality.  Do you think that the
consciousness thinks you are being
impolite?  I don't know what the Yes, you
do.
What do you
think you would think you thinket
you what now pick one pick anything what
is let you get away for pretending Pretend anything [
anything [
music] fromure [music
]
aller all in allat
Now it is a wise old being from put who
knows now since it is in your estimation a
now since it is in your estimation a
wise old
being what do you think it thinks of
well I think it
All right.  Do you mean exactly as you are?
Yes.  No matter you know what to call it
or not.  Yes.  Then what differ does it
make? Why notate to as you feel like to it doesn't care what
Why notate to as you feel like to it doesn't care what
you call it will be offendrbody else to have
it might it
might not everybody always have
have
yes good vibration as
any of don't [music
] have grinning
yourself the equality of knowing
that however you wish to act
You will be able to keep up
with simply recogn that if and when a
labeling of any type is necessary it
will be there
in whatever it needs to be there.
If it isn't there, you don't need one
yet.  Whatever you are
to call it whatever you will.  It doesn't
matter the important idea is simply
toate to it as you feel
so let the interaction com
I a tiny little fear and then I was
afraid that feeling fear would put it off
a little bit so once again what you
are receiving because of the definition
of your understanding of what it is it is
nonjudgal it is not going puta not
and not need so
many proper
formalities of before you will let it be
all right toct
with it will be able to in whatever house Oh, that
is to abul
only that you love
yourself and stop pushing your so all. so all.
Thank
you.  I
have myself up to and vulnerability
and vulnerability
vulnerability good vulnerability is not
weakness do you think it is?
No, I think there is a strength in a
strength vulnerability is strength vulnerability complete vulnerability pay
alone is being open to
everything being open to all that
is being open to all that is is being connected to
all that is being connected to
all that is a strulability is
strength it is
trust it is knowing that you open
yourself up to all that
is then you will be supported by all that
is because all that is once you
allow yourself to recognize yourself as an
integral integral integrity
integral part of all that
you create your to function like
integral part and all that would not be
all that  is without
you therefore vulnerability is strength by
definition judgment is what creates the
feeling of weakness not vulnerability
Judg on
your there is nothing
else.  There is no one else to judge.
Judg of others is judg of yourself.  Judg
from others if you accept it is judg
yes there are a lot of different
frequencier the idea of ​​unity is to
equality to all the diversity with
creation again allowing all the ways all
that is ofing to be equal on them does not
mean it has to
your life just because you recogn that there are
life just because you recogn that there are
other frequencies doesn't mean that
one of those frequencies has anything at
all to do with the you know your
frequency to be if you simply recognize
that it has nothing to do with
you okay because are exposed
to the reality  that other ways to
other ways to present them all that is to
you doesn't mean that you have to
feel your I am have been very influenced by
your I am have been very influenced by
other enerv that is your chice to beuen nothingu you
but nothing they are offering
how would you like to be
influenced byolution
yes no yes i do no
you it is up to you to be influened
but you create your version of
that gift in reality if you are
experiencing you have cre your
all you are doing ising that it would
be for you apprate to create if
you simply understand that  the tool you
are being offered is  equal to any other
tool is valid if you should decide to accept
it it will serve you because you do not
accept anything
else but if you simply recognizez that it is
a tool you do not need and that you
can learn what you need to learn in
other ways in ways you consider to be
more positive then simply recognize that
it does not have to manifest in your
life that if you recogniz what the
purpose would be should you have accepted that
idea then you can also recognize
that the same purpose can be
served by creating another way in which
it can manifest  in your life one that is
more relevant to the vibration you know is true
for
you that Do
you understand that the I still have
difficulty with a belief?
Why do you insist that is
your because it always has
so one moment is not connected to the
next now is
now has nothing to do with the unless
you choose to make a connection the present
is not a result of
the now is now it is always a new now
just because you may choose to define I just recognizing
just recognizing
thatle in time is
ownarate now is now and not the now you used to
now is now and not the now you used to
be
the only things
you in any given
now are the result of what you define
your reality to be according to what you
believe it should be redefine your
reality in other words  if you simply
recogn that you have a choice between
the preference the opportunity to believe
preference the opportunity to believe
for easy
easy
well which one do you prefer it is
difficult for me to change it is easy
for which one do you
prefer you are making your choice right
now because you are choosing to make it
difficult to choose
Which one do you
prefer? Why obviously if you prefer it to be
Why obviously if you prefer it to be
difficult I need to learn from it must
serve you.
However, you can also understand that
the opportunity to choose to prefer that it is easy
is always just as equal a choice
at any given moment.
At any what you
have all right I through
the now I will easy and as you tr do it
will understand something
again change is the only constant in the
unerse things are always changing
always transforming are they
they
recogn that is what happens any what you
think always stays the same is never the
same never every moment is a new moment
even when it seems to be the same as the
last moment it is a new
version of the idea you are creating the
idea that there is a continuity [music] Come on
you what happ
to come identity
come identity
your personality construct in artificial construct
created of things belief emo
and thoughts is a through which
the white of your consciousness is
broken identity is always changing you
as a person is always
changing the person is not a fixed thing
the consciousness is in a sense but the
person is never fixed do you not understand
that you yourself recognize
that many times individuals go through situations
and when they erge from these
situations you say well you're entirely
different person you is true saying consciousness recognizez
the consciousness
but it is a different person a different
personality which is the same thing it
is  an artificial construct that now has
been  tailored to fit the new
idea that the consciousness is willing to be memory is created
in the present as
well you may think you are dredging
something up from the past but if you
really stop and understand it and think
about it you recogn you are creatingory
in the the
idea is that you will find that many
individuals to forget the
so inity because they are to recogn that
they will know what they need to know in
the present when they need to know it
and do not have to have association with
the past in order to know what they need to
everything is  created in the present
everything the present is the only time in you
ever ex is always
always
well can you a time ever when you could not [music ]
now yes or no i can look at other you are that
In other words, let
me anything you can ever
experi is always
now.  You follow me.  You are experiencing
the idea of ​​a memory of the now when you
were living that it was still now when
you were living it, wasn't
it?  There is always and only ever will be
now.  It is the only time there is
now.  Is it the same moment all the time?
It is one eternal moment that can
transform into different versions
of it does so and is so simultaneously
but because you have
created a reality in which you have the
idea of ​​linear time it does not seem to
be the same moment but it is as we
said all things are one
ince line that is one manifestation of now existence
because the only time you ever
perceive linear time is from the
now youate to the past and the future
from the present you notate to the present
from the
future you follow me yes all is
Does that ass
you?  Choose what you wish to be.  Now all
choices are equal.  All choices are
equal.  Allowing all choices to be equals
you to choose easily because then nothing is beyond
your reach.  They are
all on the same level. [music] [music]
I
to about
was feeling that I have experienced a lot.
feeling that I have experienced a lot.
All right.  Danger.  Danger.  Come on
everyone.  Have to do
is with public recognition.  Public
recognition. Yes.  My
name scares me.  Why?  Why?  I don't
know its another life or something to be
quite honest.  What
life?  Do you think maybe you did a bad
job once and somebody st you?  Could be.
I
don't I had a dream the
other I was people
the golden large came [music
] it go into
and I don't know where I would have that
now but when I was
younger I
here do you know what you are afraid
of being killed yeah
being what is being killed What
What
is not transition not
why make a differ trans
may what you are Do
you feel that is something you might
misuse?  Do you feel that you cannot feel
that extent of your own power
without the idea ofunction with
integrity?  Do you think it will get out?
I never would I don't think consciously
that I would use may do this
right now your
imagination imagine that you are
successful what does it feel Define Define
now
what is going on to you you are
successful how you know you are this is a time you
time you
So tell
us how do you know you are successful who let
you know this how you find out
you what are some the sign well I just
know how I feel now how you feel how you what I
think you what you
Yeah, I see
that freedom of that
all freedom of
expression up.  Anything
else?  Are there any other sign that you
need to allow you to know you were
now?  What else did you create?  What
other feedbate?
Now that you are what going are you withans
that you know you are working
are working
with me a people people people you enjoy
working yeah
and having ideas that
I new possibil not just the
So new form of expression
freedom of expression anything else
of more freedom of yes this is not going to be
very [music]
[music]
All right.  So you are saying that you
prefer not to right all right thing.
M
so that before you to know that
you with your belief system said that
freedom ofang
What you are may is you
that you have created a scenario at some
time in your life when you got needb forcing your
and may now are to do that I
can't.  No one can.  Only you
can.  Do you think that what you have to
share is
sharing? Yes.  Really?  Oh yeah.  Oh, I do seem very
Yes.  Really?  Oh yeah.  Oh, I do seem very
sure.  Oh
boy.  Well, I like to I don't know if
it's worth it, but same thing.  Same
thing.  If that is what is your
exciter is for you are willing to be the
individual that you know your to
recognized if a so life even the of your
present life you found that expressing
yourself attracted let say a negative
then that is simply your
opportunity to recogn that other
individuals can recogn
and can inde that
power you will
individual who may recogn that you are
willing toess your
freely may find that that causes a
reaction reflection
any so they give you to you
will accept the belief that if
they can't do it or  don't think they can do
it that you shouldn't or that you
still can regardless of what they have
chosen for themselves and recognize that
in your willingness to continue to express
yourself you offer them the best
opportunity to see in your reflection
which they can also choose to express
themselvesely a
gift your own unique manifestation
of all that
is by always being willing to express
yourself as that gift you will always again be
supported by all sa live act
live act
love it
is what you are you are life
itself breath it in breath it
out the
golden glob is your own power and it  has
the power to
transform you from  the
child that was
restricted into in your terms an adult
that is
limitless the child in a sense while
always with you is in fact dead
so in this way
recogniz that its death has allowed for
the birth of an adult that is
livless.  For only the aspect of the
child that you were holding on to is
what felt
repressed.  You know, you know children should be seen
and not heard that sort
of thing.
M now you can be seen
and you will be thank
you to the idea that we come to this planet
as learning do we take on
the do we choose before coming to this
planet [music] [music]
to
individuals basically yes yes certain
circstances yes yes
[music] so
so
noent but then at the time and point
where it becomes uncfortable uncomfortable uncable uncfortable uncfortable
that may be part of the
lesson would you then that to
placeently and love and that would
indication can the idea is that does have to
can the idea is that does have to
translate into but simply the recogn that vibration is not
your vibration
you have to translate as far
as if you harmony
up and then you still have harmony
differuse you could create
together you
Would you use would you go back to the
idea there is a
overed chice that we make
in what we are sharing with you is
tolyysicality to be obvious reflection
of what you have chosen to experience
and if you find that there are in your
terms unlik vibrations where there used to
be like vibrations then it is
indication that things are changing
according to and
you  the way to find out
if is to let it  go understand that even
if say around
Yeah.  I wanted to ask you um you talked
one night about trust being activating
could you reflect on that
more I found that to be very useful to
me.  thinking a lot about it and I wonder
if could give some more
dimensions it is simply willingness to
understand that every idea comes with
all the ingredients necessary for the manation
of that idea that nothing comes
so that if you are willing to be an idea
and know beyond the shadow of a
doubt that that is simply the idea that
represents the vibration that feels best
to you then everything that will be
necessary to you being that idea will
automatically synchronistically be presented
to you in your life.
Allow yourself to be to the fact that
whatever you do need is there by
definition simply assume you have
whatever you need and therefore if you
need anything will
excit your physiological translation of
the vibration that the you to be follow
what assum you have whatever you need
and if you need anything else will excit
will excit
the vibration [music ]
Therefore this is a simultaneous
occurrence not to speak exactly
evolving your concept through time is of
evolution you may find that it is just
as bal to look at it as if you decided
in this way to have an entire  series of
human reincarnations in this way and
then in a sense after the fact perhaps
project consciousness into the idea of
the mineral kingdom just
because now because of what you have
created linear time to be once you are
in linear trans
look at it in a line you look at it this
way the idea is that you first and forem non-nysical
so you got used to physicality
in varying stages of
complexity arriving so to speak where
you are now
and because the human is more
aware moreware that would be aware in a different sle ma knows
what could that form
you  are in a sense but recogn that is
in your higher  to have the
reflection and included in the
knowledge so can you experience Thank
you very much. All right.
about it is being communication with all
that is it is knowing and recognizing
the connection it is recognizing that that is
what you are it is again once again
the allowance You can
You can
always connect everything and always
radiate your compassion for them but recognize
that the idea of ​​praying for
someone else does not necessarily have to
include the idea that you are
reinforcing that you think they need
because you are only sending the
vibration that they are less than what
you imagine they should be the idea is
simply that you support them as they are
and trust that what they have
chosen to  be willve them and that they
can choose to recognize it and then choose
what they prefer that is how
you pray for someone
else. What
about we have already discussed the idea
of ​​trusting that
your life as it is what
you have chosen it to be that
you are in control of everything you
experience that it serves you let it and
you will see how it does
then you will choose
Praying again being in touch with all the
different levels upon which
we trusting that how any particular
level manifest itself is the result of
being in touch with all the other levels
and not the result of not being in
touch.  Did you that prayer is the
trust that in this way what is happening
in your life is the result of being in touch
with all levels of yourself and
not the result of not being in touch
trust that is direct communication all
that is with friend that FR [music]
[music]
con may what are going to do now?  That's
the interesting part I don't know.  Yes,
you do.  What excites you?  Well, I have a
lot of things that are called that I
call.  Yes.  Do any of them excite you?
Yes.  And many of them are taking the
form of businesses which one particular
business which can happen and happening is
I the last 15 years a struggle for
me.  All right.  And it was a profession
that I did out of
necessity out of chice but not
understand and how strugle by chice
point is ching to not strugle in new new
and
going like a I
used to think was netive thing I don't
know why this is happening. are are
mel and conscious notar vibrat graduation graduation
[music]
andesmination years of that I don't
have another example
where they have syu
and there was another form [music ]
]
Istal that I often for meditation and I
can see through the cstal if I want to
open my eyes the flame flickering and I
left it on all night which I do many
times just when I was waking up this
morning in those early hours as we speak
about I had like an experience which
felt like I was actually experiencing
this and I was  judging it thinking about
my mind the experience was I saw the
flame to the channel go out and I said
to myself in my dream that's an amazing
thing I tuned into the cstal just as the
flame was going out in my dream in my
dream okay I don't know how much time
but all of a sudden I smell this awful smell
in real life and the whole part of
the candle had cracked the glass and the
wax was all over and huge flames left up
and smell me jumped out and it put out
because it was a lot of smoke and all
day long today  affected by this
thinking we bring things to us that we
have to learn from what did I bring this to myself and
myself and
I ins Igen. as you
as you
are because are
you have
theme and to accelerate anything
thates you
will you are to your dream con
and l that enth you spk I
justleep the connection that will you
know that when you wake up you will be
dreaming and always away when
youle you will blend as you say since
you are creating it to take time give it
some time go easy on your you had
was [music] graduated i
graduated i
to last week I was channeling my friends
and when it was all
over I was getting up and I realized
that I didn't need  to channel
any I just knew and I realized since
then that I had actually integrated with
him. Thank you.  Thank
Thank you.  Thank
you.
And it is very
nice and
[music] um I've also noticed some other things
um I've also noticed some other things
happening.  Okay.  I
noticed that my business has gotten very
very busy.
time I have a lot less time when you integrate you create less time yes
so in
this way simply recogn the time you have is
all the time you need okay
and then one other thing I notic is
my
husband it's like he's grasping for
me like he feels like I'm
disappearing show him you are not
disappearing We all the individual to see in you a
We all the individual to see in you a
reflection of the potential with himself
to know that nothing is ever l
that a
relationship is
forever no matter what the definition
definition
and there was something Thank you.
Our perception at this time of the
golden ring the vibration that the you have
ring the vibration that the you have
created
So inted by
your what is worry worry wor
It seems such a chronic stake for me.
Chronic chronic chronic.
I
know.  Are you excited
about understand that is when you allow
yourself to trust that you can live in
the moment
now will be chronic anymore
.
only separation and create time more
time and allow time for things to happily chronically
rearnation I would
like I have 14 and I find with
the idea of ​​judg I find it very
difficult not to judg with mine in
are getting her to do scho regular
things has you that it is easy for you to be judgal
but I don't I don't do it
well I feel that the area I have
difficulty is I feel the responsibility to have
her understanding w learning
If you are to
[music] be be
difficult if
you
do in creating communication
I'm not sure I'm fighting with it all
time.  What I would like to do is have her
how about you her feelings on what it is this I
about you her feelings on what it is this I
have.  There's not a high
interest. What is there a high
interest?  Present time there doesn't
seem to be too much.  Have you
asked?  Do you think you have presented
yourself in such a way that you would
feel?  Not why don't you find out what
the interest is that is there?
and your daughter to
adtine to be allow them to learn rather
than enforcing a particular methodology I
don't I personally actually left out
the aspect of my husband who is much has
much stronger view on
forcing that do her school work and that
stu and I feel that I have to carry his
torch and I'm very getting heavy.  Yeah,
I don't want to do it.  All right.  And
again you can share with him as well.
The understanding that you find out what is
the driving motivation of another
individual is what will allow you to see
how you can suiv how they can use their
own driving motivation to learn what
they want to learn.  Thank you.  Thank
you.  Recogn you have all chosen to be
with each other.
You are all teachers and [music]
[music]
learners.  What do you mean by being?
responsible to someone is being complete
of yourself you can be so that they have accurate
of
you to see themselves
with beingul who you are allow them the
opportunity to see with you
opportunities that they can then choose
for themselves if they to
with can I know I have can be welleng
whatever is a
situation I have a 15yeold I wasen her
and I sympathized with you like to get the
son and daughter
to perhaps there may be for the families
with him need to own
then you canare the understanding that
you have of what is being done and
simply to that  individual that every
individual is as powerful as they need to be to be
anything they want without having
tour [music ]
that if comes upon a definition that
requires enforce themselves upon someone
else there is easier than you animal
you animal
conscious take animal conscious conscious
understanding fromings
other animal kingdom represented own
conscious and really cross the human
conscious that they could evolve in
their own sense yes but there also is
the opportunity for all levels of
consciousness to transform into other
levels of consciousness this is not
reincarnational experience this is
something quite beyond that
Yes.  As long as you with a
identification consciousness.
after a long time so may there is the
opportunity for the animal consciousness the
fragment there to
recogn perhaps to other different levels
of consciousness and form an attachment to
it and draw to itself assimilations
of different portions of the
consciousness of all that is so that it
can also interact in that way but then
it is no longer the idea of ​​animal
consciousness and not exactly the same
thing that made the decision to do
place [music]
Yes.  And I take that to me that
our blending will
that whereas at another time you said it
was to years I have to say that I like the
years.  Then perhaps that will be
your reality.
Oh,
great.  The other question I
have um is that I've been experiencing
particularly now all through the evening
almost a feeling that I could um jump out
of my skin.  It's a type of tension that
seems to originate from the solar.  Yes.
The ch of intention creative pressure
very much the expansion of yourself to
all different levels of yourself in
terms of your skin.  Yeah.  All right.
Then another interesting thing to that is
that a year ago September I was told
that I have a growth on my left ovy.  In
addition to the fact that my uterus is
enlarged.  I've been trying to Yes. that those
that those
areucing there is not malignant anything
just I had it checked by sound scan and I
wonder if you have any insight that do
you have children no you want to yeah
when a few years
well any are you sure think when
there and that would be
convenient any daddies around
any daddies around
as far as them being fathers
another way you saying is that it is
entirely all right with you to put some
sort of regulatory upon yourility toce Absolutely and
Absolutely and
this a growth on my
fascinating absolutely fascinating.
having a baby and it's [music] [music]
thing that
[music]
it until the timing is
correct. Okay, that's actually
Okay, that's actually
really simple that's lovely.
be in touch with the
consciousness you will understand the you will it
and in that
way the insistence will [music ]
]
be what insist isleer yes
isleer yes
theyent differentquen many though [music]
many more things you are conscious
choices if you would but listen to what
you say about
your i havey understanding this that is a
chice listen to your you are ching
thatity i have wait a
Why we will at this time extend
yourinder that if you are willing now to
understand the idea we have describ
synchronicity one two all synchronic act
like it with
integrity explore the idea of
coincidence and synchronic in the
literature that is available in your
civilization explore we than
you for the interaction of
the gift of your cons of your time you
and us all that is the sharing
thates forever we exciting and