[Applause] Thanks, Frank.
Hi again, everyone.
There are uh once again enough new
people here that I'll give a very brief
background on what it is that's going
on, how this happened to me, so there's
a little bit of a foundation for
everyone. My basic on is are any of the
new people here not familiar? Is there
anyone here is not familiar with
channeling at all? Anyone to whom this
is completely new? Here's one.
All right. Okay. Um my basic
understanding of what most channelings
are is that they're the result of an
agreement or an arrangement that is
created prior to the physical life. And
then the person that is going to be
doing the channeling finds situations
that occur in their life to get them to
remember and fulfill that agreement with
whomever they made that agreement. So
everyone's path how they get there is
different. For me the biggest turnover
point began about 12 years ago when on
two separate occasions within the span
of the same week with four friends
present with me the first time and two
friends present with me the second time
we had very close broad daylight
sightings of Bashar spacecraft
physically over Los Angeles. What I
didn't understand then and what I
understand now is that sighting was his
way of sort of jostling my subconscious
memory to learn what I needed to learn
to fulfill the agreement that I made to
do this. So as the years went on,
spurred on to do some more research
based on that sighting. I learned what
channeling was about, read a lot of
books on it. Ultimately I was introduced
to several mediums. One of the entities
coming through one of those mediums
offered to teach mediumship for whoever
was interested. Even then, I took him up
on it, not so much thinking that it was
something I was going to do, but I
thought I'd learned something more about
it since I pretty much read all the
books I could find. When I was under
that toutelage in a receptive state is
when Bashar and his people made the
mental connection. And as soon as they
did, the memory of having made the
agreement came back. Along with that
memory came the knowledge of who they
were, who I was to them, what the
agreement was all about, the what the
ship sighting was all about. Dream
encounters that I had with them that I
totally blocked up to that point all
came rushing back in that one. And along
with it came the message, now is the
time for you to start doing this if you
still want to. Do you still want to?
Obviously, I said yes. And that was
about 3 and 1/2 years ago. And I've been
doing it since then. They do present
themselves as an extraterrestrial
consciousness. uh they do have somewhat
of a physical form, although Bashar is
not his name specifically. They do not
have names. They're pretty much
telepathic in their society, but he's
chosen it as a convenience for us.
Um it's not that you have to believe
that the way this is presented is
exactly what's happening, but that the
interaction itself is simply for you to
get out of it what you want to get out
of it. Um so please feel free to
interact. When Rashar comes through, a
lot of times he will simply he will say
something that he feels is indicative of
what the group may or may not you know
collectively need to hear and then he'll
open it up to what he calls sharing.
When he says sharing that's his way of
saying you can say or ask anything you
want. Of course that's true at any time.
Um please speak up loudly. We are
recording so that the questions or your
statements get on the tape as well as
the answers because many other people
will hear the tapes and it's a little
bit frustrating when they can hear the
answers but not the question. Um the
only other thing is that please you know
if you have something to say if you want
to ask something or say something or
share something don't be shy and if
there is something that he says that you
do not understand if he puts it into
terminology that is not clear do not let
him go on. stop him and ask him to
explain it again because he will. It's
no interruption and he doesn't look at
it that way. One of his reasons for
being here is to assist us in learning
certain things about ourselves. And if
you do not, you know, if you let him get
away with something that that is turned
in a way you don't understand it, then
you're not getting it and he doesn't
feel like, you know, he's going to be
doing the best job that he can do. So,
please by all means, you know, speak up
loudly and get him to clarify something
that you don't feel you understand. The
only other prerequisite is to uh just
enjoy yourselves, have a good time. This
is your time and I'll see you all later.
I'll say how are you all this dream time
of your time as you create time to
exist.
Allow us to begin this interaction this
evening of your time with a little bit
of a reminder of certain ideas we have
spoken of briefly which we now find we
have an opportunity to speak of more and
more often as you have now entered
through the doorway of what to call your
new year. Thus indicating to yourselves
that you are embarking upon ideas and
attitudes and perspectives and levels of
consciousness that you have hitherto not
explored up to this point. Allow
yourselves to realize that you have
entered quite realistically a type of
playtime. Now the idea that your
physiological reality is becoming one of
reality is becoming one of
effortlessness, of ease, of
synchronicity, of harmonious creation
without struggle, without strife, and
that you have now the opportunity to
leave far behind you all the
methodologies that caused pain in your
reality. All of the endeavors and all
the explorations of yourself do not have
to come in the format that you call
pain. Every single thing that you could
possibly discover about yourself or need
to discover about yourself can be
presented to you by yourself in a format
of ecstasy in a format of effortlessness
in a format of play and discovery and
challenge in a positive way. Are you all
following along so far? Is this
translating to you? Yes. Recognize
therefore that many of the ideas we will
undertake from this point forward now
that you have passed through the doorway
we have spoken of for so many months of
your time that is the doorway that
allows you to now know that you have an
effortlessness spread out before you
that the path you have chosen to be can
be walked in full light and full ease
and full joy so that you can run and
jump and play along this path. No need
anymore to cautiously watch for every
little foothold. Is there a, as you say,
pothole there? I cannot see. There are
so many shadows crossing my path. I do
not know what I am going to fall into
the deepest, darkest chasm of my
consciousness because I do not know what
lays out ahead of me. There may be many
rocks against which I will stub my toe,
my shin. I will fall on my face, land in
the dirt, and I will not be able to find
my way. I may come to many crossroads,
and I may be confused as to which
direction to take. All of these ideas of
confusion and negative sense now that
you have entered this doorway are long
since passed. Each and every one of you
in being willing to form a gathering, in
being willing to look at your lives in a
joyous way, will now begin to allow that
life to unfold in effortlessness and
ease. And allow the path, no matter how
many junctions you may have created in
that path, to be one that is always
fully illuminated by the light of your
own knowingness, the light of your own
trust and the light of your own faith,
which is a light that shines most
brightly within you, and that you can
let out to illuminate the path. So that
there remains on that path no longer not
one single shadow of a doubt about who
and what you are and what ideas in life
and what experiences in life are true
for you. For one of the first and
foremost things you will learn upon this
path is that as you interact with all
other beings in your reality, you will
discover firsthand and in a very
physical way that the truth is composed
of all truths and that every single
individual's truth is real and correct
for them. And that the idea of all the
unity you will now begin to experience
in a more accelerated way upon your
planet. All the desire you have had for
peace and harmony upon your planet. All
the desire for oneness to express
yourselves through your society in a
degree of oneness will be most easily
created upon your planet when each and
every one of you learns to allow for the
infinite diversity of every single
individual to be expressed to its
fullest extent. The unity you desire
will be the result of allowing and
equalization and validation of each and
every path of each and every method that
exists upon your planet. Knowing that
each and every way is simply that
individual's way of choosing to learn
what they need to learn and that you can
simply by living the path that is true
for you shine like a brilliant light set
an example to those individuals not that
they have to choose the idea of
effortlessness and ease but that if you
set that example they can see within you
a reflection within themselves that
allows them to know if you can live a
life of effortlessness so can I for I
deserve it just as much as you And you
deserve it just as much as me. And we
both, all of us, deserve it just as much
as anything. For creation gives you the
birthright of ecstasy. You are created
of love. You are created of ecstasy.
Happiness is your divine right, as you
say. And there is no reason now from
this point forward that you should have
to create a life of suffering in order
to learn the things you need to learn.
Are you all following along? Yes. We
will therefore a little bit later on in this
therefore a little bit later on in this
interaction share with you a
specifically designed exercise meditation that will
designed exercise meditation that will
allow you to get in touch with the child
within yourself. Allow you to understand
that you can play now as a child. Not so
much in a childish manner but in a very
childlike manner. And that this is one
of the ideas that will allow you to
begin to experience in your physical
reality true
agelessness, true living in the moment,
and true longevity. As you begin to
refresh and rejuvenate yourselves
through your very attitude, through your
very perspectives, through your very
points of view, and through most of all
your willingness to give birth to that
child within you once again, and to no
longer keep it buried within you as your
society has taught you to do. All right.
All right. We will open at this time
therefore to the interaction of sharing
the Yes. You and then you. Uh you have
mentioned in the past the fact that uh
Hawaii can be likened to the heart
chakra of the planet. Could you We are
not the first ones to say so. There are
many individuals upon your planet that
have been sensitive to the energy of the
different vortex or gateway points
around your world. And for many
generations they have likened the idea
of what you call your Hawaii area to the
heart chakra in your body being the
heart chakra of the planet if you will.
The reason that this is so basically is
you will find that within what you now
call the Pacific basin there was in
times past in your terms of counting the
island continent of Laoria. And in this
way you will find that the Hawaiian
island. Now the remnant you call the
Hawaiian island still has the energy
connection to that ancient civilization.
That ancient civilization was almost
totally instinctive, hardly analytical.
And in this way therefore they
functioned entirely from the heart. They
imbued this entire area this entire
energy matrix with that energy. And it
still exists today. Many of you are now
reforming connections to the lives you
have had then and allowing yourself to
bathe yourselves to immerse yourselves
in this heart energy to get back in
touch with what you were then. You are
now completing a cycle begun so many
tens of thousands of years ago. You are
now allowing Lamura to rise within you,
within your consciousness, within your
energy. Now that you have explored for
many tens of thousands of years the
analytical path, the idea of thinking
yourself into many degrees of limitation
and separation. Now that you are at the
end of that cycle, you are forming a
reconnection with the heart energy, the
instinctive energy, the knowing energy,
the trust energy, the love energy. And
this simply represents the focal point
that still contains that energy. The
very rocks, the very water, the very air
is imbued, is crystallized with the
energy of the civilization which for all
intents and purposes still does exist
for everything in time exists
simultaneously with everything else and
linear time is but your illusion. You
follow me? Yes, I do. Does that assist
you? Thank you very much. Thank you very
much. Yes, for sure. Hey, two days ago
there was a a global unity for one
moment. I hope there you what a lot of
people. Did you say you hope I hope then
you are not adding to that unity for
hope implies despair.
You know you know you know there was you
know you know there is
okay I have two questions about All
right. What I'd like to know, I'd like
to know if I would like to know what
effect was felt outside this planet. I
would like to know whether oh much much
much understand you have had the
intention and the attention of many
civilizations for quite some time. Your
willingness as a planet to unify
yourselves in one thought in that way
was much enjoyed and much appreciated.
For you are then saying out loud to us
that you do wish to become one world
that will have the ability to interact
with other whole worlds. We await you
with joy.
Thank you. I I have one one more
question. A lot of us experienced that
moment in a different way and in
different places obviously all over the
all over the globe. I uh some of us and
I personally had a very physical
response to it as if somebody had
punched me in the chest. I shared this
with some people who also felt the same
thing. Other people I've heard have seen
experienced flames. Uh I wonder if you
could just comment on what that is. Why
why that reaction work? Each and every
individual when they tap in through the
chakra of intention through their
mentality through their art through any
gate through any connective bridge
through any link of energy from their
body to all the other bodies from their
consciousness to all other
consciousnesses will interpret that link
will interpret that energy and interpret
that connection by whatever symbology is
pertinent to them by whatever symbology
represents the portions of themselves
that they have now needed to unlock to
allow them to begin to create that
peaceful reality in their own individual
world. You follow me? Yes. Whatever you
felt, however you felt it, is indicative
of the way you needed to feel it was
indicative of the symbology in your mind
that would best serve you in relating to
the idea of how to assist in the
co-creation of a unified world. It has
opened a gate, opened doorways within
you. Many of you may still allow some of
this opening to occur more strongly in
your dream reality than your physical
reality. But we now perceive that you
are allowing your dream and physical
realities to blend together since they
are of course one in the same reality
anyway. But now you will begin to see
not only in your dreams but in your
physical reality many things beginning
to occur synchronistically
coincidentally not accidentally that may
have previously been only thought could
occur in your dream reality. And one of
the symptoms that will now increase
rapidly upon your planet will be for
individuals to begin to blend the dream
and the physical reality to such an
extent that there may be events that
occur in their life that perhaps will
come out in conversations with other
individuals that will allow the
individual to stop for a moment and
realize did I live that physically? Did
I dream that? I don't know where that
came from. But it does not matter. It is
all becoming one. And as you blend the
dream and the physical reality, then you
will understand that all the things that
have ever been possible in your dream
reality are possible in your physical
reality. And that it is that malleable.
Whatever any individual felt during that
connection was simply their way of
recognizing that a door within them had
opened, that a lock had been unlocked.
And in this way, they released a portion
of themsel, integrated a greater portion
of themselves, and now you are more than
you were. You follow me? Yes. Thank you.
Thank you.
[Music]
I I am looking at my sleeping cycle and
saying that I would like to change it.
Go right ahead.
And this is something that I've been
interested in doing for a couple of for
a while. I see. The sense of it is that
I don't have any control over my
pattern. But you do, you are choosing,
you are making the decisions that allow
you to perhaps unify with what might be
called the more natural biological cycle
of your planet wherein you find many
individuals will actually be quite
active in what you call the early
morning hours and perhaps a little bit
lethargic in the afternoon. That is
actually your natural biological cycle.
If you have created a society that says
you must be awake during your natural
sleep cycle, then you attempt to force
yourself to be asleep during your
natural awake cycle. When you begin to
explore the integration of yourself,
when you begin to rely and exist upon
the direct energy of the universe, you
will tend to fall back into that natural
cycle. But because you may still be
trying to follow your society's day
night cycle, you may find yourself
waking up in the middle of the night and
saying, "Oh, what's wrong with me? I
cannot sleep. I have all this energy. I
must have a disease called insomnia."
No, it is quite a natural thing. Allow
yourself to begin to realize that as you
blend the dream and the physical reality
together, you will need less sleep
anyway. Because sleep is basically for
the purpose of making the connections
from your physical self, physical
consciousness to your higher
consciousness that you have for tens of
thousands of years not allowed yourself
to make while you are awake. You are now
beginning to allow it to be all right to
blend your physical and higher
consciousness while you are awake. So,
you will need less sleep. Do you follow
me? Yeah. I have a
couple questions in relation to that.
What about the idea that the cycle is in
relation to the earth and that it's
natural for especially people that live
out in nature to go to sleep because
it's dark to get up at
dark to get up at
dawn. In this way, you will find that
there are many individuals that even
though they may, as you say, retire at
dusk and arise at dawn will still find
many ideas that you call nocturnal
energies to come up, nocturnal
activities. Indeed, they may arise
approximately 2 a.m. and then re-retire
approximately 4 a.m. That period of time
being very highly psychically active,
very highly creatively active within
your biological mechanism.
Okay. I find that I'm very sensitive to
noise and to just the presence of other
people. Guys, so for instance, like on
this trip, I love having roommates and
having people come around me, but I find
that I don't get enough sleep or like,
you know, sort of
getting that change. All right, you are
becoming hyper sensitive to more and
more energy in that way. All you really
need to do is allow yourself to
recognize that your sleep is not
something that can be interrupted. the
sleep you truly need. Allow yourself
when you hear of anything that you would
formerly have called a distraction,
allow yourself to include it. Not
exclude it.
Include the sound. Include the noise.
Include the pattern, the biological
rhythms going on around you into your
mentality. and they will actually help
you get into the state you call sleep.
Do not attempt to think that you need to
shut them out in order to have peace.
The idea is now that you are making more
and more connections and you want to
make those connections. So include them
to have peace. Do not exclude them to
have peace. You follow me? Let them
blend. Let them become their own natural
noise, their own natural rhythm. Play
with them. Ride the noise as you would
ride the waves in your water. Use your
imagination. If you hear different
noises going on while you are attempting
to drift off, as you say, to sleep, then
pretend you are drifting on an ocean, if
you wish, floating, and that every ID
you call a noise is yet another eddy,
another current, another wave that bobs
you in this direction, flows you in that
direction. And pretty soon, you will
allow yourself to treat it as music, as
energy motion in that way. And before
you know it, you will be fast asleep.
Let it be music to your ears. Let it be
fascinating to you. Bring up the
childlike curiosity of what the noises
you attract to yourself could mean to
you, what your imagination can make of
them. And when you make a game of it,
you will fall into your imagination just
like that. So in terms of waking up,
like I'm asleep and I'm waking up. What
would be the
What am I creating? Why am I creating
that?
It may be the idea that you do think
them to be distractions. And so you
continually prove your belief to
yourself, that you can be distracted,
that you attract the idea into your
life, that you can be interrupted, that
the connections you need to make are
being blocked by something seemingly
beyond your control. But they are not
being blocked. There are no blocks.
There are only unexpected directions
that you refuse to go with. When you
refuse to go in that direction, no
matter how unexpected it is, then it
seems like a block. Play with it. Let it
in. Examine it. The more you sit there
and meditate on the different noises
that you hear, even the ones that wake
you up, you will find yourself going
back into the meditative state in
exactly the way you need to go into the
dream meditative state to make the
connections you need to make. The noises
that are there are there for a reason.
Allow them their own distinction because
you are attracting them. If you did not
need them, you would not hear
them. Learn what they teach you. If only
to teach you that you believe you can be
interrupted. You are not on a path. A
path is what you are. You cannot be off
of yourself. You cannot be interrupted.
There are no things in life that are
interruptions unless you choose to
believe that they are. It is only your
belief that they distract you from what
you think you need to do that allows you
to perceive them as a true
interruption. As soon as you let them be
a part of the path, you will not hear
them. You follow me? Yeah, thank you. And I
You follow me? Yeah, thank you. And I
appreciate that. It feels good to me.
One last thing is regarding When I'm
tired and I feel like, boy, this would
be a good time to sleep. It feels
natural and I'm sort of then sleep.
Another choice I see myself making is
often to just be active with other
people. There's stuff going on even
though like there's this body that would
be a good listen to your body
consciousness. Again, this is connected
to the idea that you have bought into
that you're going to miss something
important. You are not going to miss
anything. you need to have in your life
to be the person you chose to be in this
life. So on one hand you give yourself
the opportunity that when you know you
are sleepy, you interrupt yourself with
things you think are important rather
than simply listening to your body
consciousness. And when in that way you
allow yourself to sleep, then you
constantly remind yourself that you wish
you were doing other things. But the
idea is to simply follow your own
natural pattern and trust that you will
miss nothing. It is your belief that you
will miss out on something that
constantly creates an interruption in
your natural sleep because you are so
alert for something that might pass you
by that you don't let yourself
relax. You are going to miss nothing
that you chose to create in this life
that actually needs to be in the life
you chose to live. You cannot miss a
date with destiny.
You follow me? That's good. So relax.
When you feel tired, sleep. When you are
awake, be awake and alert. And
understand that the natural cycle that
you have chosen will then allow the
things you need to participate in to
only occur when you are
awake. It does not work
otherwise. You follow me?
Thank you very much. You sure? Yes. I I
don't know uh if this is going to but I
have a question about the planet Saturn.
Yes. And and uh our
astrology in our astrology Saturn rules
structure to some degree. Well, and I
wonder if our understanding of structure
is really clear. I I I have a some kind
of I seem to have a conflict with
freedom and play and structure. All
right. Within myself. All right. And I
think sometimes while maybe my being in
Capricorn ruled by Saturn, maybe
emotionally I'm tied to structure. I I
don't know. All right. I just wonder.
First of all, recognize that you have
made the choices to associate yourself
with this type of idea, this type of
energy. You are not literally ruled by
anything but you. You follow me? Right?
The choices you make will be the reality
you experience. Now the idea, the
metaphor, the
representational idea of a portion of
your energy that is represented by
Saturn is the type of structure that
simply indicates the different styles or
patterns that are available to you in
this particular earth reality for you to
use to learn what you need to learn It
does not mean that you are rigidly
affixed into a specific pattern. It
means that you have before you, let us
say, a platter of various choices. Each
and every one of those choices will be
indicative of the general overall
structure that represents living in what
you call earth plain reality, third
density. But there is a wide range of
freedom as to how to experience that
particular reality. Saturn is simply the
focus portion of the overall
consciousness that creates the entire
solar system in which you exist. That
represents itself in the form you would
call the council. The council is simply
a portion of the overall consciousness
of the entire being that your solar
system is that represents an awareness
of the holographic patterns that are
available for you to choose from to live
the different styles of physical life
that you wish to live. This is the
structure you are sensing you following
so far. Well, I think sort of all right
completely. Let us put it this
way. Look at consciousness as a valve.
All right. Right. Assume that there is a
large quantity of homogeneous energy of
no particular pattern or structure in
the universe. All right.
Yes. No. Maybe. Yes. All right.
Allow yourself to think of your
particular solar system with your planet
Earth, your sun, your planets around
your sun, including Saturn, to be
valves, gateways that allow that
homogeneous energy to be
translated in a certain way that will be
representative of a certain environment
that you as an individual consciousness
wish to experience. So you set up this
environment by creating different valves
that will allow the homogeneous energy
of creation to be translated in specific
formats. This valve will let us say
allow the energy to flow through itself.
And when it comes out of that valve or
let us say when the white light of the
homogeneous energy comes through the
prism of Saturn so to speak, it will
then break down the white light into the
spectrum, the specific spectrum that
represents this are representative. This
pattern, this flow, this spectrum
represents the overall rules by which
this system will function. Now there are
many other valves that will create
different let us say attitudes,
different biases of that energy,
different perspectives, different flows
of that energy. But what you call Saturn
is your portion of the overall
consciousness that represents the
regulation of the flow of patterns, the
flow of choices that you can experience
in this particular solar system. It is
an energy
gate. A physical planet in that sense is
only a symbol for an energy gate.
Is this making any sense? I think so.
Therefore, when you choose the
timing when you as a non-physical being
will enter into this particular
scenario, you then take upon yourself to
some degree the representational
patterns that are going on at that time,
all the energy patterns of relationships
going on between the different energy
gates. And you solidify that pattern
into your energy as your energy as the
representational individual that you
are. And so you say, well, this planet
rules me because I injected myself into
this physical matrix when such and such
an energy through this valve was
interacting with all the other valves in
exactly the way it would have to to
create me to be the individual
representation of energy that I am.
Now that is still very malleable once
you begin that life. You can fluctuate
it to a great degree. You have much
range of freedom. But you will still
carry the original imprint of your
choice of entering the game at that
particular time. You will still carry
the original congealment of that energy
in your solid form. You follow me,
right? Yes, I do. Does this assist you?
Yes. Anything else is up to you. You
have the freedom as a physical
consciousness to arrange that idea, to
arrange that pattern and create whatever
experiences will be representative of
the infinite variety of choices in which
you can experience the you you are. You
will always still be you in this game
that is fixed in this particular energy
pattern. But you as a persona can change
over and over and over and over and over
and over again. And you do. But you will
always be recognized by everyone else as
you. You follow me? Right? That is the
original imprint which you can fluctuate
and overlay with as many personas as you
desire. You will still be recognized by
your signature vibration.
Does that assist you? Yes, I think it
does. All right. Thank you very much.
Thank you. Sharing. Sure. you and you
would you comment on uh the differences
that the peace meditation has made? You
will see them in your life. You will
understand that individuals will now be
attracted in your life that will come to
you already with a knowingness or they
will come to you with a searching that
represents something you can share with
them. You will begin to attract more
synchronicity into your lives. You will
find your lives being as we have said
effortless that you will attract the
situations necessary to allow you to be
the individual you need to be without
struggling or wondering where you are
going to get the opportunity to be the
individual you want to be. Everyone that
interacts with you will bring to you
something you need and those you
interact with will need something from
you. This will be the major change you
will begin to see. Also, you will see
major changes taking place in what you
would call your society structures, your
economic structures, your social
structures, your religious structures.
All of these ideas will begin faster and
faster to homogenize into one
another. So that you can recognize that
the only structure, so to speak, that
you need upon your planet at all is one
that provides service in allowing
individuals to be who they are, not one
that attempts to mold them into the way
they think they should be made. These
are the changes you will begin to see.
And also because of your willingness,
you have opened up many more gates that
will allow us and other civilizations to
also open up more contact physically
with your world. So there will be what
you would call an increase in sightings
of our crafts.
Does that answer your question? Yes.
Thank you. Say, could you comment on the
J sighting? What civilization was that
that was
It was not any particular civilization.
It is what we refer to as a large survey
craft that contains representatives of
many civilizations.
Any particular
many? Was there any significance to it being
Was there any significance to it being
it being visible this time?
Yes. The significance is that it is now
allowable. The significance is that it
will occur more often. The significance
is that your individuals, your people
upon your planet will now realize like
your government already realizes that
this is something real, that we exist,
that you can interact with us if you
wish to. But it is still up to
you. Like the dolphins, when you reach
for our craft, we will remain just out
of reach until you allow yourself to
function as we function. Just as the
dolphins remain just out of reach until
you function as they function, until you
identify as them. When you begin to
identify as us in your own terms, as
your own civilization, we will not be
out of reach.
What exactly? One moment. You are next.
I would like to explore with you the
idea of the council which you mentioned.
All right. Now first of all before we
begin understand we are using your
earth's terminology and we do not
necessarily imply that it is exactly as
literal a council of beings as your
civilization might
think. It is not a council in the
governmental form you are used to
thinking of.
I have been um in touch with
uh consciousnesses who represent
themselves as being of a council. Yes.
Is is this the same council of which you
spoke a few moments ago? The Saturn idea
primarily. Yes, it is connected to that.
There are aspects that are connected to
what we also refer to as the
association, which is the collection of
many civilizations, not only your own
solar system, but the primary council
vibration you are in touch with is the
fragmentaryary representation of the
association that specifically is of the
vibration of your solar system.
they have communicated to me mostly in
terms of theme of a shift from being in
the service of Orion energy guys
uh into I'm not sure what it's into I
guess um but I would be interested in
any uh sharing that you could do in that
respect and especially as that pertains
to having stepped through the doorway.
All right. Now, we have already
discussed to some degree the idea that
you know that the Orion offshoot and the
Plleadian offshoot are branches of the
same family. And in this way, therefore,
you are now making the familial
reconnections. You have gone through the
lens so to speak of Orion and shifted
yourselves in the exploration of
polarity, the exploration of positive
and negative realities. And now that you
are integrating only in a positive idea
of manifestation, you are now becoming
more and more akin to your kin in
plleadian terms. And you are now
rejoining families literally.
You follow me? Yes.
That is all we will give you at this
time. I follow you.
I follow you.
anymore. You see how simple it is?
Yes. Um could you elaborate a little bit
more on identifying as the dolphins and
identifying as your Yes. Understand that
everything is a matter of vibratory
frequency. Everything operates at a
certain wavelength. Telepathy is the result of
wavelength. Telepathy is the result of
identifying with or identifying as
another being. In other words, very
simply, being in love. Okay? When you
are in love with another being, you
operate at a similar frequency. So,
though it may seem that you are actually
literally reading each other's minds,
what you are simply doing is you are
becoming the same type of prism that
translates the universal thoughts in
much the same pattern. So, you are
sharing the same thoughts because you
operate on the same wavelength. It is
not that you are directly literally
reading each other's mind. It is that
you are creating thought in a similar
pattern and so seem to be sharing the
same thoughts. That is full
identification as and that is why you
know that on your planet when you see
individuals whom you say are in love
they often know each other's thoughts.
So it is the question then of wanting to
see wanting wanting actually separates
you in a sense to some degree. Yes. The
idea is to be like
unto. Then when you create the vibration
of what you imagine us to be for
yourselves on your own world, then you
create your world to be the type of
world that shares the same frequency
vibratory patterns that we have created
on our world. And that is what allows us
to interact with you face to face. When
you choose to create heaven on earth,
the heavens can come down to earth. You
follow me? But until you identify your
own version of that idea, as long as you
continue to think that we need to rescue
you or need to save you from yourselves,
you are not getting the idea. You are
not understanding that you are your own
creators and the realities and the world
you experience is exactly as you created
to be. If you don't prefer it, create it
to be the way you want it. And you will
be the ones that allow us to be able to
interact with you by tuning yourselves
to the same wavelength. Otherwise, the
two programs can't meet. You follow me?
Yes, I do. Does that assist you? Yes,
that's Thank you very much. What is
fear? Fear can occur for many reasons.
Fear can occur for many reasons.
Generally speaking, fear is a belief
that there is a portion of your
consciousness that you might discover
that could intrinsically have the
ability to do harm to you and so you do
not want you make the choice to not want
to discover it. You will find that the
idea of fear is that when you do not
listen to the connections you know are
true for you, but you still insist on
having the life you want, then when you
do not listen to those connections that
come at first subtly, then they will
become noisier and noisier and noisier
and noisier and more and more obnoxious
until you are forced to listen. Until
you are forced to stand right in the
moment and stop looking everywhere else.
Fear creates you, forces you to look
squarely at something you keep refusing
to look at about yourself that you say
you need to look at, that you say you
want to look at in order to grow as a
being. But in your society, you have
been taught that you can have portions
of your consciousness that can, shall we
say, do you in because you buy into that
belief, because you do not realize that
there really is nothing you could
possibly discover about yourself that
cannot be put toward the positive
integration of the total being that you
are, then you create the idea that you
don't want to look at certain portions
of yourself. But as long as you express
the desire to be an integrated being,
which you will always do automatically
because you are a creator by birthright,
then you will constantly create fear in
your life to force yourself to look at
the portions you do not want to look at
consciously. When you are willing to
look at those portions and understand
that they serve you, you will fear
nothing. You follow me? Yes. Does that
assist you? Yes, thank you very much my
fearless one.
You in uh in embracing the ideas of belief
in uh in embracing the ideas of belief
created reality I am finding that I
think I need certain things in my
reality in order to exist. All right
i.e. money i.e. uh doicile etc. i.e. All
right. Okay. But in this way, recognize that
Okay. But in this way, recognize that
there is not necessarily the need at
this time to break down the different
symbols of abundance to recognize that
you are abundant. Definition of
abundance. The ability to do what you
need to do when you need to do it.
Period. That's it. That's abundance. Now
if you have that ability then you do not
necessarily need a specific
representational tool that you are used
to thinking is the only tool that
represents abundance if you are still
able to do what you need to do when you
need to do it. Not that you cannot have
it. You certainly can. You can have
anything you truly desire, anything you
truly want, anything you truly need.
However, recognize that many times in
the exploration of integration, many of
you will begin to realize that certain
things can occur in your life without
the tools you are used to thinking must
be in your life to bring it. So, you are
exploring many different ways to create
in your life what you truly need to do.
And you are learning that there are many
more tools to abundance than the ones
you are used to thinking of, such as
money. Money is a very valid and
valuable tool, a valid way to represent
abundance. But it does not exist
everywhere. It does not exist on
art. I get the money to have this thing.
So getting the money involves this whole
other process over here that may take
years and years and years when all the
while if you had been willing to let
your abundance serve you automatically
and synchronistically you may have been
able to turn around and find someone
that's tapping you on the shoulder all
the time saying but I want to give you
this thing why are you so insistent on
making all this money and taking years
and years and years and years to get
what I want to give you now. So the idea
is simply to trust that you are always
abundant and that if money is the way
that you can be abundant quickest then
money is the way that will come to you.
An opportunity will come into your life
that will allow you to make the money or
you will be given the money or you will
get it somehow that will allow you to do
what you need to do. But if you simply
trust that you are abundant and follow
at any given moment what excites you the
most and that is the most important key.
what excites you the most. Then life
will support you 100% as life has always
supported you and it will allow you to
attract into your reality whatever
situations will allow you to do what you
need to do when you need to do it. And
if money does not come with it then take
that as a sign that money is not
necessary for that particular
interaction. If it were it would have
been there
first. You follow me? Yeah. Follow what
excites you the most in life. Even if
you have been taught to believe it can't
support you, it
can. Excitement is the physical
translation of the vibratory energy of
the path you chose to be in this life.
That's what excitement is. The energy
that represents the path you chose to
be. Therefore following at any given
moment the situation that brings with it
the highest degree of excitement is
taking the path of least resistance is
living an effortless life and it will
bring into your life all the individuals
and all the situations necessary to
allow you to continue to be that
effortless being. That's the way life
works and it does work that way when you
let it. There is
absolutely nothing too simple or too
good to be true.
Are you sure about that? Absolutely.
Doing what excites me the most. Doing
what brings me the most joy at any given
moment. At any given moment that you are
capable with the tools you have at hand
of acting upon. So what I found out that
there's times at which I seem to exist
with levels of denial. All right. Be
that certain programming be ways ways of
being. So what I need from you is a
shortcut. Get me around that denial or give me
Get me around that denial or give me
some tools or uh share with me how you
might suggest uh me to get out of my own
way. Trust 100% trust in the idea you prefer
Trust 100% trust in the idea you prefer
to be rather than 100% trust in an idea
you don't prefer to be.
Welcome. You did not have to do anything
special in order to deserve to exist.
Infinite creation obviously therefore
believes you deserve to exist. Give
yourself the same benefit of the doubt. All
doubt. All
right. Sure. I'll accept.
Understand? We are not telling you to do
something you are not already doing.
Each and every one of you has
100% trust in the idea you are
experiencing in life. We are simply
telling you that you can put that 100%
trust behind any idea you prefer. And
when you do, that's the physical reality
you will get because you always get the
physical reality that is representative
of the idea you have 100% of your trust
behind. If you have 100% of your trust behind
If you have 100% of your trust behind
the idea that you will succeed sometimes
but not too
often, that's the reality you get. And
then you say, "Well, what's wrong with
me? I'm not functioning correctly. You
are functioning
perfectly. You are getting exactly the
representation in physical reality of
the idea you have 100% of your trust
behind. If you don't like the definition
of the reality you get, change the
definition and put 100% of your trust
behind that." Then that's the reality
you'll experience. It is that simple.
Simple mechanics, simple physics. The
patterns seem to be so rutful. If you
say so, that's your
so, that's your
belief. Now, do you choose to prefer to
believe that that is chiseled in steel,
or are you willing to look at that as
nothing more than tissue paper and blow
it
away? When you say, "Well, it seems to
me that I cannot do this." Well, but our
this is the way it has been. So
what is that the way you want to be now?
If the answer is no, then don't keep
putting energy into the idea. Well, it
seems to be this way. If you truly are
changed, if you truly are going to act
like the person who has changed the
definition of their reality, you won't
say the things you used to say as the
old person who believed you were in a
rut. Because the new you knows there's
no such
thing. So don't talk that way if you are
the new person. You follow me? Thank you
very much. Understand? You take
absolutely no time to change because you
do project a world of linear time
reality. It may take a little time for
the physical reality to transform into
the representation of the real belief
you are being. But don't let that let
you believe that you haven't changed.
You change the second you believe you
have. Let your physical reality take
whatever time is necessary to transform
into a reflection of the fact that you
have indeed changed. Do not be
impatient. The only reason that you any
of you create impatience is because you
think you need patience and you don't.
If you are enjoying every single moment
of your life because you know every
single moment of your life is there for
a reason. Then you won't be waiting for
something better to come along. You will
be enjoying what you are doing now. And
when you are not waiting for something
better to come along, you don't need to
be patient. And if you don't need to be
patient, you don't create impatience.
So if you know you have changed, if you
are able to recognize that you have the
ability to
consciously there is no mystery in this.
Consciously decide choose I am now
different this belief such and such and
such is now what I
am. Act like it. If you do not see your
physical reality on the
surface, change
immediately. Don't immediately fall back
and say, "Oh, well, I failed. Oh, well,
I guess I'm no good at this. Oh, well, I
guess I can't really change myself. Oh,
well, it's too difficult to change." Why
give up that soon? Recognize, first of
all, that it takes a little bit of time
for the physical reality to transform.
However, no physical symbol and no
physical situation or circumstance has
any builtin
meaning. They don't mean anything. The
things, the circumstances, the props in
your life don't have builtin meaning.
You give them meaning and the meaning
you give them is the effect you get out
of it. So if you know you have changed
and you see something a situation occur
in your life that on the surface appears
to be the same or similar to something
that used to occur, why simply assume
that you haven't changed. Oh well look
here it happens again. I am in the same
rut over and over and over again. No,
you are continuing to believe that the
surface appearance has the same meaning
and it
doesn't. If you are different, it is
different. Give it a new meaning. Give
the meaning to the situation that you
would imagine a person who is different
in the way you want to be different
would look at it. Do not look at it the
way you used to be. Look at it the way
you are now. Say to yourself, "Well,
look, if I was really this different
person, if I was really this person, I
want to be all abundant and all of this.
If I were that person, how would I look
at this situation? Would I not see
something positive in it? Would I not
have a different perspective, a
different point of view? Yes, you would.
So, look at it that way, not the way you
used to. By looking at it the way you
used to, you constantly reinforce the
old reality. And that's what creates the
rut. Simply because you assume that just
because a situation on the surface
appears to be the same as it used to be,
that it has the same reason for being
there or has the same meaning built into
it. No situation has builtin meaning.
All situations are fundamentally
neutral, blank, empty, zero. The meaning
you give to it based upon what you have
been taught to believe it represents is
exactly the effect you get out of it.
Positive meaning in, positive effect
out, negative meaning in, negative
effect out. It is up to you. Again,
simple physics, simple mechanics.
Nice. Um, I'm wondering how close of
contact do extraterrestrials
have you talked to United States
government very often? Our civilization
specifically does not. There have been a
couple of civilizations that have had
face-to-face dialogue with certain of
your governments, specifically what you
call your own United States and also
what you would call England.
And do the governments listen at all or
to some degree understand that there is
now I will use a term that is very
colloquial in your language and it does
not necessarily imply exactly the same
thing that you might think it means. But
there is an overall timetable. There is
an overall plan, so to speak, to allow
your civilization to acclimate to our
civilization to acclimate to our
presence in a way that will not upset
your social structures too much. We are
not here to destroy your planet
socially. We are here to assist you in
remembering who you are and allow you to
choose to change your social system at
the rate is comfortable for you. So this
is the fragment of our overall plan that
your government finds agreeable for it
allows them to get in touch with the
fact that their shift in power is not
going to actually result in a loss of
power. It is going to result in a gain
of their own personal power. Though for
now because of what you have created
your governments to be they think that
allowing interaction to occur with our
civilizations would result completely in
a loss of the power they have come to
cherish. You follow me? So we tell them
in that way that it can proceed to some
degree slowly but that the information
can come out bit by bit at a rate that
will allow them to think they still will
maintain the power they are used to. But
what they will begin to realize is that
they are actually gaining their own
self-empowerment as every single
individual on your planet is gaining his
or her own self-empowerment at the same
time. And therefore the government will
no longer be that which rules you but
that which serves you. For you will then
recognize that there really is no
separation and that you all are your
governments. You have created them to be
what they are. You are your governments.
They are an extension of what you fear.
Protect us, you say. Protect us from
this. Protect us from the things we
fear. Well, there is a very broad range
of what your government has been taught
to believe you will fear. And so they
will protect you from
everything. If they are born out of
fear, in order to survive, they must
generate fear. When you take back the
fear. When you take back the
responsibility for your fear, then there
is nothing you need protection from and
no reason to have the idea of a
government that stands between you and
direct interaction with us. But for now,
we allow the rate to continue at
whatever rate is comfortable. And they
do realize that bit by bit the
information cannot be suppressed because
now it is in your consciousness to
recognize that we do exist and so it
will come out at whatever rate you are
comfortable with. But there have been
some face-to-face
interactions. Some individuals in your
government as you say colloquially are
for it. Some of them are against it.
Does that answer your question? Yes it
does. Can I ask another question? You do
not have to ask if you can ask. Proceed.
Um, it's about what's going on with the
government in the United States right
now. They're having with this uh
controversy with Iran,
guys. Central American wars having their
real self shown in
public. It's symbolic of it is symbolic
that now all of the things that used to
be covert on your planet are now coming
to the surface and creating themselves
in an overt way so that it is not hidden
anymore. You are allowing the
subconscious and unconscious portions of
your social structure to come into full
light, into full consciousness, so that
you can see what you have been creating
your world to be. So that you can see
what you have been choosing to back in
terms of your government and social
structures. So that you can all decide
in the open, is this the way you want
your world to be or do you wish it to be
some other way? You are now creating
what was formerly covert to be overt so
that you can decide what type of reality
consciously you actually prefer and
whether or not you truly wish to
continue to keep things hidden from
yourself. That is why you are airing
your laundry so that you can decide whether
laundry so that you can decide whether
or not you wish to continue to wear
it. You follow me? Thank you very much.
And let me remind you that when you say
they are doing this, they are doing
that, that is the same as you. We are
doing this, we are doing that. They are
not separate from you. You are your
governments. You follow me? I I follow
that theoretically. One moment.
Understand that you always have the
capacity without
accusation, without invalidation and
without judgment and without accosting
them to communicate to your government
the way you would prefer your world to
be. When they start hearing from enough
of you, perhaps they'll begin to believe
it. But if you simply say, "Well, it's
their job to fix all of this. I have no
power in this. I have no say in this. I
can't possibly affect them or move them
in any way, shape or form. It's up to
them. Then you only allow them to
continue to separate themselves from you
and they do not then receive the message
that you want your world to be
different. So without attacking them and
without accusing them, communicate with
them. You're only communicating with
another portion of your own higher
consciousness. Communicate to them the
way you perceive the world can be. Share
your dream with them. share your dream.
Then when they begin to hear this from
more and more individuals, the dream can
be realized. They will allow themselves
to recognize, all right, all right, it's
all right. Now we can share the
information with you. Now that we know
it will not upset things too much. You
follow me?
Thank you very much, female.
Um, I've got quite that is all right.
Speak up. Douche, what is it that men
and women have to learn in order to be
able to do
um their companion kind of work on this
planet? Is something that they have to
learn? Yes. What they need to learn is
that every male contains masculine and
feminine energy and that every female
contains female and male energy and that
if every male and every female is
willing to marry those energies within
themsel, there will be no struggling,
there will be no strife, there will be
no disease on your planet at all.
It is up to every individual to learn
the balance of energy within themselves
and that everyone is in fact an equal
reflection of everyone else and that
everyone contains both sides to be
utilized and to be put forth in life
when and where each and every one of
those particular attributes is needed.
But that no one side is better than any
other side, no one side is any worse
than any other side. That every
individual has chosen to express
themselves in the way they have
expressed themselves. Every individual
creates the reality they experience and
it is up to them to marry those two
polarities within each and every female
within each and every male. That
marriage will absolutely erase every
single problem on your planet.
You follow me? Yes. Does that assist
you? Yeah. Thank you. Also, I'd like to
know if there are any dolphins where you
live. No, there are a four.
No, there are a four.
you would find similar to smallish whale
we call a Caesar. It is white with what
you would call zebra stripe black. In
this way, however, it is more the idea
of a fragmentaryary consciousness of the
total consciousness of our planet and is
not distinctly a separate, if you will
excuse the term, alien species as yours
is. Your planet to us contains two alien
species. the land beings and the water
beings you call the dolphin
whales. Recognize therefore the great
joy and opportunity that you have for
many planets in that way do not have
multiple sensient
species and you will find that you have
a species upon your planet that you can
learn to communicate with in various
ways and methods of tonality and
emotionality. You have one of the few truly nonh
You have one of the few truly nonh
humanoid alien species on your planet
right with you side by side. What a joy.
What an
experience. You follow me? Our planet
basically at this time contains mostly
the human form humanoid as you would say
life form as is represented by my body
approximately of average 5 ft of height.
white whitish gray skin coloration, wide
set eyes, no hair on the males, hair on
the females, mostly white. You will find
in this way that there are very few of
us in number, as that is simply not
necessary at this time for us to be
great in number, and at any time fully
twothirds of our population do not exist
on the surface of our planet at all, but
are traveling in what you would call
spacecraft. The majority of our
population is not permanent. It is made
up of the comingings and goings of
different beings from different places
in the different portions of the galaxy.
And also it is made up of temporary
embodiment when such as many beings in
your society are in your dream state and
visit our world and create a temporary
embodiment for themselves to experience
the reality of our world and then allow
it to simply dissolve when you wake up.
This is the majority of the population
of our planet. As for what you would
call the permanent membership, it is no
greater than approximately what you
would call 200 million for the entire
planet. Our planet therefore has very
little structures upon it. Is very much
parklike as you would say. And again,
also because the majority of our planet
at any given time is involved in space
travel and
exploration. Does this assist you? Thank
you very much.
You can you speak about
can you speak about
children who children coming in to hard
situations and growing up
and believing in a lot of what you're
saying and also experiencing a lot of
pain. All right. First of all, do
recognize that many of the children now
being born upon your planet will not
forget as much as you have forgotten.
And in this way, many of these children
may actually remind you as to what these
connections are. Many of these
connections being connections that have
come up through many past lives, many of
the hard situations that many of these
children may experience may simply be
remnant situations that they needed to
deal with in the relationships that were
formed in past life situations. Or maybe
they have chosen to be born into
difficult situations, family situations,
in order to allow the adults in that
situation to learn from the child the
things that the adults need to learn.
There can be as many reasons for a child
choosing a difficult situation to be
born into and grow up in as there are
children. But more and more you will
find that the children that are now
being born into your society will be
totally not only of a different
generation but totally of a different
culture altogether. They will have been
in a sense or let us say lack of a
better term processed now mainly through
the opaces of the energy vibrations of
Arcturus and Sirius and also many of
them will be returning plleadenss
wishing to be born upon your planet to
assist in the transformation at this
time. Many of them will be beings of
light and express it very early on. And
again, as we have said, many of them
will remind the adults who have chosen
to forget who they are, who they are.
But any difficult situations will simply
be the remnant processes that the
individual has chosen to be born into
that they feel they believe they need in
their lives to learn what they need to
learn. And in this way you will find
that more and more of these children now
that they are being born into a new
culture, a new belief system, a new
generation will no longer need to choose
family situations that bring inherent
difficulty with them. You follow me? For
the end of the reincarnational cycle is
at hand. And you will find therefore
that all of the contracts, all of the
agreements, and all of the arrangements
are now finalizing themselves within
this transformational life or within the
next one or two following. Then you will
find that many individuals upon your
planet will simply live longer lives,
not needing to have experiences shuffled
off or segregated into many separate
lives, and that many individuals living
now will actually still physically be
alive in 300 of your years. And that in
approximately what you call 2 to 3
thousand of your years, your society
will have completely finalized anything
it is needed to learn within the
physical reincarnational cycle of the
planet Earth and will no longer be
physical, allowing themselves to make
way for the next group of
consciousnesses who may be willing to
use the Earth vibration for their own
understanding and their own tutoring of
the ideas they need to experience. How
would you suggest that adults who are
working on childhood for whatever reason
they are engaging with that function now
in particular in their male and female
relationships and how that's getting
worked out on the planet. All right.
First of all, I would suggest that you
begin to recognize that you chose what
you went through for your own reasons.
So get in touch with how it served you
in a positive way. Many individuals will
choose to be born into lives in what
they would call diametrically opposed
belief systems within their parents so
that they have something to push against
to absolutely ensure that they will be
brought up with a polarity belief system
that will be more indicative of what is
needed in this transformational age. You
follow me? So in that way first of all
recognize that you knew what you were
doing when you chose the family
situation you were born into and you
still know what you are doing. Another
suggestion would be to recognize that if
you now are at the point where you
realize that you made that choice, then
as soon as you realize that it was a
choice, you are out of the cycle. You
are no longer attached to it. And that
the idea of the past no longer be
connected to the present. The past does
not control the present. The past does
not rule the present. You are at any
given moment whatever definition you
prefer to be. As long as you continue to
believe that what you were in the past
must control what you are now, you will
continue to create a life in which you
think you are controlled by that past.
But as soon as you recognize that you
are aware consciously as a physical
being of knowing that you made the
choices you made to get to where you are
now and that you simply can be what you
want to be now, then you can simply act
like what you want to be now and that
what you want to be now has nothing to
do with what you used to be. And could
you address jealousy as a human emotion
and how it serves us? what is its
purpose and and uh male female jealousy
is an invalidation an invalidation of
yourself. Jealousy in this way as it is
expressed upon your planet is when an
individual sees something in someone
else and believes I don't have that and
I want
that. But recognize if you have the
ability to see something in someone
else, you must contain it because you
can only perceive what you contain. So
jealousy only results from the belief
that what you see in others you don't
have. When you recognize that what you
see in others that you desire to be real
for you, you do have and that your very
ability to have seen it in someone else
is an indication that you have the
ability to be that way yourself. There
will be no need for
jealousy for you will be able to then
say, "I perceive something I have
desired to be in that individual." And
oh, happy day. Now that I know I can see
it in that individual, that means I have
the ability to manifest it just as
easily. You follow me? There is no need
for jealousy when you validate yourself
and love yourself unconditionally and
love all beings unconditionally and
recognize that you are a complete being.
You are not incomplete. You may believe
you are incomplete. You may believe you
see something in someone else that you
don't have. But that's only a
perspective, only a point of view. It is
your opportunity to recognize that when
you see something in someone else that
you desire to be, you can recognize that
you have the potential to be that idea.
Now, when you see something in someone
else you do not desire to be, it still
means you contain just as equal a
potential to be that idea. But you don't
have to if you don't prefer it. simply
recognize that everyone is a reflection.
You are only looking at mirrors when you
look at other
people. So what you see if you see
something you do not prefer, simply
recognize that the potential exists
within you because everyone contains
every probable reality and method of
expression. But if that you do see
something in someone that you do prefer
to be, then take it for granted that you
also contain
that also. You contain that and with
that dependency or sense of need. It is
not a dependency. It is not a sense of
need. It is a sense of selfawareness. If
you are seeing a reflection of yourself
in everyone, then you know you are
complete. You are not dependent upon
anyone to complete you. You are
complete. And when you begin to function
as a complete individual, then you
attract into your life individuals with
whom you can share your completeness.
But that does not manifest as a
dependency. You follow me? Yes. So
loneliness is an
incomplete not real.
But but and if if these are so
unreal, what is the purpose of them
being felt and being people are feeling them a
felt and being people are feeling them a
lot in these last days as we walk
through this door? Yes. But one moment,
one moment. Understand that when you
feel something, that is not the first
thing that occurs. Any feeling you ever
create in your life only happens as a
reaction to something you already
believe to be
true. Feelings are secondary to belief.
They do not come first. It is not simply
well this is simply the way I feel when
this situation occurs. No. As we have
said, no situation has builtin meaning.
You bring into every neutral situation a
belief about what that situation means.
And if you bring into that situation a
belief that that set of circumstances
means you are going to be lonely, then
of course you're going to feel lonely.
But if you understand that your
loneliness only stems from the fact that
you believe the situation that you are
involved in is inherently loneliness
creating then you will not have to feel
loneliness by recognizing that you do
not have to believe that the situation
has to be manifested in that
way. You follow me? Yes. When you
understand that you are
always at the same time alone and
connected to everything. then it is up
to you to choose which way you believe
you will
function. So if you feel lonely then
that simply is an opportunity and an
indication to you to realize that you
believe in
loneliness that you are not connected to
the infinite
creation. Your choice up to you. Now, if
you choose to feel lonely because you
choose to believe in loneliness, then
accept that you chose to believe that
way. And as soon as you accept that it
was your choice to believe that way,
then you will understand that you have
the ability to choose to feel and
believe another way. Do not deny it. Do
not run from it. Do not attempt to get
rid of that idea. There is nowhere to
get rid of anything to. You are your own
universe. Acknowledge that you obviously
chose to believe in loneliness. If you
feel lonely, ask yourself well, how does
it serve me to feel lonely? How does it
serve me to believe in
loneliness? You will get an answer if
you listen to yourself. Even if the
answer is only well, you chose to
believe in loneliness so that you could
learn you don't prefer to believe in
loneliness because it makes you feel
lonely and you don't like it. So now
that you have recognized why you chose
to believe in loneliness and now that
you have the experience, if you no
longer need to have the experience, then
choose another belief and you will get
another feeling to go hand in hand.
All right. All right. And last question.
Y. How can sound and dance best to serve
this planet at this time? By moving to
whatever moves you. By allowing yourself
to recognize that everything is
vibration and that when you discover for
yourself what is the movement, what is
the chord, what is the vibration that
hits home with you, then you will be
radiating that tone. You will be moving
that dance for all to see. You will be
being the fullest facet of the
multi-dimensional crystal you can be.
And by simply moving to what you know is
true for you, you give others the best
opportunity to see in you that you are
following your path that you are living
your dance that you are playing your
tune which lets them know they can do
the same. You follow me? Yes. There may
be vibrational tones that can generally
assist many individuals in your society
as well. You can explore with some of
those generalized tones and recognize
that when you find the tone that moves
you, what you are doing is you are
finding your signature vibration. When
you then recreate your signature
vibration, your entire body chemistry
and cellular structure and neural
pathways will begin to vibrate.
according to that tone. When you impose
upon not in a negative way, identify
with allow your body to identify with
the tone that moves you the signature
vibration. Then you allow your body to
go back to its zero rest idealized
state. And in that state, there is no
imbalance and no disease. Therefore, if
you can assist another individual in
finding their idealized signature
vibration and get them to recreate it so
that they can immerse themselves in that
vibration, their cellular structure will
begin to identify with that vibration.
They will allow their body, not make,
not force, allow their body to snap back
to the zero rest state represented by
that signature tone. then they will not
have disease at all. Understand the only
reason you have disease or imbalance is
because you hold yourself out of
balance. When you let yourself go, you
will snap back to zero. The ideal
blueprint rest state of the
consciousness that you are. And in that
state, there is no imbalance, therefore
no disease. So a tonal vibration that
represents a person's signature core
vibration can allow them to have
something to identify with to allow them
to snap back to zero. You follow me?
That is the dance you can share if you
are willing. But first and foremost, be
your own dance. Be your own tone and
live fully that which is true for you or
anyone else you would like to assist
will not believe that you can assist
them if they don't see you as a living
example. You follow me? Yes. Thank you
very much.
Charlotte. Yes. A couple things. A quick
uh sharing. All right. My New Year's I
was uh with two other people which made
three of us and I just thought it was a
little symbolic. And everything is
symbolic. Everything has significance
according to your own consciousness.
Well, it was just a fun thing. I had
three dice and I threw them on the bed
and I said the triad and they all came
up threes. Yay. More and more
synchronicity, more and more
co-incident, not accident. There are no
accidents. Any exceptions, Bashar? No,
none. Not even just one. No.
Well, I thought of you right away. Of
course, my synchronous gift to start the
new year. Thank you for being willing to
give that gift to yourself and be a
reflection of your own synchronicity and
higher consciousness acting in the
physical realm.
Okay. Uh the other thing is
uh I've
been working on uh I've been waiting to
see something come through just like do
it on my own and to see what it would
bring me and now I'm ready to reflect
with you and just ask you. Um I have a
camera and a telephoto lens and it was
last seen in my house and I was
wondering if you could tell me if it's
still in my house. Yes. Thank you.
Now, when you begin to get the
picture, perhaps you will allow yourself
to recreate that symbol in your life. If
necessary, allow yourself again to stop
waiting for things to
develop. Live the life you are living,
the way it manifests in the moment, in
the now. Well, I I really uh wanted to
bring that lens with me because it's
very important and dear to me and and I
would have much preferred to have it
with me. But you are your own camera.
Now, this is something that is analogous
to something we have shared with many
individuals of late on your planet. You
will find that and you will find that
some are present that can speak from
experience. Many individuals will now find that
Many individuals will now find that
their recording devices of all types
will cease to function in these
interactions because it is now up to you
to be the recording device and not need
the external
symbol. You are taking the pictures. You
have them eternally.
It's a art form. It's a way I share. We
understand what you are saying but
understand also what we are sharing with
you. You are simply giving yourself more
opportunity to truly live in the moment
with the tools you were born
with. When you allow yourself to rely on
them more and more, you can avail
yourself of the symbolic tools in your
reality of the mechanisms and the
technology. But you will always give
yourself the opportunity to recognize
precisely and especially when it is most
important to you to rely on the external
symbol to actually create an opportunity
to rely on the internal camera on the
internal recorder. You follow me?
recorder. You follow me?
Uh, sleep on it. Yeah.
Thank you. We will at this time take a
short break and then breathe. I'll
I'll
say sure you um two things that I would
like to to ask about. One is could you
give us any uh assistance in knowing our
signature vibration?
You will always be able to recognize the
vibration which first of all always
strikes a chord as you say within you
causes a resonance within you that which
moves you perhaps even
emotionally. Now there may be many
vibrations that can be the signature
vibration of the entire civilization
that you are. This is why you will find
what you typically call classical music
so lasting in your terms. It will invoke
many signature vibrations of the total
consciousness you are as a
civilization. It will pull from you the
emotion, the resonance, the harmonics
that you identify with that which
releases from you the pictures, the
feelings, the states of consciousness
that put you in touch with more and more
of yourself. You will always know it
when you hear it. Allow yourself to
explore and experiment and see what in
your terms simply feels right for you.
Okay, you follow me? Yes. Can it change?
Like to some degree it can, but you will
find that there will usually usually
always be a particular tonality that
will remain relatively the same because
it is indicative of the tonality that is
your portion of the collective
consciousness. And even though that can
change to some degree, it will always
have similar characteristics from what
it had before. As long as you exist in
the relatively similar
reality, it will change only drastically
when you drastically change your reality
from one whole system to another. Is it
a sound that we make or hear? It can be
both. It can be either. But recognize
this. It is the
representation of the vibratory
equation that is your reality. So you
see if the vibration changes your
reality changes. If your reality changes
the vibration changes. We're not simply
speaking of an idea of an auditory tone
that is disconnected from the being that
you are from the reality you experience
yourself to be. You are able to create
an auditory symbol of the vibratory
frequency that represents the actual
physical reality you are. That is the
signature vibration. And that is why if
you use your signature vibration, you
can unlock yourself from any particular
reality by taking yourself back to the
zero rest neutral point that will allow
you to then create any type of reality
you choose and impose that vibration
upon it which will then create that
reality. Any idea you choose to be,
anything you desire strongly to be
creates the new overlaying vibratory
equation that patterns the homogeneous
energy out of which all matter is
created into the format that represents
the reality you want to
experience. You are an energy sculptor.
You don't have to know the particular
frequency range in technical terms.
Whatever idea, whatever in your
imagination, whatever picture, whatever
feeling, whatever desire you are drawn
to, simply acting upon that idea, simply
invoking that particular pattern, that
particular nuance, that particular
perspective, that particular point of
view, that particular picture or
imagination will automatically tune you
to the appropriate frequency, will
automatically start you radiating at the
appropriate frequ frequency to rearrange
the energy into the forms of matter that
will physically represent the vibration
you are now being. The idea you are now
being. You follow me? Yes.
And you? I was wondering how you could
find it. You know it's like coming to
yourself. Yes. That is one way. You will
know when you hit it. You will know when
it feels right. You have done this
already many times. When you attempt to
find your range in a song, is there not
a range that feels comfortable? Is there
not a key that you feel more at home in
than another? Yeah. Then you are able to
find what is comfortable for you to work
within. So it can be a range, not just one tone.
So it can be a range, not just one tone.
It can be arranged to some degree, but
there will usually be one tone that
represents your idealized state of
comfort. It will usually be the tone
that you can evoke or create most
effortlessly if you are doing it
vocally. You follow me? Yeah. If you are
using what you call a musical
instrument, again, simply patterning
after what is most effortless for you
and also the one that seems to resonate
as you say colloquially within your gut,
within your heart. The one that gives
you the
mood, the one that invokes the desire,
the one that aligns you, the one that
creates you to become mood emotionally.
That's the one you
follow. That's the one. You follow me?
Yeah. Thank you, guys.
Thank you, guys.
You talked about the dream state and the
waking state becoming more permeable.
Yes. In my own terminology, I talk about
the conscious state and the unconscious
state. And I'm wondering how that
becomes more permeable through the use
particularly of hypnosis or the trans
state that bring about a more
permeability between these two parts of
us. First of all, you will find or they
become more permeable as you say because
they originally started out as one
thing. Any idea you have of a conscious,
a subconscious, and an unconscious is
only a belief system. They do not exist
as truly separate entities without the
belief that keeps them separate. They
are permeable because they are one and
the same thing. Dream reality and
physical reality are one and the same
thing. You through belief systems of
what you think physical reality is have
created them to seem to be totally
separate ideas. And usually your society
has thought the dream reality is not
even real. It is real. They are simply
different aspects. The dream reality and
physical reality are different aspects
of one total state of consciousness. So
as you blend the dream reality and the
physical reality, you will find your
conscious, subconscious and unconscious
minds becoming one consciousness. Or as
you blend the conscious, subconscious
and unconscious minds to become one
consciousness, your physical and dream
reality becomes more one reality. They
are simply different aspects or simply
different reflections of the same
idea. You are at any given moment an
idea. That is what you experience as a
That is what you experience as a
physical
persona, an idea that your consciousness
is being. Right now, your society is
experiencing itself as a persona,
experiencing the idea of a segregated
dream and physical reality, a segregated
outer aware, consciousness,
subconsciousness, and
unconsciousness. It is an idea. It is
one of the ways you have
arranged orchestrated if you will the
total consciousness that you are. But as
you begin to use whatever tool you find
valid that works for you to blend these
ideas together, then all you are
actually doing is removing the
separations you have imposed into what
is basically intrinsically one
homogeneous thing to begin with. You
follow me? Yes. That is why they are
permeable. Does this assist you? Yes. Thank you.
Does this assist you? Yes. Thank you.
Thank you very much. And what female?
What if your dreams are nightmares?
First of all, recognize that there may
be brain reasons why you may be creating
that scenario. You may be wishing to
play out certain negative ideas in your
dream reality rather than your physical
reality. Now, doesn't that make you
enjoy your nightmares a little bit more?
For you may be playing out certain ideas
that would be as you say hazardous to
your physical health in the dream
reality where you know that you are
indestructible. That may be your safety
ground for exploring the different
facets of yourself that you have been
taught you cannot face in physical
reality without undue harm to your
physical person or your psyche. But your
nightmares may be allowing you to get
used to the fact that you can face these
things in physical reality and that they
do not have to bring you harm. But you
are doing it on whatever level you will
be able to do it on so that you will not
create harm in yourself. It may simply
be an indication that there may be many
things you have been taught to believe
in that will allow you to perhaps think
that there are certain portions of
yourself that you cannot face in
physical life. But once again, there is
nothing that you cannot discover about
yourself that cannot be used in a
positive way if you so desire. Your
willingness even to participate in this
interaction, this day of your time, will
perhaps open up dream doorways and dream
realities within you that will allow you
to begin to realize that you can blend
your dream and physical realities
without necessarily having to expect the
dire consequences of your nightmares as
manifestable in physical reality. You
follow me? There are many many reasons
for why many individuals may create the
idea of nightmares. But generally
speaking, it is usually an indication
that there is something that they are
not sure they can deal with in physical
reality. And that is why they subscribe
it to the dream reality where as you say
all hell can break loose and you will
still wake up safe and
sound. It is your way of getting it all
out. Now when you know that there really
is nothing to get out in that way and
that you are simply exploring different
facets of yourself, you will not need to
express them as nightmares. You can
realize that you are just as much in
control of your dream reality as your
physical reality and vice versa. And
that when you experience the nightmare,
if you can allow yourself to realize
that you are dreaming, then you can
simply change it, transform it even as
you are dreaming it. And that will have
a profound effect on your ability to
transform your physical reality in the
way you desire it to be as well. You
follow me? Yes. Thank you. Thank you
very much. Yes. Um male then female.
Sure. During the uh during the prayer
meditation, the peace meditation
uh I wondered whether the dolphins and
the whales joined with us in that
meditation on behalf of the planet or
were they in the audience and your
civilization? They since they are very
interlin with your dream reality and
since they are members of your planet
directly were very well aware and very
much in tune with the vibration that
your planet was creating. They allowed
it to pass through their consciousness
with a great deal of ecstasy. But of
course, for them, what else is new? In
this way, however, they put their own
portion of their consciousness, backed
you up, so to speak, with a type of
chorus, an underlying foundational
vibration that bolstered and reinforced
your own trust, your own faith, and your
own certainty. You follow me? Yes. Does
that answer your question? Uh, yes.
Sabbath. Another question. All right. Uh
in our American Indian culture, guys, uh
where they don't seem to be involved
with dolphins at all. H one moment. Some
factions are recognize there are many
different aspects to what you are
collectively referring to as your
American Indian culture. Well,
specifically the hopes. All right. uh
they seem to use and I have seen it in
both in meditation and in fact they seem
to use uh the symbol of the eagle nice
and specifically an eagle feather with
crystal nice when they heal and exercise
and and whatever and I wondered if you
could comment on the relationship
between the dolphins to us for example
and the eagle to the hopes that there's
a relationship the eagle to the hopy is
their symbol of their own higher being
their own higher consciousness the
dolphins are your equal equal
partners. They are your co-sensient
species. They can be used symbolically
in many ways. They can be used as a
symbol of higher consciousness. But in
that sense, the idea of the animal form
eagle is a symbol of the hopes higher
being, higher spirit, higher
consciousness. In that sense, the hopy
would directly relate to the dolphin
more as a brethren rather than a symbol
of their own higher soul. You follow me?
Yes. Does that assist you? Yes. Thank
you. Thank you. Female. Um, yes. You are
something that's so simplistic that you
brought Indian culture up. I was curious
as to what the symbology. I know that in
the Indian culture there's a lot of
symbology and omens regarding animals
and I was interested in what the owl
essence carried with it. What the omen
of seeing an owl. It is much the idea
itself of the spirit that does transcend
the different levels in a sense what you
might call colloquially a ghost so to
speak. It is in this way silent and
swift. It is in this way able to
traverse the darkness, able to traverse
the night, able to see clearly into what
you would typically call the nether
world, the nether dimensions. In that
sense, it is in many ways the
spirit that can transcend
dimensionalities. It is in that sense
also a nature spirit in that sense to
them one that allows for the movement of
the wind. One that represents the
movement of the wind, the movement of
the electromagnetic field through which
your mentalities are connected. And that
is why it connects into the idea also of
knowledge and wisdom.
You follow me? Yes, I do. Frank and I
have been citing a lot of them uh lately
and we were just wondering why we were
seeing so many and and that sort of
thing. The other question I have is kind
of a personal one and that is um also in
the Indian culture there's uh from my
understanding of it that people can have
an association with a totem animal that
that I was going to ask you what my
totem was or is
you may find that it may change from
time to time. There are times when it
has been what you call a mouse.
There are times when you find that it
has been what you
call different types of bird for now it
can be the owl if you wish to represent
the idea of the spirit of the night in
that sense and the things you are
exploring within that portion of your
consciousness. One
moment. At times you will find there
have also been several varieties of what
you would call marine life that you have
identified with in different vibratory
signatures that could be called your
totem in that
way. But these ideas do shift do change
to some degree. Basically the totem is
one particular aspect or one particular
mode of representing one aspect of a
person's signature vibration. The aspect
that connects into
nature. You follow me? Mhm.
The idea of the mouse also being that
which can be seen to be to some degree
polar with the owl will allow you to
recognize that the mouse explores many
of the small in between spaces that you
do not think perhaps that you are able
to get into. In this way also you merge
it with the spirit of the owl. that
which can go through the wall, that
which always knows where the mouse is
hidden and can allow itself to find the
mouse in that way. So you have that
which is your physical conduit going in
between the walls, going in between the
cracks, going into places you do not
think you can go and conversely you have
the polarity of the owl which goes
through all walls and sees through all
blockades if only.
One more last thing. Um, since we're
here in in Maui to uh interact and be
more like dolphins and and perhaps have
physical contact with them. I've had a
lot of water dreams while I've been
here. Nice. And I did have one I'd like
to share with everyone that I was a bit
startled by. I didn't realize um that I
would have fear um in meeting the
dolphins in a real physical contact. And
I had a dream that was very vivid. Um,
and I was swimming with dolphins, about
six of them. And in the midst of playing
with them, this last dolphin came in and
he was quite large. And the energy was
so intense that I began to experience a
great amount of fear. Yikes. And um I
was actually afraid, you know, that it
that he was going to harm me in some
way. No. I woke up and I felt rather
ashamed of myself. God is all
right. I so I I was also buzzing about
that too. Simply the last one shows you
the limit you are willing to go to to
believe you can handle that level of
power in recognizing yourself.
Next time that one will be at the
beginning and perhaps you will end up
with a whale.
Thank you. Thank you very much. Sharing.
Yes. Yes. Yes,
um when when we were doing the peace
meditation the other night after well
while well well we began our uh
interaction with a an oming
um yes
and quite a while after that was over I
pointed out that that that sound was
still going on and quite a few of us
whenever you said that uh there was the
chorus. Yes. From the citations kind of
perked up and wondered if that could
have been what we were hearing. To some
degree, but also you by living more in
the present are beginning to sense that
no sound ever dies.
That exists now. And you gave yourself a
little bit of a hint that it goes on
forever. Great. Thank you. Yes. Also,
um, once before you shared with us a
citation folk tale, and I was wondering
if there was another one that you could
share with us. Nice. Great. Good.
Now, yeah. Then
yeah. Then
follow. Let it be
told that at the time you call
Avalantis when there was as you say a
delegation of dolphin
interacting with your land human of the
time what you would call the scientists
of the time but not exactly scientist as
you know it now.
There was the understanding that they
would find different
find different
substances upon the ocean floor that the
humans could not reach but that were
very easily reachable for the
dolphin. So they made agreements with
the human to find certain ideas, certain
substances for them that they could
utilize in their human technology since
the dolphin had no need.
So in this way, bit by bit, they brought
up more and more metallic substances
from the ocean floor that could be
rendered into the devices. More and more
crystallin substances of a type which no
longer exists that could be rendered
into many different devices which the
Atlanteanss could use in that way.
Then there came a time when you will
find that the dolphins went down and
discovered new stores of very
beautiful shells, very beautiful stones,
very beautiful crystals in various
colors and thought that the humans would
love to learn about these ideas and so
brought these shells, these stones,
these crystals to the surface.
There they were to find that by the time
they had found these artifacts and
brought them to the
surface that there were now two type of
human in Atalantis, those that could
appreciate the idea of the new doorway,
the new connection, the new symbol that
the dolphins had found and those that
for some reason could not. The dolphins
were much puzzled at this idea and began
for the first time to realize that there
were now more and more two types of
human brother, two types of human
sister. those that could go with the same flow
those that could go with the same flow
and identify with the dolphin and those
that had become more rigidized and could
not see the changes could not see the
beauty indifference but were expecting
the same things over and over again and
would not stand for any deviation.
This began to spread among the dolphins
and they began to recognize that a time
was at
hand when a portion of their human
brethren, a portion of their human
sisters were going to go to sleep in a
different type of
dream and would not
awaken for approximately 10,000
years. And so they did not bring these
new shells any
longer. But they always remember where
they were. So that when the human
brethren or when the human sisters would
awaken again, they could once again
bring from the ocean floor these
crystals, these shells, these
stones to the newly awakened humans to
let them know that once again they were
sharing the same dream. So be alert and
be aware that you will find in the years
to come that your dolphin brethren and
sister will bring to the surface things
you have not known
existed but at once you knew about long
long ago. And when you see these things
again, great
emotion, great tears, and great joy will
release from those who receive these
gifts from the dolphin. For it will mean
that you are awake again, awake in the
same dream as the dolphins, and they
will rejoice, and there will be much
playing and sharing among you.
In this way, you may find that some of
these gifts will begin to be delivered
in your dream realities first, and you
may see some of these represented as
very transparent bubble-like crystallin
balls that in this way will contain a
vibratory awareness that when you hold
them, you will know in your heart and in
your mind what the dolphins are saying
to you. M allow these dreams to begin
and you will set the pattern for those
gifts to come from the very bottom of
the ocean. Your unconscious mind and the
dream you have been dreaming to the
surface to the sun to the land to your
conscious mind and the dream you will
now dream as you dreamed so long
ago. The dolphins have told this tale
for generations and
generations and they are very glad that
you are now reawakening into the same
dream once again.
We thank you. Thank you very much.
Yay. I was uh we already talked about
being of the
vibration of your
uh society and the dolphins, but you
didn't really get very specific on
uh being of the vibration of the
dolphins so we could like uh interact
with them physically while we're here in
Maui. Was there we again are
generalists and the idea is not to
search for the
specifics. The idea is to have and to
hold in your heart and in your mind and
in your imagination the unconditional
outpouring of love and ecstasy that you
feel the dolphins give. Identify with
them, identify as them, and you will
radiate at the appropriate frequency to
attract them to
you. Have in your imagination the
scenarios of playing with them and they
will get the picture.
Well, I personally I was very much
projecting uh and calling and inviting
even the day before that I went and I
was dragging my fins when we were in the
water to be you know maybe they were
still coming and they were going to get
there after we left and say where did
everybody go? So, I was like I was uh
personally and I know uh you do not need
to continue to keep testing yourself.
Oh, it didn't happen the first time.
What's wrong? Something must have gone wrong.
wrong? Something must have gone wrong.
What am I doing wrong? You are still
creating expectations, specific expectations. If
expectations, specific expectations. If
it doesn't happen exactly as I picture
or expect it to, then something must be
offkilter. Things do not have to
Things do not have to
be picture
perfect camera
person before you will simply allow
yourself to recognize that things are
setting themselves up and proceeding as
they need
to. Relax and enjoy what you are
learning. If you do not allow yourself
to live in the moment for what happens
the way the moment occurs, you are not
learning the lessons in the moment and
you are not getting any closer toward
the picture you would like to
experience. When you allow the moment to
deliver to you what it needs to and take
with you what it gave you rather than
what you think it should have given you,
then you will allow yourself to
transform into a more close
approximation of the original picture
you had. But when you place the
had. But when you place the
instantaneous expectation demand upon
yourself that if it doesn't happen
exactly as you pictured it the first
time that you do not think things are
proceeding in that direction then only
you are not getting out of the moment
what will actually allow you to proceed
in the direction of the picture you
desire. Well I I personally just figured that
Well I I personally just figured that
they were probably busy and
help be there the next time I wasn't.
You do not have to make excuses for
that.
They are very very very
very well aware of the proper timing.
Okay. Thank you. Relax and enjoy
yourself. When they see you playing as
one of them, they will know they can
join you. But when you are pretending to
play, where are they? Well, I'm not
really having a good time until they
show up. You do not give off the
vibration that lets them think you're
one of them. You follow me very much.
Have a good time. I am. Thank you.
You then you then you could you speak
about soulmates? Soulmates. All right.
Now to some degree.
To some degree, in one sense, everybody
is your soulmate that you find yourself
interacting with at all in life because
everyone has something they can reflect
to you. And if you are interacting with
them, you have something you can reflect
to them. And as souls, you are mated in
that way to learn what you need to learn
from each other. The way you generally
mean the idea, however, simply is that
many times two individuals will create
an agreement to meet up in a physical
life to reflect to each other when they
have arrived at a certain point of
understanding in their lives. When they
realizing and recognizing their own
completeness. for recognize that many
individuals in your society have for a
long time thought well if only I could
find my soulmate everything would be as
you say hunky dory I would be complete
life would be wonderful I would be happy
but understand that an individual that
does not believe that they are happy or
complete before that point will usually
only attract a relationship into their
life to reflect their belief in their
own incompleteness when you know you are
incompleteness when you know you are
complete when you know you are a
complete individual. At any given moment
you are always expanding, you are always
learning, you are always growing. But at
any given moment for the idea you are
being at that moment you are perfect,
you are complete as that idea. The next
moment you will be a different idea, a
different complete and perfect idea.
Perhaps more expanded, perhaps more
grand, but never better just different.
So when you know you are complete in
that way, then you can attract that
individual into your life that you have
made the agreement with to come into
your life and say now I can reflect to
you that you have arrived at a point
where you know you are complete. So let
us as two complete individuals share the
joy of our unconditional knowingness
together. You follow me? Yes. That is
what is most often represented as the
idea of soulmate or twin flame.
Sometimes they can be soulmates by
association, not necessarily extensions
of the exact same soul. And sometimes
they can actually be counterparts or
extensions of the same oversoul.
You follow me? Yes, I do. Does that
answer your question? Yes. I have one
more. All right. I wanted to know about
the energy on the crater of Halaka.
Halaka. Very powerful magnetic
vortex. Very powerful magnetic vortex.
Is it a female energy?
There are manifestations of that type,
but those are only manifestations of an
energy which is basically
neutral. No energy in and of itself is
intrinsically male or female. It is
always both in
both in
probability because of what the
idea generally speaking of this
particular area on your planet
represents. Many times the energy has
been manifested in a feminine fashion, a
very nurturing fashion, a very mother
earth sort of fashion. But it contains
just as much of the idea of masculine
energy. It is a vortex and like any
vortex, it is a gateway and a doorway to
all levels, all dimensionalities and all
polarities. What you feel in it is what
you put into it. What you need to get
out of it is what you feel. So if you
find it to be a very strong feminine
energy, that is because you are
exploring certain ideas about your own
femininity at this time. If you find it
to be very masculine, then you are
exploring aspects of that particular
idea of your consciousness. And it can
shift back and forth until you will find
at some point in your near future, as
you count time, all energy gates and all
vortices and all ideas upon your planet
will be able to be experienced equally
by males and females as both masculine
andor feminine energy. You follow me?
Yes. But it is a very strong, very
powerful magnetic gate, magnetic door to
all levels of consciousness and all
dimensions in the multiverse.
Thank you. Thank you. Sure. Sure. You um
I'd like to explore with you the idea
you talked about before about
um twothirds of your planet being in in
spaceship or traveling all the time. All
right. What do you wish to go? Um, I
have a similar idea in this in the earth
plane of what I would call a traveling
city. A number of bases in different
points, very refined environments,
including environments under the water,
specific takeoff points in New Zealand
and exploring other planets. You can
create these on your planet. Your planet
is now beginning to recognize that it
does have the technology to create many
of these ideas.
much more of this idea of technology
will come out in your years to come in
the very near future. It is that timing
more a product of a
collective collective
uh consciousness or can it is the
product of collective consciousness but
at this time you can use your individual
consciousness. There is enough leeway in
the collective consciousness to allow
you to exercise whatever degree of
individual consciousness you desire to
exercise in creating that particular
type of environment. Go right ahead.
Well, it doesn't it doesn't appear that
there's a uh so to speak refined enough
environment for where I feel my own
sensitivity is to travel in those
manners. You will find that that is
simply because much of this information,
much of that type of technology has been
suppressed by what you have created to
be your governments. But again, in your
years to come, as you do your own
research, as you do your own
exploration, you will find that much of
this idea and understanding does exist
on your planet. And there are many
groups and individuals that are now
joining other groups and individuals.
And pretty soon, these groups and
individuals will become in your terms
strong enough to be unsuppressible. And
a lot of the information that has been
suppressed will begin to leak out more
and more after the fact that your
civilization does have the capability of
creating these environments upon your
world right now. It is only a matter of
priority. That is all.
Uh I have another question. All right.
Uh do you have a particular
uh signature vibration that translates
into our physical dimension as far as a
graphic symbol or uh shape which Thanks.
One can could you? It is the equilateral
can could you? It is the equilateral
triangle.
primarily blue, black,
violet with you will find perhaps a
pinkish or violet aura,
aura,
pointing at times upward, pointing at
times downward depending upon the direction of
downward depending upon the direction of
consciousness and the way and the
methodologies being utilized. eyes.
Will that do does it have a a particular
sequence of movements that it generates
or is it mostly a static form or It is
everchanging but generally the overall
vibration you would perceive out of the
everchanging matrix of vibrations would
be that of the equilateral triangle. The
lines of the equilateral triangle
generally represent what you would call
the standing waves. The combination of
all the waves interacting together would
read out of the hologram as an
equilateral triangle. You follow me?
Yes. Does that serve you? Yes. And as I
begin to imagine that triangle, in fact,
two triangles, one above, one below the
two opposite directions, there appears a
set of uh symbols between them which are
some kind of uh they aren't recognizable
to me as any language or or sets of
symbols that I can translate into a
knowingness for myself. In a sense, you
have already translated the symbols
themselves are a translation of a
knowingness of a telepathic knowingness.
You have created your own representative
symbols to let you know that you are
aware of the concepts. We will allow you
to explore this within your own
meditations as to what they mean to you.
We will give you one more assistive
tool. Pay
attention. Heat. Heat. [Music]
explore in your dreams what this
vibratory signature will allow you to
discover. Thank you. Thank you for your continued
Thank you. Thank you for your continued
excitement and much love. I'm your sir.
Uh I wish you would tell me a little bit
about your opinion of the use of peyote
and other psychedelic materials when
they are employed
sacramentally. Uh both in a general
sense and to me in a personal sense they
seem to have opened up a greater depth
of loving and clarity of truth within
myself. Can be used that way. Once again
understand any idea, any tool which you
feel is valid for you will create valid
experiences in your life in that way.
Now your planet has provided you with
what you might call the natural tools in
that way. And so you may find that
certain individuals can avail themselves
of those particular tools to unlock
certain ideas to unlock certain
perspectives and understandings within
them as you have indicated that you have
done. But also understand this, a tool
is only a tool. The power is not in the
tool. The power is in you. And what the
tool has allowed you to now be in touch
with is the fact that you can recreate
what the tool seemingly created anytime
you wish through the opaces simply of
your own self-empowerment and your own
consciousness. The tool is there to show
you what you are capable of. And after
that point, you can recognize that you
don't need the tool. after that point.
Now, if there are different aspects you
wish to explore in that way, nothing
about that is right and nothing about
that is wrong. It is simply that it is
up to you to allow yourself to whatever
degree you are comfortable with to
recognize that the idea on your planet
of addiction only occurs when an
individual continues to believe that
they are not in control of their own
lives, that they do not create their own
reality, and therefore they have to rely
on something outside to change their
reality for them. And they do not
realize that the power is not in the
tool. The power is not in the drug. The
power is within them. They have used
their belief system to allow the drug to
show them what degree of power they can
exercise at any given moment. And for
that reason, the drug is valid for it is
a reflection. It is a mirror. And it is
for some an opportunity to become let us
say unlocked from the belief systems
they have bought into in growing up in
your physical system in your social
system. But that is still an opportunity
for them to realize that once the drug
quote unquote shows them they have the
opportunity to unlock in that way then
in all reality you no longer need the
drug. You follow me? Yes. One more one
more question. Okay. I in a moment of uh
clear channeling uh I was told that
there was great wisdom in the events of
my birth. I also tracked down much of
the anxiety that I've experienced
throughout my whole life to some
terrifying experiences connected with my
birth. And I've been trying to uh in
some way fathom the wisdom of that kind
of uh situation that uh produced terror
in a big All right. Thank you very much.
Now again recognize that certain ideas
to some degree some degree are
carryovers from other lives. You follow
me? And it is a continuation of that
momentum that karma so to speak. But do
remember karma is completely
selfimposed. It is not a retribution. It
is not a judgment. It is an indication
of the continuation of your own choices
and momentum to explore the polarities
you wanted to explore in this particular
life to set the standards and the
parameters that you wish to create in
this life to become the individual you
wanted to become.
Now, all that you now recognize as the
so-called terror in your birth is simply
an indication to some degree of starting
at the most highly concentrated end of
the negative polarity spectrum that you
could possibly choose. So that it would
be an indication of extremely how far to
the other end of the polarity you would
end this life in.
[Music] You created a
very terror and that much limitation in
your life. So soon means you are that
strong that you are strong enough to
have used that much terror as simply
something to get you where you wanted to
go. That's how strong you are and that's
how accelerated you are becoming. Know
that you did it for a reason. Know that
the acceleration in your life is a
direct result of that confinement and
restriction back then. And then you will
allow yourself to accelerate and expand
at a phenomenal rate. It will never be
too fast, never be more than you can
handle. But the more you live in the now
in that way, the more you will find that
you exist everywhere at once. And the
more you recognize that you exist
everywhere at
once, the more it will feel as if you
are standing perfectly peacefully still
and calm.
Breathe a sigh of
release. You knew what you were doing
and you still do. And you have used it
to propel you through the doorway at a
phenomenal acceleration. For you
acceleration. For you
know that when you take a seed and you
squeeze it most tightly between your
fingers is when it travels the farthest
and the faster.
to follow it. I sure do. I got chills
going up.
Then we together have struck a
chord. That is the feeling we are
speaking of. When you hit your signature
vibration, use that energy to propel
you. It has always propelled you. You
are free. Ultimately free.
Fly. Thank you. Thank you.
And with
that, recognize that you are all just as
free. If any one of you could not have
applied this idea to your own lives, you
would not have been here to hear it. You
would not have attracted it into your
reality. You would not be able to use
it. Anything you hear from anyone else
can be used as a reflection for
yourself. There are no accidents in what
you overhear. None. If you can relate to
overhear. None. If you can relate to
this
idea, I know all of you felt the
acceleration. Then understand that that
is your own core vibration. That is your
own energy. That is your own
acceleration. Get in touch with that.
Feel it. Feel the ecstasy. Feel the joy
that you
are. None of it is too good to be
true. You are made of
ecstasy. You are made of love. This feeling
This feeling
now, that vibration
now is the specific exercise we spoke
of. Being in touch with the
spontaneity, the knowingness that all
you have ever created in your life has
gotten you to where you are. And what
you are now will get you to where you
are going if you live what you are now. Any
now. Any
idea, any methodology, any technique
that you wish to use, use it. If it is
within your integrity, if it is that
which represents your desire, if it
works for
you, use it. As long as you know that
you are powerful enough to create
anything you want without having to hurt
anyone else or yourself in order to
create it, use
it. Use it. And if you wish that
technique, whatever it is your
imagination comes up with to be the most
impactful, then use it
now. Live
now. Anytime you ask
yourself, how do I allow this idea to
manifest most quickly, you always have
your answer.
live now. That's
how anytime you find yourself asking
yourself a question, finding yourself in
a puzzlement, finding yourself in a
quandry, simply when you say, "But
how?" Then answer yourself, live now.
That's how be the
how be the
child now that always has fascination
and curiosity with
everything. The child does not
differentiate this is good, this is bad.
The child is fascinated with the
circumstances and supplies their own
meaning because the child lives
now. As we were discussing with one of
your members only recently, you will
find that the two times in your life you
allow yourself to act like a child is
when you are a child and when you are
very old.
It is all right in your society for
those of you that are very old to be
childlike, but find yourself being
childlike when you are a middle adult.
Oh, what's wrong with you? Oh, grow up
at your
age and all of those other wonderful
ideas. When you are willing to know that
it is all right to begin to act like a
child now, then you won't have to get
any older to let it be all right to do
so. Live now. That's
Live now. That's
how it is. So very
simple. At this time, we will extend to
each and every one of you our joy and
our ecstasy and our appreciation in
allowing us to experience the different
vibrations, the unique vibrations that
each and every one of you individually
are and collectively are together. For
us, this is a gift that allows us to
know yet another way that all that is
and the infinite creation has of
expressing the creation that it is. We
thank you for sharing the dream that you
are with us and allowing us together to
co-create a similar dream. We bid you
exciting dream lives and life dreams. We
bid you a fond and unconditionally
loving and exciting good day.
How did everything go?
We will be having another channeling
session on Sunday and the location is
not yet decided. So see me if you want
to find out about that and I'll give you
the number. Also we'll have um tape sign
up in the back.
Thank you. Thank you. What time is it?
Great.