All right, I'll say how are you all this
evening of your time as you create time
to exist.
We will begin this interaction this
evening of your time with the idea of
the exploration of the concept you call
guilt. In this way recognize you have as
a society for a very long time
engendered the idea of guilt.
This in this way allows you to create
many wondrous occasions of
self-inccrimination, self-invalidation, self-limitation,
self-invalidation, self-limitation,
segregation and separation in your
lives. and many times is the primary
ingredient, the primary symbol to allow
you to prevent yourself from creating in
your lives what you prefer, what you
desire and what you know deep within you
beyond a shadow of a doubt is what you
deserve to experience in your life.
But the idea began very long time ago in
your terms of counting upon your planet
and your civilization. Not that other
civilizations do not experience it, but
you have delved so very deeply and so
very strongly into it that your
civilization in many of the
civilizations we have encountered has an
expertise with this particular idea that
is matched by none. In this way, their
fold, not that this makes you any less.
In fact, the idea of your willingness to
experience such limitation, in many ways
actually makes you strong and is in and
of itself an indication of how strong
you know you are to be able to subject
yourself to such high degrees of
limitation. So in this way, at this time
to many individuals, including our
planet, you are known by the title the
masters of limitation.
In this way you are now at the end of
cycle of limitation and beginning the
cycle of integration. But one of the
ideas, one of the kernel and seed ideas
with which you have created and allowed
the creation of limitation to continue
has been with what you call the tool of
guilt. Guilt in this way is what always
will perpetuate limitation. always
perpetuate separation and keeps you from
separation and keeps you from
recognizing your own
self-empowerment and your own connection
to the infinite creation. For recognize
that fundamentally speaking, while many
of you for a long period of time have
always assumed that hate is the opposite
of love, guilt is the true opposite of
love. Hate may be a
diametric damic polarity expression of
love, but guilt is the true mechanical
opposite. For love is complete and utter
selfworthiness and creativity and guilt
is the belief in lack of self-worth.
Hate still involves some concept that
you deserve something. Whereas guilt is
completely devoid of the sense of
deservability. Do you all follow along
so far? Yes. In this way, therefore, the
belief in your own lack of
[Music] self-deservability allows you to be able
self-deservability allows you to be able
to create a scenario in which you
actually keep at bay all of the things
in life that are yours by birthright,
such as happiness, such as ecstasy, such
as
creativity. And in this way, guilt has
been the bitter pill that has been
injected and created into your society
by your society to keep you on the
status quo of lack of
selfmpowerment. Because when you truly
believe that you are not connected to
all that is, when you truly believe that
you must control by force in order to
get anything at all in life, then in
that way do you further the continuation
of limitation, further the continuation
of guilt. And in this way, therefore, it
has become the very ethic of your
society. When you do not believe you are
connected in that way, then you do not
believe that you can create things you
desire in your life with ease and
effortlessness and things have become
worthless to you if you do not create
suffering in order to get it. No pain,
no gain, as you say. Recognize in this
way that that has become the ethic of
your entire civilization that you cannot
have anything in your life that is
worthwhile unless you have suffered.
Unless you have, as you say, earned it
in that way. But recognize, you do not
have to earn it. You already own it. You
were created from ecstasy. You are
created out of love and light. It is
your birthright. Everything you do can
be an act of love and effortless ease of
creativity made in the image of the
infinite creator you are. And that means
quite simply that you are an infinite
creator and a multi-dimensional one as
well. This is simply the natural you.
And in this way, if you will allow
yourselves to realize that you no longer
need the tool of guilt, then you will
allow yourself the
expansiveness of your birthright. You
will allow yourself the
expressiveness of your
vitality. And you will then be able
beyond the shadow of a doubt and with
all clear consciousness to create and
attract into your life the things you
know you deserve. Because you will find
that when you remove guilt from your
toolbox, you will then find that what is
left will be the following. Recognition
and realization.
realization.
Nothing is too simple or too good to be
true. Nothing. Any exceptions, Bashar?
No. Not one. Nothing is too simple or
too good to be true. And nothing is too
wondrous, too ecstatic to be
yours. Nothing. You
deserve all that you can conceive
of
because you
exist. And if you exist then obviously
all that is the infinite creator
believes you deserve to exist. And if
you exist with the desire for creating
peace, harmony, joy and ecstasy in your
lives, then you are not created with
that desire without also having been
created with the ability to attract that
into your lives.
You are not given a desire without also
being given the ability to accomplish
that desire. The universe and infinite
creation does not do extraneous and
pointless things.
Then foe, since you did not have to do
foe, since you did not have to do
anything special in order to deserve
existence, since obviously all that is
believes you deserve to exist, give
yourself the same benefit of the doubt.
Treat yourself with the same
unconditional respect and love and grant
yourself permission and grant yourself
the right to create life as you desire
it to be. For you have the ability to
create it that way. And all you need to
do is remind yourself that your ability
to conceive of that idea is in and of
itself the indication of your ability to
create that idea because you are a
multi-dimensional creator. And as you
think and as you feel and as you
believe, so you experience the creation
of the physical reality around you.
Always. No exceptions. Your physical
reality is always the product of what
you believe it can be or fear that it
will be. For to fear that something will
happen in your life is the same thing as
saying you believe that that is the
strongest possible reality that will
come into your life. Your physical
reality is always the product of what
you believe it can or will
be. But
situations do not happen in your life to
show you that you are stuck in them.
Situations do not happen in your life to
show you that you have failed at
creating a better one. No. Situations
come into your life to show you what
beliefs you have been taught, what
beliefs you have bought into, and if you
don't prefer them, to change them. You
always have a self-regulating mechanism.
The self-regulating mechanism to always
allow you to know what beliefs may be
buried in your unconscious mind. the
self-regulating mechanism that will
always allow you to know precisely how
to bring those beliefs to the surface of
your conscious mind so you can change
them if you don't like them and
reinforce them if you do is the
experience of physical reality. If you
see a situation that you are involved in
that you don't prefer, then simply
recognize the only way it could be in
your life is for you to have a belief
that allows it in your life. Therefore,
now that that situation has shown you
what the belief is you have within you,
then you are free. You have the
opportunity now to say, "Aha, now I have
the definition of the belief that has
created this. It has been buried within
me. Now it has come to the surface
because here it is all around me. Now,
if I don't prefer it, I can understand
what the definition was and I can change
that definition." and then use 100% of
the trust, the same trust I used to
create the negative scenario to now know
that once I have changed the definition
to a positive definition, reality will
reflect that definitional belief just as
strongly as it reflected the other
definitional belief which I did not
prefer. You have your own selfguidance system,
You have your own selfguidance system,
your own builtin guidance system. And
this is why when we interact with you,
what you will always sense from us is
that whether you choose to believe in
yourselves or not, whether you choose to
believe that you have the capability of
creating the reality you desire, we
believe in you. And we will always
reflect to you that you have that
capability. For we know you do. We do
not believe that you have it. We know that
believe that you have it. We know that
you have it beyond a shadow of a doubt
because all beings in creation have the
ability to create the reality they
experience. You all follow along so far?
Thank you very much. At this time, we
will extend our appreciation to you for
your willingness to cocreate and
co-share your particular unique view
points of reality, your particular
unique expressions of creation with us.
And we will open this idea with sharing
you and then. Yes. Would you share a
little bit about your civilization and
your ideas and concepts about yourself
for those that have not interacted with
you before? Oh, right. We call our
civilization in our remnant language
Esasani, which in your language
translates into place of living life.
Casani, the people themselves mean
living life. In this way, we are
approximately in your terms 500 of your
light years in the direction of the
constellation you call Orion. We have a
degree of physicality. You would
perceive us if you were to shift into
our vibrational plane, which is slightly
different than yours. You would perceive
us as being of average 5t of height,
very slender, white whitish gray skin
coloration, large upturn eyes. Males
have no hair, females have hair in this
way. usually whitish, though there are
exceptions. The closest racial
characteristics that we can compare to
on your planet would be similar, not
exact, but similar to what you call
Mongolian or Eurasian. In that way, our
eye coloration is actually grayish. But
in that way, you will perceive them to
be all black because the pupils of our
eyes encompass almost the entire span of
the eye. In that way you will find that
fully at any one time the population of
our civilization twothirds of which will
exist in spacecraft onethird of which
will exist upon the surface of the
planet which in your terms is very open
and part life. We have no builtup
structures upon our planet since we
utilize our spacecraft for such
endeavors of exploration of the ideas
throughout the universe.
In this way, with slight adjustments,
you could exist upon the surface of our
planet and we could exist upon the
surface of yours. When you travel
through any space time continuum, you
are always making slight adjustments
within the vibrational frequency of the
reality in which you exist. Anyway, you
cannot see our star directly because we
are not quite in your vibratory plane of
existence. But the idea of our planet is
that we have in this way the expression
at any given time of ecstasy and joy and
trust which allows us to interact with
each other in a completely synchronistic
manner. And therefore because we trust
that all interactions will always be
taking place in the right place at the
right time with exactly the right
individuals. We do not have what you
typically call the social structures of
government upon our planet. nor do we
have what you call a monetary
system. Will this suffice? Yes. Thank
you very much. Thank you. I have some
sharing and also a couple of questions
from my brother who interviewed you the
other night from channel 9. Good. And he
uh is working tonight instead of being
here. First of all, I I'll ask the
question that maybe other people are
interested in here and that is about
music on your planet. Do you have scales
and what kind of you know musical form
do you have and also what kind of
instruments? We have some degree of
instruments that are created many of
which are spontaneous many of which are
remnants from older times in our
civilization. The majority of our
instrumentation will usually be
percussive in that way bellike. There
are a few string and a few of what you
would call wind instrument but there are
very few and again they would be similar
to what you would call your oriental
instruments Chinese in that way very
simple tonalities will be created with
these instruments as the majority of the
tonalities we experience are actually
now at this point created telepathically
and shared in that way that's
interesting would our gamlon orchestras
be similar in some ways. It seems
defined the terminology does not exist
within the memory bank Indonesian
Indonesian bills and gongs and uh it
seems to some degree although you will
find that they will be simpler in
structure in many different ways and in
this sense you will then allow yourself
to recognize that many of them may be
tuned to particular tonalities which
represent the general
combined tonal pattern of our
civilization. They will be few in number
and very simple in construction.
That's interesting. Okay. Now the
sharing um he described to me when uh
the medium was uh going into his place
and you appeared. He saw light and he
could just feel you there and he saw a
physical manifestation. Also before the
channeling he was wondering how a an
extraterrestrial would get a name and
the name Esasani just popped into his
head and he had never heard that before.
He simply was tuned into the wavelength
of the event in which he was taking
place. Yes, everything is a single
event. Even though you may perceive
yourself to be an individual part of it,
you bring to that event your own energy
and take from that event the energy of
the combined event. He is simply
sensitive and open to receiving
information in that way and hence with
his own abilities was able to tap into
the wavelengths that represented in
whatever terms made sense to him the
idea of the event or terms that would
soon make sense to him. Good. Also, he
would like to have an experience of
actually an encounter with a spacecraft
and in time. All right. Also, he would
like to be a gobetween between the
extraterrestrials and the news media. If
that is his interest in that way and if
he is willing to simply at any given
moment follow in life what excites him
the most, then he will lead himself into
that type of interaction. He has already
placed himself into a particular type of
activity that is very conducive to
creating situations of that type. All he
needs to know if that if that is what
excites him in that way, then he will
lead himself into such interactions.
Simply keep himself open and do not put
expectations in his way. Also, he's
working on scripts for television and um
he was thinking maybe he could reach the
general public with you know in a
fictional way to prepare them. It is one
way that many individuals upon your
planet create and assist in the
preparation for your world to be able to
interact with other worlds by slowly but
surely and definitely and solidly
rearranging the concepts in your
civilization to allow for many different
concepts to come in from other
civilizations as well. For do understand
us interacting with you is not to be at
the cost of your own culture. So it must
take place at whatever rate will allow
your culture to maintain its own
integrity and at the same time be open
and willing to interact with other
cultures as well. Could he get some help
in a creative way from he will once
again attract what he needs. All he
needs to do is center in himself and
open up to his own higher consciousness
and all the concepts he requires will
come through from his guides, from his
own higher consciousness and from any
other connection he has made, whether it
is in your terms extraterrestrial or
not. Recognize that every individual has
their own connections in many different
levels and none of you are original to
this planet anywhere. So the idea is
that since time is your illusion, all of
those connections and all of those lives
in other civilizations still exist. Tell
him he can find the counterpart of
himself in another civilization and ask
the counterpart what ideas may be
necessary to allow this civilization to
learn what it means to learn. That's
exciting. Thank you very much. Thank you
for your sharing. Sharing you could you
please tell us a little bit more how we
can let go of this terrible need in
order to have something and have that
happening in a relationship right now.
All right. How's this? If you feel you
have to control in order to get
something, you'll never get it.
Never. Never. Never.
Now, does that allow you to turn around
a little
bit? If you try to control a
situation through force, you will never
truly control it. Because true control
is
allowance, not
force. True control is allowance.
You are already familiar with the idea
of an analogy in your society that to
hold water your hands must be
open. You follow me? No. If you tighten
your grip, where does the water
go? So if you keep your hands open in
allowance, then the water stays put. You
have what you desire because you are
willing to allow it to exist in its
natural state in your hand. But if you
insist that you want to bend and shape
it in the way you think it should be, it
all runs out of your fingers and you
have no water pretty
soon. You follow me? So the analogy is
is that when you try to control by
force, forcing something into the shape
you think it needs to be in order to be
satisfactory to you, then you are not
trusting the natural inherent ability of
that thing to provide to you what you
need. Let me put it another way if I
may. May I? Thank you very much.
If you think you have to force a point
of view upon someone
else, then obviously you do not believe
in the power of that point of view
yourself. You follow
me? Yes. No. Maybe. Thank you.
Recognize anytime anyone feels a need to
force a point of view on a situation or
on another
individual, they are simply expressing
their belief in their own
powerlessness. Forcing something on
someone else is not an expression of
power. It is an expression of
powerlessness because you do not believe
that you are inherently by nature
powerful enough to create whatever you
desire in your life without having to
hurt anyone else or yourself in order to
create it. True power is knowing that you are
it. True power is knowing that you are
connected to the infinite creation. True
power is the willingness to be open in
complete vulnerability and
allowance. Vulnerability is not
weakness. It is infinite
strength. Because vulnerability is
complete openness, the willingness to
trust 100% that you deserve to exist as the
100% that you deserve to exist as the
being that you are. And therefore the
universe will automatically support you
in that existence by automatically
funneling in your direction whatever
situations and whatever individuals and
whatever circumstances are conducive to
the continuation of your existence in an
ecstatic state which is your natural
state. So you have to force nothing. It
all comes to you when you let it. The
only reason that these ideas would not
come to you is because you are holding
them away by not creating a receiving
shape. You follow me? If water is what
you need and you are dying of thirst and
water is pouring all around you, then
you do not clutch at it and try to force
it down your throat. You open your
hands in allowance so that they will
fill with the abundance you require to
continue living.
Is any of this sinking in?
Yes. Has this assisted you? Yes.
Anything else?
I'd like to know more about the fear.
How we let go of the fear. The terrible
gripping fear. Oh, terrible. Oh,
gripping. Your heart. Oh, all right. How exciting.
Your heart. Oh, all right. How exciting.
First of all, recognize that there are
many reasons for why you create fear.
Sometimes it is because you have become
so complacent that the only way you will
allow yourself to have an exciting life
in the moment is to create fear. But
that is only because you have been
taught that that may be the only thing
that is exciting to you. You will find
something to excite you one way or
another, positively or negatively.
Generally speaking,
however, fear occurs in your life when
you have been taught to believe and you
buy into the
belief that there are portions of
yourself that you might
discover that can do you harm against
your will. There is no such thing, no
such piece of yourself. So when you are
afraid to face the things that come up
in your life, when you do not pay
attention to the messages that you
deliver to
yourself, then the messenger portion of
yourself in attempting to deliver that
message will become louder and louder
and more and more
obnoxious until you pay
attention. If you are willing to listen
to the message when it is first
delivered, it will come in subtle ways.
But the more you are taught to ignore
it, the louder and more scary it will
get to get your
attention. So that you can pay attention
to the things you have told it you want
it to deliver to you. So you can
integrate that experience into your
being. So you can grow as a being. Fear
usually only brings you a recognition of
a portion of yourself you have not been
willing to face up to that point. All
you need to do is face the fear and
acknowledge that if you are fearful, you
chose to believe in the need to receive
the message in a fearful way. And once
you allow yourself to recognize why you
would have chosen to receive it in a
fearful way, your curiosity and your
fascination will take over and you will
explore the idea of what the message is
that is being delivered. And before you
know it, your fear has dissolved because
now you are paying attention to the
message it has delivered. And as soon as
the messenger delivers its message, it
doesn't need to stick around. And as
soon as you are willing to accept the
message quicker and quicker and quicker,
then the next time it comes back, it
won't come as fearfully as it did the
last time. Because now it finds that you
are willing to receive the message
sooner before it truly has to shout to
get your attention. You follow me? Yes.
Has this assisted you? Very much. Thank
you. Thank you very much for your
willingness to explore that particular
facet of the multi-dimensional crystal
that you are sharing.
Yes. Uh I'd like your comments on other
lifetimes that my wife and I may have
led in the past or in our future
together and what you see as our purpose
in being together in this lifetime. My
my 25 words or less.
Now before we begin once again allows to
remind each and every one of
y there is nothing wrong with the idea
of the exploration of past lives and so
forth and certainly they can function as
extremely valid tools to allow you to
recognize and gain more understanding of
yourself. However, we always simply begin this
However, we always simply begin this
subject with this particular
address because in this way we will
allow you to
know your present life contains all the
tools it needs for you to understand
this present life. You do not have to
base this present life on having to know
about your past lives.
However, you will find that your
capability, your curiosity and your
mentality may have already come up with
many pictures that you find attractive,
many atmospheres that you find conducive
that you like to explore and think about
or muse about or daydream about with
regard to other scenarios, other exotic
climates and other exotic time periods
that may grab your attention. The ones
that stand out most strongly in your
imagination are usually the ones that
indicate the strongest connections to
true past lives you have actually
already created. But to sit here and ask
us to delineate all the past lives, the
idea of the most important ones and what
the future holds and what the purpose of
your present life is is to take away
from you the discovery of the
exploration of your own being and your
own spontaneity.
The fundamental purpose of the present
life is to learn from each other
whatever it is you are learning. It is
the fulfillment of the contract you
made. The fundamental reason of any
singular individual's life is to fully
be the individual you are in that life.
Because even though you are a
reincarnational being, you will never be
this you again. And this you truly does
only have one life to live. So the
fundamental purpose of this life is to
fully be the individual you are this
time. To answer the question in this
way, we will invoke participation on
your part. First and primarily where in
terms of the past are you most
attracted?
Time period. Yes. And culture. Culture.
Well, uh, aside from India,
uh, India is not actually among those
that come up. It will come up.
European culture interests me a lot and,
uh, earlier American culture interests
me. All right. And in terms of time
periods, none come to mind except
perhaps 1600, 1700. All right.
Understand this before we proceed.
Whatever it is you get through your
imagination is usually enough to suffice
for what you need to know about yourself
at that particular moment to live the
life you need to live now. You do not
need to have every single detail of the
past lives to bleed into this life to
allow you to understand what you need to
know. Every life bleeds into every other life.
Every life bleeds into every other life.
And in that life you have described
which you have had several of in that
period, you will find that the life you
are living now also bleeds into that
past life. And there are many things
that the youth then is experiencing that
actually are bleedthroughs from the life
you are living
now. In terms of what they perceive, you
then perceive to be the future, so to
speak. Now I have been an artisan many times
Now I have been an artisan many times
particular affinity to the idea of
sculpture in stone in that
way. You also had a particular affinity
as we perceive it for the
creation long time ago of what you call
fire. In this way, you were one of the
first to be called what is typically now
a
shamanistic individual in that you were
attracted by the light based upon what
you perceive to be the light within
yourself. And you were one of the first
in this way to allow yourself to
understand physically and intellectually
the generation and the creation of
biome. You follow me? Yes.
Has this assisted you? Yes, it has. And
I have another question. All right. Uh
two years ago, my wife and I met some uh
cousins and relatives of that uh nature
in France and since then have been in
some communication with them and hope to
hope. That's where we're at. I'm sorry
to say. Oh, you don't have to be sorry.
First you are hoping and then you are
apologizing. [Music]
[Music]
Well, I wish I could say with more
certainty and I Why not then? We desire
to All right, that's certain enough. I
desire. Very good. You desire to what?
To return there for um what is like a
reunion. All right. People there this
later this year. All right. And even
past that in the future to return there
to live. Well, then you have a wonderful
time.
It is totally up to
you. The future is always fluid. You
always have the ability to consciously
choose what you wish to create. You are
always going to wind up being in
synchronous accord with your higher self
as long as you do at any given moment
what excites you the
most. Excitement is the thread that
represents the path you chose to be in
this life. So follow it.
Thank you. Thank you. I have done
nothing. Yes. Are you
Yes. Are you
a star?
If you wish to use that nomenclature.
Yeah. So are you by the way since to us
you come from another star.
Yeah. But you answered my second
question and all the star people
actually now living on this planet as we
originally said none of you are original
to this planet. None of you. No
one. You are all star people. Now what
you colloquially in this age call star
people are simply individuals who have
perhaps remembered that portion of
themselves and the connections that they
have made in other lives or between
lives with other
civilizations and have chosen to be of
assistance in this transformational age.
by choosing to be born upon your planet
at this time to be of assistance in that
way. You follow? Yes, I do. Thank you.
Well, thank you very much. Do feel free
at any given time to shine as brightly
as you desire
to share it for sure. you and
you've mentioned previously that you see
the energy around Hawaiian Islands,
Maui, especially as what might represent
the heart space or a heart focused. So
have many individuals upon your planet.
We simply reflect the knowingness that
they have already realized long before
we began interaction with your world.
From that analogy of the heart
that analogy of the heart
Please, what is the space? What is the
energy? What special energy does New
Zealand hold for us and for me? It is a
very plastic state at this time. In one
plastic state at this time. In one
sense, as we have already discussed it,
it represents a type of plasticity into
which a certain imprint of fourth
density reality can be made.
[Music] You are making such an imprint.
Now in this way allow yourself to know
that great change is probable in that
area. That things are very fluid and
very flexible. And therefore what you take
flexible. And therefore what you take
with you in that area can go into
imprinting the matrix of the energy of
that area and allow it to become far
more conductive and conducive to
interactions that may go on in the
future as you call the future between
other civilizations and your
civilization. It is not the only area in
which that will take place. The area we
now perceive the physical channel to be,
what you call the Hawaiian Islands, will
also be extremely conducive to the same
type of energy, but it will be slightly
differently expressed. You follow me? Yes, I do. Thank you.
Therefore, when you wish to create the
idea of a total
environment, that will be one area along
with of the Hawaiian area that will be
most conducive to accepting and
receiving a new truly new total
environment in which other individuals
can experience something they have never
experienced upon your planet before.
Will that do?
That that is very helpful. And I have
more specific feelings
about the pristine quality of life in
New Zealand attracts me in a very unique
way. The combination of air, water, yes,
and the the flora and fauna there are
very much like as it were a garden of
Eden in a sense. Yes, it is very
indicative both of an ancient ancient
past and also what you might term your
near future. It carries both
future. It carries both
polarities. Yes. I I sense an
interaction. Can you validate possibly I
sense an interaction between the the
human rather the
mammal and um I think your term is the
land mammal and the water citations
citation can go on there as they are
going on in many different areas. case I
sense myself drawn to the then that
simply may be your meeting place whereas
other individuals will develop
attachments to other meeting places for
there are many around your entire
world have a good time thank you I'll
send you post oh all
right do not wish you to pay the postage
all the way to
our telepathically Oh, thank you.
Yay. Oh, there was someone else. Yes,
I want to thank you for being with us
today. I was here the other night and it
feels like a real privilege. We will
extend our
appreciation as well to you. Thank you.
My question is in terms of our world and
our history that's gone on here,
although there's many forms of
inequality, one of the ones that
extends all the way throughout much of
history that we know about is this
conflict between male and female. And
I'm curious if you can comment, not
conflict, but inequality. If you can
comment on that in your perspective of
your world. Simply that each and every
individual contains both masculine and
feminine energy. And when they allow the
masculine and feminine energy within
each and every individual to become in a
sense married, you will not create
problems in your world at all. Nor will
there ever be again disease.
So how do we get there? You are already
there. Now, do you wish to live as if you are?
Now, do you wish to live as if you are?
Yes.
[Music] Yes. Then do so.
Live as a balanced
being. Be in your terms assertive when
it is applicable, receptive when it is
applicable. Be the balance of the male
and female energy. Be an equal
being. Love others
unconditionally. Be willing to
participate but not force your point of
view on
anyone. Blend,
harmonize, balance,
balance,
breathe, feel the energy within you. It
is all right with you. You have been
physically male and physically female
many many many times. All of you, you
all know what it is like to be one
another. If you allow yourself the
opportunity to delve into your
imagination, you can pick up on whatever
way is the way you need to express that
balance. Then simply live as if there is
that balance in your world and you will
automatically treat all others with
equal respect and they will pick it up
from you whether consciously or
unconsciously. They will know that you
see in them the same balanced potential
state. You follow me? Yes.
If you wish to perform some sort of
ceremony within yourself, then use your
imagination to do that.
I feminine side do take the masculine
side and so
[Music] forth. Learn to allow your polarities to
forth. Learn to allow your polarities to
live in harmony together because they
cannot live without each
other. You are one integrated
being in a sense. When you cease to
think of yourself as containing
polarities and begin to function as a
homogeneous being, then they will
already act as if they are blended.
You follow me?
So trust your instincts and use your
reason when
necessary. All right. Thank you. Oh,
thank you very much. All right. Um
Bashar, I'm curious. I really Oh, how
exciting. I I imagine that you you don't speak in
I I imagine that you you don't speak in
terms of days in your civilization, but
what's like we do not really follow the
flow of keeping track of time in that
sense, but since we do have a
physicalized world and since a day is
simply a single rotation upon its axis
of the planet, we do have days.
Incidentally, they are actually quite
close to your own. Approximately what
you would call 25 of your hours.
Therefore, in that way, however, you
will find that our year is quite a bit
longer. Since our star is greenish
yellow, much hotter than yours, our
planet is farther away from our star
than is yours. And hence the diameter of
our orbit is broader than yours. So
whereas you have approximately the idea
of 365 and one quarter of your days
making up one of your years, our year is
approximately 454 of our days.
Thank you. Um what I'm wondering is like
when you leave here, what's the first
thing you do when you go home? First of
all, I am still at
home. I am not actually physically with
you. This is a telepathic link from within my
This is a telepathic link from within my
scout craft which is at this point over
my own world. Do you have your your
friends and family around you also?
Always since we are always
telepathically in touch. We are always
connected no matter where we physically
are. To us the idea of space and time
are not limiting or separating factors.
You follow me? Yeah.
Does that assist
you? I do many things. Anything that
excites me. In one sense, in your terms,
I am a technical engineer, pilot of a
craft, also a social engineer, and that
is why I am interacting with your
society at this time and I interact with
many other societies that are similar to
your own.
Bashar, the other evening, I asked you
if you actually ate food and you said
that you didn't do that.
that you absorb energy directly. Absorb
energy directly at this point. I was
just curious and wondering how you know
since so many people are choosing
consciously or unconsciously
to what we call starve
to so many people are choosing
consciously or unconsciously
to what we call starve to death guys.
you know what's the possibility of
um by creating by you know how can we
teach ourselves to absorb energy thank
you many of you are beginning to do so
and that is why many of your diets are
changing and becoming lighter and
lighter and lighter and lighter you do
not have to force yourself in that way
to do that but you will simply find that
as you elevate your vibrational
resonance you will simply lose the urge
for more dense sustenance Now, the
individuals in your planetary culture
that are physically starving in a sense
have chosen that particular scenario
because of late it has now allowed many
other cultures upon your planet to go to
their assistance physically and provide
them with the physical sustenance they
require at the same time because of
their particular situation.
And it is only because the energy and
the combined consciousness of a world is
awakening to the idea that you can exist
as a unified culture and interact with
other unified cultures that allows us to
be able to interact with you and allows
you to be able to perceive us.
Otherwise, we would never meet. On such
different vibratory planes, would we
be? Our ability to interact with you is
an indication that we are beginning to
share the same dreams with all of it.
Are you sure? Yeah, I do. Oh, thank you.
Has that been of assistance? Very much.
Thank you, Michelle. Yes. Then you uh
what is the reality of nuclear
destruction of this planet? Neil, thank
you. Recognize first of all that our ability
Recognize first of all that our ability
to share that information with you at
this time stems from your planet.
Whether you consciously realize it at
this point or not already having made at
least a total unconscious decision
approximately as we perceive your time
seven of your years ago to not
annihilate yourselves by nuclear war.
This is why many things now, many
escalations of surface violence are
coming out because now you know it is in
a sense safe to get it all out of your
system and it will not lead to
annihilation. You are bringing what was
formerly hidden and covert and creating
it to be overt and out in the open so
that you can now all look around and
say, "Wait a minute. Look what's going
on. Look what we're doing. Is this the
way we want our world to really be? If
not, let's change it. You now know it is
safe to bring all of that out in the
open, examine it, and create it to be
the way you wish it to be. We can also
tell you this at this time
because you have made that decision
yourselves. However, we can also tell
you the following because you have made
the decision yourselves that you never
would have been allowed to annihilate
yourselves through nuclear means
anywhere. It is your world. You can do
with it what you will as long as what
you do remains in your own
backyard. Nuclear annihilation would
have torn through the dimensional
fabrics of other space-time continuums
and affected more than your own
civilization. recognize that your government is very
recognize that your government is very
well aware and has been aware for quite
some time that your devices had they
been activated simply would not have
worked. They have been given blatant
demonstrations that that is the case.
There have been many craft not from our
civilization that have centered
themselves directly over what you call
your missile silos and deactivated all
of the launch mechanisms.
Your government is very well aware of
this and much of this information bit by
bit will begin to leak out into your
society. The more you blend yourselves
together with the idea of what you have
created your government to be and the
more you allow them to serve you rather
than rule you, then they will be able to
share with you the information that they
have kept from you. basically in that
way to protect you in the way they
thought you wanted to be protected.
Sure. You follow me? Yes. What about uh
accidents such as Chernobyl? There is no
such thing as an accident. In truth,
what you call your shuttle disaster,
what you call your country's interaction
with Libya, and what you call your
Chernobyl, Soviet disaster are three
parts of one event.
on both sides. Did you have your
technological disasters to show you the
directions that you are proceeding in
lead to the idea of breakdowns of your
technological society and the disruption
in that way of things that have been
formerly held secret? It is on both
sides an
indication an outward example of the
belief that your society has that if you
allow what is inside you that drives you
to the surface that it will destroy you
because you are full of cracks and leaks
because you do not think of yourself as
one homogeneous idea. So in this way,
those three events have allowed you to
re-examine in total conscious faith the
ideas and the routes upon which you were
proceeding. They served their purposes.
Understanding is absolutely no accident
and no mistake that there was a teacher
on your shuffle. She has taught her
lesson. The lesson she truly was born to
teach. You follow me?
Allow yourself to recognize that those
three incidents operate and function as
a fulcrum point, a switching point, a
pivot point in your history when you
will find later on that it will be
written. This is when you began to
re-examine truly around that time all of
the methods that you were utilizing in
your civilization to accomplish that
which you desired and began to realize
that there were more natural means of
accessing the creativity and creativity
that you truly wish to experience
before. Yes, for sure. Thank you very
much. On that same point, um could you share
On that same point, um could you share
with us your perception of how the
collective has progressed since we're
completing its now one year cycle from
when that began as and it was created
again in what you call the 39th year,
the transitional year before the 40th.
This being now what you call your
1,987 year being the 40th year since
your world knew beyond a shadow of a
doubt that other worlds and other
civilizations existed.
7747 to 7787 of your counting is the
40-year cycle necessary for the change
of an entire culture. To when you first
truly discovered that there were other
civilizations to where now the majority
of your civilization is willing to
accept the fact that there are other
civilizations. In this way, as we have
said, within the last three of your
years, and particularly since the
acceleration of those particular three
incidents, you have accelerated
greatly. You will now find that since
those incidents, you as a
incidents, you as a
civilization in terms of your colloquial
thinking used to be quote unquote, now
this is very arbitrary and very
abstract, but it will do in your
terminology. But you as a civilization
used to be approximately quote unquote
300 of your years behind us.
Now you are only 150 years.
You follow me? That can also change. And
as we perceive your energy within the
next 10 years, you will in a sense only
be approximately 75 years behind. And
then within 30 of your years, we will be
keeping pace.
You follow me?
Then you will be becoming what we are
representing to you as your future
selves. And there is the interaction in the same
And there is the interaction in the same
space basically. Yeah. And with many
cultures. Thank you. Another one on that
thing. I when you spoke be I heard you
before speak about the um the craft
hovering over a missile silo and the
computer launch codes.
That suggested to me then that when the
government heads do get together and
have these summit meetings that they're
not actually talking about what they
said. Um, is it pretty much that they are
Um, is it pretty much that they are
friendly with each other and they're
keeping keep allowing each other to stay
in power? Whether they are friendly
literally or not, they both know what
the game is that they are truly players
and the game has to do with that there
is never the idea of um destruction or
war. And so is it mostly a monetary in a
sense? Yes. gain. It is the idea of
maintaining what they fear they will
lose. Power. Not recognizing that the
equalization of the entire world will
actually be the gaining of their own
selfmpowerment along with everyone else. Yes.
Different. But enough information has
crossed the lines now so that both of
your quote unquote sides know just about
enough. Would you clarify that for those
of you that might not
40 of your years ago in this way there
was what you call a crash of a
spacecraft from the system of Zen
reticulum upon your planet. Your
government came into possession of the
physical craft and the
bodies alive. No.
What does it look like? Approximately
three and a half to four feet of your
height. Again, white whitish gray skin
coloration. Enlarged head. Not quite as
much as what you would call human more
humanoid in that way, enlarged eyes.
What about the craft?
The craft is still in pieces under
surveillance in many different areas of
your country. primarily near what you
would call the area Virginia.
What caused the craft?
There was surveillance being done by
that craft in what you would call very
heavy lightning storm. And there was
some portion of what you would call your
radar installations that interfered with
the guidance systems of the craft and
caused a momentary disruption in the
inertial field of the craft which
allowed it to expose a portion of its
field its area layers to the electricity
in the sky. When struck by the
electrical charge it shorted out the
craft and it crashed. And what was the
value that they got out of creating that
reality into their life? You have now
been initiated on the 40-year cycle that
allows you to begin to be brought into
the association of civilization. I'm
talking about the other
civilization craft. Yes. So are we.
In that way, whether they were conscious
of what they were doing or not, the
incident began a series of events in
your civilization that has brought you
now to the understanding you have and
the ability to join the association of
civilization. You follow me?
You follow me?
Yes. Many
Many
circumstances from the Yes. Many
circumstances will occur that may seem
on the surface to be accidental. I
realize, but it did not take that
civilization long to realize what the
possession of one of their crafts would
mean to your civilization. And so they
became very very
very connected in terms of surveillance
on your civilization to assist not to
remove the idea but to then assist in
the guidance of understanding on your
planet of what you now have come into
possession of. And where are they? They
are in the constellation you call Seda
reticulum.
If you wish to familiarize yourself to
some degree with that civilization, you
will find that within your literature
are many incidents of interactions
between the beings of that civilization
and the beings of your own civilization.
One in your terms of the most wellknown
will be that referred to as Betty and
Barney Hill.
Research your liver ature and you will
discover some ideas about that
civilization. Can I ask you a couple of questions
Can I ask you a couple of questions
about the physicality of your
civilization? Yes.
Uh because you obviously have some
physicality as you say. What in what way
does that serve you? Do you experience
physical pleasures as we do and how do
you procreate? Thank you. To some degree
it serves us by allowing us to interact
with civilizations such as your own that
need that type of relationship to be
able to interact. Also because we exist
in pure ecstasy in that sense it is a
very pleasurable state in which to exist
as you will soon find out upon your
planet as well. There is nothing wrong
with existing as a physical
representation of consciousness.
Although we are now as you are going
from a transitional third to fourth
density, we are going from transitional
fourth to fifth and soon will not have
embodiment because we will no longer
need it for the idea that we are. But
simply as a civilization, we chose to
experience certain ideas of physical
reality so that we would also be able to
exist and assist other
civilizations going through a similar
experience to be able to interact with
them in terms relate to. We procreate
similar to you in that sense, although
it is more of an energy exchange and
energy activation of the cellular
structures that begin to create what you
call the fetus. The gestation period
being approximately seven of your months
rather than nine. In that way, it is
born similar to your own in that sense
except that we are in conscious
communication with the entity being born
prior to birth, during birth and after
the birth as well.
You following? Yes. Does that
assist then it assists you? Thank you
very much. Hey All right.
All right.
Hey, um as you were saying in the 30
years that we are beginning to see the
dimension that we are headed towards,
does that mean the physicality of the
bodies that we exist in now will also
begin to
dimensionally become more exceeded in
the vibration as well? Yes. So that
indeed we will begin to have in a sense
a lighter, more resonating body. Yes.
Things will appear to be brighter to
you. You will see colors more clearly.
You will see energies that are now
invisible to you. You will be able to
truly see boric fields, the
ethereomagnetic field, and any other
interactive vibratory field that
connects the idea of your total
consciousness upon your planet. That's
the Yes. Is there anything more you can
Yes. Is there anything more you can
share with us?
You will have no disease.
You will sleep and eat
less. You will create your dreams upon
your
planet. You will interact with many
other
civilizations. You will rebuild many
sections of your world, landscaping
them into pleasing forms. You will cease
to build on many sections of your
world. You will build in space. You will
explore space and dimensions of
time and other levels of
experience. You will begin to truly see
through the illusion of physical reality
as your own projection. You will be able
to come and go in and out of your body
at
will. You will then find that you no
longer need to reincarnate at all. And
any time you wish to have the experience
for a brief period of time of a physical
form, you will simply have a very few
bodies that you will all share.
What approximate population?
You will find that within what you call
1,000 of your years, it is likely, not
absolute, but likely that you will be
down to what you call 50 million.
What about in
You may in this way be beginning to
reverse the
trend down from approximately what you
would call 6
billion. For in this way you will find
that you really are not overpopulated.
You simply do not aortion the land you
have in equal
ways. But again, once you begin to move
out of the phase of
reincarnation and once you allow for
more longevity of the lives you already
have, then you will decrease your
numbers in that sense.
And many individuals will simply remain
as a non-physical support system for
those individuals who wish to continue
for a time in physical
reality until at such time approximately
what you call 2 to 3,000 of your years.
Hence, you will no longer need to be
physical at all.
Some of you may still remain as a
support system non-physically for other
beings that may then wish to use your
physical reality as a new experiential
reality and may begin their cycle a new. Thank
Thank
you. Sure. the concept of the global
brain as it's been talked about the last
several years with the shift from four
and a half or five billion into the six
billion range which is a as you know the
cycle of number of cells that allows for
transformation. Can you share with us
the concept of the global brain as it
will affect the planet earth for the
next one two or three years? You are
already a global brain. How does it
affect your planet now?
seems to be amounts of chaos in certain
areas but that is simply because you do
not have the neuronic circuits of the
pathways of the global brain all
proceeding in the linear direction in
the same way. Could you speak more on
that for the next few years? What that
might be or what it might
take? Understand this. You have already
passed over the threshold or what we
would call the flashover point in that
way to allow the majority of your
society to create harmonious accord.
Even though every single person will
still be expressing themselves him or
herself as an individual, you will still
be able simultaneously to express a
harmonious accord in the general
direction of how your energy is applied.
And as soon as in this way you arrive at
the point you call 2011 to
2013, that flashover point will kick in
in full force and you will begin to see
a spontaneous explosion of synchronicity
around the globe that will allow you to
know you can get anything done anytime,
anywhere. You follow me? You will know
you are in full communication in
whatever way you need to be with every
other individual on the planet and we do
not just mean human.
Yes, you follow me. I do follow you.
Then you will begin to function as a
global brain. And what that means is the
body of the earth in that sense will be
able to move in
unison and its cells will not be in
conflict. It will be self-supportive in
that way. It will
crystallize and within the
etheromagnetic sea that will crystallize
your consciousness in that sense being
embedded in that sea. Then every ripple
that any individual creates within that
sea will be felt by every other
individual and responded to accordingly.
The specific event we had approximately
nine of our earth days ago. You familiar
with the world meditation
for it had a very large impact in
creating a new gate. The opening of a
doorway through which you have all now
passed. And again one of the results of
having passed through that doorway will
be to see more and more synchronicity
occurring in your life. more and more
coincidence. Right place, right time,
right people, right situation, exactly
when and where do you need it?
Approximately how many how many of us
were involved on this planet in that meditation? including the
including the
idea of even a flicker of a
thought regarding the meditation which
also has its effect. We perceive that it
is in the neighborhood and this of
course can be our own point of view on
how we perceive your energy but from our
point of view it is perceived to be
approximately 710 million.
That's great.
Thank you. That includes all of the
flickers as well. No. Hey
Could you speak
up? I remember she remembers us
discussing the idea of many different
dimensions or levels of experience.
I guess the idea seems to be that
normally an individual would
that's how you think of it linearly from
the third density point of view is it
possible
in a sense to some degree
Yes, because you already exist on every
level. There is to exist upon
simultaneously. On the 12th level, you
know this. On the third, you may not.
But the idea is is that on the third,
you can become whatever representation
of that connection you need to
be. You follow me?
You are not sure. All
right. Allow me to ask you a question if
I
may. In your terms of linear thinking,
in the way you have put the question,
what would be your reason from going
directly from third to 12th without
experiencing all the ones in between?
then you will probably remain in the
third dimension until you realize they
can be. The idea is that when you invalidate
be. The idea is that when you invalidate
an experience you obviously chose to
have, then you are not getting out of it
what you can get out of it. And it will
usually allow you to remain in that
experience until you understand the
reason for why you chose to be in it to
begin with. The quickest way to get to
the 12th level is to realize that you
can absolutely and in every way, shape,
or form enjoy the
third. Does this make any sense to you?
But you don't believe it can be done.
All right. But understand there are many
different kinds of limitation. It is a
form of
limitation just to be focused in a
specific way. Even in what you would
call 12th density, there is still the
idea of a particular awareness or focus
that allows you to conceive of the fact
that you are in 12th density. That is
still a type of limitation. You
following? Limitation in and of itself does not
Limitation in and of itself does not
have to be inherently negative.
You are simply buying into the belief
system or one of the belief systems in
your third density
reality that all limitation is
inherently negative or that there can be
situations that are inherently negative.
But there
aren't. No situation has any built-in
meaning. Whatever meaning you give to a
situation is what you have been taught
to give to that situation. Is what you
have been taught to believe that
situation means. But no situation has
builtin meaning. No situation means
anything. The meaning you give to a
neutral situation, a neutral set of
circumstances, a neutral set of props,
the meaning you give to that situation
utterly determines the effect you get
out of it. So if you do not find third
density pleasant then it is because you
have been taught to believe that it is
not. Only that belief only that belief
creates third density to be effectually
unpleasant. Only that belief. There is
nothing built into physical reality that
says physical reality has to be
unpleasant. Just because it is a
limitation in a particular way does not
mean that you cannot soar with
exuberance in third density reality. And
again, paradoxically, since you obviously have
paradoxically, since you obviously have
chosen to be in third density reality,
it is our suggestion that when you allow
yourself to realize that you can become
absolutely ecstatic in third density,
that's when you will have cognition of
the fact that you already exist on all
the other levels already. And simply
allowing yourself to know that will be
the simple matter of shifting your
perspective rather than feeling like you
have to climb your way out of some thick
dark mire into which you have
fallen. It is all point of
view. The idea and perhaps this will be
of assistance to you if you are willing
to absorb this directly into your heart.
Pay close attention to the following
definition. Your idea and we are
speaking in general as well of going
from level to level to
level, plane to plane to plane. That
idea, that process is simply the process
of
recognizing that you actually are the
dimension itself that you previously
thought you existed
in. So if you find yourself thinking
that you exist in third density, think
again. You are third density. You are
the physical universe. The physical
universe is you. When you know you are
all that you experience the physical
universe to be, you are in control of
what it is you do experience the
physical universe to be. Then it will be
heaven on
earth. 12th density on earth in earth
terms. All levels align at a particular way of
All levels align at a particular way of
thinking in a particular mode of
thought. All levels
align. All you have to do is realize
that going from level to level to level
is the recognition that you already
exist as that level and thinking of
yourself in that point of view. When you
allow yourself to operate as the
collective totality that you are, then
no one level will seem to be
overwhelming because you will be drawing
on the totality of all that you are. You
are not cut off from yourself in 12th
density. You are always able to draw
from all of the power, all of the
existence, the totality of the spirit
and the soul that you are. Then no one
level will seem to be
overwhelming because any one level will
only be seen to be a small fraction of
the total
being the total
creator that you
are. You follow it? And when you
function in that way, that enjoying
where you are when you are there, living
in the moment, living totally in the
present is paradoxically exactly the way
to allow for the future and all the
other levels to accelerate most quickly
into your present
experience. For you do not go anywhere.
All happens within
you. You bring those experiences to you
and even that you are not literally
doing. Nothing in the universe truly
literally actually moves or goes
anywhere. It is all perspective and
point of
view. All of
it. Do remember this. And this also may
assist you greatly when you allow it to
sink into whatever portion of you it
needs to sink into. And do not think
you're not getting this. You are getting
it on whatever level you need to relax
within yourself. But do remember
this. Many of the ideas of what many
people in your civilization believe to
be
entrament. I'm stuck here. I'm stuck
there. is because you have been taught
to believe that consciousness exists in
the body. It doesn't. The body exists
within your
consciousness. There is a vast
difference in the realization of those
two definitions. Ponder that while you all
definitions. Ponder that while you all
enjoy a short break.
Thank you. All right.
Now, ponder that for a moment then, if
you will. The
idea that consciousness does not exist
in your body, but that your body exists
within the consciousness that you are.
The idea therefore is very very
unlimiting, very expansive. For you can
recognize that what you colloquially
think of as your body is but one focal
point within the combined idea of the
consciousness that you are out of which
is created.
all the physical reality you
experience. In this way, you can allow
yourself to know you have much more
mobility in that sense because you can
always allow yourself to diversify your
focus, disperse your point of view,
broaden and expand the way you look at
yourself, the way you look through
yourself, the way you look through the
idea of yourself. that is expressed in
bodily terms. The body is immersed in
the collective consciousness that you
are. The body functions much like an
anchor point for the prism that allows
the white light of your consciousness to
channel through to funnel through that
prism and become the specialized
spectrum of light. differentiated
spectrum of light that creates the
differences you see in physical reality.
The prism is formed as many three-sided
things are from the three ideas you call
belief, emotion and thought.
Belief, emotion, and thought form the
ego structure that allows you to
maintain a focus in physical reality to
function as a physicalized form of your
consciousness or a physicalized
representation of your
consciousness. Your personality as a
physical being, your persona is not
literally who or what you are directly
in that sense nor totally in that sense.
It is in a sense an artificial
construct. It is a
representative of a particular idea that
your consciousness is being as an
expression of physical reality. So as
that prism, as that cornerstone that you
create your persona to be, then you
allow the white light, the homogeneous
oneness of your consciousness to become
focused into and through that prism and
display itself as the spectrum of
differences that you perceive physical
reality to be. It is simply one way of
expressing yourself. And you do it
because it is one way you can express
yourself because it is one of the ways
that you can express yourself in
creation as an aspect of
creation. Remember this. Each and every
being in creation is simply all the
different ways that infinite creation
has of expressing itself as the creation
that it is.
But everything that takes place takes
place within the idea of the consciousness
within the idea of the consciousness
that you
are. Out of the consciousness that you
are is created all
experiences that any fragment that you
create yourself to be may interact with
or interact as.
For literally any experience you are
having is not happening to you. It is
you happening as that experience. It is
you interacting as the event of the
experience. It is your consciousness
intersecting the idea, recognizing
itself, knowing itself as that
particular event or that particular
experience. You cause an intersection to
take place between the self and the
ability to reflect the self to the self.
Selfawareness in that way is what
creates all the experiences you have. It
is in and of itself the ability
self-awareness is in and of itself the
ability to create experience in a
seemingly I say seemingly objectified
manner. For there is no true
objectivity. Everything is a subjective
experience. Objectivity is a tool. It is
an attitude you can use to allow
yourself to glean clear insight on many
of the meanings of the experience that
you are subjectively.
By the way, allow us to interject at
this time that what many of you refer to, not
time that what many of you refer to, not
that we care whether you use this or
not, but what many of you refer to in
any given situation as
skepticism is usually thought in your
society to be a display of objectivity.
Skepticism is not objectivism.
Skepticism is an already inherent belief
and bias in a particular direction.
Contrary to what many of you think,
skepticism is not what you typically
call a true scientific trait.
Objectivity is. Skepticism is a bias and
therefore it is an emotional trait in
that sense and not truly what you would
call scientific even in your own terms.
However, recognize that all points of
view are valid since they allow the
individual to determine the experience
that they are being and therefore allow
them to determine what experience they
would prefer to be if they find that
they are creating themselves to be an
experience they don't prefer or what
experience they would rather reinforce
if they find that they are being an
experience they do
prefer. But
remember, it
can, as it did for us in our
civilization, make a profound
difference in your recognition of your
ability to create the reality you
desire. If you will remember that
consciousness does not exist in the
body, the body exists in the
consciousness that you are. And
everything is malleable. And only the
things that seem solid are the things
you believe are solid. And only the
belief makes them solid. Only the
belief. Everything is energy. Everything
is malleable. Everything is
you expressing the unique facet that you
are of infinite creation. For sure. Yay.
Does that mean that if I believe that
this country were liquid that I could
slip down through it as a republic? Yes.
And you will find that there are
individuals upon your planet who are
beginning to exhibit such
traits. For example, what you call
levitation, what you call billocation,
what you call
teleportation is all of them. Yes.
All of these are examples that you truly
are the reality you create and that when
you rearrange the definitions then the
reality will also rearrange itself
instantly. It is only because you have been taught
It is only because you have been taught
only because it has been truly ingrained
within your thought structure that
physical reality as you have been taught
to believe physical reality is is the
only way reality can be. That you very
often do bang into a wall when you walk
towards it because you haven't been
taught to believe because you haven't
been taught to believe. You need to
believe that it is solid. It has served
you to believe so in the past. But now
that you are beginning to awaken to the
fact that physical reality is only what
you make it, now you can play around a
little bit more freely with it because
you now know you are in control of it.
You follow? Yes. You you made me think
of an example I heard about at Stanford
research. Oh, right.
They were playing with
psychoetic experiences, mind over
matter, guys. And they found that when
they set up an experiment that people
were very familiar with, for instance,
rotating a table in front of them, guys
had a great deal of difficulty, but
something they knew little about, like
moving a laser beam inside of a vacuum.
Yes. They had a great deal more success.
Yes. Because there was no expectation in
the way. Quote unquote. Everybody knows
you can't raise a table by levitating,
but almost no one in your society knows
what is possible or not possible with a
laser
beholder one's belief system by getting
in touch with what it is to begin with
and then redefining it. Okay. Tell that
if you wanted to practice levitation you
would just one very appropriate way
would be that if you do know as we have
discussed an individual who already does
it go and be in that environment and
mimic what they do because you can
identify with them and create the same
pattern they create in their life in
your life and then you will act the same
way and have the same results.
Yes, I do. If such an individual isn't
immediately available, um, what would be
the next best way?
You can attract one to yourself if you
feel you need it. And you can always use
your imagination and attract to yourself
whatever information you need to allow
you to become such an individual. We
would recommend that great deal
of
breathing in silent
centering. Breathing in deep and
rhythmic power will infuse your body
with a type of crystallin energy that
will allow you to arrive at the center
point of balance from which point
anything is
possible. I understand. You will then
quote unquote lose your fix on the
reality you think of all the time and
begin to accept more postulates from
other realities.
Yes, I really do. Thank you very much.
And then
you move this at least for me to a much
more personal. All right. I know that
you've talked about patterns. I've been
aware from my own personal experience,
my personal primary relationships that
my pattern has been one that has not
been what I would call successful,
lasting valuable to me in a very way.
Oh, and I would like to have your input
if you would regarding the past
relationship that this was and what will
be and what is necessary for me. to make
that take place. Did you learn nothing
of a positive nature from the
relationship? I learned something of a
positive nature from the relationship
which was to see more clearly the pattern that
was to see more clearly the pattern that
I have had and the the the
to recognize what your belief system is
and if you do not like it to change it.
This is what you are saying. All right.
Now all right.
all right.
Now in this way what is your
definition of the belief within
you that you have discovered?
I'm not sure. Can you vocalize a
definition for the belief?
Yes. Go ahead. That
I see myself um showing less of my
power, of my goodness, of my positive
self-esteem and
[Music]
self-confidence. If you use those things
you wish to use at any other time in
your life in a personal relationship,
what do you imagine would
happen? That I would empower that
relationship as I've empowered other
aspects of my life. And is that what you
wish to do?
Yes. Do you find yourself holding back
from doing that in a relationship?
I have to say apparently so because I
see that as the result perhaps only
because you may be looking for that
relationship in order to feel complete
in your life. That's that's very
truthful. Yes. But understand you are
already complete. Not that you will not
grow, not that you will not expand, not
that you will not broaden your
understanding of yourself. But as you
are, you are already complete. as the
idea you are being at this moment. You
are a complete version of that idea.
When individuals in your society very
often believe they need the other
relationship in order to recognize
themselves as complete, then very often
what they only attract is a reflection
of the belief that they are incomplete
and that is what they attract as the
other individual. A reflection in the
belief in their own incompleteness. When
you know you are complete, when you
function as a total being in that way,
then you can attract an individual to
reflect your belief in your own
completeness and share that as an
equality rather than feeling like you
need the relationship or you will not be
complete in my life by not having that.
Understand that nothing is missing.
Nothing. Not one thing.
Nothing. You have it all right there,
right? Everything. The only thing that makes
Everything. The only thing that makes
you think something is missing is that
you believe something can be missing.
And so when you go looking for it, you
create a sense of loss to give you
purpose in
looking. But nothing is missing. It is
an illusion. It is an assumption.
Perhaps it comes from this basic and
fundamental belief that many of you are
taught in your
society that you must
achieve or that you can try to achieve
perfection. Do you believe you will
achieve perfection or do you believe you
desire to achieve perfection? Both
understand you will never achieve
perfection. Do you know why?
over here. Yes. Because you are already
perfect. Now you say, "What do you mean
I'm already perfect? I don't have this
in my life. I don't have that in my
life. How can I be perfect?" The idea is
to paradoxically recognize once again
that every moment that exists, it exists
for its own sake, on its own terms. And
one moment has no business being
compared with another moment.
Everything you do at any given moment is
a perfect manifestation of the thing you
are doing. Not that you will not do
different things later on. Not that you
will not do more expanded things later
on. But the thing you are doing now is a
perfect flawless manifestation of
whatever it is you are doing. Even if it
is perfect miseries, it is still perfect
for what it is. And paradoxically, the
way to then create in your life what you
would prefer to create is to allow what
you have created to be perfect. Because
nothing that comes along will then be
better. It will simply be different. But
it will be equal to anything else you
have ever done. When you allow all
possible choices in your life to be
equal with any other choice you could
make, then every choice exists on the
same level. And then it's easy to choose
which one you prefer and manifest that
in your life. Only when you think of
things as being on different levels,
this is better, this is worse, this is
good, this is bad, and so forth, do you
then create the separation that makes it
hard to reach for something you want.
Oh, perfection. There it is somewhere
just beyond my reach. Oh, someday maybe
if I try very hard, I'll reach
perfection. But boy, am I going to be
tired by the time I get
there. When every choice you could make
and every experience you have is on the
same level, then you won't have to climb
for anything and you won't have to feel
that you ever fall down to
anything. Everything is laid out before
you on the same level. Everything you do
is a perfect manifestation of the thing
you are doing. You are allowing the way
your life unfolds to be the way it needs
to
unfold. Then is when you have greater
control over how it
unfolds. Is any of this making sense?
Yes. Are you
sure? Yes.
And without asking you in a prophecy
from a prophecy perspective yet I still
want to ask what do you see lies ahead
for me by way of the lessons to be
continued and uh result regarding the
relationship. If you are willing to
recognize and as soon as you are willing
to
recognize that you are complete and have
a lot to share and that you are willing
to share as an equal with another
individual, then if that relationship
still remains necessary in your life, as
soon as you are willing to recognize it,
it can occur as soon as 3 days from that
point. Whatever that point is, when you
decide to create that point, within 3
days, you can attract an individual to
represent what you are now willing to
know about
yourself. It does not need to take any
longer than
that. Be Yes. So when it occurs is up to
when you decide that you will allow
yourself to be completely and utterly
valid as you
are and that you always attract the
individuals into your life that reflect
back to you what it is you need to know.
First of all, love yourself
unconditionally as infinite creation
loves you. Infinite creation loves you
unconditionally. Grant yourself the same
respect and the same
attitude. Then share and be of service
to other
individuals and you will feel always
nurtured in that sense and you will not
feel a lack of anything.
Then when you already know you are
nurtured 100% as you are, you will attract a
100% as you are, you will attract a
multitude of individuals who will be
more than willing to reflect back to you
what you already believe yourself to be
a nurtured
being. But first you must behave like a
nurtured being.
Then you can attract an individual who
will reflect that
nurturing. But they will have nothing to
reflect back to you if you do not
already believe that you are
intrinsically just because you exist a
nurtured being.
being.
Yes. Thank you.
I had one here.
All right. So, I wanted some clarity on
the apparent paradox, the philosophical
paradox, philosophical paradox. All
right. Yeah. I um I'm very very familiar
with all the writings of Jane and the
second teachings and I quite believe all
of this, but I perceive a paradox
in the the difference between everything
being in a constant state of becoming
Yes. as Tess teaches and everything
already exists. And everything already
existing. Have everything and all its
possibilities already exist and our
focus simply changes. Yes. Then how can
there be any becoming?
Do recognize that the term becoming is
mostly conducive to your third density
point of view because you think of a
beginning, a middle, and an end, and you
think of things becoming. But there is
also true creation. When you realize
that thoughts are things, then any new
perspective or point of view is also the
act of becoming even though the
perspective is about something that
already exists. Does that make any sense? Yes.
exists. Does that make any sense? Yes.
So any perspective that you generate
that may be in your terms a new
perspective, a new way of looking at
something that already exists is in and
of itself also new creation. We do
understand that it does translate as a
seeming paradox in your reality. But
understand that paradox when you are
dealing with paradox then that's when
you know you are dealing with the higher
levels of reality. For you know that if
you can perceive a conflict or dichotomy
since it is your perception that there
is a polarity you know that both sides
stem from you and somewhere within you
must coexist must be blended as one
thing. When you see a paradox it is
simply let us say a translation
difficulty into third density terms. But
everything is the same one thing
manifesting in all the multi-dimensional
simultaneous ways that it
can at the same time in different
ways. Does this make any sense? Oh yes,
it all makes sense. That's
not a problem. You can use it you can
utilize it as a tool. Yeah. Simply
assume that the universe and infinite
creation has the label infinite creation
because all things are possible. Even
paradox and on one level it is not a
paradox simply because it is accepted
for what it is.
Evolve it.
Enjoy it. If it makes you laugh, use it
that way.
Paradox is getting in touch with the
center of yourself.
For sure. You close.
Closing time. Close. You are very close
to opening time.
But at this timing, therefore, we will
respect your schedules and in this
sense, we will extend to each and every
one of you our appreciation. Yes. One
more question. One more question. Yes.
About dolphins being aliens. Dolphins
being alien. Well, to us they are since
they are on your
planet and not on
our but they are the co-sensient species
on your
planet. And in this way, when you allow
yourself to begin to utilize the
co-interaction with them as your
practice in interacting with other
alien, if you will,
civilizations, then you will react and
interact with us as one whole world. For
you have the wonderful gift of having
two sensient species upon your planet.
In a sense, they have just as many
incarnational connections in many
different ways as you do. And in that
sense, they are the same type of soul
that you are. So in that sense, since
none of you are original to the planet,
neither are any of them. And in that
sense, they are just as alien as you
are. Many of you interacted in the times
of Atlantis.
Many of you incarnated as each
other. This is something which has not
gone on recently simply because the
humans have locked themselves into a
particular cycle. But it is something
that may occur again when you loosen up.
Are they conscious of that? Some of
them not all of them for many of them
are also locked into their own cycle at
this time. But they do have a broader
memory of your familial connections and
that is why they are very eager to
interact with you. Will we have ever be
able to understand their language if
they seem to understand ours?
Yes. But it will be mostly an emotional
understanding. Even though you can have
an analytical understanding of the
sounds they make, you will find that
perhaps the quickest understanding will
come through
emotional attachment because true
telepathy is emotionally activated. When
you love
unconditionally, then you know what that
person is all
about. You follow me? Yes. Thank you for
your sharing. Thank you for your
willingness to allow us to share with
you our unconditional love and our
belief in the idea that we cocreate
together. We would simply once again
remind you. Give yourself permission to
wake up and
dream for physical reality is but what
you dream it to be. You are living a
dream right now. And dream reality is
real. Create the dream you desire.
Follow your excitement. It will never
lead you
astray. We thank you for allowing us to
experience this interaction. We bid you
a bond and unconditionally loving and
exciting dream life and life breed. Good
day. [Music] [Music]
Good night.
How did everything go?
[Music] Thank you. Thank you for all.
Thank you. Thank you for all.
[Music]