[Music] [Laughter] [Laughter]
[Music]
I'll say how are you all this evening of
your time as you create time to exist.
Allow us to begin this evening of your
time with an interaction as we remind
you we entitled last week cacina dreams.
The idea of what you have for a very
long time in your society in the Native
American society called a cacina energy.
We have discussed from time to time
briefly with you and we have given it in
your terms our own labeling. We have
called a cacina being a cacina
consciousness and extraterrestrials
extraterrestrial. What this basically implies is that even
What this basically implies is that even
to us in our civilization, the energy
consciousness that is represented in
your society by the kacina exists in
between, if you will, the universal
realities that you and we are generally
familiar with in calling our dayto-day
universal reality. They exist and
inhabit and actually create. the
membranes if you will, the structure,
the lattice work, the matrix, if you
will, that separates and defines by
vibratory frequency all the
multitudinous infinite number of
multiverses that there are in existence.
They exist in the universe of the
lattice work in between. Therefore, they
represent a very peculiar and
interesting and fascinating type of
structure or vibratory relationship with
the multitude of universes. And in a
sense, because they are in between, so
to speak, can project themselves from a
particularly different point of view
into any one of those universes and may
manifest in any way, shape, or form they
so desire to represent the energy
through what you would call the
archetypal clothing that any particular
civilization in any particular universe
would need to perceive them within in
order to understand their existence. at
all. In other words, a kachina energy
does not really have a type of
physiology as we understand
physiology. No matter how different the
physiology may be even in what you term
non-physical existence, it has a certain
shall we say physiology to the energy.
But kacina energy has a completely
different type of what we have referred
to before as a quasi planar reality
quasiplanar physiology.
They are if you will a type of
mathematical pattern in and of itself.
They are in a sense actually made of the
template which gives definition to all
the things we you and us consider the
physiological universe. They are the
primal energy essence cohesive
consciousness in a very particular
format that actually represents some of
the primary pulse if you will of the
existence factor itself. Is all of this
making some sense so far?
Therefore, they have the unique position
of being able to branch out, if you
will, into any particular physiological
or non-physiological reality, taking
whatever form is necessary to relate to
the beings in that particular universe.
And as such, they exist constantly in
their zero rest point in a sort of
unlocked state from any particular
universal reality. They exist in that
frame of reference that divides and at
the same time unites all the different
multi-dimensional universes that there
are. So they are in a sense if you will
to be colloquial the glue of existence
in that way. They thus when they project
into any physiological reality will be
projecting from a multiple or you can
look at it conversely nondimensional
point and as such can perform what you
would consider many feats of magical
apparition. For they are
multi-dimensional beings and can extend
any portion of themselves into any
particular reality or a number of
realities simultaneously. What you
perceive them to be in your physical
reality is almost always but an aspect
or a fragment, a very minuscule aspect
or fragment of the total being that is
projecting itself. In a sense, it can be
said that that entire matrix is one
consciousness with, if you will, many
fingers poking into different realities
all the time, coming and going,
observing and reflecting back to itself
all the different aspects in different
universes of which it is a part and to
which it is connected and in which it is
interplaying with all of the reflections
or mirrors or fragments of other types
of consciousness, you and me, that it is
interacting with from time to
time. Its fundamental purpose in
existence is to always create at any
given moment with whom it is interacting
an absolute reflection of what might be
called the archetypal or primal power of
the collective consciousness of the
entire society that they are interacting
with or the entire culture at any one
moment that they are interacting with.
They are a prime archetype in that
sense. And within any capacina
projection, any number of beings can see
different faces, different aspects. They
are in and of themselves multiaceted
mirrors, constantly changing, constantly
transforming. You can say they are the
act of transformation itself. So they
are very slippery. Their surface in that
sense is very much like mercury. Not
literally but in the sense of mercurial
that any being looking upon them will
only see what that energy represents to
that being. They have as many faces as
there are beings in creation. They are
in a sense a reflection of all the
multitudinous facets in the multiverse
in their own universal terms.
So when you or should you or if you
desire the idea of blending and linking
with that particular type of
consciousness, that particular type of
being, you can find yourself looking
into many mirrors. You can use that
energy as a tool to see by reflection
through them every single personality
aspect that you have created your
persona to
contain. You can with that one
interaction interacting with what you
may call the same aspect over and over
again. Review every single idea, every
single mode of operation, every single
pattern of consciousness that you can
imagine yourself to be at any given
moment. Review them all of them if you
wish, one at a time if you wish. And you
can actually play in a sense with them
by allowing them to reflect to you
whatever particular aspect of your
consciousness you are dealing with at
this time. So you can actually have what
appears to be a disassociated
conversation with that particular
portion of yourself. They are in that
sense differently than you might think,
but they are still nonetheless in that
sense very good at what you call
dialoguing the entire individual, the
entire persona that you are and
reflecting back to you in a whole
truthful sense precisely the aspects of
your consciousness you are dealing with
at any given moment. So that is why they
have been likened to in your terminology
the path of a warrior in that way and
why those cultures that are very boldly
able to live in different
dimensionalities at once within their
imagination such as your American Indian
culture finds no difficulty in invoking
these beings and calling them forth and
interacting with them on what you would
call a day-to-day basis because when
beings are willing to be that open then
always they will be given by those
beings absolute reflection of the idea
that they represent the energy that they
represent, the pattern and the path and
the purpose that they represent at any
given moment. So they are very good
guides and companions in that way. But
they are simply reflections. They never
live your life in that sense for you.
But they will show you what you are
capable of being. They can show you your
entire potential in a flash of light.
They are in that sense quite the magical
extension of all that you can imagine
yourself to be. And if you so desire, by
invoking that symbology, if you feel so
inclined, by using that tool, you can
very rapidly flash through all the
different ideas and fragments you have
diversified yourself into and bring
there together a thunderclap of
integration within your very soul and
elevate yourself and accelerate your
vibratory pattern very rapidly, very
easily, connecting not only to what you
call the electromagnetic universality,
but also to the planet upon which you
exist. Very strong connections down into
the ground and up into the heavens are
made in the moment of the meeting of
that lightning and that thunder clap.
You all follow
along. Sleep on this idea. For there is
much more than just the words you are
hearing being funneled through this idea
at this time. And those that are
receptive and those that have a desire
to be receptive to the idea may find
many unusual dream doors opening this
night of your time, ones far different
than those you have even opened up to
this point. Therefore, at this time,
even now, we will bid you exciting
Kacina dreams this night of your time.
And we will also at this time extend to
you once again our unconditional
appreciation and love for your
willingness to interact with us and
function as the ambassadors of your
society and allowing me to function as
the ambassador of mine and in return for
that wonderful gift you have given me. I
ask you simply how may I serve you?
Bashar I have a brief uh request of uh
Joan Bishop who's our regular attendee.
her father passed away and uh last night
and she would like to know she asked me
to ask you if there was any information
for uh the widow from the husband her
father simply that this being and our
perception is going to begin quote
unquote a long journey of exploration in
the non-physical realm and within what
you would call the next three days of
your time there can be a very loving
communication in the dream state to
assure those still physically alive that
that being is perfectly fine and
beginning to open eyes in ways that have
never been opened
before. So simply receive if you will
the kiss, receive the heart in the dream
state within the next 3 days and send
the nourishment and the nurturing what
you call the bonvoyage. It is not that
that person is actually going anywhere.
Their energy will be felt for a very
long time, but they are beginning a type
of exploration and a type of journey
that will take them far into different
realms for quite some time.
I thank you for Joan. Thank you. Thank
you, Sharing. Hello, Bashar. And to you,
that was very exciting information about
the Cacina. I'm going to definitely tune
in on that one. All right. Um, Bashar, a
couple weeks ago, a friend gave me a
psychic reading as a gift. And when I
was there and the channel was bringing
through the information, one of the
first things that she said to me was she
said that I am surrounded by and have a
very angelic energy. And I realized that
that's something that I have been told
over and over and over again and I'm not
really sure I know what that means.
means you can spread your own wings and
fly as high as you wish to. Means that
you are in that sense aligning your
vibratory energy with what is
colloquially referred to as an angelic
level of consciousness which generally
refers to levels of consciousness that
have never experienced physiological
reality. So in that sense if you wish
now this is all in a sense a metaphor an
analogy. It has some literalist to it
but you do not have to take it
completely literally in order to get the
essence and the energy out of this. In a
sense let us say you decided to
incorporate yourself even though you have very
yourself even though you have very
strong attachments to levels of
consciousness of which the majority have
never experienced incorporation in
physical materiality. So you are
functioning in a sense as a probe on
your own behalf out of your own choice
and are able to siphon back some
experiences of physical materiality to
those beings in that level that have
never experienced physical materiality.
And in return they send their loving
vibration to you to act as a guideline
to always allow you to know the power
that is within you for creating the
reality that you desire. But you are in
that sense as many of you are as all of
you are really quite angelic in that
sense that you can spread your wings.
You can fly and elevate yourself to the
highest levels of creativity within the
physical realm. You follow me? Yes, I
do. And would in turn would they send
back like some ideas of other realms
that would come out in my work? Is that
Yes. You have a capability of actually
physiologically manifesting in many
different creative ways ideas that are
acted out on non-physical realms but
have no physiological counterpart to
express them by. So you can in a sense
create a representative physiological
counterpart for many expressions of
consciousness that have not to this
point expressed themselves in physical
materiality. You can be their hands to
sculpt out of the electromagnetic energy
of physical reality a particular type of
sculpture through which their spirit and
idea and essence may be
representationally living in your
physical reality. You follow me? I like
that. I like that. It is in a sense an
art and that is what we perceive you can
project very strongly, very cleanly and
very purely with pure lines in any way,
shape or form you desire through
movement, through physical mass, through
color, through light, through
sound. Express the angelic art of the
utilization of energy itself in that
way. breathe
life into those works.
And are there beings that are like
guardian angels and that kind of thing?
They're in our mythology in our in our
religious dog. Yes, in a sense. But
again, remember that guides and
guardians do not live your life. They
simply nudge, right? Reflect, right?
They reflect, right? They hint. They
tap. They remind
ever so subtly and ever so lovingly.
Thank you very much, Bashar. Thank you
very much. And by the way, how are the
dolphins doing on Essani? They are
perfectly fine. Will they be put back to
Earth one day? Are they being programmed
in a sense? Not programmed. But many of
them do not want to go back. I could
understand that. Or not for the reasons
you may think. Simply that they are
content to await the idea of the
transformation to a certain point where
they know they will be joined by others
of their kind and by you. So that they
also will be able to welcome you to
foreign shores with something that you
might recognize as familiarity. Oh, I
like that. But some will come back to
help in our transformation. Oh,
telepathically all the time. They do not
have to physiologically come back in
order to be of assistance. That's true.
They are sending from where they are
quite strongly.
That's great. Thank you. Thank you very
much for sharing sharing.
Good evening Bash and to you. So my
question has to do about polarity.
Polarity. All right. The creation of it.
Today when I was thinking what kind of
came to me was
um okay using the biblical legend as a
vehicle maybe to for this little
exploration. All right. Go right ahead.
Any analogy will do. Okay. So I wondered
if if some kind of human conscious
decided to um okay man
manifest male female s okay so then
there was Adam Eve um in a sense s okay
if so Adam is Eve and Eve is Adam
because they kind of came from the same
s each contains both ideas right and so
with I don't really believe so much that
because of the temptation of some object
whatever this object was that created
this polarity I believe that it was the
polarity I believe that it was the
judgment of one of the
other are you following me yes this is
an analogy the so-called temptation the
idea of the tree of knowledge of
positive and negative is simply that
knowledge and experience of polarity
of limitation of high focus. So the
choice in a sense to go into a reality
and in a sense for a while lock
yourselves into a reality where you
would know positive and negative as
separate things rather than functioning
as an integrated being simply created
the so-called quote unquote fall. And
all that means is you lowered your
vibratory frequency so you could
experience a physical reality of
polarity. The idea of a fall is not a
judgmental one in that sense. It is
simply one of physics.
Ah well then
um why why would why did we want to do
that? I mean I hear things. Well,
because I well if it's why not then why
do we try to find out anything else?
Every experience is going on
simultaneously. Every experience this
you simply happens to be focused as this
particular idea at this particular point
in your timing. But the overall you is
having many experiences on many
different levels. Of course, it is part
and parcel of this particular level to
ask that kind of a question. Why am I
here in this one when all the rest of me
is somewhere
else? That is one of the things that
goes handinhand with this particular
type of experience. The ability to ask
that type of a
question. But the idea is that you did
wish to explore all corners if you will
of the universe. And this is one equally
valid with all other expressions also
also also also in exploring it in the
way that you have to such a high degree
of focus. You have had experiences that
are quite unique and in a sense not
really experienced by the vast majority
quote unquote of consciousness within
existence. So highly focused are you?
You have had discoveries and
perspectives and attitudes and creations
about yourself that well makes you quite
a magnet to many other civilizations who
are quite fascinated by the way you have
gone about creating your reality.
Also, this high degree of
focus represents vast change within
creation and all civilizations that are
connected to you, including ourselves.
You are catalysts. You are in very many
ways what has been termed agents of
change. You decided to explore the idea
of the transformational powers of this
particular physical dimension and you
have done it very well.
So now you are going to explode in ever
expanding spirals of knowledge and
experience to share with all other
beings that are connected with you
including us the ideas that you have
learned and how now to put them into the
expansion of creativity throughout the
universe. It is simply if you wish to
put it this way been an intensive study
course. Yeah. But that is a wonderful experience
Yeah. But that is a wonderful experience
and we thank you for the choice that you
have made. Okay. Does that answer your
question?
Yeah. There are more All right. All
right. There are more, shall we say,
pragmatic answers to this idea in terms
of representing your historical path as
a group consciousness. You can also
recognize that the idea of injecting
yourself into physical materiality, as
many of you know, can be a very
pleasurable idea. Many of you simply
found at one point or another that it
was let us
say unsuspected that the particular type of
unsuspected that the particular type of
injection into physical materiality that
you created would create a feedback loop
to keep you in physical materiality
longer than you originally anticipated.
However, now you have played out the
majority of that loop and now you have
recognized the ideas that you have
learned. So rather than simply playing
what if, play what is since you
obviously have made the choice to be in
the physical realities you have made,
play them out. It can be of great
benefit to all beings that interact with
you. All right. Okay. Thank you very much.
All right. Okay. Thank you very much.
Thanks, Ching.
Hi Bashar. Hi. I'm very glad I have a
chance to meet you and I've enjoyed so
much all the ideas that you've been
giving us these past. We enjoy
reflecting your ideas back to you.
Bashar. I have been working a long time
to improve the contact I have with my
soul. Oh, all right. And to improve the
contact you have with your soul. Yes.
Working a long time. Yes. The
um what I've been experiencing is that I
often feel um a sense of loneliness or
being cut off from it. Oh. And once in a
meditation I tried visualizing
uh from my soul's point of view how it
saw me. And it had the same feeling. It
felt like that my being here on the
physical world cut it off from me and it
wanted me back with it. Ah that is very
exciting. Do you know why you and your
soul have the same feeling?
I would like to know why. Oh, I'll tell
you frankly.
Because there is no difference between
you and your
soul. Only your human civilization has
made a distinction. You are your soul.
Your physical reality, your physical
body is your spirit. is your soul in
physical terms. So it was the same you
choosing to feel the same way. That's
why you got an answer from both sides.
That was the same. You are your soul.
There is no true connection that needs
to be made between you because you have
never really been separate except in the
illusions that you have created. You are
your soul. Surprise,
surprise. Now what do you think about
that? Well, that sounds good. Sounds good. All
Well, that sounds good. Sounds good. All
right. What else can it be besides
sounding good? Well, then why do I feel
this yearning to to connect with my
soul? That yearning is a yearning to be
the soul that you are. In other words,
to express your soulhood, express your
spirit, to express the you know yourself
to be. May I ask you a question, please?
Oh, thank you. Are you doing in your
life the things that excite you the
most?
I'm working on it. Working on it. All
right. Do you enjoy working on it, or
would you prefer to be doing the things
that excite you? Or is working on doing
them more exciting than doing them?
Either is fine. I'd rather do them.
All right, then. Why don't you?
Well, some some of them are a little
expensive, like traveling.
Abundance. Abundance. Remember, the
ability to do what you need to do when
you need to do it. Does not always have
to come with the tool of abundance your
society has taught you is the only tool
that represents your abundance. Can come
in many different ways. Doesn't always
have to take money. It can, nothing
wrong with that, but it doesn't always
have to. And sometimes money does not
represent the path of least resistance.
and the quickest way you can actually do
what you want to do.
So many of the things that are quote
unquote holding you back or keeping
these things away from you are your
assumptions based upon what you have
bought into from your society since
birth that you have to do it in a
certain way or it's not valid any other
way and you can't even imagine any other
way it can be done and will not let
yourself believe that there are a number
of other ways that it could come to
pass. What you need is to relax your
What you need is to relax your
definitions about how you become what
you think you want to become and start
acting like you actually are the thing
you want to become. As soon as you start
acting like the person you say you want
to become, you will start having the
type of life that person has. You will
attract to yourself all the things that
type of a person attracts in whatever
way, shape or form represents your path
of least
resistance. Do you know that many
individuals in your society as well,
surprise, surprise, actually do a lot of
traveling and never spend a scent?
Are you aware that that's actually a
possible thing to do? I've heard rumors
of that. Rumors. Distant rumors from far
across foreign shore. Now someone out
there is traveling around and having a
good time and not needing really much
money to do it because of what they are
doing. They simply are the definition
that requires perhaps a lot of traveling
and therefore one way or another the
traveling occurs simply because they are
someone who contains a definition that
requires a lot of traveling. So if money
is necessary, it comes to them. If the
circumstances will come without the
money, they come to them and allow them
to be the idea they choose to be. Allow
them to be the idea they are willing to
act like they are. So the idea basically
to explain it mechanically is to follow
what excites you at any given moment
because excitement is your physical
translation of the vibratory energy that
represents the path you chose to be.
Therefore, when things excite you,
contrary to what you have been taught by
your society, it is that excitement that
lets you
know this is the thing you actually can
do most
easily. This is the thing you actually
will be able to do most
abundantly. This is the thing that
represents most who you are and
therefore you will be able to accomplish
effortlessly. That is what excitement
lets you know. So why hold back when
something excites you? Act upon it with
your integrity. And every time you act
upon something that excites you, that is
the most exciting thing that you have
the ability to act upon at any given
moment, it will lead you automatically
into whatever circumstances are
necessary to give you the ability,
whatever that may be, to act upon the
next most exciting thing that will come
along. And that will usually be on an
elevated level. So if there is something
you would like to do that is very
exciting to you that you do not believe
you have the capability of doing now all
you need to do to create that capability
is act upon whatever you can act upon
that represents what excites you the
most at this particular moment and it
will this particular moment and it will
lead to every other idea because
excitement is a thread and it is one
continuous unbroken thread throughout
your entire life. So doing the things
that excite you the most is what your
purpose in life is all
about. You are reincarnational beings as
we have said many times. But the you you
are now only has one life to live
because you have never been this you
before and you will never be this you
again. Therefore, the fundamental purpose to
Therefore, the fundamental purpose to
this life is to live it to the fullest,
to be the fullest possible expression of
who you happen to be at this moment. And
the way you can do that most easily is
to do what excites the you that you are
the most. It's that simple.
most. It's that simple.
Now, we recognize that one of the
greatest difficulties your society has
in believing that you can do what
excites you the most is in believing
that it is that simple. Because your
society loves
complexity, love struggling. I really
earned this good time. I worked hard for
it. I suffered for years and years and
years so that now I could deserve a
little
happiness. All right, that's one way of
life. And if that's the way you prefer,
then work as hard as you want. And
perhaps someday you will give yourself
permission to earn happiness even though
of course you already deserve it just
because of who you are and you don't
really have to earn it at
all. So the universe lets you
know happiness if that's what you want
right now. Absolutely. We will not argue
with you. We will even assist you in
knowing what it is that would allow your
life to become absolutely effortless and
abundant. We will give you a clue. Call
it excitement if
you but that's how you know you are in
synchronous harmony with the idea that
represents most who you are at any given
moment. Is any of this making some
sense? And does it seem workable for
you? Yes. Thank you. If you simply act
upon it, we guarantee 100% you will
attract the circumstances that will
allow you to continue in that mode. It
never doesn't work. No exceptions, not
even
you. But the way to allow yourself the
full benefit of that positive effect is
to start functioning like the soul you
actually are. and stop assuming that it
is something somehow disconnected from
the you that you are. You are your soul
in physical terminology. That's all. So
be the soul you imagine yourself to be
and you will expand accordingly. You
follow? Yes. Thank you. You very much.
God bless you. And
you sharing.
Hi Bashar. How are you? Perfect on you.
Very good. Uh, I'd like you to give me
some information that's pertaining to my
life now. Whatever you think. Or just
anything? No. But anything? Uh, no.
About my career now. About your career
now? Yes. In the future. Oh, and the
future. Right. Right.
Didn't ask for the past as well. How
about the moon and the stars? Why not?
All right.
I will simply repeat the same question.
Is what you are doing as a career the
thing that really excites you?
Absolutely. Absolutely. Really? Yes.
Without a shadow of a doubt, right? Then
what are you asking me for? I'm asking
you for if it is that obvious to you,
what do I have to say? I know. No, I
thought you might have a message for my
teachers or something for me.
All right, here comes one.
[Laughter]
Hi. Having a wonderful
time. We see you are having a wonderful
time. See you soon. Keep up the good
fun. Okay.
Lovingly yours, your guide.
[Applause] C O
D now. Okay. What career pretel have you
created yourself to be? If you are
willing to share this with us. Uh I want
to get into med I am in the metaphysical
field as a hypnotherapist. All right.
Are you having a good time doing that? I
love it. Do you love being of service in
that way? Yes, I do. Do you find that
you attract into your life the things
that you need at any given moment? Yes.
Yes. Well, it's coming. Coming. Coming.
All right. Do you recognize that at any
given moment you really do have what you
really need to represent who you are
willing to be at that moment? Yes. All
right. So it is always one for one. Yes.
Right. All right. So the boldness and
the willingness that you
exhibit whatever you choose to expand in
whatever way you choose to expand it
will see the reflection of that
expansion in your outer
exterior reality.
May I ask you a question? Certainly.
What do you envision and what do you
imagine your art, your craft
transforming into in what you call the
future? Is there something coming up
that represents a different modality
that you would like to function in
different from what you are functioning
in now? Would you like to add something
or delete something or alter something,
use a different kind of a tool? Anything
I can do to improve myself? If any new
knowledge certainly is always welcome.
Uh
new knowledge about unconditional love.
That too. That too. All right. Okay. Uh
do you have a desire to express
unconditional love? Yes. Do you feel
that you do? Uh quite often. Quite
often. All right. All other times are
conditional.
Now does that
mean that therefore you do not express
unconditional love at all since there
are times when it is conditional? Well,
I don't think anyone uh you know
completely I mean we try but we have we
try or do we have our ups and downs.
That's life. Oh and that life
that's a song right? Okay. Whose life is
that? My life. Your life. All right. Do
you like ups and downs? Definitely ups.
Definitely. Definitely ups.
Do you recognize that you can continue
to create ups and still have challenges,
diversity, exploration, and discovery,
and that you don't need downs in order
to have variance in your life? Right.
Absolutely. All right. Then are you
saying you no longer prefer downs?
Right. Right. Just ups. Right. All
right. Then is that an unconditional choice?
Then is that an unconditional choice?
Yes. In other words, no matter in what
way, shape or form your life manifests
and attracts to you circumstances,
situations, and relationships, you are
willing to unconditionally assume that
everything that occurs in your life is
therefore a part of the ups and never a
part of the down. No, I I feel it's a
lesson. Lessons you go through, okay,
experiences, but lessons do not have to
be downs. No, that's right. Well, you
look at a look at a negative thing in a
positive way and turn it around and make
it positive. Yes. All right. Then that
is unconditional trust. If you simply
assume that everything is a part of the
positive path. Absolutely. Yes, I do.
All right. Okay. Then that is
unconditional trust and love. Okay. It
is that easy. Okay.
Now, one moment.
experiment a little if you have not
already done
so with a
tool that you call
fluorite. Do you find this might be fun?
Certainly. Oh, you don't have to do it
just because I suggest. No, no, sure.
All right. You may find yourself in
working with that tool discovering a
reflection, a trigger that allows you to
become more aligned with the actual
electromagnetic field by which you can create a stronger
field by which you can create a stronger
identification pattern with all the
individuals that you give assistance to
so that you can in a sense truly become
them, understand
understand
them and therefore reflect back to them
the idealized state. They can create
themselves to be and create an
electromagnetically conductive and
conducive atmosphere for them to
truly create revelations and spontaneous
awakenings within themselves even if
they simply come within your biological
field. Okay. Now I don't how fluoride in what
Okay. Now I don't how fluoride in what
way? I'm I don't understand that
exactly. Fluorite crystal. Oh. Oh, okay.
Okay. A bluish tinge. Okay. Can be of
best service to you to function as a
trigger to align you to that particular
electromagnetic frequency and therefore create that
frequency and therefore create that
spark between any gap that is imagined
between you and those you
serve. So that you can immerse
yourselves in one fluid and know
yourselves as one
interaction, not polarities, but one
interaction so that you can intertwine
in an act of love. And that act of love
will center and automatically heal
anyone you come in contact
with. Because only those that would be
willing to participate in that act of
unconditional love would be attracted to
you. You follow me? Yes. Does this
excite you? Absolutely. Then happy
swimming. Okay. Thank you very much. We
can also suggest that perhaps some play
in water would be of benefit for you and
tune you in to other vibratory
frequencies, particularly the dolphins,
that can also assist you because the
dolphins have a very strong healing
art. Very strong. And you may find
yourself interacting with them and
actually having in a sense telepathic
discussions about ideas just with your
imagination that can be of best
assistance to you in much the same way
that the dolphins were of assistance to
healers in Adalante times by telling
them of the things of the sea that would
work for them as tools in their
healing. So swap tails.
Yes, you may take that in more than one.
Thank you. Yeah, thank you very much.
Really appreciate it. And we appreciate
you very much. Thank you. Sharing. Good
day, Bashar. And to you. Um you've said
before that
everything that happens in the world and
in our lives um we have created. Yes.
And it's one way or another
unconsciously or consciously. Yeah. And
it's all symbolic of something
basically. Yeah. All physical reality is
a symbol for the ideas that you are
creating yourself to be. For the
interaction that you are creating
yourself to be with yourself at any
given moment.
Everything. No exception. Every little
thing. Every little thing. Now,
different things may have quote unquote
relative degrees of immediate
significance to you, but it can be no
other way other than your willingness to
co-create a situation with other
individuals and you have created every
little thing in it. It is absolutely no
accident that you are wearing, what you
are wearing in interacting with this
group, the colors you are wearing, what
you are saying, how you are standing. No
accident. It is a part of the
orchestration. It may have relative
degrees of importance to different
individuals. But by you being who you
are, you create a backdrop against which
all other individuals can understand who
they are. So it is not an accident.
follow me. Yeah. Yeah. There just seem
like there's so many little things that
happen in life that just I can't see any
um symbolic meaning in Again, they may
not be immediately pertinent to you, but
nonetheless, you form a part of the
symphony. Any one note may not
necessarily know why it is sitting next
to another note but from the whole scope
it is necessary to create the melody
that comes out of the entire symphony.
You follow me? Yeah. So you do not
always have to have analytical awareness
of the symbology of every little thing
in order to simply know that you are
supporting that framework for yourself
and everyone else by being who you are.
Okay. Does that assist you? Yes, I will
think about that more. Oh, all right.
Have a wonderful time. Thank you. All
your thoughts will be added to the
collective idea of who you all are.
Thank you,
Shann. Hi, Rashard. Hi. Um, I kind of like to
Hi, Rashard. Hi. Um, I kind of like to
explore the area about our three
children that we have. All right. We
have three daughters. And the middle one
seems to be of a different energy than
the oldest and the youngest daughter.
All right.
Um, it is not that unusual. I know. Um,
but I just wondered if you share
something with me about the same
building as you do have.
The middle can function as a fulcrum for
the balance beam on which the other two
are sitting. Each one perhaps being a
sitting. Each one perhaps being a
representative of an extreme idea with
the one in the center
functioning as what you call a random
element to allow the triad that they are
to experience motion. So it is not
simply a static polarity sitting there
staring at itself. The third creates the
ability for the peak, the fulcrum on
which the balance beam can teeter and
allow motion to occur. Things being
played and exchanged back and forth from
the two polarities on the end through
the fulcrum in the middle. So in a sense
the middle child usually is the one who
soaks up all that is going on for either
child on either end and can use it in
very unusual and creative ways as a
result because they are in a sense the
facilitator the communication beacon
between the other two on different
levels. You follow it, right? I do.
Um one have been very very sick for the
last two
days. And the middle one told me that um
her fever that she had gotten she got
while she was on Mount Sha. All right.
And I was wondering is there anything
you could tell me about that? simply
that when individuals open up to more
energy than they may have been used to,
sometimes that energy will be felt as a
friction in the body if they do not
think that their body can handle it. And
the pouring of a faster energy through a
slower body can cause friction which can
translate as fever. When the energy is
acclimated to then the vibrations will
be balanced, they will be matched. There
will be no friction. There will be no
fever. It is simply symbolically
representative of going up another notch
so to speak, climbing another mountain,
so to speak. Okay. Also, my husband and
I did the workshop and as you know
things can get a
little unnormal. Unnormal.
Yes. You see that was the whole idea of
the workshop to create unnormality so that
workshop to create unnormality so that
you could once again center on your
naturalenness rather than your normaly
right well you're simply out of practice
being natural boy that's that's for
sure but our children seem to be going
through this also and they do the
workshop but they are your children and
therefore you are one relationship ship
and they have done similar things many
times and they absorb things directly
from you and they reflect them back to
you and in a sense they are acting like
little safety valves letting off some of
the steam that you would not be able to
really handle. Good. You follow me. Boy,
do I. All right.
Um that's Thank you. I I appreciate
you're sharing that with me and I just
want to say I love you very much. I
would love you very much. One
suggestion, stand around with your
family in a circle and all breathe and
exhale very deeply into the center,
creating a new atmosphere that can
support you all and letting some of that
energy flow through you. All right. Oh,
that'd be Do not keep it all bottled up.
Good. Thank you very much. Thank you for
your family reunion.
Sharing. Good evening, Bishar. And to
you. I'd like to thank you for the
recognition and connection with the
Kacina energy. Well, thank you. And also
that the ending of the Aztec calendar,
if I may share with
everyone, is a symbol of people
beginning to create their own time. Yes.
Colloquially, once again, the idea of
the convergence. Thank you. Thank you
very much for your willingness to
participate in such an exciting time
upon your planet. My question which is
for you but also for everyone here is
simply how may I serve you? You
go for all of you serve us already by
simply doing in your life what excites
you the most. Thank you. Thank you very
much. Shedding.
Shedding.
Good evening. And do you? Oh, good. I
could use a little bit of help. All
right. Okay. I had reconnected with a I
originally thought it was a group called
the But you want this help from me.
Yeah. And anybody else you can pull in. No.
And anybody else you can pull in. No.
All right. Anybody else you can connect
in with? All right. Feel free. Okay.
Good. It was called the my impression
was called the golden ring. Golden ring.
The less associated a little bit less
associated. Golden wind. Golden wind.
Okay. And then I reconnected with him
again recently. Less than about a year then
recently. Less than about a year then
touched back into me again. Connected in
what way? Uh just reconnected like
started communicating again.
Telepathically. Telepathically.
And then uh at the original time I
thought that it was a non-physical or
out of the universe existence and that
some members of the group had come to a
physical existence and then they had
gotten lost and then I had come to kind
of help them get out you know but then
my impression more recently u changed.
It changed from like being a group to
like being I was an aspect of the golden
ring like the expression came as I am of
the golden ring. can be a group can be
one idea. Okay, these are not
contradictions and that uh the purpose was to try to uh
and that uh the purpose was to try to uh
find the beings and also any that like
the beings had gotten stuck so to speak
in a physical existence so to speak and
then I also had the impression maybe it
was a just a fun game same thing to do
and I had come to so the whole thing
bowls around I'm trying to find out what
who your fellow club members are not so
much that is trying to resolve
of what do I want to do in a
metaphysical way with my life you know
right now does not have to be in a
metaphysical way I mean there are
individuals who have never heard the
term metaphysics who are living quote
unquote very full lives in every sense
of the
word so it does not necessarily have to
come with that connotation simply to be
the living of a full life doing what
excites you the most
Okay. But I had I was still trying to
follow along with this path that I had
brought with me. Yes. Well, all the
clues will drop into place when they
need to. It is perhaps a part of the
spice that you feel is necessary to lure
you into different areas of
investigation so that you will learn the
things you need to learn about yourself.
I feel I've like I'm already doing it,
but I can't seem to sort it out a bit.
You know, will it sort what out? sorting
out what I'm doing and trying to figure
out what it what excites me the most and
which way to go.
Excitement's a little bit is a little
bit confusing. All right. Well, why are
you here this evening of your time? Did
it excite you to come here? Yeah. All
right. What will be most exciting for
you to do when this interaction is over?
Most exciting? Yes. Will you go home?
I'll go home and go to sleep. The most
exciting thing, but that's what I'm
going to do.
All right. If something came along that you
right. If something came along that you
thought were more exciting, would you do
that? Yeah.
All right. Are you sure?
Well, perhaps. Oh, perhaps. All right.
You see, the idea is to keep it simple
and take it one step at a time. When we
talk about the things that excite you
the most, we are not always referring to
the idea of having to know the thing
that excites you the most in my entire
life that I will ever conceive of. It
simply means the thing that excites you
the most right now.
Right now. Right now. For some reason, it
now. Right now. For some reason, it
doesn't seem to
uh satisfy me. Doesn't excite you, huh?
Does Yeah, it doesn't satisfy me. It's
like I have done and I have the ability
to do several things and what is called
meditation. I can I have channelneled
for some period of time. I
can heal people. Yes. Without you know
this is all channeling. Remember that
channeling is only doing what you really
love to do.
You know I like doing it. It's it's like
what else do you think you wish to be
doing? I don't know. I'm trying to sort between
I don't know. I'm trying to sort between
the May I ask you another question.
Okay. Why must you assume that you
should be doing something differently
other than what you are doing?
It just seems that I'm not putting
enough um I do the things that excite me
a
relatively small part of my life.
Why not make them your whole life? Well,
that's what I came here to try and sort
it out. Well, what is there to sort out?
All you have to do is act upon the
opportunities that present themselves in
your life that excite you and then you
will be doing all the things that really
excite you. Do you not believe that's
possible? That's true. But the No, I I had
That's true. But the No, I I had
realized something while I'm waiting and
that is part of the thing I had rejected
for it was the healing of like non no
you know spiritual healing of people.
Yes, because I have a consideration that
I was wanted to let the people heal
themselves. They always do, right?
Always. But for them to realize that on
a conscious level instead of being in
the position of healing someone and then
you have uh someone perhaps worshiping
you. Well, why don't you simply say
after you have assisted in the healing,
you know, you did that, not me. You
allowed me to assist you. You allowed me
to create a conducive atmosphere in
which you gave yourself permission to
heal yourself. But you did that. That's
how powerful you are. You
see, now why don't you share that
information with them? Okay, I can do
that. Well, yes, you can. And one more
little thing. Oh, all right. Is it
become from your description of the the
cacina? Yeah. It seems I don't know if
we're all related in here. It just seems
that there's some connection. I might
have some connection. It just seems so
close. Then follow your instinct. Follow
your imagination. wherever and whenever
it may take you. Your imagination is
there for a reason. Start relying on it
a little more often, perhaps all the
time if you wish. Use your instincts. If
your instincts tell you that
individuals in that sense are healing
themselves, share the good news with
them. If your imagination and instincts
tell you there's a connection here with
this kacina energy thing, follow it.
Follow it up. Follow your
nose and you will discover exactly where
you need to be. You see, the idea of
doing the thing that excites you the
most is
all hinged upon that word
doing. This is a world of action that
you live in. So when you have a gut
hunch, when you have the instinct and
intuition and imagination to know what
you're all about, act like it.
and act like it fully carry through the
entire idea. You don't have to be a
healer that quivers at the thought that
somebody else might give you your their
power away in that sense to you and that
you might be worshiped in that sense.
You don't have to be that definition of
a healer if that's not what you prefer
to be. So don't act like that definition
of a healer and you will not find
individuals coming up to you saying,
"Please take my power. Please take my
power." Simply say, "No, thank you. I
have enough of my own.
That's yours. I can't use it anyway.
You follow me? Yes. Create the
environment and the attitude that you
wish to create so that the interactions
that take place will all take place
within that attitude within that
environment. Why assume it must take place in any
Why assume it must take place in any
particular way? It will take place in
the way you prefer it to take place.
Okay. It is that simple.
I want where you have any idea where to
follow up the kachina energy or any way
you have an idea they have ideas listen
to their ideas pick the one that moves
you the most follow your instinct follow
your imagination now when you first
heard the idea of the kacina energy what
pictures did you get
I don't know if I have any pictures of
such I what I immediately picked up on
it though I connected on it the first
time I heard it All right. And I felt
there was a connection there. Create a
picture now. Think, Kacina. What do you get? Any
now. Think, Kacina. What do you get? Any
images at all? Like a big bright light.
A big bright light. All
right. Does the light have a name? Does
it have a direction?
It doesn't appears to be like a like a
circular pattern. No. All right. Like
from
All right. Like from a sun. Like from
your son. All
right. What does the symbology of the
sun represent to you in terms of the
places upon your planet?
Source of energy, light, the places upon
your planet. The sun. I don't
understand. Try it again.
When I say sun, what is the first place
you think of? Up. Up. Looking up.
Looking up. All right. One more time.
Places upon your planet. Okay. Ready?
Okay. Sun.
Sun. Central America. All right. Central
America on the Yucatan. Maya. Maya. All right.
on the Yucatan. Maya. Maya. All right.
in the Mayan area then. Do you feel like
going there?
Yeah, I felt like going there several
times. I haven't
u I've been slow. I don't think I've
ever been exactly in the mall. I've been
to Costa Rica
and Panama, but never I mean I go to
Mexico all the time. All right. But I
haven't been to that part of Mexico. All
right. Do you feel you need to go to
that part of Mexico or are the parts
that you visit sufficient?
What about new Mexico as opposed to old
Mexico? Anything there? Any bells? I
like Arizona. You like Arizona? Why do
you like Arizona?
I've been reading about Arizona. It was
a Oh, you've been reading about it?
Arizona and I visited there several
times. There was a interesting enough
there was a a tribe of engineers called
the Anastasis who disappeared in Arizona
about 1300. Yes. And what interests you
so much about that? Just that part of
the legend is that they may have
traveled to a different dimension. Did
they return to a dimension from which
they had come? Well, wouldn't you like
to find out if that's so?
That's interesting. Yeah, that's
interesting. I'm still more I'm more
interested in the me what I'm doing. Me
doing it. What makes you think that's
not a part of you? No, that's true.
And what makes you think that what
you're doing won't find connections
there? That's true. You see, the idea is
to begin to look at everything as a part
of what you are doing. If it interests
you at all, there must be a reason for
why it interests you. Yes.
So follow it. It may not play out as you
expect, but you will get out of it what
you need to be who you are. You follow
me? Yes.
There will be more information coming to
you very soon. Not from us but from
another source.
Thank you. Thank you.
Hello Bashar. Howdy straw. How you
doing?
You know what?
It is wonderful that we can talk at this
moment. Is it? You're right. Yes. But I
have something to share with you. Go for
it. Now, we have spoken many times about the
Now, we have spoken many times about the
idea of doing the things that really
excite you. Yes. Yes. And we have spoken
many times about different ways of
manifesting these ideas into your
physical reality. Yet we have done that.
All right. No way, shape or
right. No way, shape or
forward are we calling up any
shortcoming on anyone's
part. However, however,
here it comes. I can now give you a
little bit bigger
hint than I was capable of doing before.
I'm glad your capabilities increased.
Oh, thank
you. This is only a reflection of your
own increased capabilities and
awareness. Remember the strawberry patch on
Remember the strawberry patch on
Esani. Oh, very well. And you know how
you are dearly waiting to experience the
planting of the strawberries in that
patch with us. No, no more. Ah, no more.
Why not? Well, I can simultaneously be
planting them with you. My awareness is
expanding into that area. Ah, yes, that
is so. However, there is one idea you
may have missed. Yes.
Why not plant the patch on earth first?
Lovely. So that there is a doorway at
both gates. I like it. You see, that is
what we are really saying in terms of
playing out your dreams. Play them out
where and when you can.
And that is what brings the full dream
into contact with itself. But until
there is a matching vibration on this
end, this end has nowhere to go.
Well, you know, the the patch will be
planted very shortly. Well, that's up to
you. That is up to you. But we would
find it most exciting if you would. I
will. Thank you. May I ask my question?
Yes. Traditionally in our culture as masters
Traditionally in our culture as masters
of limitation, Yes. We have
created welldefined focus in being
separate from individuals and and I
think the manifestation of physically
separate to the point where when we when
someone dies or someone goes in a
direction that uh dimension out of our
dimension we experience loss
we experience loss
or the feeling this particular emotion
that is defined as loss, grief, sadness
the feeling of missing the individual.
Yeah. And I've been practicing and at
times very well able to get the feeling
of them not being separate. Yet there is
still the nonfocused physical
dimensionality when someone is Yes.
Okay. I would like some uh suggestion in
accelerating the transition to the point
where it is as physically satisfying as
when they are physically present. Do you
like what you call the traditional form
of meditation? That is sitting
quietly, closing your eyes, centering
yourself, and truly stretching out with
your imagination. Yes, I like it very
much. All right. Then what you can begin
to do when you are rested, not when you
are tired, when you are rested, but
still in a very dreamy state.
This is especially good when you are not
in an excessive need for a nap, but
nonetheless take a nap during the day.
Then, as you simply drift and float in
your imagination, begin to defocus
yourself and project yourself into their
reality or what you imagine it to
be. And therefore, go to them on their
terms. And you will begin to feel your
And you will begin to feel your
heartstrings being played by those
consciousnesses. And you will know very
certainly beyond a shadow of a doubt
that they are there and you can speak
with them. But you see the idea is more
often than not that you will speak
through the heart once they are in that
defocused state.
So we simply suggest that you expand and
diffuse the idea of your limited focus
of yourself and play their game. In that
sense, meet them halfway rather than
assuming that they have to come all the
way back to let you know they're still
around. In other words, create a
vibratory frequency that is in harmony
with their go to the
threshold between both worlds.
Yes. and also the strawberry
patch. Create that reflection on your
end of what you imagine that end to be
like. And then you will be able to meet them
And then you will be able to meet them
halfway because you will begin to speak
their language. You see, many times
individuals do quote unquote make an
attempt to communicate back to physical
reality, but no one's
listening because they do not listen
with their
heart. because they do not listen in the
same way that they are speaking in that
diffused and open manner, non-focused
manner. So enjoy those imaginations and you will
So enjoy those imaginations and you will
begin to hear the music from the other
side. That's fascinating. This also
applies you know I noticed that for
instance when an individual who is in
physical dimensionality is separate from
me
that the difficulty in the apparent
difficulty in getting them is because I am imposing
in getting them is because I am imposing
a particular structure. Oh life
very interesting. So that that yeah so
the allowing the particular way in which
they need to manifest to defocus and
then allowing mutual creation outside of
our individual focus.
Yeah, I I see where you're going. Do not
be afraid to really redefine the
reality. Oh, so you're interacting with me now
Oh, so you're interacting with me now
remotely. E
you follow me? I do. Because to a
positively oriented being everything is
an interaction of one type or another
because that's all there
is. Interaction is all there is. The
is. The
individuals doing the
interacting are the interaction that
creates the apparent illusion of
individuals doing the interacting.
M you are the interaction. So how can
you possibly be separate
a coin cannot have one side. Yes,
it is again recreating that awareness
rather than the traditional awareness is
very good. So all you need is a little
more boldness with your definition.
Lovely. Thank you my friend. Thank you
very much. My pleasure.
getting.
Hi. Hi. Um, I'm wondering if you can
clarify something for me. Lately, I
don't know. Okay, let's see if we can
work on this together. Lately, I You can
work on it. Okay. All of it.
Lately, I've been feeling um a
mechanical kind of uh metal feeling
coming through my crown chakra and
playing out and trying feeling as though
it's breaking through my throat. All
right. Okay. And I'm wondering if that
is a channeling or if that is the
beginning of a channeling. And I'm
wondering if my uh ear and throat
problems that I've had for the past year
is a result of me not allowing that to
come through in some way to some degree,
but it is also a memory to some degree.
It is a connection of a past life
memory. And some of it has to do with
orals as you call them that you created
in those lives that have to do with
listening and speaking and a fear to do
so again so that you will be put through
the same
ordeal. You follow it
now? In a sense, it is more of yourself
breaking out of the
shell. And some of those cracks can feel
like a strain for a while until you
recognize that the shell has the ability
to expand rather than
break. Get a little more rubbery. If you
feel this energy to be so mechanical,
get a little more rubbery.
You follow me? I can soften it in that
way for yourself. It is never going to
push faster than you are capable of
taking. But you may be creating the
assumption that it is doing so and
therefore creating the so-called
difficulty that you are having now.
What would you say if you would allow
yourself to say what you know that
energy would say?
I would say the teachings and the
experiences that I've had in this
lifetime, what I'm conscious of and uh
the duality of of what I'm aware of of
what happened. Repeat after me.
2 [Applause]
All a reminder for you. More laughter in
your life. More
life. More
laughter resonating in those
cabins. More laughter.
laughter.
Relax the muscle in your throat.
Relax the
glands. Relax the secretions.
Let yourself be
lubricated. Let yourself be smooth as
oil. Let yourself be honey
thick but not
choked nor guide.
Let yourself breathe the sweet
atmosphere of the knowledge and the
light and the beauty that you are and
smell the flower and the
fragrance in nature. That
fragrance in an herbalistic way can
assist in
clearing and purifying and freshening
and opening. Some ideas of
opening. Some ideas of
mint. Some ideas of evergreen for
you. Very
strong. Evergreen. Very
strong. Breathe the evergreen air.
Breathe the ever green air. Light energy
Light energy
is yours. Dip into the well and drink of
its pure crystallin
water. Drink and refresh and soothe the
parched ideas that you have come out of.
The desert is
over. You follow me. Thank you.
Rejoice in the evergreen
air on the high slopes of the
mountain. We thank you. Pleasant
dreams. At this timing, you may all
enjoy a short break. We will resume
contact. momentarily.
I don't see any. Continue.
Hello, Bashar. And to you. I'd like to
share something. All right. By all
means. Yeah. Last week, I had a
realization that about my dream I'd had
the the morning before. I I had uh I've
been dreaming that it was Saturday
morning and I had this whole day to
doeth as I pleased. And I was going to
go to the good earth and eat breakfast
and read for a while. And then my alarm
went off at 5:30. Remind me this was a
work day. I thought that was just
interesting. But what I realized
was the job I had last year. I was
working about 6 hours a day. I had a lot
of time actually. And uh but I was so
aberated on the subject of time. I
wouldn't even ride my bike to work cuz
it took an extra 10 minutes. I had
computer programs and every one of them
took too long. I was just going nuts on
the subject of time. All right. And uh
so recently I've had a job working 7 to
7 and driving over the hill 40 minutes
each way. And I realized from the dream
that I really I don't I'm not hung up on
this time anymore. I got all the time in
the world. Yes, you do. All the time in
the universe. All the time in creation.
I I really because you created, right? I
realize I think it was because something
I heard on one of the tapes where you'd
pointed out to someone that they were
overextending yourself. Anyway, whatever it was, I'd
yourself. Anyway, whatever it was, I'd
like to thank you for that reflection
because it hasn't been improving the
quality of my life on Thank you for
choosing to do so. Thank you for
allowing us to be a part of your choice
in that way. Okay. Thank you. You are
welcome. Sure.
Sure.
Hi, Bashar. Hi. Um
Um
Um He's waiting for me to finish
laughing. That will never
That will never
end. Be waiting long time.
Um I'm I'm at a basic standstill. A
basic [Laughter] [Laughter]
standill. All
right. Is that off the shelf? No clue.
No clue.
Um, can you say there is a space that I
like being in more than any other, which
is
feeling like everything is equal. Yes.
That there is absolutely no big deal.
Yes. None. Yes. And yet and yet I always
go back to little issues that distance
me from that like reputation.
Reputation. You know, I play out in my
mind's eyes. What if? What if I did
something absolutely horrendous? All
right. You know, d in order to really
understand for myself what unconditional
love really means. All right. You're
playing what if. What about So what?
Yeah.
What if I did something really
horrendous? Well, so what?
What if? So
what? Yeah. Okay. Um,
I guess it's just a matter of me really
believing that it can be a matter of you
simply trusting your conscious
commandment. Really believing that you
have the conscious ability to do what
you prefer to do and that if you
consciously know what you prefer to do,
there is no reason to assume that you
will do what you don't prefer to do
because your conscious commandment has
that much power.
Is it perhaps a matter of believing you
simply consciously have that ability
that you can simply know what you're
going to do and what you're not going to
do?
No, I think it's a matter of willingness
to even act. Willingness to act at all
because I am sick of being within
judgment and very much crossing my arms
and saying I'm not budging until I
really feel free without judgment. I
mean not it doesn't have to be complete
100% free of judgment but enough so that
I want to
act. You see the paradox of this
situation is is that standing still
therefore is a judgment on
everything. Acting is the sessation of
the judgment. But you must act in order
to cease the judgment. If you stand
still while you are waiting to be free
of judgment, you are compounding your
judgmental interest. because you are
refusing to act upon the things that
motivate you. And that is a judgment in
and of
itself. You follow?
I mean, I'm sure you're right, but I
don't really You don't have to be sure I
am right. The idea simply is is that
judgment is the sessation of action. It
is the invalidation of motion. It is the
idea of ultimate limitation and
confinement. So refusing to act in that
sense is the ultimate judgment on every
single one of those actions you
represent and do understand represents
your interests in life. The action the
trust of the action is the sessation of
the judgment of that
action. Okay. Um, too simple. No.
Uh, okay. I have another one to move on
to. Um, you speak of integrity a lot.
Yes. Um, when I when I was taught what
Um, when I when I was taught what
integrity was all about. Yes. To me it
was taught in a negative way or at least
I for me it was a negative way to say
it. The way the way it was told me was
which I broke out of later and later had
miracles and no judgment. The way it was
told me was um well, you can't possibly
love yourself if you're not acting
within your own integrity. I see. And
thus, one becomes or I did a bit of a
robot. Cuz at first it was wonderful to
be in touch with that. Afraid to be a
rogue. E huh. Afraid to be a
rogue. You know those individuals that
do all sorts of what you call dastardly
things and think they're just grand.
I am just wonderful. Look at all these
horrendous things I have done.
You can at least like yourself a lot
even if you are a rogue. Right. Okay.
That was the biggest issue that that I I
had bought into that extensively for
like 3 years. Yeah. And now
No. Now I don't think that I really buy
into it. Well, all right then. Why the
cessation of
action? Do you really
believe? It is all right if you really
do. But do you really believe that you
would choose to create something
horrendous? No. Not if No. Well,
then then what stops you?
I don't know. I think lack of desire.
Oh, lack of
desire. All right. So you're saying
nothing interests you whatsoever except
perhaps standing still for the moment.
Right. Do you find standing still
fascinating? Sort of. Sort of. All
right. Do you understand what
absolutely perfect standing still
represents?
Something like ultimate action or blah
blah blah. Innocent blah blah blah.
I could not have said it better myself.
They have discussed the idea that when
you are moving at infinite speed and are
everywhere at once, the same feeling of
standing perfectly still is created.
Well, I think that's where my desire for
accepting all experiences, not just
experiences that are within integrity.
That's why all these dastardly things,
you know, all right. All right. We
understand to some degree what you are
going through in the sense that you are
now collecting and recognizing in the
collection of all things everywhere.
Yeah. That you do accept the negative as
well as the positive side of yourself.
But accepting that balancing that and
blending that has absolutely nothing at
all to do with what portion of that you
choose to manifest. Okay. But what are
these I mean I'm with you on that. I
would not choose to do that most likely.
Let me just leave that little bit open
for the moment. All right. Um um I don't
know. There's just there's something
about it that is not ringing great for
me. It might have something to do with
the way I was taught about integrity.
But there's always that though I would
prefer probably not to. Right. It just
seems like wouldn't it be an
invalidation to say not to? Wouldn't it
be invalidating to say don't behave out
of integrity?
Well, in a sense it is judgmental. Yes.
But the idea is simply a matter of
recognizing what you prefer to do and
whether or not you are actually
exemplifying what you say you want or
whether you are in a sense fighting your
own integrity, fighting your own
ecstasy, whether you are creating a
so-called contradiction or
not. Going upstream, going with the
flow. Yes, in a sense it is judgmental to tell
Yes, in a sense it is judgmental to tell
an individual that is fighting their
ecstasy, don't do
that. But it is not judgmental to say,
you know, you don't have to do that.
Absolutely. All right. And there is many
many many ideas that certainly can be
explored in the act of standing still.
So perhaps you are excited about
exploring all the different ideas, the
multi-dimensionality that comes out of
the act of standing still. For if you
are in that sense choosing to stand
still, then in a sense that's an act.
Mhm. It is an action. Now if you quote
unquote use it after having made the
choice that you will stand still, then
you can use it in positive ways. And the
act of standing still does not have to
be an act of
belligerance. So you can transform even
the idea of standing still into an act
of creative expansion and explosion.
Perhaps it is simply that you will go
ultimately inward instead of expressing
yourself outwardly for a while.
Okay. I think it also has something to
do with this feeling that somebody is
watching me. You know that when nobody
is watching you. Yeah. Other than
myself. Everyone is watching you.
But I think you know what I mean. There
is that that sense of I haven't really
let go of the fact that it's me that
will ultimately look at my life yada
yada yada yada
yada yada yada yada
yada. Fascinating language.
[Laughter] Why does it bother you this idea that
Why does it bother you this idea that
someone is watching? Because I feel that
I would be more likely to perform and
that's something that I would much
prefer not to be doing if you know what
I mean. I know the whole thing, the
whole karma, the whole this, the whole
that. I know you've clarified karma to a
great degree, guys. But I don't know.
Somehow it's still there's still that
reputation to uphold. It's I don't feel
free to honestly do whatever I want to
be doing. I still feel
doing I still feel a little bit like
like it really you know there are
limitations there are whatever there are
all right of course you know you are
absolutely free to feel that way okay
well that all right thank
[Laughter]
you one moment While you
While you
are standing
still, one suggestion can be to
function as a singularity. Are you
familiar with the term? Yes, I am.
See what happens if in your imagination
while you are standing still you
function as that singularity and see if
you propel yourself through yourself
into another
universe. See who you meet. Have
dialogues with all that you
do. And you can go on a wondrous
journey that will create the type of
conversation that will allow you to come
to terms with the idea of who is doing
the watching and who is being
watched. And when you find them both to
be
yourself, then we shall see where you
choose to go from
there. But play as you will. You are
free to do anything. Even consider
yourself not
free. That is how powerful you are. All
of you. That is what being a creator
means. Pleasant dream. Thank you, Shannon.
Shannon.
Hello, Bashar. Hello. I'm very, very
happy to be here tonight. I've known for
a long time that I'm from Orion and um I
miss it terribly and so this is very
exciting to me. Well, you have lots of
friends with Yes, I know.
That's that's part of what I wanted to
ask is um since I was very little, I
knew that I belonged in Los Angeles and
have been drawn to uh the movie
industry. And through hits and misses,
I've been in and out of the area. Now
I'm back permanently and lately
um I've connected incredibly um in my
office building and with people who I
recognize as old friends and there are
some with me tonight and others from
Orion who it who say yes I'm from Orion.
You know it's like hey I'm from De Moine
and it's it's fabulous. What planet is
that? [Laughter]
[Laughter]
Well you know it stick around. and we'll
show it to you sometime. Oh, thank you.
You're welcome. But, uh, it's it's
tremendously exciting and all of us are
feeling a tremendous connection and a
sense of urgency and a sense of
anticipation and like even that
electrical storm last Saturday seemed to
affect all of us in such an incredible
way. It's not what you call your
ordinary storm. It was a great release
of electromagnetic activity in your
consciousness. Well, all of us have been feeling the
Well, all of us have been feeling the
results of that. And I'm I'm fascinated
with as I said the connection even in
this office building where we are in
this particular hallway where we're
working. We're all coming together and
it's exciting. Yeah. Tremendously
exciting. Is there something
electrifying? Yes.
So is there something that we're going
to be working on? Is there something in
the movie industry because this is
centered by Universal Studios. Is there
something because that's what I feel
drawn to is is there something
there's a powerful uh influence of the
movie industry on people. Yes. And um
I'd like to be connected with that. Is
is there something coming up that Yes.
Yes. What if you please
only that individuals as we perceive it
are moving into position and will
co-create at least three
manifestations, three expressions you
call film that will function as a trilogy, as
film that will function as a trilogy, as
a triad that will take many individuals
to another level
altogether because they will be util
utilizing the medium, pun
intended, for what can be truly gotten
out of it. They will understand the
interreationship between matter and
mind. And in this
way, transformation can truly be
transformation can truly be
created at the flick of a switch.
Now the structure of the
message can be gleaned out of all the
individuals present that you are
associated with and in recognizing those
that also are connected to the pattern
and in looking at the pattern
itself and in recognizing the entire
story.
One having to
do with the
origins, one having to
transformations and one having to do
with the integrated result. One, two,
three.
I hope I will be connected with that in
some way. Why hope? I will be connected.
You are connected. I am connected. or
you would not have the capacity to ask
the question you have asked
for you would never know about it. Well,
I feel this is what I've been drawn to
for many many years as
Thank you very much. Thank you very
much. Be creative. Trust your instincts.
Use integrity. It is what the whole
Orion idea now is all about. The
blending of the polarities of the old
negative and the new positive into a new
light. A new balance, a new home.
Earth, you follow me? Yes. Thank you
very much. Oh, thank you very
much. Shutting.
Thank you, Bashar. I I'm sitting there
just laughing because I I responded when
you said about creating gateways here on
Earth so that we can link up with the
gateways on your planet I see and
elsewhere throughout the universe the
infinite universe and what um the little
piece that I've been carrying around
building it gradually for six years I've
been calling the best game on earth the
goal of the best game on earth is to
create peace prosperity, health,
security, well-being, joy on Earth
together by the year 2000. Sounds like
fun, doesn't it, though? And the game is
basically an interactive media game
which involves television and radio and
print media where we tell the true story
of real people's lives and real entities
lives as we live out our lives joyfully
and uh start piecing together this new
reality that has been talked about a
great deal here and in other places
around the the country uh and I'm
certain throughout the universe. Nice.
and then having a 900 number up on the
screen. If you want to get involved,
call and then begin to uh let people
organize themselves into the new pattern
so that people can go where they will
most gain out of this game. And uh it
just when you just this last little
segment here, it was just such a
beautiful little alignment. You know,
people are getting into position and I'm
sitting there, you know, on the runway,
you know, coming down into position. I
must I'm about to take off. Yeah, as it
were. You know, so I want to thank you
for this opportunity to share this and I
would just like to say that I'd like to
work with you and with other people. You
already are, aren't you? Absolutely. I'm
thrilled. Thanks. Thank you. More power
to you. And to you,
shedding.
Hi Bashar. Hello.
I have a question about meditation. Oh,
what? I'd like to know how I can open up
more to med uh in my meditations. How I
What are you doing now? Um I'm using
some audio tapes sometimes in the
mornings and and in the evenings and
then I'm also meditating on my own. Do
you like bells?
Yes. You like tones? Yes. You like
color? Yes. You like light? Mhm. You like
Yes. You like light? Mhm. You like
sweets scented breezes. Yes. Do you love
animals? Yes. You love trees? Mhm. You love water
Yes. You love trees? Mhm. You love water
and all of nature?
Yeah. You like mountains? Yes.
Like to climb on rocks? Let them support
you and uplift you. Mhm. To the sky.
Yeah. Can you imagine leaping off that
mountaintop, spreading your wings like a
bird, and flying and soaring, floating
upon the breeze? Can you imagine these
things? Mhm. Then do you not see that
you have the primary tool right in your
imagination to take you wherever,
however, whenever you wish to
go? Yes. Do you not trust that your
imagination is the fundamental tool of
all meditation?
I think I haven't been trusting myself
enough. No. All
right. You can, you know, paint a pretty
picture then live in it.
it.
Really? How's that? I like that. Thank
you. Thank you. You're welcome.
Shannon, sharing. Yay.
That's what I want to do tonight. By all
means, I want to share an experience I
had at the same time everybody went to
Mount Chasta. Yikes.
Um, on May 30th when the people were in
Mount Chasta, I had a very beautiful
experience and mine was in a restaurant
in Thousand
Oaks. My experience changed me and the
way I felt about myself. Thank you. I
felt like a failure all my life. I've
always created the fear of failing in
any situation, any task or with any
person. All right.
I wanted to try so hard. Yes. I'd
stumble and fall and hurt myself. All
right. I've always been awkward and slow
and my parents thought I was dumb. All
right. And my class classmates would
call me stupid. All right. I couldn't
stand tall because I didn't feel tall.
I would hunch my
shoulders. Even if I'd accomplished
something, I could not accept praise
because I'd think I was just lucky and
next time I'd fail and I
would. And if any moment I felt powerful
and joyous, I knew it wouldn't last. And
it
didn't. I didn't know how not to know
that or to know I could know something
else. And that was what my friend Vita
who seasoned to past lives helped me
change because I saw the past life
experience where I had drawn the
conclusion that I was a failure.
She said, "I see you standing on a sandy
desert all
alone. You are like a sparkler, but
there is a flame in front of the
sparkles. The flame is getting larger
and is engulfing
you." You let
it. You decided to stop the flame so it
would not destroy your people.
You stopped the flames by letting them
engulf you. You believed you knew how to
do this. You went forth into the
flames. You did it. Do you understand
that you did
it? Because you believe that doing this
would prevent destruction by fire ever
again. And when you incarnated into the
following life, you came in at the time
of war, flames, and
destruction. You drew the conclusion
that you had
failed. I could see the picture in my
mind and I knew and know it is
true. You did not fail. as she said. And
as she said this, she took hold of my
hands. I felt such love and energy
coming from
her. I started to
cry. I'm not a
failure. Then I got the most beautiful
feeling of joy and
release. I started to cry because she
saw how I felt all my life. I couldn't
explain the feeling to anyone. and it
wouldn't go
away. Then I saw that life. I saw how I
was dressed and I was standing in front
of my children saying
goodbye and telling them I would not be
back and what I had to
do. As I walked across the desert alone,
I knew I would stop the fire.
I knew it was an evil energy that would
destroy my
people. I saw the fire coming and
prepared myself to stop it. And I walked
into it. I felt the fire go up my spine into
it. I felt the fire go up my spine into
my jaws and then a great pressure
building in my head.
Then an exhilarating, joyous feeling of
bursting out the top of my head with
immense
energy. Then I came back to
now. I felt so light and airy and like a
July 4th sparkler with sparks came
coming out of the my little
fingertips. When Vita and I walked
outside, it was dark. No moon, but the
sky had a beautiful rosy glow and the
stars looked like diamonds in the sky.
It was clear, and so was
I. I felt I could see behind objects
such as stop signs and street lights. I
could see the other side.
Veta said, "You are perceiving in the fourth
said, "You are perceiving in the fourth
dimension. I feel love for every
creature on
earth." You know how you feel when you
have done a job and you've done it well
and you say to yourself, "Job well
done." That's the way I feel. I feel
like that
now. I know I'm not a failure anymore.
Thanks to my lovely friend Beta and
myself. We thank you for your anthem of
old earth. We thank you for the
discovery of the bright light within
you. We thank you for letting it shine
in your life and illuminate the path and
the changes that you have helped create.
You have had an
impact and the
transformations that are occurring upon
your chosen world of your birth
reflect all that you have ever done to
serve it and it loves you back as do we.
We thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you so much, Bashar.
At this
timing, allow
us to ring with the
tone, the tone of the interconnected
spaces, the tone of the substance you
hold dear, the tone of the reality and
the dreams you prefer.
You are the key. Turn in the lock and
open. We extend our unconditional love
and will
never tire of telling
tire of telling
you how much we
appreciate your choice to be who you
have chosen to be.
You are a great gift and we cherish
you. We thank
you. Exciting dream
life to all and to all a good night.
Let it go.
[Applause]
Thank you all very much for being here
tonight. Those of you who want a copy of
tonight's tape, you can have it tonight.
It's two 90-minute tapes for $10.