first thing that represents the
strongest beliefs you had in life, then
many of you will experience the
realization, the seeming physicalization
of those beliefs, of those fears. But if
someone had an
idea, that hell would be extremely
painful in that way. Then if they
immediately find themselves in that
self-created scenario, they are very
unlikely to be able to hold on to
sustaining that degree of pain and
self-infliction. In a sense, and again
not meaning to be derogatory nor
flippant, hell, the concept you usually
hold it to be, could only be populated
for very long by
massochists, by true massochists.
For as soon as you know that the pain
you are enduring is not something you
can tolerate, it will lessen because
your mind in the non-physical reality
instantly translates into the seeming
experience you are having. And the
second you are aware that the second you
change your thoughts, the scenario
around you changes. You'll begin to get
the idea pretty quick that you don't
have to hang around in that
scenario. And then it becomes clearer to
you that whatever you believe at any
given moment even on that level and
especially in a sense on that level in
many ways is what most quickly manifests
and realizes into the experiential
reality you are having. You all follow
along. So these ideas they are states of
So these ideas they are states of
being. You can be in that
state anywhere, anytime, any way you
wish. There is a way that heaven and/or
hell can be expressed on earth. A way it
can be expressed on any other
civilization's planet. A way it can be
expressed in any dimensional level in
which the concept of that type or degree
of polarity may
exist. But it is not unique unto its own
place. It touches all levels in that
sense because any frequency can be said
to be its own place. In that sense, you
can say it is its own place. But both
are places that bridge all and contain
all other dimensions of experience. So
you can be in either state wherever you
are. It is up to you to choose which one
you prefer and which one you believe is
most representative of the being you prefer
representative of the being you prefer
to
be. You all follow
along. Well, thank you very
much. One other
point simply in allowing yourself the
ability to recognize that you can
manifest heaven upon your earth.
Remember that desire to do so in and of
itself, desire is in and of
itself. Manifest ability.
Desire is what physicalizes,
materializes, manifests the belief
blueprint you have drawn up in your
imagination. So to simply know that you have chosen
So to simply know that you have chosen
consciously chosen with your conscious
commandment the vibration you
prefer your desire to choose that
vibration is all that is necessary to
manifest the reflections of that
vibration in your life. Now some of you
may wish to create processes
between the desire and the
manifestability but when brought right
down to basics desire itself is manifest
ability. The desire strong enough is
enough to create it to attract it. That
is all. any other process you invent, it
is your enjoyment to do so. So enjoy the
process if there must be one. And that
enjoyment of any process between desire
and manifestability will shorten the
distance between
them. We thank you and at this timing we
will ask you how may I be of service to
you? Good evening, Bashar. I'm to you. It's
Good evening, Bashar. I'm to you. It's
Joan. Guys, um you knew that, didn't
you? Guys,
I really want to thank you for what
you've said this evening because once
again, it helps me realize that um it is
that easy. Nice. To want to enjoy life,
to want it to be simple, to want it to
be heavenly. Yes. And it is. Yes. And
the more you get that idea, the happier
you are. So, thank you very much. An
upward spiral. So,
well, it's been very exciting this week
and I have something I want to share
with you. All right. And everybody else
here, I received something in the mail
that I thought was quite fascinating.
It's called the Whale Adoption Project.
Okay. And apparently um a group called
calling themselves the International
Wildlife Coalition has been studying a
group of whales that live in the North
Atlantic and cruise up and down the
coast of Cape Cod and who knows where
else. and they have identified over the
last several years 70 individual
whales and have actually taken pictures
of the flukes as they dive and given
them names and written up a little
report about each one. And for
$15, you can adopt a whale of your
choice and thereby I love this idea. it
so makes it so personal and thereby
assist um this organization in making
life on this planet safe for whales and
bringing them under under the protection
of all the nations on the
planet. So I immediately went over the
list. There is a list posted on the back
bulletin board and some of these flyers
for all of you that are interested in
having your very own whale, so to speak,
or at least sharing that consciousness.
And I adopted three. Yes, you were going
to say something. or simply commenting
perhaps on the human adoption program
the whales might
have which in dream reality may have
translated out into the concept of the
adopt a whale program the humans came up
with
perfect synchronicity. Oh yes. Well, I
just would like them to know I am
definitely up for adoption.
So, in looking over the list, I
immediately found two names that I
thought, of course, I've got to have
Navajo because that to me represents the
planet itself. All right.
Right. And then I came across Sirius. I
thought, well, of course I have to have
Sirius. Oh, of course.
Obviously. And then I thought, now I
need a whale to represent Esasani. What
can I find on this list? And do you know
they had a name lightning? And I thought
how wonderful, how perfect.
Utar in Esasani means lightning. Thank you
in Esasani means lightning. Thank you
because I know Esasani means place of
living light. And that you call
yourselves the sun. So those are the the
whales I chose. And I invite you all to
go choose a whale this evening. And for
those people that are going to be
listening to the tape,
uh, you may write to the International
Wildlife Coalition, 320 Gford Street, Falloff,
Coalition, 320 Gford Street, Falloff,
Massachusetts. That's F A L M O U T,
Massachusetts 02540. And ask for your whale adoption
02540. And ask for your whale adoption
list, and I'm sure they'll send you one.
Thank you very much for your share.
Thank you, Bashar. There's one thing I
do want to mention in addition to this
and that is a few weeks ago I shared uh
a waking dream that I had when I went to
the New Life Expo and and heard
um uh two people channeling on Saturday
night. Yes, thanks Lanna. When I get up
here and connect with this energy, I
somehow lose where I am or maybe I gain
where I am.
Um anyway, at that time I realized that
for 3,000 people to be there paying 20
to $25 a seat to see
channeling to me meant we are entering
the fourth density reality on this
planet. And my further vision that I
forgot to mention
uh was that I saw all these people going
back to their homes and their little
subdivisions and wherever they were
scattering off to and each of them being
a spark that would ignite others to a
new age reality. And then I just had
this visualization of the entire planet
sparkling and lighting up as we each
ignite each other.
And I
thought this is fantastic because we are
becoming Sissani ourselves. Yes. Living
light. So thank you very much. We thank
you for turning on the switch.
Sharing.
Hello Bashar. Hello. I have a sharing.
All right. Uh last Friday evening I was
uh created the opportunity to experience
a Tibetan gong uh meditative experience.
Oh what? And as that began I remembered
at that moment how you had last Thursday
night described
uh a way for a a pregnant woman who
wanted to create the idea of dolphins
being present at her uh the birth of her
child. Nice. And so I immediately
through my imagination created this
ovoid blue egg of electromagnetic
energy. And as it expanded, my
consciousness expanded with it. And at a
certain and with the intention of making
a dolphin contact and uh at a certain
point a a whitish membrane
uh opened within that blue ovoid egg of
consciousness and I saw ah a gateway an
opening I should go through that and
immediately like exploded through it and
for about the next 10 or 15 minutes I
don't have a conscious recollection of
of my experience. experience. You'll
have lots of fun.
I'm sure of that because when the
consciousness did come back, I was in
the water swimming with dolphins and the
water was uh wasn't light, but it was uh
murky or dark and we're really having a
good time and but I was looking I go now
who where am I here? And so I said in my
in my imagination, who am I? I And as I
said that, this sort of large whitish
dolphin comes up onto this flat rock
that the water was lapping over around
where we were swimming, turns its head,
and sort of like shakes the water at me.
And um that recognition threw me into uh
a sea of thoughts, guys, where uh there
was different colors in in every aspect
of of my being. and its
interconnectedness with other beings,
other lives, every event in my life.
Wherever I would turn my attention, it
would just like shoot out into all these
arms of ideas and uh concepts. And so I
experienced that for a while. Meanwhile,
I'm not even hearing the gong at all.
I don't even know that that's there
until I slowly seem to start withdrawing
from that sea of thought forms of uh
telepathy or or whatever that experience
was seemingly that nice and um came back
to the music but it had been going for
about 25 minutes by that time nice and
then came slowly back into my conscious
reality of being in that room listening
to the gong and I wanted to share that
as an experience that I'm sure everyone
can uh create on their on their own as
and also asked for an interpretation of
when I said who am I that white dolphin
that came up on the rock um my idea is
that it's either uh something in a past
life of mine or it's a guide in this
life or
both this means it is a strong Atlantean
connection that way in connecting with
the dolphin astral form
It is a counterpart of you. Ah, you are
a counterpart of it. Okay. You have been
as many of you have been dolphin in
certain lives, human in others in that
way. And many of you still have strong
connections to your dolphin counterpart
aspects in the astral realm in that
sense. So you were in a sense looking at
a reflection of yourself in a different
kind of mirror. Okay. which immediately
projected into the mental plane if that
was the next sea of sense. I see. All
right. So that you know that everything
is a part of the same sea and that you
swim in the same dream.
It is all one sea. It is all one dream.
Enjoy. Oh, your future speed dreams.
Thank you very much. Well, thank you for
your sharing and your willingness of
blending. Ah, and I have a question from
Lynn Muro who wanted to know the
different places on the planet that
represented the chakras of the planet,
especially the root chakra, the
condolini. Is that right, Lyn? Okay. There are
There are
areas in what you might call the central
African area on your
planet. There are very powerful sources
of
connection to the power of the earth. In
that way there are
way there are
also in what you call the hoping
settlement of
Arab similar strong
connections in what you call your
southwest United States
area. There is also the crown chakra of
Shasta. In that sense there is also the third
In that sense there is also the third
eye chakra of Tibet. In that
sense there is the heart chakra of
hapa. In that
sense there is also in what you call
your South American Central American
region certain
aspects of the throat in that
way. There are many also very strong
vortices round about your planet that
are gateway to all the chakra points and do
gateway to all the chakra points and do
remember that each and every one of you
is a gate and you are fundamentally
connected to all the other gates upon
your planet.
You may find a desire within you to
visit certain areas to partake of the
energy of that area which may make it
seem to be stronger for you. But
wherever you are and whatever your
imagination is tuned to will place you
squarely in that chakra point in that
energy point and you can make whatever
connections you wish from wherever you
are for all places are within
you. All right. All right. Thank you.
Thank you very much. Sure.
Hello Bashar. Hello. Uh conscious
commandment. I had a desire to be with
dolphins Sunday evening in my dreams. I
see. So I consciously put myself in blue
light. All right. And I got some
extraterrestrial dream instead. Instead.
Yeah. So I I um where does conscious
commandment play a part? I don't usually
have dreams that I recall and I woke up
at 5:00 in the morning very excited with
Well, obviously your conscious
commandment is working. There may have
been a few mixed expectations in with
it, but you did get what you asked for.
And do remember that in many ways the
dolphin society is very alien to you.
And so in that sense, you may have
interpreted some of the blending of
their energy as extraterrestrial, but
the dolphin energy is blended with
extraterrestrial consciousness,
specifically Sirius and Arcturus. So you
may pick up many flavors in one contact,
but all the energy was there.
Um, I'd like to share this dream and
maybe you can give me some insight. I
was at my parents house Sunday evening
and I had the dream afterwards that I
came out of their house into the
driveway which had been totally
upheaved. Uh the cement is all broken.
Oh and there was a truck of a sort
almost like a an army truck and I could
see through the
window in a driver position almost an
ant base. Next to him were four to five
male figures of sorts, dark skin, um,
all of dark skin. Nice.
And they were speaking to me
telepathically. I could visualize almost
words on a screen going by very quickly.
And I remember them talking about the
number 1 to remember this that I would
need this number that I would be
musically teaching and learning a
musical instrument. I would need foreign
languages and I would be traveling a lot
and I needed to do all of these things
and to remember all this and it was very
loving and I wasn't afraid and I was
embracing all of this listening. Yeah.
And it seemed just like I understood
that I needed to do all this and it was
wonderful. And I went back inside and I
drew someone out of the house and said,
"Hey, look at this. Look who's here."
And this person came out and I don't
remember who it was. And he said, "Oh,
isn't this great? Hello." And so anyway,
I extended my love to these four or five
beings. And the next minute they were
gone. Nice. And for some reason, I
thought it was a truck, but it just
disappeared. and they were on a platform
of a sort window, but it wasn't a truck.
You had an astral encounter with a
spacecraft. It is a mixture of new Orion and
It is a mixture of new Orion and
reticulum energy. You are perceiving
both races. This is
races. This is
because more paramount in your life
right now are the specifics that you do
need to learn. But regard the aspect and
the understanding of the music as
something that will also assist you in
understanding the emotionality of
communication between yourself and
dolphin life as well. Certain aspects,
certain connections that you have to
certain civilizations of what you might
call an extraterrestrial nature once you
get used to those connections can allow
you to expand to other levels,
specifically the serious level that will
put you more directly in touch with the
dolphin energy. But you can interact
with Dolphin at this time specifically
through the idea of tonal quality music
and the same degree of empathy and
compassion and love that you shared with
them. They did give you an opportunity
to exercise to express that love and the
same type of communication can go on
with dolphin consciousness. Now in that
particular interaction the dolphin
consciousness was present but it was
mostly as you say in the sidelines
watching. But they did put in, as you
might say, their two cents.
But it was with regard to the
recognition of your affinity for the
musical quality. You follow me? Yes. All
you need to do is continue to act upon
these ideas and you will give yourself
more recognition of the connections that
you say you have desired. And by the
way, you have not experienced the whole
dream yet anyway. I I feel like there
are parts I'm missing. Oh no no no no no
no no no no you have not experienced it
yet. Oh there is more to come. This is
the first part of the conscious
commandment you have exercised. It was
the foundation that has been laid. It
will continue. Why are you assuming that
the dreams you request have to take
place all within the span of one of your
nights? It can bridge many nights, many
interactions. You follow me? Yeah, your conscious
You follow me? Yeah, your conscious
commandment is still in effect, still
going on. The momentum is still
moving. You will discover the rest, all
the different pieces. Let it all fall
into place. Nothing has stopped. Nothing
has ceased. All right. All right. Pleasant
ceased. All right. All right. Pleasant
dreams. Thank you. I have one other
question. Um I seem to have a great love
for uh about the 1890s Paris art,
artists, impressionism, fashion. Did I
live in that time? Any such strong
attraction to any particular historical
era is usually an indication of that
fact that you have a life there. Yeah,
explore it to whatever extent you wish.
It is up to you. But such attractions do
not happen without a reason. Now do
remember once again that time is your
illusion. So in many ways that light
still exists and that is why anything you wish
exists and that is why anything you wish
to discover about it is easily
discovered based upon what aspects of it
truly move your curiosity and excitement
because it is not so very far away. It
is as simple as switching a dial and
looking through the eyes of the you you
were then like looking through another window
then like looking through another window
in the house in which you are presently
living. Rather than truly thinking,
well, I have to go back to them dim dark
past dredging up through across the span
of time way back there. It is right
here, right now. All within you. And for
the you you were then, this life is
within that life as well. All lives
bleed through to each other. There is
leaked through from every life to every
other life.
Whatever it is from any life that leaks
through into any other life that causes
you to have a pull, an attraction
towards that life are the aspects of
that life that fit into whatever it is
in this life you are doing. So you can
draw from the total being that you are
since in many ways you are an artist
now, right?
So merge and blend wherever your
curiosity so desires. Use your
imagination always. Your imagination is
the gate through which you can walk. All
you need to do to allow yourself more
freedom to do so is to stop asking
yourself is my imagination
real or is that a real experience or am
I just imagining it? There is no
difference between a real experience and
one that you imagine. There may be
different degrees of manifestation of
the real experience in your particular
realm, but that doesn't mean that just
because you imagined it, it is not
real. You cannot imagine
non-existence. So anything you do
imagine is on some level somewhere
somewhere real. You follow me? You're
speaking of the dream also. Yes. Thank
you. That answered my question. Thank
you very much for being willing to exist
on more than just one level. Thank you,
Sharon. Good evening, Bashar. And to
you, good day. Good day. Uh, a few weeks
ago, you commented on some of the
properties and characteristics of these
round stones that were found in Georgia
that some people call cosmic eggs in a
symbolic nature. Yes. Not in a literal
physical nature. I wonder if you could
tell us the origin of these objects.
Where do they come from?
This is not within our realm to do so at this
is not within our realm to do so at this
time. Okay. Someone else will provide
that information. All right. I have um
three small crystals as double
terminated crystals that I got in a most
unusual way from a most unusual man. And
do remember before you go on that
acquiring things in the most unusual way
is becoming as you say the most usual
way of life. Of course.
Do proceed. Similarly, I wondered if you
could comment on the origin of these
crystals.
What is their nature? Define them and
give their aspects. Uh they're about um
3/4 of an inch long. They're double
terminated. They're very small. They're
about an eighth of an inch in diameter.
They're very light. They're not quartz
crystals. Nobody seems to be able to
identify them. What is their coloration?
Uh they're quite clear, like clear
quartz crystals.
You may find certain individuals among
you that may have identification for
them. In that way, what we perceive at
this time is that you acquire them
because they are representative of
connections you have to individuals who
have made different agreements and pacts
with you through many different lives.
They are an awakening symbol, a
recognition symbol. They are in a sense
calling cards. And because there are
three of them, they are functional along
the basic trinary level of creation.
They are a way to remind you and awaken
within you recognition of other
individuals in your life at this time as
associates from the past so to speak
from the present and from the future.
That is one of the three representations
of this idea. They are aligning crystals
to bridge the gaps that are usually
created in your society between the
concept of past, present and future.
They are keys in that way to open the
doors between the areas that you usually
create barriers to exist. You follow me
very clearly. That is our perception at
this time. There are individuals with
you tonight of your time who can place
more identification upon them. Now that
you have made them aware, at your break
time you may find some assistance. Thank
you. Thank you. I have one brief one
brief last question having to do with
the dolphins. When we met originally in
in October, I asked you about two
islands in the Bahamas that you were
trying to we are in the process of
acquiring at time to create a dolphin
center. Yes.
Uh quite recently in the last few weeks
we have encountered a benefactor who has
offered to build us a a research center
in Florida where we now are to expand
our facility to purchase it to fix it
and so forth and so on. Uh it seems to
be real because the dolphins are very
excited. They've been jumping up and
down for three days since this whole
thing began to be discussed here in
California. That and I guess my question
is you said some wonderful things about
those two islands in the Bahamas. One
thing leads to another. Act upon
whatever opportunities present
themselves to you that excite you now
that you are capable of acting on. And
one thing that excites you now is a
thread that will lead to all other
things that excite you. One step at a
time. Thank you. Thank you.
Sh. Hello Bashar. Hello. Um, I have been in
Hello Bashar. Hello. Um, I have been in
the process of becoming aware in my
dreams and recently in conversation with
you I mentioned to you about a friend of
mine Sandy Sandre or Sandy Keys who who
has recently passed away about a year
and a half ago. Hi. And
she after our
conversation came to me in a dream and
uh she did in this dream, she did in
that dream. She uh I was with I believe
I was with somebody else that's here
right behind me when I asked a question.
And we were uh we did a healing
together. We did we did a healing of of
two people and Sandy came up to me. We
were walking down the street and said,
"Uh, do you want to go with me?" And I
said, "Yes." And she grabbed my hand.
And we went up to this woman's house and
we were about to go through the walls of
the house and I said, "No, no, wait a
minute." Thinking from a third density
point of view, you can't do that. And
she said, "No problem." We went right
through. And we came upon a woman that
had recently lost her child and was
there crying and moaning about the baby.
There was a uh like a small uh crib that
she was rocking back and forth and we
did a lot of healing
uh for the woman and then we left. Nice.
And we went to somebody else's house and
helped to heal them and I saw what I
believed to be were large uh centipedes
or something like that on the ground and
was afraid to step on them. She said,
"Don't worry, they won't they won't hurt
you. They're the things that are the
things people draw to them in diseases.
Thoughts in a sense. Thoughts, right?
Thought forms. And uh I was afraid. She
said, "No, don't worry about Oh, you are
in the astral realm. Nothing can touch
you in that sense." I realized that we
were talking up a storm the whole time
this was happening. And then we went out
of this went out of this guy's house and
we saw him in a car and he was to stop
somewhere and it was like an indication
of he was to stop at a light and he
didn't or make a stop and it was an
indication if he received the healing
that we gave to him and he didn't stop
and the next thing I knew is I felt I
was looking at her and it felt like her
head part of her head was like
dissolving and I was looking into her
brain and I realized later that that was
and it it didn't scare me or frighten me
or anything. It was just looking at her
and it was like she was showing me
something about the impermanence of
physical of a physical body is that that
would be the way of communicating to her
and that that it's not that important.
Yes. And then I felt that
And then I felt that
I swallowed something and woke up
feeling that she had poked me a couple
of times on the uh on the right side of
my ribs. And uh as I often described her
in this dream of us poking one another.
Yes. It was astounding and ecstatic and
I was I was overjoyed by the whole
experience. Thank you for allowing your
physical dream and your non-physical
dream to blend and merge so that you can
live your dreams. You know, many of you
are of quite a bit more assistance than
you know in your dream lives to other
individuals. You all have things that
you do. Many of you have dream
jobs in a sense and you many of you do
go about assisting other individuals in
many different
ways. As you begin to blend these two
realms together, the non-physical and
the physical, all of these different levels,
physical, all of these different levels,
particularly what you call the astral
level immediately above your physical
level, will begin to materialize into
your world.
So that interacting with beings on that
level will become quite common place
and they will be able to have more
interaction with you. That fluid
communication will create an ability for
individuals to not have to feel they are
stuck between one level or another or
fear the symbols that are created to
represent their fears that manifest in
those astral realms.
Thank you for having the willingness to
go exploring and to bring a bit of where
you went back to your own level. More
and more blending. We thank you. That
makes a difference on many levels and
allows many more things to be possible
in your
society. Enjoy.
I do. Thank you very much. Thank you
very much.
Next time, say hi for us. I will. In
fact, I did. I asked her if she knew
you. She said she did. Thank you.
Hi, Bash. Hi.
Last Saturday, um I had people say I was
sick and um it was in my abd abdomen and
it was on the left and right side and
they took me to the hospital because it
was so severe pain. And um they took
tests, they gave me medicine, they took
blood and everything and they didn't
know what it was.
And they said, "Well, since you're
feeling better, we're going to let you
go home and it will be a mystery." Oh,
mystery. And that I wouldn't know what it was.
And that I wouldn't know what it was.
And I was wondering why I created this
situation for myself and what was the
sickness. Do you find that at this time
you in one sense have allowed it to be
demystified?
How long did it take for the situation
to alleviate itself? Approximately what
you would call one to two of your day.
How long? About three. Three. All
right. How do you feel now?
Not too great, but okay. Not too great,
but okay. All right.
One idea is to simply allow you to know
that regardless of the structure of
information that has been set up on your
society, regardless of the structure
that you refer to as
authority, even to that structure, there
are many things that are a
mystery. And that you you are your own
final answer. You are your own
exploration of any mystery you create.
Everything does occur for a reason and
many of the reasons can be extremely
simple. The reasons in and of themselves
do not have to be mysterious in that
way. Many of the things that individuals
may not understand at any given moment.
They as you say chalk it up to mystery.
But that may simply be another way of
saying that you do not have to have
conscious analytical awareness of all
the things that occur in your life for
why they occur at that given moment. But
that somewhere down the road it will
make itself clear, make itself plain.
Now, one of the ideas was to allow you
to know that you don't necessarily have
to worry about relying upon the
authoritative structure so much and that
you eventually will alter yourself one
way or another regardless of what they
say they can or cannot do. It allowed
you to go through a door of trust
regarding authority and allowed you to
know that the final authority is in you.
That is one of the reasons you created
that idea because in the past you see
you have created in many different lives
many run-ins as you say with
authority in that
way. Now you have given yourself an
opportunity to know you are
relaxing your creation of authorities
all over you. You can interact with them
freely. You can allow them to be who
they are. And you can discover that even
the authority that is supposed to know
everything still contains mystery and
room for
exploration. So that you will become
more equal with them in that
way. And they in a sense will then not
have to
create a gut ache in that sense in you.
You will learn how to allow yourself to
encompass them. They will learn how to
allow themselves to encompass you so
that you can allow each other to be who
you are and respect each other for what
you are and not thinking that any one of
you has to be more right than the other.
There are a few aspects of this idea
that your guides have to share with you
as
well and this will be shared perhaps in
some of the events that occur in your
daily life or in your dream realities
beginning tonight of your
time. But in a sense you have taken
yourself through a process and you have
allowed that process to take you beyond
the old expectations of the old society
placed you on a different level.
Recognize in many ways that you were
clever in doing what you did and the
experience you created was not unlike
the experience that many other
individuals have had and the physical
channel before you has had. for
recognize that that particular area of
abdominal pain is an area your medical
practitioners have absolutely no way of
doing anything
with. There was nothing they could do
for you. That is an area outside their
understanding but not outside your you
created an
occurrence. an occurrence that they
desired to assist you with but could not
because of the limitations they had
placed upon
themselves. More and more individuals
that give them the opportunity to
recognize that there is something here
that they are out of touch with will
allow them to explore more and more in
different areas. Now knowing that the
studies they already have do not answer
at all. You are luring them in a sense
out of their
shells in many ways and that is one of
the reasons you have co-created that
with them and you have in many ways also
used it as a part of your own process to
take you through a gate. Sometimes those
gates are painful simply because of the
expectations and belief systems you have
been brought up with in your society.
But bit by bit those gateways and
processes will become less and less and
less painful. What is your physical age?
painful. What is your physical age?
11.
You are at a master
number. 22 and 33 are also master
numbers at which you may experience
another large threshold gate. But you
have actually adopted at this age. An
idea that it takes many other
individuals until the year 33 to act
out. You have cut that into thirds. And
so you are accelerating that much more
quickly. We thank you for your boldness
in that way, for it will make a
difference in any other interactions you
now have from this point forward in your
life regarding what you decide needs to
be mysterious or can simply be
understood for the commonplace
occurrence that it is and the creation
that it comes from you and serves all
individuals involved. It is not isolated
within you. Just what do you have to
gain from it or learn from it but also
what they what their part your medical
world whoever else you interact with
have also to learn from it. You're a
very bold teacher in that way. You will
be boldly teaching for quite some time
and each interaction that you have in
our perception will become more and more
bold as time goes on.
Thank you. You're welcome. [Applause]
Sharing for sure. One
moment to the individual we were just
speaking with. There is another name,
another vibration that has to do with
you. And we find to our great joy that
we are allowed now by your guides to
share it with you. In no way, shape or
form do we mean this name to elevate you
in ego above and beyond anyone else, but
it is something that you may cherish and
hold within you. And that name is
Brightar. Thank you,
Brightar. Continue. I
I
wanted, excuse me, to ask you um about
the direction of my life. That way,
[Music] turn left at the corner.
turn left at the corner.
That's how I came here.
Now, first of all, before we continue,
you know that we are not making fun of
you yet.
We are creating fun with you. I
understand. And this is one of your
answers right here. The idea of the
direction of your life. Allow it in
whatever way you do choose to go. At
least allow it to contain some
fun, some laughter, some
lightness. Go. I usually do. All right.
Continue. Um I wanted to I kind of uh my
life seems to be in a third phase is
kind of how I put it. I want to
backtrack just a little bit. In uh 74 I
met my spiritual guru and I studied with
him for about 9 years and traveled with
him and I went through a lot of um
transformation, understanding, surrender
and uh a lot of training. uh he left his
body in ' 82. Hey,
and uh then I kind of came out and got a
job and started working and I was doing
that for about 3 years. And now at the
beginning of this year, it seems like my
spiritual direction has drastically
changed. It always will. And a lot of
people, a lot of events are coming to me
to be involved in spiritual work rather
than manifesting out so to speak normal
work out in the world. And we understand
I'm trying to be open to my direction.
All right. But again, do remember that
much of what you are describing is
becoming the normal work out in the
world. Right? So you're not alone.
Manifesting your direction is simply a
matter of deciding what excites you the
most in all the things you are offered.
Excitement is your key. Which one do you
prefer above and beyond all others?
Which excites you the most? Whichever
one it is, follow it. Excitement is the
key. Excitement is the vibration of
ecstasy that represents who you are, who
you can most effortlessly be.
So are you willing to believe it is that
easy? Yes. All
Yes. All
right then. It is that easy. There is no
need to be in a quandry about the
direction of your spiritual growth.
First of all, do remember you are a
spirit. Anything you do will be a
spiritual act. If you decide that it is
in the direction of your growth, then it
is an act of spiritual growth. Your body
is not what your spirit is in. Your body
is your spirit in physical
terms. So whatever you decide represents
the thing that excites you the most.
That is the light that shines most
brightly in the direction you can
go. It is that easy. Excitement is the
thread that leads to all other
excitement. Excitement is the
translation of the energy that
represents the path you chose to be and
represents the path you can be most
effortlessly and the path that will
support you most
abundantly. Excitement tells you all
these things. It is the one sign you
usually all ask for. Give me a
sign, please. Oh universe, oh all that
is, oh God, please tell me, give me a
sign. The sign is called
excitement. That is the sign because it
is the vibration that is straight
ahead. It's the frequency that is
straight ahead. So follow it with integrity.
ahead. So follow it with integrity.
You will always be
supported in whatever way abundance
needs to manifest in your life to allow
you to continue to be the exciting being
you have chosen to
be. It is that
simple. Let it be that simple if you
will. Does this assist you? Yes, it
does. Anything else? Anything else?
No.
Why? Then enjoy and we thank you for your
Then enjoy and we thank you for your
joy. Sure.
Sure.
Hi. Hi. Uh this is my first time uh
coming forward. Uh you've answered all
my questions during all the other
sessions that I've been here and I thank
you for that. Um I did want to ask one
moment. We thank you for
creating and allowing with us to be a
reflection of that which you already
knew. You answered your
questions. You follow me? Yes. Thank
you. Yeah. I had other questions while I
was sitting here and I answered those.
I'll force them to.
Uh, I did uh I don't know how to phrase
this. I'd like you to shed some light on
a situation that happened to me in the
last Monday in January. I was on a
business trip in San
Francisco and I was uh there over the
weekend and for some reason I had this
uh something that that I had to write a
short story and it was about the three
bridges that cross the bay. Uh I crossed
two of them on a very rainy stormy day.
wrote part of the story and couldn't
quite make it to the third bridge. I was
discussing it with a friend
and in talking we decided the third
bridge which was the Golden Gate which
leads north of San Francisco and away
was also leading to something unknown as
also leading to something unknown as
well as something very exciting and sort
of growing. Yes. Uh so the next day that
Sunday was a sunny bright day everywhere
except when I crossed the bridge and we
went to this beach. It was uh in a fog
and the cloud formations did not look
like anything I'd ever seen quote
unquote in this lifetime. But it look
very familiar.
And uh I hadn't planned on getting out
of the car or anything, but I ended up
doing that. Walking towards the shore
there, all kinds of cliffs and high
rocks, and I decided to go ahead and
climb the rocks. Oh my. Everything was
fine until as I was climbing, I round to
a corner and there was a like a slide
area and you know, clips had broken
away. I all of a sudden came face to
face with my fear of heights and I froze
and I couldn't move at all. And even
though there was, you know, people
everything there, I felt like I was
totally alone and in communication with
someone or something.
I decided that I couldn't leave that I
had to climb to the top of the mountain
and that for some reason I got there to
work through this
through this
simple and I just wanted to know there
was more to it than
just learning to be alone with a big
fear and overcoming it. Very well done.
We have also discussed a certain
technique and exercise that we refer to
as the golden
gate. It being that you begin to form as
you were doing connections to your
higher self, your future self. That is
the dialogue you had in a sense. But the
golden gate represents you as a gate.
And on one side is the fluid, the golden
energy, the light out of which you
crystallize your physical reality. As
you pass the fluid through you and allow
it to crystallize on the other side, it
becomes the physical reality you
experience. The golden gate idea is in
recognizing that the flow of energy does
not simply go one way but goes both
ways. And that when you change an idea,
what you do is you allow the
crystallization to melt, dissolve back
through the gate in that sense, become
fluid and plastic again so that you can
allow it to come back through and
recristallize in a new format as a new
you. You, the you are now the you that
went up that hill. That is true. You are
literally a different person.
literally a different
crystallization. You walked through the
gate, through the golden
gate, and came back as more of your
higher self. Hello. Hi. Hello. Hi.
Welcome.
Thank you. And you? Thank you.
Bye. Sherry.
Sherry.
Hello, Bashar. Hello. Um, I have a
question uh with regards to some changes
that I've been going through in the last
year. All right. Um, I have always had a
a very good idea about my direction as
far as my career and what it would take
for me to be fairly comfortable with
myself. Fairly all right. Fairly. And um
well, does that mean relatively
comfortable or comfortable in fairness?
That's a very good question. Oh, thank
you. You're welcome.
I I don't exactly know how to answer.
Oh, that is all right. Okay. Um we like
to play around a little bit. I do too.
That's okay. Um, in any event, I um with
that direction in mind, I
have over the years created obstacles
for myself that have tended to repeat
myself that have tended to repeat
themselves. I That is an
illusion. Nothing truly repeats for it
is never the same time.
Mhm. In that sense, it is always now,
but it is never the same now. The
illusion of repeatability is only there
because of the assumption of
repeatability. The assumption that the
outward appearance has to carry the same
meaning with it every time. Not so. The
meaning you decide to give it based upon
how you think you have changed over the
years will allow the outward symbol to
transform. When you stop putting the
same meaning into the same outward
symbol, it will change into another
outward symbol.
And therefore it will not be an obstacle
but will be able to be seen by you to be
a part of the path you are not an
interruption in it.
You follow me so far? Yes I do. Um I h I
have a question. I don't know if it's a
little on the broad side. However,
I would like to know
if my career and the way that I have
chosen to direct myself towards it
now is going to work out the way I I
want if it's going to benefit me or if I
should maybe be
finding a different way to go. My what a
complicated question. I know.
Uh it is not that the answer in that
sense is complicated. The structure of
the question is complicated and that is
what seems to complicate the
answer. If I should, I wonder my career.
Now you have heard us discussing the
idea of what excites you. Yes. Mhm. Mhm.
What do you think about the idea? What
do you understand about the concept of
simply following what excites you and
allowing that to let whatever your
career is unfold naturally? What do you
think about that concept? Can you use
it? Is it something you can
use? Is it something you can trust?
Not always. All right. Your choice. Why
not?
When do you think you can trust the idea
following your excitement? And when do
you think you can?
I'm not always sure of it. Sure of what?
What excites you? Right. All right.
But perhaps you are changeable of it. Oh
yes. Oh yes. Oh yes.
But changeability has nothing to do with
whether you are sure or not. You may
think it is. Many individuals in your
society because they are taught to
believe in
unchanging stability when which is of course a
stability when which is of course a
contradiction. Change is the only stable
condition in creation. Therefore, that
change itself is a stabilizing
condition. But you have been taught to
think of static as stable. Therefore,
when things do begin to
change, you cannot find a way to hang on
to it, to define it as something stable
because you don't think it is. But it
actually is more stable than being
static. Which is more stable, walking or
trying to stand on one leg?
You follow me? Thank you. Therefore,
allow yourself first of all to recognize
that of course it will always fluctuate.
Of course, it will always change. But
that doesn't mean you can't be aware of
where your excitement
lies. Simply redefine the idea. You will
know you are always very
aware. Now might be that your definition of how
Now might be that your definition of how
you are looking seems to make it
difficult to find it. And that simply
means that when you say, "Well, what
excites me?" You may be looking for the
thing that will excite you above and
beyond anything else you will ever do in
your life. Now, that may not come to you at
life. Now, that may not come to you at
that moment.
However, if you keep the concept very
simple, very
basic, you will know that when we say,
"Well, what excites you?" We mean what
at this moment out of all the things you
are aware of that you can do at this
moment is the thing that excites you the
most that you are capable of doing.
Doing that because excitement leads to
all other excitement will automatically
step by step lure you into whatever
other scenarios will give you the capability
scenarios will give you the capability
to act upon anything else later that
excites you that you may not be capable
of acting on now.
So keep it simple as an
example. Not because it is specifically
us, but since you are in this
interaction this evening of your time,
we will assume that this at this moment
is what excites you more than anything
else you can think of doing. If this
conversation, as you say, takes a second
seat to something else at this moment
that does excite you more, go and do it
because that's where you
belong. So simply ask yourself, if this
is what excites you out of all the
things you could be doing right now the
most, we welcome you. After this
interaction, what out of all the things
that will be available for you to do
will be the thing that excites you the
most at any given
moment? Take it a step at a time, a
moment at a time. Then you will place
yourself in the habit of acting
spontaneously, instinctively on whatever it is at any
instinctively on whatever it is at any
given moment does represent the thing
that excites you at that moment. And bit
by bit, that will lure you into all the
other things in your life that will ever
excite you. And when you arrive at all those
you. And when you arrive at all those
other things, because you went through
all the things you did before that
excited you, when you arrive at each and
every new thing that excites you, you
will have right there with you in hand
all the tools necessary to be able to do
the next thing that excites
you automatically. automatically.
effortlessly,
abundantly, instantly,
instantly,
joyfully. How does that sound? It sounds
great. Thank you. Do you find that you
in your terms can understand this idea
and allow yourself to believe it is that
simple? Yes, I do. Well, thank you very much.
Yes, I do. Well, thank you very much.
Thank you. Enjoy.
shedding. Hi Bashard. Hi. I'm Cynthia.
This is my first time here and I'm
really I've really enjoyed it. Thank you
very much. Oh, I've enjoyed you all.
Thank you very much. I've enjoyed
everybody, too.
Uh gosh, there's uh this what you what
you talked about this evening is exactly
what I've been reading in a book this
week. So, I guess there was a reason.
More
synchronicity. Once you go into fourth
density, can't seem to get rid of that
fcky synchronicity. Everything just keeps
synchronicity. Everything just keeps
cropping up coincidentally at the same
place at the same time with exactly all
the individuals who need to be there.
What are we going to do about
this? If this is not stopped pretty
soon, it might infect the whole planet.
[Music] Thank you for sharing that.
Thank you for sharing that.
[Laughter]
I have a question I'd like to ask you u
pertaining to um twin flames or
soulmates. Um yes, I I've recently
become engaged with somebody and I feel
a very strong bond with them. So much so
that uh many lives together. That is one
of the questions I wanted to ask you.
But is there such a thing as coming from
the same?
Yes. Is that a possibility that I It is
very typical. Understand the oversoul that
typical. Understand the oversoul that
you are usually has many
counterparts. You may make an agreement
as one aspect of the oversoul with
another aspect of the oversoul to
reflect to you certain ideas within
yourself at a given moment in your
physical life. And that is usually what
you call the twin flame or the soulmate.
But in all reality even though other
individuals may not be a part of the
same oversoul immediately on one level of
oversoul immediately on one level of
course everyone is a part of the same
infinite oversoul and therefore anyone
at any given moment you are interacting
with in any type of relationship is in
one sense a soulmate. You follow me?
Mhm. But you can make special
agreements, if you will, specific
agreements if you will, with certain
aspects to reflect to you. When you
allow yourself to arrive at a certain
point in your life, that represents your
ability to know yourself as your own
complete relationship and then allow
another individual to reflect and share
that knowledge back to you equally.
You follow me? Yes, I do. That that
could pertain to a parent as well, could
it? Oh, yeah. Okay. But we understand
the term in which you mean it and this
is specifically the case you are
discussing now. Oh great. Okay. Uh one
other question. Um is there is will will
I ever connect with my mother again?
She's left this plan. I mean in your
terms how long ago? Uh she died seven
years ago. Six seven years ago.
In your terms of what? of this life she
passed on.
Do you mean in your terms of natural
cause? Yes. She's of an enlarged heart. Is that
Yes. She's of an enlarged heart. Is that
what you're asking me? How she died?
Yes. Yeah. Of an enlarged heart. I won't
know if I'll ever be in touch with her
again. Oh, you have been through your
dreams many times.
And how about in in one instance that I
that occurred a few months ago in uh
back home in the house that we grew up
in together and uh I came home and after
leaving do you know what I'm talking did
you have a strong emotional release a
tremendous one and also a physical sign
I thought from her with a beam of light
a tremendous innocence yes it has
allowed in many ways using her
manifestation symbolically it has
allowed your heart to expand to enlarge
but not in a detrimental way. You follow
me? It has filled you with the emotional
self. And that in many ways that
expansion, that enlargement of your
empathy, your compassion, your heart
energy is also what has allowed for the
solidification and the attraction into
your life of the twin flame in that
sense. So, it's her way of saying it's all
So, it's her way of saying it's all
okay. Is there of
course do remember that from that level
everything is all okay.
It is her way of simply sharing that she
still loves you very much. That all
messages on one level are received but
that she is on and about her life while
still reflecting as a guide in many ways
but that you are also on and about your
life. And what took her through the gate
takes you through another type of gate
even while you are still physically
alive. The enlargement of the harp
energy.
Okay. We thank you for your loving
sharing. Thank you very much for the
answer. You may all at this timing enjoy
a short break and we will resume contact
momentarily.
How's everything going?
Thank you. There's refreshments over
here if you want any tape. Uh you can
see Lyn who's around the corner there
making tapes. You can have tonight's
tape tonight. By the way, we have two
highspeed tape duplicators.
All right. Okay. Continue. [Music] Hi Ban.
Okay. Would you
like one more
time to speak? [Music] [Music]
Everything quite
friendly, quite
enjoyable, all
individuals, all
people are your friends, love you,
support you and would
you and would
enjoy what you have to
share. Everything you have to
say, they
will treat as a
gift. It is up to you.
Then in your
heart allow yourself to know we will
speak in your dreams
dreams
when it is
quiet and we are
alone. Thank you for your willingness to
be here this night of your time.
Thank you. Our love to
you. Our love to
you. Continue.
Um I would like to uh explore with you
further in regards to the letter Z and
you said nomenclature.
Just uh elaborate a little on that. In
regards to the nomenclature,
we in this way for you at this time in
our perception represent the
perception represent the
placeholder. Nomenclature that
opportunity, that
availability to name something, to
understand its
vibration. It is in a sense like unto
what you call the parentheses in your
grammar that you can fill
in. Now the essence is there no matter
what label you apply upon
it to some degree that letter is similar
to our
translation of one of the worlds in our
system which in our ancient language is
called. The mar means the
The mar means the
zone, the area, the holding place, the
placeholder, that which represents
something unidentified but of which the essence is
unidentified but of which the essence is
spelled.
Nonetheless, the your letter functions
much the same way. It functions as a
dial. It functions as a translation
device. It functions as that which can
connect into many different frequencies,
many different
vibrations by which you can know the
essence of them, but not necessarily
that you must label them anything
beyond Z in that sense, the placeholder
in that
sense, the end of your
alphabet, the end, the omega in that
sense, the other side of the polarity
that you are exploring.
In many ways, it simply allows you to
attach something without necessarily rigidizing
something without necessarily rigidizing
it by a full
label. It is a tool of flexibility. Many
things can occur within the zone, and
you can lump them all under the
nomenclature of the zone without
necessarily having to identify each and
every one of them to get some use out of
them. You follow me? Yeah, just included
within the zone. Yes, in a
sense. The idea now is for
blending, not
separating. It is therefore a limbo
nomenclature. And many references, many
names that are given to many of you in
the contacts you make within your own
channeling. Some of the names may begin
with Z in that sense and that lets you
know that it is being used as a
placeholder that it will do. For now,
the energy is real. The name is not
important. You follow me? Yes. Does that
assist you? Yes. I'd like to ask you
something that branches off from that.
The letter Z and the angles of me and
the A. And uh the other day I was uh he
told me to make a little uh if I wanted
to a lapis triangle nice or try uh
tetrahedral nice and uh I got both of
them made more or less. Oh boy. Close
enough. I was playing with the flat
triangle and I was just thinking what it
would look like if I was in one of the
angles. I would see two points and if I
was on one of the sides I would see one
point. And um just in regards to
vibrations and angles and uh if you
could say anything about those.
Well, as we have said the triangle of
tetrahedral structure is the basic
building block of the physiological
universe. All structures in the physical
universe are based upon the tetrahedral
pattern and the one
representational symbol that can define
all aspects of physics.
All understandings of vibratory
awareness within the dimension you call
physical can be gleaned and derived from
the one symbol of a tetrahedrin that
points up and a mirror image that points
down. For it contains in its definition
all the dimensional definitions that
describe and define what you call the
physical reality.
So it is that which allows you to work
with the fundamentals of
creation. The template upon which all
physical reality is based is pattern all
things occurring in threes in that way.
So that any two will support the one the
apex the foundation and the apex the
totality of your consciousness. the
three sides of the prism that you are as
an artificial personality
constructed belief, emotion, and
thought. Does that assist? Yes. Thank
you. Mind you, I just want to share that
um I've heard it a million times seems
like uh imagination creates reality and
I just think it was either yesterday or
today like really is becoming more and
more uh real. The imagination is real.
Yes, it is. Thank you. Thank you very much. Sharing.
much. Sharing.
Hello, Bashar. Hello. I come here not
knowing what I'm going to ask you about.
Oh, spontaneity. Thank you. Trusting
that a bit. Yes. Uh, the thing that
excites me most at the present time is
darkness. And I've been channeling
darkness and different aspects of have
been emerging. and I would welcome any
input you have on this concept and the
experience of darkness.
First, our congratulations at your
willingness to understand that you have
reached a point of personal power
wherein you know that nothing you could
explore on either polarity will ever be
more powerful than you.
So it is a reflection of your
willingness to know you are centering
balancing and from that point of view
the exploration the observation of your
preferences are all equalized on the
same level. You are now getting in touch
with the
idea of the polarity within you that you
may refer to as darkness. Knowing that
anything you will discover in that
darkness, you will be able to
transform through the light of your
consciousness into a positive reality, a
reality of light. You are now willing to
know there is nothing within the
darkness you could ever stumble across.
Nothing within the darkness you could
ever discover that could not
discover that could not
become a part of the light you prefer to
be. This is using the foundation of the
This is using the foundation of the
triangle with the polarity of light on
one side, the polarity of darkness on
the other, blending them to be able to
create the apex to elevate and enlighten
yourself by including the totality of
yourself, which then allows you to have
a base upon which the apex can stand.
And then of course that apex, that
pyramid, that
triangle being fundamentally where the
symbol of the wizard hat comes from to
begin with.
Finally, does that assist? Yes, it does.
I would like to explore further two um
aspects of the of this. Oh, one has to
do with uh channeling what was was a um
a large a high suspension bridge. It's
about 10 ft wide and it was sagging
toward its center and uh it seems like
um I'm walking down this bridge but not
getting anywhere. All right. Okay. Uh
that's one thing. All right. Um the
other has to do with this book uh
Communion. Uh having read this book, I
come away from it with a feeling of
perhaps sadness because the book is
couched in terms as I read it in terms
of physical suffering
um extreme fear on the part of the
author. I and uh the this story uh I
pretend when it gets out into the public
will will not convey the kind of message
that you and Zars and others like that
are conveying about extraterrestrials or
other levels of consciousness. Not so
for recognize if you will perhaps reread
that idea. You will discover now looking
at it from the other side of the bridge
from the positive aspect that the author
came to many realizations that the
source of all of the discomfort and fear
that was felt came from him and was not
inherent in the interaction.
The author made many realizations of
this nature and has in your terms done
quite a credable job of owning his
feelings in the interaction and this
will come out. It will come out. But
again, you have the opportunity of
viewing it from either side of the
bridge and allowing that to be blended
and balanced and knowing that everything
manifests in perfect timing will allow
the bridge to be straight and true and
allow communion to happen across in two
communion to happen across in two
directions rather than feeling that
there is a midpoint that no one will be
able to cross.
Everything is going quite nicely from
our point of view.
Okay. Another manifestation of this has
to do with this game that's going around
town called
Airplane. Undoubtedly, you know about it
and u it seems to elicit a lot of
feelings about money uh worthwhile guilt
um the whole spectrum as you say. whole
spectrum. Correct. All right. I would
welcome some comments about that. All we
will say at this time is any tool you
attract into your life, use it if you
feel it is an expression of your
integrity. If you in viewing the overall
idea feel that too become involved with
any tool will be an expression of the
lack of your integrity or the support of
in that sense a
situation which may instill within
others more capacity to play
victim than decide whether or not you
wish to become involved is totally up to
you. Your perspective in many ways will
determine the aspects of the whole idea
you encounter. Your belief systems going
in will determine in many ways the
outcome. But take into consideration
simply what your beliefs about the whole
idea are and let that be your guide as
to your participation.
It seems to hold the uh the choice of
treating it as a a third density game or
a fourth density game. There is always
every aspect
and they are completely different games.
If I were to play as a fourth density
game as a fourth density game that would
mean that everyone would always win.
There would never be a loser. Yes. And
that it would go on indefinitely. And it
would mean for me personally a very
almost instantaneous transition into
fourth density. But we cannot recommend.
It is up to you. Oh, I wasn't asking for
we know but others were. [Music]
[Music]
Thank you. Thank you. Good to be with
you again in this close range. We are
never far apart. Yes. Thank you.
Our hearts with all of you are always
touching
sharing. Good evening and you good day.
I want to ask you some questions about
yourself and your world if I can. Of
course. Um I've haven't been here only
for a few weeks and I guess I missed
some stuff that you probably already
talked about. Um in terms of a different
vibrational level than your world as
opposed to ours. Yes. Is the physical
reality in your world the same or
similar to our world? Similar. Yes. Um
you have bodies. Yes. Are your bodies
like ours in terms of two arms, two legs
and that sort of thing? In that sense
you would call it humanoid as we have
referred to you very often as the
[Music] sunish. We are of average 5t of your
sunish. We are of average 5t of your
height. white whitish gray skin
coloration is is a humanoid or a or a
satanic type body a a common thing
throughout their various universes
within a particular frequency range.
Yes. Understand again that usually any
society that begins to explore space
will usually run into and attract to
themselves those that are similar to
their vibration first so they can get
used to the idea that there are other
beings at all. Then bit by bit as you
expand your awareness of the different
frequencies, you can encounter very
different societies from your own. So if
if your world is a different vibration
level, it's still a close frequency to
ours. Yes. If I were to fly towards your
world, would I ever get to it? If you
made the frequency shift, yes. If you
stayed in your own realm, you would go
right through it. Okay. As we would go
right through your own without making
the frequency shift. So when your
spaceship is here, it's physically here.
If it were because we make the frequency
shift. I could touch it and Oh yes.
Um now another question. You have you
have an excellent command of English. I
do not speak English at all. Okay. Daryl
speak. We are simply activating whatever within
We are simply activating whatever within
the channel's vocabulary is necessary to
translate the content. So that was my
question. Would you when you're speaking
to us through Daryl, could you speak to
us in French or Japanese or only if the
translation device is programmed with
those languages? Okay.
So, um another question in terms of
telepathy, do
you when I was growing up, my concept of
telepathy was if if you're telepathic,
you could understand and know everything
of any being you come into contact with.
Not always. That's not the truth. Not
always. telempathy if you wish perhaps more
telempathy if you wish perhaps more
precisely defines the idea and the idea
is that you are on a similar frequency.
Now you can understand quite a bit but
it may not be necessary for you to
understand absolutely everything there
is to understand about that being except
what it is that the interaction is for
going on between you at that given
moment that you can fully understand.
But recognize that telempathy once again
is not directly the reading of mind. It
is
identification strongly with another
individual. So that you are both
interpreting primal energy in similar
thought patterns. You are creating the
same thought patterns, mimicking their
thought patterns and that is how you
know what they think quote unquote. The
emotions are creating what you
understand. Telepathy is an emotionally
activated response. That is why
individuals that are most often in your
world considered to be in love are the
ones that most often as you observe them
the ones that know each other's
thoughts most quickly because being in
love is expressing
telempathy. You act as another
individual. You are in synchronous
accord with them. So you share and
create similar thoughts at the same
time. That is how telepathy works. You're not
That is how telepathy works. You're not
actually going into their mind and
pulling out the information. You are
thinking along the same
lines. Think wisely. I know you
do. Okay. I have a personal question. Um
over a period of 10 years, I shared my
life with a monkey. Um,
and often a lot of the dreams that I
recall that during that period, she was
in the dreams as representing this or
that. I'm not sure what, but she was in
a number of my dreams. I ever since she
died, she has not seen any of my dreams.
And I was wondering if you could
explain, first of all, I'm kind of
curious in terms of animals, in terms,
especially an animal like that that was
so close to me in terms of the way you
thought and so on, what the relationship
is between a human and a primate like
that. And also in terms of reincarnation
and just why I'm not why I would have
seen her in my dreams when she's alive
and I'm not now is her is this the
consideration you call a monkey or an
ape? This is a monkey. This is a
cappuccin monkey. Recognized in this
way. Animal consciousness in
general is an extension an expression of
the collective consciousness you are as
a society.
It is reflections and aspects of the
different aspects of you all of you in
many different
ways. In this particular
sense, the conversation as we perceive
it that went on between you while
physical life was maintained was
reflective of some of the ideas you were
discovering about yourself. Some of your
natural connection to creation in many
ways and also with you a specific
connection to a second density
consciousness. so that you could
incorporate what might be called second
density consciousness. That which was
prior to all that you all know as your
civilization, but yet to which you are
connected as another level, another
world, the earth, if you will, that
existed before the earth you now know.
And in that sense from which your
present situation was
created in drawing that connection
together and then in finally
incorporating it within yourself you
remove the need for the reflection
outside yourself. The communication now
goes on within you rather than between
you and another level. You follow me?
Yes. You are now those two levels and
now you are gathering up the second
which of course already implies that the
first was absorbed to the third and now
accelerating to the fourth. For
recognize the idea of acceleration from
level to level, density to density,
dimension to dimension is not at the
exclusion of all the dimensions you have
gone through. It is at the integration
and incorporation of all dimensions you
have gone through. Fourth
density is the blending of the third,
the second and the third. That was my
next question. Thank you.
But in terms of individual energy, would
she as a monkey and what personality she
had, did she is she reincarnable or is
her energy? Oh yes. Oh yes. Oh yes.
Now that particular
consciousness is now undergoing a
transcendence of evolution in soul terms
and will now
if she
chooses begin a new cycle of
incarnation out of the old cycle and can
begin the idea you would call we
understand it may be very confusing in
many ways. case. That is not the time to
explain the whole evolutionary cycle,
but would now begin the cycle you would
call
protohuman. And then we'll go on and
create her own third density reality and
move on into fourth eventually in
time. Reincarnation. When you are in a
cycle, usually reincarnate from what you
are into a similar idea.
But there are from different
reincarnational cycles evolutionary
steps as well. And that being is now
beginning an evolutionary step into a
different layer, a different
level. So while she has served you in
many ways, you have served her by
letting rub off on her some of the
aspects by which she can evolve into
what you now call the protohuman
consciousness to become more of let it
say an aware aspect of the consciousness
of which she is a part. A
deterministic aspect rather than simply
in your terms an instinctive one.
Is this making sense to Yes, it is. Is
that a Yes. Thank you very much. I have
one brief more thing. Brief more. All
right. Um, since everything is
synchronistic, would it not make more sense to speak of
would it not make more sense to speak of
other lives as opposed to past lives? It
is up to you. We simply use the
colloquial terminology since for many
individuals it is in your terms easier
for them to understand what we are
referring to. Whereas sometimes other
lives may carry a specific reference
across the time track you are living in
now. But yes, they are all simultaneous
and all lives simply are other lives and
even that is a separation. All lives are
one life expressing itself in all the
ways it can. Okay. Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Shedding.
Hi. Good evening.
Maggie, I'd like to thank you for share
your time with us. Oh, all the time in
creation. My pleasure entirely.
My stomach is spitting honestly.
Probably about sticking out too, but I
think I have to go through this and I'd
like to ask um for your help
if I possibly have the power, the
willpower and the energy to go through
with my vision.
I have dreamed about and visualized.
Yeah. Due to several events that have
occurred over the past year. For
example, um organiz my vision was to create a
um organiz my vision was to create a
special organization. Yeah. Which would
go on for years and years to come.
uh organizations for concern drivers
uh consider people support the
good habits support positive spirits and
um guide bad spirits or bad drivers or
in that sense okay and events have
occurred that I've had a bad accident
due to a a rowdy driver I've been out
for some time for what I've had um other
infections and also other events that
occurred which kind of led into that
position or led into that vision to
create such an organization. All right.
So you have used these experiences in a
positive direction. Yes, I have. Thank
you. And I feel kind of I feel real
strongly that I'm being pushed to do
such work in a sense. Yes. But do not
forget you are doing half the
pushing. One hand is the guide, one hand
is yours. It is always 50/50. Okay. or
if you wish 100 100
at this point I feel like I'm at a
um narrow path and I some click and go
ahead with my willpower I have available
or I wait until I get some other event
happening to me in order to go ahead
with all you need to do is act upon any
opportunity that presents itself to you
that excites you the most as we have
been discussing. Now this does not
necessarily have to involve well
willpower in the sense that most of you
usually mean that. We are not
necessarily implying that you mean it
this way. But as a delineation most
individuals that we have communicated
with in your society when they say
willpower usually evoke pictures of
struggle of conflict of force.
Willpower. The exercising of willpower
is an
allowance, not a struggle. It is simply
the knowingness that you are the
strength relative to the idea. Okay?
That your ability once again to desire
it is your ability to manifest it. So
act upon whatever excites you the most.
Situations do not have to seem connected
to one another to be connected to one
another. It is excitement that always
lets you know that they are connected to
one another. Even though they may not
appear to be on the surface, you have
the ability to manifest anything you
have imagined, anything you desire. You
are an infinite creator. As you all say,
you are made, all beings in creation are
made in the image of God. Well, yes, you
are. And that means you are an infinite
creator as well because that is the
image of the infinite creator. So act
like that simply know you have that
power simply because you have had the
ability to imagine what you wish to do.
The ability to imagine it is your sign
that you have the power to do it. And
were those signs perhaps then to go
ahead with my vision? Always whatever
excites you the most is the clearest
representation of the path you chose to
be. Be it. Yeah, it see it seems uh
really true. Okay. Be true to who you
are. Yes, you are. Enjoy. You are firmly
in the driver's seat.
Yes. I hope I will be and um I can help
a lot of people. Oh, yes you can. No
need to hope about it. Hope implies
despair. You are. You will. You are
assisting many individuals right now.
Thank you very much. Oh, thank you very
much. Good day.
Sure. And to you, my friend. Um, I have two
And to you, my friend. Um, I have two
things. One of the question is, and the
next one is the sharing. No. All right.
What I know you have discussed this idea
with us a few times on here. Thanks. And
I forgot what the heck you said. I kind
of at the time that you maybe you don't
need to be reminded. Well, maybe not.
No, because actually it's
not. It's interesting because the fear
that I'm approaching right now is
interesting to me. Where does it come
from? Still. Oh, yeah. And it's more
Still. Oh, yeah. And it's more
interesting to me almost than it's
fearful. Oh, very good. You are allowing
the energy to be read as excitement
rather than anxiety. True. But I also
know that there it's showing me
something and I forgot what to look for
to find out what it is that it's showing
you. Then you have already learned it.
Go on to something
else. Sometimes you can learn things so
quickly that you forget what the idea
was all about. Go on to something else.
If you need to be reminded, an incident
will occur to remind you.
Okay, you're not going to tell me. There
is nothing to tell. If you have
forgotten, you have changed your reality
to not include the need for the fear. Oh
no, I didn't forget the fear. I forgot
what the fear was supposed to symbolize.
It is one and the same idea. Oh, okay.
One in the same idea. Now, generally
then can it not simply be for that? Yes,
actually. That's enough. Yeah. Yeah,
that's fine. Oh, what? That's funny.
Yay. It's actually that leads into the
sharing that I wanted to do and um that
came came as a result of going out one
evening and having an interesting
experience with self invalidation. Oh,
what? And I thought it was rather odd
because I don't normally get into that
kind of um of an expression. All right.
Maybe not the you are now, but obviously
the you were ended. Oh, yeah. I
definitely did and I did it knowing that
there was something unusual about this
and that there was obviously some reason
I was getting practice in the situation
and and so the next morning I got up and
I was looking it over and um I thought
well that's interesting because the
situation that I attracted myself to
that I created
um an uneasiness and feeling bad about
myself da da I realized that I was the
one that was putting those thoughts
there and I was putting them there and
then saying, "Oh, well, this is the way
I feel in this situation. Why do I feel
that way?" Well, the why I felt that way
was because I was creating those
thoughts because you believe that way.
Yeah. Right. Right. I thought, "Ah,
okay. Now, that's interesting." And that
would certainly make valid the whole
evening of feeling bad just to have that
realization. So I went in and I sat down
at my piano and I played for my own
amusement not professionally but just
just for the enjoyment of it and it has
served as a perfect reflection immediate
reflection to me and on many many
occasions as a meditating tool and as a
reflection to show me from second to
second how I am dealing with myself.
guy. So, I was playing and I have many
many many times this
lifetime very heavily invalidated my
playing and I know I've played in other
lifetimes and I've played very well and
this lifetime I have all these awful
feelings of I don't like to stay in
other people's rhythm. I want to break
off into my own rhythm and then I
invalidate myself because I don't stay
in other people's rhythms and I play
differently from other people and I
don't fit into any of the normal
normally accepted roles that a pianist
fits into. Oh, I know.
I know. I know. And that's been an
interesting process in itself of
accepting that in myself and saying, "So
what? What the hell?" You know, I play
for me. Thanks. What the heaven?
[Music] I play for me. And it's okay for me to
I play for me. And it's okay for me to
play according to my own in rhythms with
inside. And it doesn't really matter
whether assisting an outside
person paradox when you are dealing with
paradoxes when you know you are dealing
with your higher consciousness. When you
know you are being your higher
consciousness for it is listening to
your own inner rhythm and being true to
that. That is what puts you in step with
everyone else. Right. Interesting. Even
though it seems the opposite, right? At
first it may seem so. Right. But you can
always use paradox to your advantage if
you have that point of view. True, true,
true, true. Remember, all the unity you
will experience upon your planet will be
the result of the granting of equality
and validity to all of the differences
within your culture. Right? And that's
certainly been where some of my greatest
um excitement have come from is by
breaking out of those normal expected
things that everybody agrees on and this
is the way you do it. I don't want to do
it. You know, you're still functioning
with an integrity even as you express
yourself differently. You are simply
learning to express yourself naturally
instead of normally. Right. Exactly. And
it seems abnormal but impactful. In
fact, it's totally normal. It's the most
natural world, right? For me. But that's
not even the win yet. Let me tell you
about this. There's um I was sitting
down at my piano and I was I was just
fresh out coming out of that realization
that I was putting those thoughts and
feelings of inadequacy there in my
space. and I sat down and I started
playing and old tape started running on,
you know, you're really messing up and
you're really not getting the notes
right and you're not in rhythm and what
if somebody's listening and all this
kind of stuff. And I I just stopped
right there and I went, "Well, you're
creating that, too." And I remembered
that how many times I listened to you
say to people, "Well, if you want to
become something, then be it and act as
if you are." And I thought that's always
been a little bit out of reach for me.
Like, well, maybe one of these days I
could do that, but I'm really not ready
for it now. Right now, I need all the
becoming processes to do those things,
but that's what I'm really used to and I
can I can deal with those tools, right?
Many of you play that tune. Yes.
Yeah. I sat there and I decided
that was real good. That went right by
me. Um, I sat there and I thought, "Okay,
Um, I sat there and I thought, "Okay,
well, I'm just going to I'm just going
to be a good pianist because right now
I'm just going to know that I'm a good
pianist." And that seemed very
courageous for me to do at the time.
And I thought, you know, really,
this is very weird and I don't really
expect anything to happen from her, but
you do it, right? Well, that's the way I
stepped out of it. this work. So anyway,
I sat down and I said, "I'm a great I'm
not a great pianist. I'm a good pianist
and I really know what I'm doing and I
do it well." And I could not believe
that obviously you could.
You're right. I did. I observed the most
interesting transition of my playing and
the relaxedness with which I was
approaching my pain. And even when I
screwed up, I just went, "Oh, hit a
wrong note. No big deal." And there was
none of this. Oh, there you've done it
again. And see what a bad pianist you
are. It was just, "Oh, I hit a wrong
note." And I went right into creating
the right note. You hit a note which
allowed you to determine whether or not
you prefer that one to be in the reality
of who you are or not. So, in that
sense, it is not a wrong note. Exactly.
Right. Right. Oh, but I sat there and I
played for two
hours and I would shift I would kind of
shift into the viewpoint, shift out of
the viewpoint, shift into the viewpoint,
shift out of the viewpoint and it was um
and more and more often I was able just
to maintain the viewpoint without the
effort and be it. And it felt so
wonderful. And then now I've been
applying that in other areas like this
area that I had the fear in and just
went, well, I just am it. I just am this
this person who is creating that thing
which it is that I want to create and
that I'm a little bit afraid of
creating. Yes. And it's starting to
unfold more. Yes. And the speed of
unfolding correctly just by my making
that decision is incredible. And I
thought about it afterwards and I
thought I thought I thought about it
afterwards and I thought now I'm gonna
want to explain this to somebody and I'm
gonna want to tell them how it is that I
went from point A to point B. Right.
That makes sense. Yeah. And um I thought
what is it exactly that I did because I
didn't do a process. I didn't do a step.
I didn't I went from one reality and
just led into the next reality. And all
I did was decide to decided that, oh,
I'm going to create the reality right
now. You created the you you wanted to
be and simply became it. Right. And then
I started acting like that person would
act. Okay. I was almost pretending to
myself and I just thought this is the
most magical tool anyone could ever
have. Yes. Just cuts all the credit and
goes straight to the heart of what it
is. That's it. All it takes if you are
willing to play it that way. Thanks for
helping me that real
[Music] braimo. We thank you.
Strawberry is still waiting.
You want to go
Steve? I already went you going to pick
me up at this ship or what?
You always give you always give me that
communication when I ask you that one
and then I give you this. What do you
think Daryl thinks of being called a
communication device?
This is enjoyable.
See, would you share with us um a little
bit of data about the energy gate on the
15th of this month that you've been
talking about?
It will simply be a
representation of a new level of
consciousness. Now,
Now,
coincidentally, we have just had an
example from someone about how you can
use the energy gate. Imagine right now,
right now that there is someone, a
future you on the other side of that
energy gate you call March 15th, eyides
of March, which by the way is your full
moon. Very powerful gate symbolically
for all of you. Imagine that the future
you you desire to become is already on
the other side of that gate, waiting for
you. Waiting.
Now, as
you step through that
gate, it will therefore be or can be for
you an
opportunity, if you wish to use it this
way visually, to step out of an old
shell and step into a new shell, a less
restrictive shell.
be through that gate your own walk-in.
You understand? I do. You, the you you
are now with no negative
connotation will
die. The new you you are on the other
side of that gate will be the new
representation of your spirit on the
other side of that gate. Whatever you
are now stays on this side of the
now stays on this side of the
gate. Anything you will have after that
will only be representative of that side
of the
gate. Nothing else. That will truly be
in many ways for all of you. Day zero,
moment zero.
Lovely. Happy birthday. birthday.
At this
timing, allow us to
extend once
again to our utter joy, our
appreciation in sharing with
us the sparkling
gift, the flame of your
heart, the joy of your love, the clarity
of your consciousness.
We thank you for this experience with
you. We thank you for being willing to
function as the ambassadors of your
world and allow us to function as the
ambassadors of
ours to bring us day by day that much
closer to sharing the same
dawn on each other's world.
which finds
you. Allow yourselves to be heaven on
earth. It is within. Good night.
How did everything go?
Thank you all for being here tonight. You're
You're
welcome. It's uh