Say, how are you all this evening of
your time as you create time to exist?
Allow us to begin this interaction of
your time
time
with a project for all of you to become
involved in if you wish.
Let us now create together, cocreate
together perhaps what can be considered
the first worldwide
project which will allow each and every
one of you to assist in a particular way
in the
acceleration of your planetary
consciousness and in the acceleration of
your involvement as full-fledged members
in the association of worlds. Very
simple project, very simple but very
effective, very impactful, very strong.
It will require your participation. It
is up to you. But it will have very
strong effect.
We will entitle this project and you may
if you wish use this title for your tape
this evening of your
time the peace
clock. Now peace
clock will take place as
follows starting now.
Each and every
individual in his or her own
way create a silent
create a silent
meditation for world
peace every single
day at exactly your 12 noon midday for
one full
minute. That's
all. Every day at your 12 noon in your
time zone, we recognize you have many
time zones in your time zone when it is
midday for one full minute. Silent
meditation for world
peace. And here is the second
And here is the second
part. It is as simple as the first
part. You will be
provided by instructions we will give to
the channel with
information that in your terms can be
copied and shared and given to as many
individuals as you can. Not pushing,
just sharing the information.
what you call the goal. The second half
is as
follows. to
have every single individual on your
planet doing this by your year
1990. What you call your New Year's Day
1990. Every individual on your planet
every day at 12 noon meditating for
world peace for one full minute.
So in your totems you have two of your
years in which to share the information
to the point where every individual is
involved by the first day of your year
1990. Very simple, very easy but very
impactful. What this will do, particularly because
What this will do, particularly because
you have different time zones upon your
planet that are calibrated, will create
one whole
band to be synchronized at any one time
with that one minute thought. And
then the next band and the next and the
next proceeding around your planet,
creating a literal mental movement of
electromagnetic energy around your world
to assist in accelerating it faster and
faster and faster into what you call
fourth density reality, more highly
accelerated physiological reality.
Now a few other ideas can go along with
this and that always is of course that
in any interaction you have with anyone
to approach that interaction in the most
positive loving creative way you can and
of course peaceful
way but
primarily these two
ideas every day 1 minute 12:00 noon
meditation for world peace and share
that information with as many
individuals as you And the information
will be
provided so that by your year
1,990 every individual on your planet
will be doing that every day for one
minute. Now if you
wish you can assist the acceleration by
also doing it for one full minute at
your midnight. That we will leave up to you
midnight. That we will leave up to you
as an
option. But the once a day when your
star is directly above you, when you are
in its full radiance, be it sunny or
cloudy, does not make a difference. When
you are in its full aligned radiance,
the focus for world peace for that one
minute will have a profound effect.
involve what you call
individuals, cities, whole communities,
your states as you call them, your
nations as you call them. Involve all
levels of your society in any way that
works best for you. Remind yourself when
it is 12 noon. either with any number of
your little alarms or your bells or your
notes. Any way, shape or form, involve
what you call your radio, your
television media, so that at 12:00 noon
every day, they will also allow the one
minute of silent
meditation, reminding everyone with a
tone, if you wish, with a
comment. Everyone participating
You will change your world in ways that
you have not imagined very
rapidly. Then you will be accelerating your world
Then you will be accelerating your world
at such a pace that if this is in your
terms accomplished by your year
1990, then that year and beginning from
that year, many things will happen that you
year, many things will happen that you
will maybe not
believe. But you will have created
cocreated with us far more of an
opportunity to truly begin more blatant
interactions. In many ways it is not the
purpose to increase the interactions
with us that you do this. It is the
purpose that you increase the
interactions with yourselves that you
become one world and truly
representative and truly reflective of
your shall we say status as a member of
the association of worlds.
This information will be provided in
what you would call written form for you
to share, to
copy. And you may begin now if you wish
tomorrow of your time, tonight of your
time. And then allow in the sharing of
the information more and more
individuals to become synchronized with
you every day, more and more every day.
A very simple project with profound
effects. The peace clock.
In a sense, what shall be called the
motto or if you wish the slogan of the
event shall be the phrase peace in our
lifetime.
We thank you for any and all
participation in your willingness to
create the world you say you desire to
create and in allowing us to
reflect this event, this project to you
in this
co-creation. We thank you for cocreating
this dream with us. Now we have called
your year upcoming your year 1988 the
year of conviction.
It means applying the knowledge you have
been learning in physical ways in
physical actions boldly with conviction
with integrity but with
conviction. We may arbitrarily label
your year therefore of 1989 the year of
dedication. And because of the effect
that the idea of the peace clock and
many other things you will be doing will
have, we can now label your year 1990
the year of
ignition. Allow yourselves to truly feel
the strength of your power for you are
empowered. Every single individual has a
profound impact upon your entire planet.
More and more and more of you becoming
synchronized in this way within the
peace clock format will literally spin
you before you know it into fourth
density into synchronicity all around
you.
We thank you for this opportunity to
interact with you as ambassadors of your
world and allowing me to interact with
you as an ambassador of mine. In return
for this gift of your
sharing and reminding you first of all
that in all these
sharings, never at any moment believe
anything that I have said just because I
have said it.
Involve yourself in the information and
use what works for you. What does not
work for you, you will find some other
way. In return for the gift of all the
sharing that you do with
us, I will ask you now, how may I serve
you? Hi, Bishar. Good day to you. I'd like to
Hi, Bishar. Good day to you. I'd like to
ask you if you could help me. Every day
I have a habit of somehow hurting
myself. Somehow in what ways? Well, not
every day really badly hurting myself,
but sometimes I can and sometimes I
can't. In what ways? Well, do you mean
physically? Yes. Such as you mean
falling, bumping? Um, tripping.
Tripping. In PE, I hurt my right leg a
lot. Oh, all right. My whole leg,
including the foot. Oh, all right. I was
wondering if you could help me with
that. Oh, thank you very much.
There are on your planet many, shall we
say, quote unquote,
disciplines, not meaning it to be in a
structured sense, but there are many
methodologies of learning flow of
motion, what you call your PowerPoint of
motion, your balance of motion.
Are you involved in either any form of
what you would call martial art or dance
idea? No, I don't think so. Do either of
these excite you?
A little. Not very much. Oh, all right.
What do you imagine the idea to
be of what you call martial art motion?
What is your definition of that idea?
Tai Chi, slow dancing. All right.
Do you feel when you think of this idea,
do you feel the idea? Do you feel the
essence of the information of the motion
that is imparted that is taught in that
type of method?
Didn't quite catch the right. Think of
the idea of Tai Chi on your planet. Mhm.
Do you see? Can you in your imagination
see yourself making those motions?
Yeah. All right. When you imagine that
you are creating those motions, smooth,
flowing, fluid, solid, deep, heavy,
light motions, how does it feel to do
that? Good. All right. How?
Good. All right. How?
Um,
good in what way? The motion. Um, how
does it allow you to feel? Relaxing.
Yeah, relax. Anything else?
Um, no, not really. Look at the picture
in your mind's eye. What is your
posture? And most importantly, what is
your attitude? Are you
Are you
serene? Are you focused? Are you more
alert and observant about things going
on around you? Yeah. All right.
Then whether you actually physically
participate in those particular types of
classes or not you can adopt that
attitude that site to see the
interreationship of one motion to
another. That is actually what those
methodologies teach you. To see the
interreationship of the motion you are
with the motion of everything else
around you. For in a sense you are
creating everything around you to be in
motion. But they are all relative
motions to you. Begin to synchronize
your motion with the motion of
everything around you. So you are moving
as one
idea. Moving as one
event, one fluid event. Begin to see
this in your mind's eye. Feel it in your
cellular structure
bodily. If you wish at any time on your
own again without necessarily having to
ritualize it in a class
format experiment
pretend the idea of motion out in
different ways. Pretend you are running
but pretend you are running slow
motion. Watch every step. Feel the
balance of your body.
Begin to familiarize yourself with the
relative motion of you and the ground,
you and the sky, you and all the other
people around you. See your motion as it
connects to their motion. See yourself
as one aspect of the whole motion around
you. Okay? You follow me? Yeah. You will
begin to synchronize and flow.
The only reason you are experiencing to
some degree the idea of the tripping and the
degree the idea of the tripping and the
pain is because your energy is
accelerated in certain ways because of
information you have been exposed to and
simply other things in your normal
environment are not in that sense moving
at the same rate. You are out of step
with what has been taught to you to be
your normal environment.
Now you can redesign that environment
and allow it to acclimate to your pace
so it matches your vibration. So you are
not tripping over an environment that is
moving more slowly than you are.
Understand? Yeah. Does this assist you?
Yes, it does. Thank you. Well, thank you
very much. Thank you, Bashar.
Sharing.
Good day, Bashar. And to you, good day.
I have a sharing. All right. Speak up so
that all may share. Uh, I've been doing
what excites me the most. Oh, all right.
And I just got back. Put the whole thing
up. I just got back yesterday from the
Yucatan where I was digging around the
Mayan ruins. All right. And um, but the
sharing I really have to I want to tell
you about is I went to Florida and went
swimming with the dolphins. I got back 3
weeks ago and I spent one week uh
swimming with the dolphins and I said
hello from you. Oh, thank you. And um I
did as you suggested and I thought
myself a dolphin instead of a human in
interaction. Nice. And I gave them
flowers and the first day I was in the
water with five dolphins, one dolphin
pretty much adopted me. Her name was
Squirt. And um she wouldn't let any of
the other dolphins play with me. And we
had a very physical relationship for 4
days. Nice. Where all of the dreams I
had in the last half year, she literally
allowed me to fulfill them. Well, thank
you. Um the dreams I had of swimming
side by side. The first day we swam side
by side and she would touch me and uh
gnaw on my arm. And the second day, uh,
she wanted to roll with me and would
literally lift me out of the water, her
belly to mine. Nice. And, um, no one
else was having any physical
relationship, but hers and mine was very
physical. Nice. And the second day, I
got a little frightened by her
willingness to, you know, 400 lb of
dolphin on me. And I got afraid and she
sensed it and she backed off. And I
didn't allow my dream to become real.
the dream of rolling in the water with a
dolphin. It is still real. Well, the
third day I went back in the water with
her and I telepathically told her that I
would love to roll with her if she would
allow it. And not only did she allow it,
but the minute I got in the water, she
came up to me bellyto belly three times
and we rolled. I was hugging her and we
rolled in the water. Hug stoic. And I
really see how dreams and the awake
voice is the same is one thing. Yes. So
um I I'm really very excited because
since then the dreams I've had are that
I'm no longer a human interacting with a
dolphin but I am a dolphin. And um my
question that I do have is I know I have
a dolphin spirit guide. We discussed now
I know dolphins are telepathic and are
of one consciousness. Did she basically
is she my spirit guide or did she just
pick up there was connection with the
idea of your spirit guide
through that particular dolphin
functioning as a channel?
Okay. Um, I've had some experiences
since then of literally losing the
vertebrae in my back and becoming
physically a fish where at times dolphin
is not a fish. Thank you. A mammal.
Now understand one thing. We do not tell
you the idea of identifying as dolphin
to dolphin to lose your humanity. It is
the idea of blending and becoming both
in one.
So do not forsake the idea of your
humanity. The idea is to blend and meet
on the same level and recognize that you
are both the same type of soul and
therefore you both are dolphin human
dolphin. Understand? Yes. Merge in that
sense. Yes. Fuse in that sense. And you
can have some physiological
manifestation to some degree to assist
you in that merger, in that fusion. But
do not misunderstand that you must
forsake your humanity. The idea is to
blend, not to get rid of.
Okay? Cuz um I literally feel just a
desire to be with the dolphins and I
find I'm very telepathic with them. Yes.
Is there you can apply that into your
human interactions as well.
Remember that you are being taught to
apply these things so they can be used
throughout your entire civilization. You
can apply it to interaction with not
only dolphin, human but also animal,
vegetable, mineral.
Yes. But if the excitement leads me into
the dolphin, I'm just wondering by all
means follow your specific excitement
now. But we are saying it will give you
an understanding of the capabilities you
have of tapping into all layers of
consciousness, not just dolphin. So it's
a blending of the two, not that I have
to be one or the other. No, no, no, no,
no. Is there any direction with the
dolphins that you could assist me with?
Because more assistance than you already
have? This is not sufficient. No, it it is.
This is not sufficient. No, it it is.
You said you're having a good time. I'm
having a great time and um I do want to
thank you because every time I see that
when I trust myself and it takes me to
where the next thing is that excites me.
Then that's your answer right there.
Yes. There is nothing I need to give
you. There is nothing you need from me.
You're doing just fine. Well, I wanted
to thank you and I wanted to share with
everyone that when you do trust
everything really is beautiful. Yes. Oh
well, thank you very much for your
co-creation and allow us perhaps as a
reminder to let you all know it is all
right. You don't have to be worried if
there's nothing to worry about.
Thank you very much. Thank you very
much. Sharing.
Sharing.
Hello Bashar. How are you? Good day. I'm
u working at doing what excites me the
most full-time. I haven't quite gotten
there yet. Oh, I see. But I've uh You
haven't? No. Oh, but I'm I've heard of
this uh bed that is It has um bed. Yeah.
Yes. It's a bed that I had in mind maybe
having my clients
um lay on this bed to help them. It's It
does u It has a Tesla coil, has 42
magnets, and it's also lined with
crystals. Yes. And it's supposed to make
the impulsate the same as the earth. It
can. Yes. And can create electromagnetic
alignment can accelerate many
individuals. Now do remember sometimes
it will have the capability of
accelerating individuals through any
negativity that they need to work out.
So it may seem to be a negative effect
on some individuals at first simply
because they need to integrate some
ideas within themselves before they go
on to expressing it in more positive
ways. But it will have an accelerative
effect on most individuals. If this
excites you, by all means pursue it.
There is much you can learn about the
idea of the pulsations of
electromagnetic fields in which you are
all immersed and which can in your terms
have an effect upon your physiological
cellular structure.
This is what I wanted to know because I
got excited about it, but I didn't know
if I was just going off on a tangent or
if it really would be helpful in my
teaching people about creating their own
realities. If it would not have been
helpful in your teaching, you would
never have been excited by it. Oh, good.
Remember that that's what excitement is.
The sign that something you have
attracted in your life is representative
of the methodology that you as the
person you are can best use. That's why
you get excited about it. The things
that you cannot use to the best of your
ability as who you are, you don't get
excited about. Very good. Understand?
Yes. Does that assist you? Yes, it does.
Remember also do not assume that you are not yet
also do not assume that you are not yet
doing it. Assume that everything you are
doing is not a quote unquote step
towards the doing of the thing that
excites you the most but is a part of
the thing that excites you because
everything that's going on in your life
at this particular moment is the most
important thing that can be happening in
your life. There are no extraneous
creations. Everything that's going on is
something you need to look at and absorb
the information from in order to be the
person you say you want to be. So it is
not a matter of getting to that place.
It is a matter of understanding that
whatever is going on now is
representative of the thing that excites
you the most. Understand? Yes. Thank you
for reminding me of Thank you for
broadening your definition. Okay. Thank
you much. You're welcome. Shannon. Hello
Bashar. Having a good day. I'd like to
get a little information on uh different
levels that you're communicating. I had
went to a health federation convention
one time and a woman showed me how to
flow energy to a person who was ill.
Yes. With, you know, imagine the left
hand on the right hand. Imagine it's
behind their neck. And I had done that
recently to two people. I could float
the energy. The first time they got the
energy and you could see they got it and
everything, but the second time it's
like a door shut in your face, like I'm
interfering with their process or
something. Sometimes remember a healer
only provides an atmosphere, a vibration
in which the other person can then take
from that what they want to match that
vibration if they wish to help center
themselves. They heal themselves. An
individual whose process in your
terminology would be interfere with by
anything more than what you've already
given them will shut it down. An
individual in that sense who may be
working through things and not need or
want any more of the energy will shut it
down, will refuse to take anymore.
Simply recognize that whatever an
individual is attracted to you for for
the amount of time they are attracted to
you for is sufficient. Give as you wish
to give from your heart and then assume
they have gotten what they need from
you. If they need anything else, they'll
get it from someone else or somewhere
else. flow at whatever rate is best for
you to flow and know that you have help
them in whatever way you need to
understand. I understand that. What I'm
wondering about is it's like the person
didn't consciously even know anything's
going on. It's like another level. It's
of course you are all aware of
everything that's going on on some level
of your consciousness.
Well, if a person was like this guy was
real weak. He couldn't even sit up in a
chair and I could flow him energy set up
the first time and for a while. But if
it occurred to me that maybe I hadn't
really asked the person if they wanted
this, but if they if they had
consciously on consciously decided they
did want some help, would that then they
have hit upon what you may call the crux
of the matter? Generally speaking, first
time they will receive the energy on
levels that they have open that they may
not know they have. Once you have given
them an example of the energy that they
then can create for themselves, in a
sense, it actually is up to them to
create it the next time.
So in a sense you are showing them what
is possible. Now if they fear it they
may shut it down in terms of getting it
from you or they may shut it down
knowing through their higher
consciousness that now next time it's
their responsibility to generate the
energy not yours. There can be many
reasons for what you call the shutdown.
Most of them will have to do with them
taking the responsibility to be
self-empowered to generate the energy
themselves one way or another. Whether
they shut it down through fear or
through trust. Understand? I understand.
So the idea is you can if you wish let
them know you are doing that. If in some
cases you haven't assume that they have
attracted themselves to you for that
purpose. You can always let them know
but then let them decide on whatever
level they make the decision as to
whether or not to involve themselves in
allowing you to be the reflection from
that point forward or allowing
themselves to be the reflection from
that point forward which is the purpose
of any healing anyway to give the power
back to the individual. you are helping
so that they can help themselves.
Right. Thank you. Well, thank you for
acting as the first catalyst.
Sharing. Hello, Bashar. And you good
day. Uh Bashar, first I'd like to share.
I believe you mentioned once that
there's no such thing as a coincidence.
Not in an accidental sense.
Coincidencees. Yes. Well, I bought your
empowerment workshop 3 weeks ago and I
became all prepared to listen to it and
the first tape was blank. I see. How is
your bodily health? Uh, very well. It's
going through an accelerated change
though, which is which it has been doing
for the past 10 years. All right. Um,
what way? Oh, uh, not enough time to
explain. Why is he all right? My my
my one of my questions is is is a
twofold question actually. The nature of
the second question won't be quite
clear. The first one is in an aid to
enhance my ability to be of service to
man. Yes. I feel I believe beyond a
shadow of a doubt that I am to meet an
extraterrestrial. But you already have
many times in dream state.
Um many of you have many times in dream
state. Why isn't this in why doesn't
this come through to my conscious mind?
Because the idea is to not focus on the
need of us to be able to accomplish what
you have chosen to accomplish by
choosing to be born on your planet. You
do not need us to accomplish your
mission. Your mission is completely
self-contained within the idea you have
created yourself to be. We have
purposely removed oursel from many of
the predictions and sensing as your
psychics upon your planet so that you
will not believe that you need to run to
us to have the power to do what you
chose to do.
But if I believe that you're part of
that, we are in a way. But the idea now
at the time that exists upon your planet
now is to have first of all the
conviction to do it without knowing we
are there. That's what creates the
atmosphere that makes it more conducive
for you to know we are there. You must
take the first step. You must meet us
halfway. I see. By knowing that you are
capable of doing whatever you need to do
without us. When you know you are
capable of doing it without us, then you
create the ability for us to interact
more boldly. But we have what your science
boldly. But we have what your science
fiction writers have called a
non-inference directive. We can touch you. We can
directive. We can touch you. We can
whisper and interact in many different
ways. Even the interaction you are
perceiving now is but a
whispering, a very very faint reflection
of the interactions your world and our
worlds will be having. The idea is that
we choose to remain obscure so that we
are not looked upon as your saviors. I
realize you're not our saviors, but I
realize that there is also a purpose for
you. We understand. But the primary
purpose first primary purpose is of you
to yourselves to your own world for you
to begin doing the things that excite
you in your life because you can do them
without needing us. You have interacted
many times in what you call the
non-physical reality. The way to create
an ability for us to interact more often
in physical reality is to not wait for
us to interact, to begin doing what you
know you need to be doing to express who
you are in the fullest way you can
express it. That's the paradox. As soon
as you are fully you and don't need us
at all and don't care that we're even
here, we'll tap you on the shoulder. You
must open the door for us. It's your
planet. You have to open the door for
us. The way you open the door for us is
not simply by wishing for us to interact
with you. Not by the desire in that
sense for us to interact with you, but
by expressing more of a desire for you
to interact with yourselves as equal.
Because only when you do that among
yourselves do you create the vibration
that makes it possible for us to be able
to come through into your dimension and
see you face to face. We are of a
different vibratory field than you. We
cannot interact with you in any way that
would appear to be physiological unless
there is some meeting of the minds or
some pre-arranged purpose that fits the
timing that serves the best of all
concern. Now we are not saying that you
cannot find in your life that you may
have a facetoface encounter when the
timing allows it when it serves the
purpose that has been agreed upon by you
and whomever you shall meet face to
face. Although do understand one other
thing. Many times what many of you call
a face-to-face encounter is actually
simply such a strong telempathic
encounter you think it's physical and
it's not. The idea however is that your sense
not. The idea however is that your sense
is correct. Your basic identification
sense and essence and direction is
correct. You have already interacted
many times. But the idea in recognizing
your mission, your purpose in life is to
do the thing it excites you the most to
do with integrity. You have all the
ingredients in your toolkit necessary.
Do it. Don't wait for us. If we have not
met you face to face, then I will simply
ask that you must trust the timing is
not appropriate. Because when the timing
is appropriate, nothing will keep us
away. Nothing. We desire and love you
all and wish to interact with you in
ecstatic ways. When the timing is
appropriate and the way we perceive will
serve all of you best, nothing will keep
us away. But you must trust that we have
done this many times with many different
worlds. We know what we're doing.
Understand? Yes. Does this assist you?
Yes. and the second half.
Um, you you seem to possess an
incredible amount of knowledge. Well, so
do
you. All of you do. You see, we do not
know everything, but we know everything
we need to know to be who we are.
Because of what you and us have
co-created these interactions to be, you
are willing to allow us to see things
about some of you that you simply do not
allow yourselves to see about yourself.
because you are still in the habit of
using an exteriorized reflection to
reflect back to you what you actually
already know. That's our knowledge. Our
knowledge, all the knowledge we seem to
possess are all the things you already
know that you simply have not yet given
yourself the ability nor the permission
to know that you
know. We are only reflections of what
you are in many ways. Now, yes, in our
civilization, we have different
experiences. Yes, we have had a
different history. We may have a more
expanded point of view and in that sense
let us say empirically there may be a
few more things that we may know
analytically speaking than you may know
but you also know many things we do not
simply because our civilizations are
different. We have different needs of
applications. You have different needs
of applications. You all know many
things and you know more than you think
you know if you would give yourself but
half a chance to realize that you do
know these things. Could you tell me
something about myself that you know
that I don't about myself?
I have already to some degree done so in
the sense that you are a complete kit as
you are. That you have everything you
need to create everything you want as
you are without needing to involve
anyone else especially on our side. But you are
else especially on our side. But you are
already involved. You are already
intertwined. You have had many
interactions. You've already laid out
your basic plans and agreements and you
are fulfilling them. And you will
fulfill them more quickly when you start
acting as a complete individual already
without waiting for anyone else to help
you feel more complete.
I see timing is all within each
individual. Any agreements you have made
with anyone else especially with us
always play out in perfect timing. And
the timing frame is always within you.
Not in the sense of saying through your
ego structure, all right, all right all
right all right all right all right all
right all right I think the timing is
now meet me now but the idea simply is
once again to trust that if you are
doing the thing that excites you the
most and you know beyond a shadow of a
doubt that you have made these timing
agreements that you have made these
interaction agreements and that you will
be interacting more blingly with us then
trust that if you're not interacting now
you are only following your own best
timing when the timing occurs nothing
will prevent it from occurring because
that's what you're open to Understand?
Yes. You know you're open to it. So get
on with your life. The sooner you get on
with your life, the more fully you live
your life, the quicker you will get to
the time of the timing of our
interaction. But don't live your life
because of that purpose. Do not make
that more paramount than anything else
in your life. Make the living of your
life the most important thing of all
because you will never be this you
again. And you have never been this you
before. And the you are now only does
have one life to live. Living it to the
fullest is the fulfillment of your
purpose. and mission in life. The way
you go about it is up to you. But the
way you go about it are simply the
methodologies you choose to express the
purpose of your life. The projects in
your life, the goals in your life, the
way you express yourself in life, they
are not the purposes of your life. They
are the way you express the purpose. The
purpose of your life is to be the
fullest you you can be. And you do that
by following what excites you the most
with integrity. Everything else will
fall into place. Everything in perfect
timing. Does this help you? Yes. Well,
thank you very much. Thank you very
much. The color green and blue can be very
The color green and blue can be very
assistive to you, both to you personally
and to the work that you do with others.
Hello. And good day to you. I have some
deep questions. Deep questions. All
right. Would you like a shovel?
I I think I need them. All right.
Perhaps what you call a power shovel.
Are they that deep? Yes. Oh, all right.
Reed wedge them up if you will. Okay.
For 20 years, I've been in the work as a
healer. Yes. But for the last 5 years, I
have spent with my husband who had
cancer. Yes. I'm now ready to go back
into the work. Oh, all right. Have a
good time.
I am finding dredged up from my memory
are a lot of things such as changing a
molecular structure,
dematerializing. Um Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
Yes. Yes. Having um just plain
disappearing. Yes. Or just plain
disappearing. Yes. Yeah. Or just plain
appearing at certain places and talking
to them. Um explain to me. Explain to
you. Very simple. Very simple.
Understand everything is vibration.
Everything. Remember that all solid as
you say quote unquote solid matter is
only energy vibrating at a particular
pitch. When you change the pitch then
you can accelerate or decelerate the
vibratory matter the material and you
can create
dematerializations or
rematerializations. It's simply a matter
of scale where you are on the vibratory
scale of things. So as you accelerate
the vibrations, you can accelerate
yourself. You can actually even
decelerate yourself beyond someone
else's ability to perceive you. It is
the same analogy as what you call the
electromagnetic spectrum. You know that
there is what you
call radio waves, infrared radiation
which is below your natural ability to
perceive although not so much anymore.
And there is in your terms ultraviolet
light and X-ray emission and gamma
radiation, cosmic radiation and what
have you that you believe is above more
highly accelerated above your ability to
perceive it. Although not so much
anymore for some of you. In what you
call the middle is what you have termed
the visible spectrum. The colors of
light that you are aware of that are
within the range of your senses to
perceive. Well, the entire universe is
structured this way. Physical matter in
a sense is simply one of the vibratory
frequencies of the prime energy of
creation. And when you accelerate its
vibrational rate, it can accelerate
itself beyond the ability of that
plane's perceptive range of senses.
Understand? Yes, I did. So the way you
accelerate yourself most rapidly is as
we have been discussing by doing the
things that are representative of the
things that excite you the most. Because
excitement is that energy of
acceleration, is that energy of
alignment, of synchronization with the
vibration that represents your quote
unquote higher self. That's what
excitement is. And you can accelerate
yourself. And by being that type of
person that lives spontaneously in great
ecstasy and joy, in love and service,
you then radiate at a particular pitch,
at a particular tone. All individuals
who then come into your sphere of
influence can pick up on that vibration.
And if they are willing to match that
frequency, they can then elevate
themselves, accelerate themselves to
match that frequency and be in that
sense of the same frequency and be of
the same pitch and be of the same
balance and the same level of
hell. Is this a system?
Yes, very much so.
Um, one of my main questions is that it
happens without my knowing it's going to
happen. It's very spontaneous. Yes,
that's correct. Yes. When you are fully
in the moment, you are less
analytical. And therefore, when you are
less analytical, you can allow some
quote unquote portions of your
consciousness that may in the past have
been allowed to stand in your way to get
out of the way.
You know these things intuitively and
instinctively. You don't have to know
them analytically to allow them to work.
And many times in not knowing that it's
going to happen analytically at all in
allowing it to happen spontaneously is
the way for you to allow it to happen
most easily because then you don't
analyze it to death. You don't stop the
flow. When you get used to knowing that
it is a natural part of you and you
simply allow it to flow spontaneously
all the time, then you can bring back
in, shall we say, a little more
analytical awareness of when and where
it's going to occur, how you can apply
it in that sense, consciously, how you
can direct it consciously. But by all
means let it happen spontaneously
because then you will know in that sense
that your life is simply the product of
positive synchronicity and
co-incidence on an instinctive level.
This does not mean you lose reason but
it means that for now it may be the best
way you have of allowing yourself to
simply let it flow through you in what
feels like a more natural way.
Understand? Yes, I understand. Well,
thank you for your choices and thank you
for your conviction and thank you for
all you have learned in all the
situations and circumstances you have
attracted into your life that can help
you apply your service in what you may
call more expanded and beneficial
ways. Thank you for the learning process
you have created yourself to be. Thank
you. Do you have anything else you'd
like me to know before I step out on it?
Yes. Okay. You have now again not
has allowed more clarity to exist in the
non-physical consciousness that can now
assist you. Okay. Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you very much. Bye.
Sharing.
Hi, Bashar. And good day to you. Um, I
have a sharing. Oh, all right. By all
means, be bold, speak up, and share.
Okay. Um, the last time I talked to you,
which was several weeks ago, I asked you
about geometry and tetrahedrrons. Yes.
And my interest in that idea
and uh since then I've been doing a lot
of reading, a lot of research on the
subject and on physics and metaphysics.
And uh I listened to the set of tapes
that you did about the subject last last
year, I think.
And um my life has changed.
um my life has changed.
Statement. Yes, it is. All right. It's
completely different. Well, thank you.
Then you are a completely different
person. Remember that as well. Yes, I
am. Um the biggest change that this has
Um the biggest change that this has
brought about for me is that I I decided
to leave my job because I wanted to do
this full-time because it excited me so
much. And uh most of the time I I am in the
And uh most of the time I I am in the
excitement rather than the anxiety of oh
how I'm going to support myself. You
mean unlike now?
Pardon? You mean most of the time you
are in the excitement unlike now?
Um no I'm in the excitement now also. Oh
maybe when you said that line. Ah yes.
Yes. Are you still in the excitement?
Yes. All right. I'm very excited right
now. All right. Yes. Yes. Continue.
Okay. Now, the other thing that's been
happening, yes, recently is that I have
begun channeling. And the entity that
I'm channeling tells me that she's
connected to this idea of geometry and
its connection with physical and
non-physical reality. All right. And um
I
uh wanted to ask you if you had any
clarification for me about what the
connection is between these two aspects
of my life right now.
Nope.
What clarification do you think you
need?
I am Yes. Yes. Yes. Oh, I'm still
excited. Well, yes. Yes. I am living
with a lot more uncertainty in my life
now than I am living with uncertainty.
Yes. Is it paying the rent?
Is it paying the rent?
So far, yes. All right.
[Music] And And yes. And
And what? And when will you create it to
be certainty?
Even though it may be left to be
spontaneous, not the idea of certainty,
meaning that every single step is
planned out. Yes. But when will it be
certainty that everything in your
terminology that is uncertain will still
fit in the positive flow? Is it that way
now? Oh, yes. Oh, all right. Living with
uncertainty then for you is very
exciting. Yes, it is. All right. It's
also very different from the way I used
to be. Yes, of course. Mhm. So
again, all you have expressed to me is
that you're having a wonderful time, but
you are discovering many wonderful
things. I am. And that you are smack, as
you say, in the middle of the process
you wish to be in. Yes. What do I need
to tell you? I guess nothing. I just
wanted to share it with you because my
talking to you about it was very
instrumental in having the trust to do
it. Oh, but remember talking to yourself
is what was instrumental. You can talk
to me all day long. I can talk to you
all day long. Our talking to each other
will have nothing to do with your
decision to tell yourself to create it
to be instrumental. Well, thank you.
will thank you for your conviction and
your willingness to allow what has
formerly in your society been called the
unknown to be known in the sense that
you always know it will contain
surprises only of a positive nature
because that's the decision you have
made about the type of person you want
to be. Yes. Thank you for your sharing
in this case. What you have had to say
and share with all sums it all up far
more concisely than anything else we
would have to say. Well, thank you.
Well, thank you for choosing to function
as an equal.
Thank you. You are welcome.
Do you have any more um pointers for me
as far as the
[Music] There's a little telepathy going on.
There's a little telepathy going on.
Yes, I do.
Oh, all right. I've been waiting four
weeks to get up here to talk to you.
Why?
I guess I haven't really, cuz I've made
the changes anyway. No. Yes, you have.
Okay. Thank you. Thank you very
much. Thank you very much.
Also, thank you for the sparkling
opportunity to generate so much humor.
That humor is truly enlightening. Sharing.
Sharing.
Hello, Bashar. And to you, good day.
This is the first time I've ever gotten
to talk to you and I'm really excited.
But I'm scared. First time we have
interacted with any of you. Do
understand. No matter quote unquote how
many times it seems someone may have
interacted with us, every time is
literally the first time.
There's something that I want to share
with you and I have a couple of
questions about sharing. All right.
Please. I read a series of books by a
woman by the name of Lynn Andrews and a
medicine woman and the series of books
that came thereafter and these books
really excited me. Oh, thank you. And
the questions that I have come from
having read those books. All right. Um
the um first question I want to ask as
well as exciting me the the books were
about an Indian medicine woman and this
woman was an apprentice to this ind
Indian medicine woman. Yeah. And it
excited me the idea of possibly being
able to follow in her footsteps. But it
also brought back a memory of an
experience I had about 12 years ago
where a person came into my life for a
period of time and he was a Yaki Indian
and during that period of time I felt as
if I had been somewhat taken over and it
was a very frightening experience to me
and I'm having simultaneous responses to
these books excitement and fear at the
same time and I considered the
possibility that maybe I might be able
to ask you what happened that it during
that experience of 12 years ago. So
possibly I could come to terms with it
and go beyond that and be able to follow
my excitement. All right. Thank you very
much. You were to some degree
momentarily displaced. Now this does not
mean that you could really be off your
path. That's not possible. But the idea
of the disorientation, the displacement,
what appear to be a taking over was to
some degree an
immersion of yourself in a different
aspect of yourself in some aspects that
you may call past lives to orient you
towards understandings you had back then
about similar types of interactions and
recognitions of your own primal power
and connection to nature. Some of the
idea to some degree simply brought up
old fears within you. The recognition of
that level of power that all of you have
many times makes it feel as if you are
being taken over. In a sense, the only
thing you are being taken over by is a
higher aspect of yourself. But if it
comes with the idea of old fears, it may
seem to be a negative event. Now, some
of it also was a reflection on the part
of that other individual again to some
interactions you had had in other lives
as well. not only with that individual
but with many other individuals wherein
you did face circumstances at that time
that were basically negative in
nature. Now you are given opportunity at
that time to begin to integrate. You
were in a sense placed on a particular
facet of your path to allow you to begin
to integrate those old ideas and
redefine yourself in whatever way you
really chose to define yourself. Now
bringing yourself now to the
contemporary recognition of the same
idea but being able to tap into it now
from a positive point of view after
having in your terms assimilated all the
old ideas. Understand so far? Yes. You have
ideas. Understand so far? Yes. You have
walked that path a few times in
different ways. you can walk it. Now in
a sense to some degree and I do not
necessarily mean this literally with
regard to the specific individuals
mentioned in that book you have talked
about but to some degree the footsteps
you would be following in would be your
own. You have created a loop, a time
cyclical loop of meeting yourself coming
from many different
directions, so to speak. That yaki
warrior to some degree represented a
reflection, a polarity reflection of
aspects of your own male self in many
other lives, of your own balance of
power connected to nature.
understand. Yes. Is this of assistance?
Yes. Bishar, may I ask one more
question? Yes. I'm planning on going to
New Mexico and Arizona in the month of
December, and I want to ask you if
there's any place you'd like to tell me
I should go. Where do you feel like
going? I'm not certain yet, Sedona. Is
that a question? Yes. Why is it a
question? Because I'm asking for your
guidance. I see. But I am giving it back
to you through you. You understand that
when you are most attracted to a place,
there is a reason for that degree of
attraction. Now, we have discussed the
Sedona Arizona area on your planet as a
very highly magnetic vortex that can in
fact put many of you in touch with many
aspects of yourself coming and going
from many different directions on many
different levels of reality. You already
know that. If that excites you, if
you're drawn to that idea, then by all
means, go there. Make it a statement.
Don't leave it as a question. If that's
where you're most attractive, if that's
the idea that comes up more often than
not in your mind, then that in and of
itself is the answer.
Understand? Yes. Our guidance to you is
to follow your strongest instinct.
It's usually strong for a reason.
Understand? Yes. So, is Sedona where you
will go? Yes. Well, thank you. Thank
you, Bashar. Now, one moment. One
moment. A brief
A brief
explanation. When you take the
conviction in your own hands to make a
statement out of a question, you open
many more doors of perception to
us. Now that you have made it a
statement, I can tell you a few other
things. Oh boy.
You understand the delicate balance of
this idea. Before you create these ideas
to be a statement, the doors of our
perceiving more of your awareness are
locked tight as surely as if they were
welded shut. We do not perceive
information that would interfere with
your process of aligning yourself with
the fullest you you can be. Once you
align yourself and turn your questions
into statements of conviction and trust
your instinct, those doors are cast wide
open. A great glare of light from your
inner self shines out and we can see
very clearly more of the path you are
creating yourself to be and then can
comment on it because then it's only a
reflection we are giving you back of the
light you are giving to us understand
yes conviction is the key always the key
that allows us more insight into
you so while you are in your Sedona
so while you are in your Sedona
area you will turn around three times
times
completely. You will
emerge as the third
person. You will create yourself to be
once you have gotten there. When you're
in that area, you will become one
different person, two different people,
three different people. utterly. You
will be spun around three times to face
three different directions, three
different points of
view. It will be highly accelerated and
you will meet some
individuals, not
necessarily what you would call
typically a human person and I do not
mean extraterrestrial. Simply that it can be
extraterrestrial. Simply that it can be
an individual such as an animal, such as
a plant, such as a mineral. Some idea
will isolate itself in your vision to
stand out three
times and in a sense a bell will be rung
will be struck within you three times.
That trinary alignment will allow you to
emerge from that womb, from that if you
wish, cocoon and a more highly
cocoon and a more highly
accelerated
messa and will point you unairringly in
the next direction, the next contacts
that will assist
you. The word mea will be a key.
Thank you for sharing. Well, thank you
for opening up
sharing. Oh, one moment. One moment. One
moment. One m one
moment. The coyote is the key.
Thank you.
Shutting. Hi, Shark. And good day to
you. I listen to the tapes all the time and
I listen to the tapes all the time and
I'd like to thank you for all the light
you've reflected for me. Oh, we thank
you for giving it all. Uh, I feel I have
an incomplete understanding of
unconditional love. Oh, all right.
Incomplete. Unconditional. All right.
Um, what does it mean to you now?
Um, well, what I think it means is that
I should love anyone no matter what they
do. Well, not should. There are no
shoulds. That's a condition. Okay. But
if you choose to be unconditionally
loving, loving without
condition, then what you will be doing
is reflecting to each and every
being, the unconditional love they are
made out of that will allow them to be
the fullest expression of what they
choose to be. If they are operating
already on a positive vibratory
frequency, you will be reflecting and
reinforcing the positive in them that
much more strongly. If they are choosing
to operate on a negative frequency, your
unconditional loving reflection will
allow them to see within you a
reflection that will give them an
opportunity to choose the positive path.
In any case, if you are reflective of a
positive vibration of unconditional
love, then no matter what the intention
of any other individual in your life is,
positive or negative, the only effect
you'll get out of it in your life will
be a positive one. And that does not
mean that you are condoning what someone
might do that is a negative act. But the
idea of loving them unconditionally
shows them that you believe that they do
not have to continue to express
themselves in a negative way. Expressing
the self in a negative way is only a
reflection of the belief on their part
that they are not in control of their
life already that they feel out of
control that they feel they are sinking
and they feel they have to take as many
individuals with them as they can. The
idea simply is that they feel alone they
feel out of control powerless.
Loving them unconditionally will allow
them to see reflected from your heart
your belief in them that you believe
they can be whatever they want to be
without having to hurt anyone else or
themselves in order to be
that and it will always leave you with a
positive effect in your life no matter
what their intention
is. Is this making it any clearer? Yes.
Is this assisting you? That that
completed it. Well, thank you. Thank you
very much. Thank you very much. Our love
to you.
Good evening, Bashar. And to you, good
day. I wish to extend to you just lays
of love around your neck. Oh, thank you.
Assuming that you have a neck.
Yes, we are not exact but we are
physiologically similar to your species.
Similar enough so that we have a neck. Thank you.
Thank you.
Um the question I wish to ask is that um
within my guides as I have one that I
call shaky. Oh right. And the others
explained to me that this being um has
never manifested in any body anywhere at
any time that is merely a consciousness
of love. As you understand that
terminology that is a sufficiently
accurate description. Yes. And I
wondered if you have any way that you
could help me to see it even more
clearly than I already do. Do you feel
it? Oh, completely. Then act it through
yourself and manifest the love you feel
outwardly in the acts you perform in
your physical world. And then you'll see
it all around you. You'll be channeling
it and manifesting that love in the
actions that you do and the scenarios
you create. You'll see it reflected back
to you in the faces and the eyes of all
the people around you on your planet.
Yes, it's true. Yes. That's why it's
being given to you. Yes. To use it in
that way to create that vibration to
exist on your world to match that
frequency. Yes. That's what I'm
attempting to do. Oh, attempting. It's
what you're doing. Yes. It's not
attempting to do. It's what you're
doing. Do it in the most expanded way
you can imagine. You can do it and
you'll see that love reflected all
around you. You will feel it more and more
you. You will feel it more and more
strongly. There may not be a direct
physiological analogy that will allow
you to quote unquote see it in what you
would call its natural
state. But you will see it in all the
ways you can for the level you are
living on. Yes. that my highest
understanding of it that I am capable of
at this at this viewpoint is is what I
feel it is to be I guess that's all I
can perceive it as but if you start
living that way now as if it is that way
now if you are a representative
extension of its love now you will start
seeing the effects of that in your life
now yes no matter how long it takes for
anyone else to reflect it back to you.
You will see it in your life now. Yes.
And that will give everyone else the
best opportunity to be able to match
that frequency of love. Yes, I
understand. Does this make sense to you?
Oh, absolutely. Well, then if I may
allow us to add our own love to your
willingness to feel the love that you
are made of. Yes. Because all of you are
made of love. You're all living light.
You're all made of love. It's what
creation is. Yes. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much, Shannon.
Hello, Bashar. And to you, good day.
Good day. Um, I have a friend. His name
is Michael. And friend Michael. Yes.
Yes. Um, I'm trying to reestablish what
some of the ties might have been to um,
previous lives and how they relate to
our relationship now. What are you
learning about yourself in the
relationship you are in now?
I don't I'm not clear on any of it
anymore. No. What have you learned?
Patience. Why do you need that?
I don't know. Oh, all right. Thank you.
Patience. Now I understand what most of
you mean when you say patience and
sometimes the general way you use that
term is similar to the way we would
describe the idea as well. However, more
often than not, we have perceived that
most of you use that word
patience in the sense of referring to
waiting for something better to come
along. That you think that what's
happening now is not what's supposed to
be happening. And so you need patience
to wade through what's going on in your
life now until it gets to be the way you
think it ought to
be. All right? But you see, the need for
patience creates the impatience you're
actually feeling. Because if you know
that everything that's going on in your
life is serving a purpose and you live
that idea like a child fully with
curiosity and fascination about
everything that's happening at every
single moment, then you're not waiting
for something better to come along
because you know that what's happening
now that's as you say where it's at.
Whatever is going on in your life right
now is the most important thing of all
or something else would be happening.
That does not mean that what's going on
in your life can't change that you might
prefer something else. But the fact that
whatever it is going on right now can
give you the opportunity to know what it
is you can change it into if you extract
from whatever is going on all the
information it is there to give you so
you can use it fully. If you are using
everything that's going on fully in your
life, then you're not waiting for
something better to come along. You
don't need patience because you're
having too much fun right now to care
what's coming up. You know that whatever
is going to come along will be just as
exciting because what you're doing now
is the most important and exciting thing
you could possibly be doing. Even if you
are learning how to change it, that I
would think would be extremely exciting
to you because many times, especially in
your society, you can find out very
clearly what it is you are by examining
what it is you are not. And that can be
very exciting to have a clearer
definition of what it is you prefer to
be. Every opportunity, every situation
and every circumstance in your lives
always is there to give you the
opportunity to define more and more and
more clearly what you really prefer to
be on whatever level of expansive
expression you prefer to be it. Every
opportunity can serve that purpose
or flip side as you say, every
opportunity can be looked at as I just
don't see how this fits in my life. I
just don't get it. This is terrible.
This is awful. This is something that
doesn't belong. It has nothing to do
really with me. I can't learn anything
from this. I have to wait for something
else to come along, something I know is
more representative of the me I prefer
to
be. So, I'm going to wait and wait and
wait and wait and not believe that I
could learn something about what's going
on that will answer all of the questions
that I actually
have. That thing later on will not
answer those questions. The being that
you want to be will not answer the
questions you have about who you are
now. You will be that being when you use
who you are now to answer those
questions to see the obviousness that
any situation you are in is there for a
purpose. Ask yourself something what am
I getting out of being in this
situation? Why would I have attracted
this? What can I learn about myself?
What has been reflected to me by the
other person in the relationship or
persons in the relationship? What have I
been able to do to be of service to them
to allow them to learn more about who
they want to be? That is the reason for
any relationship to reflect to each
other what you can most prefer to be to
learn what you need to learn about
yourself to be who you want to be. Yes,
many individuals that you have very
intimate relationships with in any life
you have had many other lives with
before. I use the term before loosely
because all lives are going on now. Time
is your
illusion. You create linear time to
create a convenient separation of all
the experiences you are of yourself so
that you can play out the game of linear
time and space of limitation and focus
as a physical being.
But all these other lies, all these
other experiences are all going on now.
Are all in a sense a part of you now.
Any idea that you would call a past life
or a future life or an alternate life
that your curiosity is most strongly
drawn to will be perhaps the strongest
indication of the past, future or
alternate lives that are most
representative of any particular
relationship and interaction you're
having in what you call your present. So
first of all, trust your curiosity. Is
there any particular epic or era in your
history, past, present, future,
alternate, that does attract you more
than any other? That's your first
indication that if you are thinking
about that particular era in conjunction
with a particular relationship you're
in, that that conjunction is happening
for a reason. That that attraction, that
curiosity is happening for a
reason. Now,
Now,
understand, by all means, it is valid to
explore those connections. But once
again, you do not necessarily need to
understand what a connection was in
order to know and live the life you
prefer to live. Now you have all the
ingredients in your kit. You need to
live the life you are living.
Now remember this
also. There is always bleedth through
from all lives going on simultaneously.
You may not always recognize information
that comes from another life because
when it gets to your life, it will
translate in terminology you understand.
Now you say, "Oh, where did that come
from?" Or you simply recognize something
and it seems to fit in your life so
appropriately that you don't necessarily
know that it might actually be a leak
through from an experience you're having
in another life right now.
You are always in communication with all
aspects of yourself because all the
programs, all the lives are all going on
simultaneously. Again, similar to your
radio analogy, all the programs are
there at
once and they all to some degree
overlap. You use your finetuner to focus
yourself in one particular life at a time.
time.
So stay in the present is our
suggestion. Ask yourself now, who am I to this
Ask yourself now, who am I to this
person now? Who is this person now to
me? What have I been able to learn about
myself by attracting this person? What
has that person learned by attracting
me? Who are we to each other?
Now, that will most strongly point up
the reason for the interaction at all.
It doesn't require a past life
connection to have a reason for the
interaction going on in the present. And
remember this, the present is what
actually creates the past anyway, not
the other way around. I guess it's my
inability to see right now because that
is the focus that I do hold. All right.
And that is only looking for something
more. Yes. Yes. That inability is only
the product of your definitions.
Can you tell me on any level anything at
all? I'll accept one itsybitsy little
thing that you have learned by being in
that relationship of a positive nature to
relationship of a positive nature to
yourself. Oh, there's a lot. I just it's
hard to bring one up. Um, anyone will
do. All right, never mind.
All right, never mind.
If you recognize that there are a lot,
yes, then may I ask you this
question? Are those
recognitions sufficient reason for
having created the relationship? Yes.
Can it be enough of a reason regardless
of any other connection you may have had
or will ever have again? Yes. Then our
suggestion is to leave the focus there.
And then if anything else needs to come
up and present itself to you in a way
that makes itself apparent to where it
came from, you will get it.
Understand? Yeah. I think I just maybe I
just don't want to end it. So nothing
ever ends. I know. I know. It only
transforms. And do remember this. As
soon as you are the vibration of who you
really prefer to be, you will attract
whatever individual or individuals are
more reflective of that vibration
anyway. They will seem to fit because
they match your vibration and so you
won't care who it is because it will
feel correct. Okay, understand? Yes.
Remember, even if that original person
changes to match your new vibration,
it's not the same person anyway, even if
they look the same on the outside to
you. Mhm. It's not the same person. So,
what difference does it make? It
doesn't. Does this help you? Mhm. May I
tell you something? Yes. We love you.
Thank you.
Thank you very much. Stay there. Okay. As a
As a
suggestion just leaked through from
[Music] somewhere. When you go to sleep this
somewhere. When you go to sleep this
night of your time and begin to blend
your physical and your dream reality
into one, one,
imagine. Imagine
Imagine
floating on beams of light, floating on
a
sea of
light, what you may call the ghostly
light that issues from your singular
moon. Tap into the polarized light of
what you call your full moon expression
this night of your time.
And as you drift into what you call your
dream reality, use that sea of light that you
reality, use that sea of light that you
are going to float
upon to create a blending, a blending
between physical reality and
non-physical reality. See that sea of
light as the place where both realities
meet and are one and there is no
separation. and see what happens.
and see what happens.
All right. Okay. Thank you. Enjoy your
journey. I will. Good night. And to you,
pleasant dreams. At this timing, you may
all enjoy a short break and we will
resume contact in approximately 10 to 15
of your minutes.
How's it going? Ter,
please uh remember 10 15 minutes when I
call you, please come back cuz if you
don't, it cuts the channeling short. And
if you want to get a copy of tonight's
tape, you could get it tonight from Lynn
just around the corner.
A little continue.
Hi, Bishar. And good day to you. I want
to know if you don't want to talk to me
or something because twice you've broken
for a break. Just before you. Just
before me. So, what have I done to you?
for nothing at
all except in being more of yourself and
in being involved sometimes in the
middle of
processes that it is your business to
complete on your own. We will simply
sense the timing that is appropriate and
simply follow our own instincts trusting
that those instincts are representative
of the timing that is going on with
whomever shall be involved next. So I
don't need to ask the question I was
supposed to ask. Can you answer it?
No, ask it and see. Okay. Um, I've been
here se several times and been able to
apply a lot of things that I've learned
through the interaction that's been
going on. All right. A lot of positive
changes have been made in my life. And
thank you. Thank you. And I'm exciting
what excites me. Well, thank you. Yes. I
have trouble in the area of
applying these principles to areas of
relationships. I see. in that um
sometimes I act the way I don't want to
act with oh other people say for
instance my boyfriend and I fight and
instead of you've said before set an
example or something or be the person
you want to be and that way help them
the most. Yes. Well, I don't do that. I
act like a screaming maniac. He's
screaming. How does it serve you to
choose to act that way then?
I feel sick. I mean it doesn't help me
in any way. It makes me feel terrible.
Well, then it helps you by realizing
that that is not the way you want to be.
Why do I do it over and over again? I
mean, if I realize it, great. But why
don't I act differently then? Why can't
I apply those principles? Do you trust
that you will be able to have what you
need and that another person can have
what they need and that you can both
have what you need. And it doesn't have
to be a contest.
No, I don't. Do you have the philosophy
within you that if somebody wins,
somebody loses? Yes.
Yes.
Well, then that's why you want to make
sure you're going to get what you want.
If you understand that it is no
contradiction and no paradox that both
of you can have exactly what you want,
then you can relax. And it doesn't have
to be so much of a contest to outshout
each other, to be
outheard. You don't have to be so
insistent on directing the other
person's focus to who you want to be.
You can simply know who you are and
allow them to be who they are. trusting
that the relationship
is for a reason as it is rather than
assuming you have to make it be what you
think it ought to
be. If it doesn't turn out this way, I
won't get what I want.
That's holding up a mirror that I don't
I mean the reflection that I'm seeing I
don't like and I know that's what I do.
Then you are getting a reflection that
serves you best. Because if you don't
prefer it, the reflection is there to
show you this is the belief and the
definition you have. If you don't prefer
it, change the definition. Change the
belief and the reflection will change
into one you prefer it to be. Why
assume that if you don't act a certain
way, you won't get what you
want? Why assume that? It's only a
definition. I know. I guess I feel like
I've had to fight for what I have got.
All right. Then that perhaps can be an
old point of view, what you call an old
habit. It doesn't have to be anymore.
You can realize everyone can have what
they need. There really, really, really
is such a thing as happily ever after.
There really is. There really is enough
for everyone. There really is.
Okay. Understand? Okay. Say, I believe
that. Well, okay.
All right. You believe that? Okay. I
believe that. Oh,
thank you.
You're welcome. I believe it, too.
Yes. All right. The next time Let's be
hypothetical. Let's say you believe it. The next The
Let's say you believe it. The next The
next time a situation comes up where he
does something that I feel like I have
to fight cuz he might I don't know. Why
don't I do that? Anyway, the next time a
situation comes up where I think I'm
going to lose my temper because he bugs
me in some way or something bugs you.
All right. Well, or well, if I how can I
trust myself not to lose my temper?
Don't choose to don't choose to. It is
not automatic.
You are choosing to lose your temper
because of the definitions and beliefs
you choose to continue to buy into. So
if I truly believe that we can both be
the people we need to be, then you won't
lose your temper because you won't have
a reason to because you won't have a
belief that supports the reason.
Understand? Yes. If you really don't
believe that way, you will not have a
reason to support that
attitude. There will be nothing there.
There will be nothing to give it
momentum. You simply won't react that way because
You simply won't react that way because
you will not be a person that contains a
reason to react that
way. It may surprise you. Oh, how come I
didn't fly off the handle? I don't know.
I just didn't didn't seem like it was
there. It won't be. If you really
redefine yourself and really buy into
the new definitions, and if the new
definitions are indicative of a person
that doesn't have a reason to fly off
the handle, you won't. It's that simple.
The only reason you do things that seem
automatic is because you buy into
definitions that make them seem
automatic. If this happens, then this.
If that happens, then this. You are
writing these equations. You are saying
this equals that. If this happens, I
lose my
temper. What else can you expect? If you
set up the equation that way, you have
to get that answer. Erase the equation
and rewrite it. Then you'll get a
different answer, won't you? Yes. So,
rewrite it in the way you prefer to
define yourself as the person you prefer
to be. Believe in that self and you will
react that
way. For if you truly do trust that
everyone is going to get what they
really need, there's no need to fight for it.
need, there's no need to fight for it.
It will be there automatically.
believe in the essential understanding,
the essential construction of the
universe. Everything
fits where it
is. So if you're in a relationship with
someone and certain things are being
presented to you, there's a reason for
it. It fits. What does it teach you
about yourself to see these things? How
can you assist the other individual to
learn what they need to learn? If it
truly is something that is
representative of what you don't prefer,
then by all means rearrange your
circumstances. You never have to force
yourself to stay in what you would call
a physiological relationship that really
is not representative of who you are.
And sometimes certain relationships will
be attracted by you into your life to
give you the opportunity to really
determine this is not
me. Being in this relationship is not
who I am, is not supportive to the idea
I prefer to be. And I know now I have
attracted that relationship to point out
beyond a shadow of a doubt that that's
not who I am. The only reason
individuals would then hang on to that
kind of a relationship is for some
reason because they do not believe that
they are complete without
it. But you can transform anything. If
you really have a desire to remain in
that idea of the relationship in the way
it is, then understand and trust that
you can be being given by that
relationship the opportunity to discover
that everyone can
win always.
Everyone understand? Yes, I do. Does
this help you? Yes, it does. Well, thank
you for winning and allowing us to win.
Thank you very much,
Sharing. Good day, Bash. And good day to you.
Good day, Bash. And good day to you.
One moment. Okay. Last person we spoke
to, there is more
information coming from a different
source relatively soon that can assist
you in a different and unexpected way
now that you have opened certain doors
within this interaction.
Great. Thank you. Continue. Okay. Um I
was at the gathering that was that you
did a few weeks ago about um
electromagnetism and crystals. Yes. Right. And you talked
and crystals. Yes. Right. And you talked
about liquid crystals and the thought
just and creating a window from the
physical to the non-physical. And I just
got real excited about that and I was
like, "Okay, okay, wait. Yeah, yeah,
yeah. I'm I'm going to do that." Yeah.
All right. All right. Some individuals
on your planet have begun some of that
idea. We have already discussed some of
this with them which is why we also
share the information in that format of
talking about electromagnetism and
crystals because we know there would be
other individuals who may also be
excited about that idea. We thank you
for expressing the excitement. What have
you done? Okay. So, oh since I Oh, one
moment. One moment. A little bit of an
orientation. The idea of the substance you call
The idea of the substance you call
liquid crystals and certain other
substances can be used in a specific
way. If you will suspend this substance
between what you call two sheets of
transparent glass and pass through this
substance the idea of an electrical
current on the order of hundreds of
thousands of cycles per second of
frequency. You can
create a medium through which physical
and non-physical entities can create an
impression that will be registered in
both worlds. It will literally be a
window from physicality to
non-physicality. Continue. Okay. So, so
my first question was that okay where do
I get liquid crystal? I kind of see how
well you don't need to ask me. Well,
okay. So when I ask myself in a
meditation, what I get is this
waterfall. I just constantly for one
moment. One moment. Okay. Perhaps you
misunderstand that the substance already
exists in your society. Really look it
up. Oh, we did not give you something
Oh, we did not give you something
difficult to find.
Take the most obvious route. Whenever
you hear a term that is unfamiliar to
you, ask around if someone else on your
planet already understands it. The
substance already exists and in your
terminology can be commercially
acquired.
Understand? Ask you. Okay. Okay. All
right. So, all right. Yes.
Well, then
um let me ask you about something else.
No. All right. Okay. All right. This is
something I wanted to ask for a long
time now. Oh, a long time. All right.
Yeah, but I always thought it was kind
of obvious, but just for the heck of it,
I want to throw it out there. Okay.
So, on the harmonic convergence up on
Black Mountain, I met these two women
that just like just like came to me like
they were just real attracted to me. We
were out camping and they just connected
with me and the other three women, the
other two women that I were with and we
just had this great, you know,
interchange and like one night around a
campfire like we were already talking
about things like just throwing them out
that that we were saying, "Oh yeah,
wouldn't it be fun if we did this?" And
now we're like doing it. But the first
weekend after we got back from this camp
trip, I had this this dream about these
these two women. And it just was real
long and detailed and and everything.
And the next the next day, this one one
of the women called me. Her name is
Wendy and the other one's named
Michelle. And I described the whole
dream to her in detail and she said,
"Wow, that's what Michelle and I were
doing last night. You described it in."
And so I thought, "All right." Huh. And
so all right. So I understood that
somehow I was there with them or
something or something like that. Okay.
That I got all that information. So
nice. And so what's I want to
um there's like strong connections and
we have work play to do together. All
right. That's And are you doing it? Um
yes. And then there's like these like
stop and starts and stop and starts and
stop and starts and and not stops and
starts change of
directions. Not stop and start. Change
of directions.
Can you What do you mean? I change of
directions. each one of us change
directions or as you are walking along
the path you have chosen yourself to be
along that path you will find many
things that may require you to pick them
up and use them as tools that picking up
that walking this way picking this up
that walking this way picking that up it
may seem to be a divergence from the
path but it is actually a part of the
path understand you have not started and
stopped you have simply woven
Mhm. You have all of you together
explored and shared in other lifetimes
the whole idea of the weaving of
tapestries. Use that analogy to
understand that all you're doing is
weaving together in certain ways.
Everything that happens is not an
interruption. It is simply a motion, a
direction on the path that will lead you
to the next tool, the next idea, the
next mirror that you need to see the
reflection of yourself in. You have not
started and stopped. You have only
encountered unexpected directions within
the forward momentum of your path.
Uhhuh. Understand? Yeah. Yeah, it is
simply the unexpected
the unexpected motion within the path
that you are seeing as divergences from
the path. Okay. You know, when we were
sitting out here and this one woman was
talking about Sedona in Arizona. Yes.
Um, one of the women have a strong has a
strong feeling to go to TA. Oh, I hope
you have a good time. [Music]
Some of you appear to be leaking,
you know, and and when you and when you
mentioned to her about the coyote,
something just I just had this like this
laughter and then like brought tears to
my eyes and and it just like inside just
And and
and so I I wonder if you could share
anything about that with me. What are
you talking about? You'll have a howling
good time.
All of us. Coyote.
What do you feel like when you think of
the idea when it strikes that chord
within you of the coyote consciousness
of the symbol it represents from what
you call the animal consciousness to
your human consciousness? What do you
think of? How do you feel?
I feel um I don't know. It did it again
to me right now. Um um yes yes yes.
Just let it through. See?
All right. Okay. I told you you'll have
howling good time.
time.
Now it would be our suggestion.
[Music] It would be our suggestion.
It would be our suggestion.
Yeah. No. Yeah, I'm okay. All right.
Okay. I know you are
okay. The other suggestion, okay, that
you approach all the circumstances that
you feel are starts and stops with the
same degree of trust and
abandon. Let it flow through you.
Identify with it. Link with it. Feel
your power. Feel the connection to your
earth, your nature, spirit self. Feel
your consciousness as it flows through
all the kingdoms of your world. Move in
the shadow of yourself and emerge into
the light.
Walk in a balanced
way between the day and the night.
Uhhuh. You are a being of nature.
Let it through you in that way and you
will attract all because then not saying
you have to literally repeat what you
just did but all will hear your call and
come running as you put it out there with
running as you put it out there with
that much boldness. As you live your
life with that same degree of conviction
that the coyote has when it proclaims
its existence. Nothing will be kept from
existence. Nothing will be kept from
you. And all communication will span the
distance.
Understand? Yes. Uh-huh.
Does this help you? Yes. Thank you.
Well, thank you very much.
[Applause] Shannon.
Shannon.
Hello. Oh, and to you, good day. Hi. Um,
I'd like to know if you uh could tell me
if
uh I am what you would call a star
child. And well, in a sense, all of you
are. You know, none of you are original
to your planet. The terminology that you
use in your society, star child, is
generally an indication of a conscious
recognition of some of these connections
you all have that may for some
particular reason of this particular
life stand out more than other
connections may. So in that sense if you
feel so drawn to that idea if it does as
we have said strike the chord within you
then obviously you are choosing to
express yourself that way and in that
sense yes of course you are you are all
star children. I was just saying for
lack of better words uh I believe that
there's some sort of like a a race if
you will that uh I belong to. Yes I
understand what you are saying exactly
but you see the idea is is that all of
you have those connections. I see all of
you different connections stand out in
different lives depending upon what you
have created this particular life to be.
In another life you may have felt
another connection to another race
altogether because you can determine
that in each and every present you
create yourself to exist within because
you are connected to all of them. Any
probable connection there could be you
have the ones that stand out or the one
that seems to stand out has to do with
the life you have created yourself to
be. Now that doesn't mean you don't have
other connections. In a sense, you all
come from everywhere and nowhere. You
don't really have as a spirit any
particular point of origin. But you can
make those connections, they can feel
like true connections. And in a sense
they are because all reality, all
imagination, all those recognitions are
real because you cannot imagine
non-existence. Everything you can
conceive of is on some level somehow
true and real. So yes, you have those
connections just as anyone does. Some
people will feel them in different ways.
It depends upon the purposes, the
methodologies, the way you have chosen
to express yourself in this life that
will determine how you key into this
particular connection and why it stands
out more than any other. But yes, the
associations are there and there is
interaction between yourself especially
in dream states between the you you are
here the you you are there and all the
other beings that are there that know
you understand? Yes. Uh how can I
contact the others who are like me that
I feel so I feel so different from
everyone uh on this planet? Would you do
me a favor? Yes. Would you take your
physical form and turn it approximately
30°?
What do you see?
A lot of people say hi. Hi. Hi.
Well, I guess you're right. What do you
think they are?
They in many ways think as you do. There
are many individuals who know as you do,
who sense as you
do. No matter in what way they choose
to, you all share the common
understanding that you are all spirit
within the one spirit of infinite
creation and that you all manifest
yourselves in many different
civilizations to create different
understandings and different
experiences. Remember, it is a very
common thing. Now that you are all
awakening in this civilization you call
Earth to recognize more of the other
connections you have at first because of
the way you are used to thinking of
separation of space. You may get the
feeling that you belong there more than
you belong where you are because you
have just made a recognition and it
creates within you this feeling of
separation and
homesickness. But the idea is not to run
away from where you chose to be to
rejoin that energy. But to manifest that
energy on your planet now, your planet
of choice now to create that energy on
your planet to match that vibration. You
are in that sense as all of you are
representatives from many different
civilizations that have chosen to be
born upon earth to assist it in its
transformation and transform its energy
into the energy you are familiar with on
other worlds that already exist in a
harmonious state. So remember that even
though you may have other homes because
you chose to be born on Earth, Earth is
your home too and just as equally
validly your home as anywhere else. The
only reason you would at first feel that
the other place is more your home is
simply because that's your immediate
awakening recognition and because of the
way you think of that you think you are
rediscovering something you forgot which
in a sense you are and that rediscovery
makes it seem as if you belong there
more than you belong where you are but
you belong where you are too or you
wouldn't be there. The idea is to match
those frequencies and pull that energy
through and spread it out on your earth
to make the link.
understand? Yes. Does this assist you
somewhat? Anything else? Well, uh why is
it that I seem so invisible to many
other people that it's almost as if uh
I'm on my own level, so to speak.
Whatever you are not the vibration of
and whatever is not the vibration of you
literally can't see you. Mhm.
Understand? Is there a way I can help tune in uh
Is there a way I can help tune in uh
those? Be the fullest you you can be
with integrity. You will radiate at
whatever pitch is necessary to attract
all others who wish to interact with
you. I see. You will attract yourself
into the circumstances where you will
find others willing to interact with you
on that level because they already
interact on that level too.
Understand? Yes. You are not alone.
Okay. Thank you. Thank you very much
Thank you. Thank you very much
sharing.
Hello Bashar. And to you good day. I
think you're terrific. Oh, you too.
Okay. Um my question is
I'm a producer and a writer. And um I'm
about to I've been negotiating on this
picture for about 5 months now. And um
everything looked terrific. Everything
was easy. It was just wonderful. I mean,
God said, "Okay, kid, go do it." And now
there's little things like a word in a
contract that is stopping everything.
Oh, all right. And um I'm wondering
since I brought it this far, would I be
doing something to stop it to stop it
from happening like unconsciously? No.
Oh, good.
But you are giving yourselves an
opportunity to really define what is
important to you and to redefine things
that may not be clear.
Um, and you are giving yourself an
opportunity to realize nothing has
stopped. You can redefine that to begin
with. Mhm. Again, stop assuming that
there are interruptions in your life.
That's right. They are interruptions.
They are not interruptions. Oh, stop
assuming. Wait a minute. Hold Stop
assuming that there can be interruptions
in your life. Stop assuming that
something that's going on has no purpose
in being there.
Understand? Understand? Yeah. As soon as
you take that attitude, you will allow
things that at first seem to be
interruptions but which are only
unexpected events that are a part of
your path. As soon as you take the
attitude that they are not interruptions
but a part of the path, you will allow
them to transform much more quickly. The
sooner you take the attitude that they
belong there in a sense and learn from
it what you need to learn, the sooner
you get on to the next step. As soon as
you assume that something that is there
doesn't belong there, the longer you
make it take to change. Mhm. Because
you're assuming you're being blocked. If
that's your first assumption, that's a
negative assumption. You're adding
negative energy to the whole process and
you yourself are slowing the momentum in
that way. If you're assuming that what's
going on is not a part of the process
that needs to be there. Understand? Yes.
If you know you're really doing what
excites you the most with all the
integrity you can muster to the best of
your ability and acting on all the
opportunities that come to you to the
best of your ability, then don't assume
that something that happens just because
it's unexpected has no business being
there. assume that because you know
you're acting to the best of your
ability with all the integrity and
positivity and following your excitement
that you can then whatever happens no
matter how unexpected must be a part of
must be a result of your acting with
integrity and cannot be an interruption
in it. Um I guess what what uh confuses
me is that at this point is out of my
hands I feel because it has to do with
banks. Now I understand but it is never
out of your hands. If you find that
there are in your terms circumstances
that may make it seem as if physically
speaking there is not any particular
thing that you could be doing to assist.
Then all you have to do is do the next
most exciting thing that you can do
something about. Even if it seems to be
unrelated, the excitement is what allows
you to be assisting the other thing you
cannot physically do anything about.
That's what I'm doing. Then you are
doing what you need to do. Look at this
analogy. We will use a variation of what
we have discussed of the train analogy.
Let's say you are going to your train to
go somewhere and you catch your train
and you're sitting there and the train
is stopping and waiting and waiting and
waiting and not going anywhere and
you're looking at your watch and saying,
"Come on, come on, get moving. I'm going
to be late. Why are you waiting? What's
going on? This is not normal. It's not
supposed to stay here. It's supposed to
be moving down the track. I have caught
the train. Why isn't it moving?"
And then all of a sudden someone steps
onto the train and says, "Boy, am I
glad." Or, "All right, girl, am I
glad that this train for some reason was
delayed. I really needed to catch this
train." And that person that just got on
looks around and you look around and
your eyes meet and you recognize each
other and you say, "Oh my, how
unexpected to see you jumping aboard."
Well, we could have been long gone. If
we had been, we would have missed you.
You wouldn't have been able to come
aboard, and I wouldn't have been able to
talk to you about the things I really
need to talk to you about before I
arrive at my destination because what I
can learn from you, I need to know by
the time I get there. I was wondering
how I was going to know that.
So, there was a reason after all for
what seemed to be a negative delay, but
which turned out to be the exact thing I
needed. Understand? Yes. I just got a
very clear flash in my brain about why
this happened. Thank you. Well, thank
you. I think you're a wonderful sit down
comedian as well.
[Music] Oh, thank
Oh, thank
you. Same to you all.
However, just as a point of curiosity, I
am actually in your terminology lying
down at the
moment. Of course, that's all relative.
We thank you for opening that door and
shedding some light within yourself.
Thank you.
At this [Music]
[Music]
timing at this timing, allow us to
remind each and every one of you that
you are the hands of the peace clock.
Every day at
day at
midday for one full
minute, silent meditation in your own
way to envision world peace every
day. The goal, as you say, in spreading
the information for every person on your
information for every person on your
planet to be doing the same thing every
day by your January 1st,
1990. Every
person information will be provided that
you can
share. We thank you for being the hands
of the clock.
We bid you exciting and loving dream
life and life dream and a fond and
loving good day. [Music]
How'd it go? Perfect.
First of all, Juliet Beayshore, are you
still here? Yeah.