I don't say how are you all this evening
of your time as you create time to
exist. Allow us to begin with a
Allow us to begin with a
reminder that we are now at this timing
in our interactions with each and every
one of
you to some
degree. pulling back a little bit to
allow each and every one of you to
remember that
you are the creators of your
experiential reality. And that anything that you may
reality. And that anything that you may
quote unquote learn from us will simply
be a reflection from us of that which
you already know yourself to be and
which we choose to reflect back to you
in our expression of our faith in you,
our expression of our belief in you. But
remember our ability to share with you
our expression of our belief in you
would not be possible if you did not
have the capacity to believe in
yourselves. For then we would not have
that to be able to reflect to you. You
would not be of the vibration that would
attract our ability to reflect that to
you. recognize their fault that in these
recognize their fault that in these
interactions a bit at a
time. So we will be interacting and
sharing with you in many different ways.
All of it now will be focused toward the
understanding that we will be pulling
back a little
bit as a sign that you do not need us
that much in that way. that you really
do not need us at all, but that you now
can be willing to know that the actions
you take in your
life, the decisions you make in your
lives are fully under your own conscious
commandment. If you wish, that is your
title, conscious
commandment. What is conscious
commandment? Many individuals as we have perceived
Many individuals as we have perceived
these interactions with your
society understand ideas of the
unconscious, the subconscious, the
outeraware consciousness, that which you
term your physical consciousness as you
say, and also what you may refer from
time to time to as the higher
consciousness. All of these in a sense
while descriptive of the overall
illusion you have
created are also still simply labels and
in this sense can be melded,
blended, pulled
together into simply one recognition of
the one consciousness that you are each
and every one of you individually and
collectively. Recognize that many of you because you
Recognize that many of you because you
have the idea that your power somehow
for creating your physical reality lies
somewhere up there in your higher
consciousness way out of reach.
Sometimes you
think because you hold that notion
because you hold that point of view. You
do not allow yourselves many times to
realize the power of your conscious
decision makingaking
ability. You as a being as a physical
being have what you term free will the
ability to choose to decide what you
prefer in life to decide what you prefer
to desire in life.
sensibility, conscious
choice is, if you are willing to
understand it, the same thing as the
same commandment. You usually typify
your higher consciousness as
having you are your higher consciousness
anytime you choose to believe that you
are. If you know you as a physical
consciousness are functioning within
your excitement, expressing your desire,
excitement, expressing your desire,
expressing your integrity and being of
service while expressing who you know
yourself to
be. Then the choices that you make in
life, the conscious free will choices
that you create is the same thing as the
type of commandment over the occurrences
in your physical reality that you
usually give to your higher
consciousness. Simply
knowing that you making conscious
choices is all that it takes to create
the reality you desire is your
willingness to function as your higher
consciousness in physical
terms. You have every ability to be the
expression of your higher consciousness.
Many of you think that communicating
with your higher consciousness still
involves some sort of separate
communication between separate things.
True immediate communication with your
higher consciousness is the willingness to act
consciousness is the willingness to act
as your higher consciousness would act
if it were physical, which it is.
So know beyond a shadow of a doubt that
if you're functioning within your
integrity and desire and service, then
the things that excite you in life, your
decision to do those things is your
ability to exercise conscious
commandment over your reality. And it is
that simple. What you
decide to decide is true for you is what
your reality will be. And it is that
simple. Your higher consciousness will
pay attention because you are the
expression of your higher consciousness
in physical terms. You do not need to
continue. Not that it is not valid as a
way to look at it. Not that it is not
valid as a process to get yourself more
and more used to the understanding that
you are your higher consciousness. Not
that it is not valid to have what you
perceive to be remote communication with
the higher consciousness, that is valid.
But the more willing you are to
recognize your ability to act in the
moment as your higher
consciousness simply because you choose
to. If you are willing to recognize that
it is that simple, then your life will
unfold as simplicity
itself, you will know beyond a shadow of
a doubt that you do create your reality
for every single circumstance and
situation in your life will be the
reflection and the feedback that will
always prove to you that what you have
decided to choose will be reflected.
back in your
life. All you need to do is understand
that many of the things that you buy
into as belief
systems upon which many times you base
the foundation of your
experience are not always really
representative of a true foundation.
They are the things upon which you base
your existence. many times just as much
of an
assumption as any belief that you base
upon it. You can't take it all the way back
it. You can't take it all the way back
to primal fundamental
creation. The only one fundamental
reality or truth that exists for
everyone in creation is simply the fact
that you
exist. That's it.
Everything else, every other experience,
every other way in which you experience
the fact that you exist is up to you
because of what you decide you will
choose to experience. One way or
another, for one reason or another,
positive or negative, fear or
joy, it is up to you. You exist and you
always will exist because existence is
eternally now. Any manifestation of existence
now. Any manifestation of existence
comes from your choices, your decisions,
your conscious
commandment. Many of you may say, well,
yes, but I have expressed unconscious
commandments from time to time that my
conscious mind is not aware of. And
these unconscious commandments sometimes
are what is responsible for creating the
reality that I may not
prefer. But again
remember if you are aware that the
commandment is coming from somewhere
within you it can be a conscious
commandment. Your ability, your willingness to simply
Your ability, your willingness to simply
know that at least on some level of your
consciousness as you have created it to
have levels to begin with. The creation
of the reality is coming from you
somewhere. Let yourself know that when we say
Let yourself know that when we say
conscious commandment, this does not
mean that the specifics of how you are
attracting the realities you are
experiencing need to necessarily be
analytically or logically understood in
thought form. But simply your knowledge that you
form. But simply your knowledge that you
do create your reality based upon your
belief. That knowledge and the
willingness to act in life as if that is
certain knowledge will always allow you
the ability to
feel that no matter where the creation
comes from, no matter what level, it is
still within your conscious control,
your conscious commandment. For once
again, unconscious knowingness is the
same thing as conscious
unknowingness, which is another way of
saying that you simply consciously do
not want to know. If you consciously do
not want to know, then you will
unconsciously know. But that is only in
many ways, not meaning to be derogatory,
an excuse. You know it somewhere within
you. And when you remove the idea that
you exist in levels, when you remove the
idea that you exist in parts, then you
will allow all of the previously created
levels of consciousness to melt into one
understanding, which can simply then be
expressed in whatever way it needs to be
expressed at any given moment to let you
live the life you choose to live.
Conscious commandment. You have it right
now. The decisions you make in life will
stick. The decisions you make will
stick. If you simply make them based
upon your trust that you are following
what excites you, doing what is true for
you within
integrity, then there is no reason to
assume, unless of course you choose to,
that the conscious decisions you make
will not create your reality as you
desire to see it.
you all follow along.
We thank you for this opportunity of
sharing and therefore in continuation of
our interactions with you, we simply ask
at this time, how may we serve you?
Hi Bashar, it's Millian. Hi. Hi. Well, I
feel I've soared very high this week.
All right. I channeled. I had a
breakthrough in my channeling and u
channeled an extraterrestrial who claims
to know you in a sense. In a sense and
an acquaintance sort of. Okay. Speak up.
Okay. An acquaintance sort of. And then
I got into an opportunity of manifesting
the kind of prosperity that I've always
felt was right. And uh then yesterday
afternoon I manifested about two inches
of doubt. All right. Two inches of
doubt. And I said, "Oh, no big deal. Two
inches of doubt." No, no big deal. And
that that doubt though, I just I feel
I'm stumbling on it. In what way?
I don't know. It It seems rather
insignificant and it seems rather
important. Well, nothing is
insignificant. I mean, compared to everything else
I mean, compared to everything else
that's been going on, it's very small.
All right. And yet, for some reason,
I've got it here in my throat. All
right. Perhaps simply that is because
you are focusing upon its
insignificance which makes it seem
larger than it is because that's all
you're looking
at. Perhaps allow yourself once again if
you are going to doubt the benefit of
the doubt if doubt is what you are going
to focus upon. Oh yes, paint it red and
feature it if you wish. Okay. Oh, thank
you. But the idea simply many times is
no matter how small anything is that you
do not prefer, if that's all you're
looking at, it's going to seem to
encompass your entire field of vision.
Oh yes, of course. Look at all of the
things in which you do not doubt. Yes.
Feel what that is like and simply apply
that same trust and certainty to this
situation. Oh wow. and let it change so
that you do not have to make it change
and follow me. Yes. Very that's that's
perfect. Thank you. Thank you. So then
the the the question I really wanted to
ask that that was sort of in the way of
was if you could shed some light for or
share anything with me about the
extraterrestrial who um I seem to be
channeling and who is sort of an
acquaintance of yours. I would just love
to hear anything that you can share with
me about that. All we can share at this
time is that it is an association energy
and that it is indicative to some degree
of the work you are doing in dispensing
information in networking. In that
sense its
propensity that being's propensity is
also for the purposes of networking
plugging information into information.
It is one of the coordinative beings of
the association that allows there to be
fluidity of communication between many
of the different civilizations in the
association. So you are exemplifying the
same traits in this life and therefore
you have attracted someone that has
shall we say colloquially the same type
of job.
Oh, that's that's great because during
some of these um these things that I've
been doing to um you know the processes
I keep getting this sort of a thought
form that I'm something like a Stargate
and I'm not sure what that means. It's
all right. The idea
perhaps put in other
terminology and again not meaning to
limit something by labeling it but
perhaps an app propo
titlement generally just as reference
for this being would be
facilitator. You follow me? Yes.
Will that do? Yes. Facilitator is a
gate. Oh, a gate is a facilitator. That
which allows others to pass through it.
Yes. To promote communication. That is a
gate. It is a link, a tunnel, a conduit
between that which exists at either end.
Yes. It feels like between the the star
family and the earth family in a sense.
But also between many earth groups and
other earth groups. Yes. That is what
you are doing. Yes. Very strongly. Yes.
Thank you for willing to be that gate,
that tunnel, that channel. Thank you.
You are channeling by bringing
information and connecting various
groups even on your own planet. That is
also channeling.
Wonderful. Thank you very much. Thank
you. Sharing. Greetings, Bashara. Unto you.
Sharing. Greetings, Bashara. Unto you.
Can you tell me when the soul of a a
person enters the uterus and the unborn
child? This will vary from individual to
individual. But generally speaking, even
though a portion of the consciousness is
within the embodiment, even at
conception, what you recognize as the
personality soul, that which you would
call the persona, usually does not enter
until literally, just prior to, or right
at, or just even after, sometimes
physical dirt.
It is usually within the actual birthing
time frame.
They're just the persona soul comes in.
What you recognize as the soul, what you
call the soul typically in your society
usually does not enter until right at
birth. Although recognize of course that
a body in a sense in any form is a soul,
is a spirit in physical terms. But what
you call the persona aspects do not
usually manifest until right at birth
and sometimes not even for a while after
and sometimes come and go for as up to
as much of what you call 3 years of time
without truly locking
in depending upon the reasons that that
individual soul has for that experience.
I see.
Also, no matter what occurs to that
physiological body, that is by understood agreement.
body, that is by understood agreement.
Not trying to tell me something, are
you? Am I?
And about this particular one, I was
wondering if you had any feelings or um
sharings on this particular soul.
Understand generally for now that every
basically child being born upon your
planet at this
time is indicative of the
transformational age and has chosen has
agreed to be born in your society at
this time generally to be of assistance
in accelerating the transformation from
third to fourth density. What you might
term colloquially old to new age
awareness. what you might also term from
limitation to expansion and
unlimitedness. Most of the children
being born now will remember very much
more of who and what they are. They will
forget far less than you did and many of
them will remind the adults of what all
the agreements actually are.
You follow me? Yes. This in general will
be true of this. There will be some
specifics but at this timing some of the
specifics are not completely determined
by that consciousness.
Do you have any feelings on um there may
be maybe since this has been strong in
past lives musical inclinations?
That'd be amazing. Why? Cuz I don't have
any. That does not mean anything. Right.
Um I've often thought about birthing
with dolphins and you can whether you
are in the water or not. Um just through
the consciousness you the energy itself
if you simply call upon them will be
there. They can project. Wrap yourself
in a blue energy field that will allow
their consciousness to participate. And
do remember by all means allow the child
to participate as well.
Then you are not bearing the burden of
the entire idea and it will not be
painful in the least. In the least you
will flow the life into your world. Let
the dolphins assist you by teaching you
the true relaxation of expansion on all
levels. Allow the child by being in
touch telepathically with the child to
assist in its own birth. Allow the total
event to simply occur in the present
moment and it will be
effortless. Effortless. Simply think of the dolphin
Effortless. Simply think of the dolphin
consciousness. They will be
there. All right. Thank you. Listen.
Thank you very much.
Shanning. Good evening Bashar. Unto you.
My love to you and all of us is fine.
My life has changed totally once again.
Oh no. Oh yeah.
I went to Florida with Boris and the
group and we swam with dolphins, played
with dolphins, communicated with them,
felt their love, extended hours.
Uh I just wanted to share that with you
because it
was almost impossible to put into words.
That's the whole idea.
Yes, I've been realizing
that. So, it's um interesting to stand
here and try to verbalize a little of it
to share with you and and the rest of
the group here because I know a lot of
people here are very interested in
dolphins. Um I wonder if you could
reflect to me a bit about some of the
changes that are going on. I I know we
talked about not so analytical more
feeling and I have been doing that. The
first two days after I got back there
was a lot
of actually almost pain and ache in the
solar plexus and also a lot of physical
muscles that were aching it because of
the unexpected
uh use of them with dolphin poles and
and so forth. Um, and I feel like I'm
integrating on so many levels. Of
course, all of them. Um, yes,
that also is the whole idea. This is
true. What can you tell me? I don't already
What can you tell me? I don't already
know. I don't know. Um, know. Um,
[Music]
I was afraid it might come to this.
You simply are beginning to find yourself
simply are beginning to find yourself
speechless.
True. But you are saying more than you might
But you are saying more than you might
know on other levels
emotionally. Again, tell empathically.
Thank you. That is true. And I I realize
it more and more. And I just today
received a wonderful letter from a
friend of mine and a subscription to the
my dolphin
newsletter. And she sent me a story that
was so touching, an actual encounter
that she had with a dolphin in Mexico
many years ago.
Then simply allow yourself to continue
to be touched and touch others wherever
you wish to
go. We thank you for your action. For it
is action in your world, the expression
of your beliefs that actually represents
equal communication with us and with the
dolphins and with all members of the
association. It is action as you already
as a society know that speaks far louder
than words.
Thank you very much. We thank you for
your action. I just do want to say one
more thing and that is that when I read
her letter, it it made me realize
again why I'm interested in this
endeavor and it's to help so many of us
make those connections. Yeah. that often
we've forgotten about
and it's so moving spiritually,
physically, emotionally
and mentally too, but particularly the
emotional. Yes. Thank you, Bashar. Oh,
we thank you very much for remembering
who and what you are. Let me share a
little something with you in the vein
you call humor, if you will. Please.
Well, simply there was and is from time
to time in encountering new
civilizations that have not necessarily
experienced the type of interactions
with other civilizations that we have
with you. Just to put it
you. Just to put it
simply, when we tell them that we are
involved in assisting a civilization to
remember who it is, well, you should see
the wideeyed stairs.
Hard to believe for
them. But in this way, allow me now to
say, if I may, of course, I would not
trade it for the world.
I have a feeling neither would we. Thank
you. Thank you. Thank you for allowing
us to experience all of you. Thank you.
Good luck. Sharing. Hi. Hi. Thank you
for being here. And you for being there.
Thank you. Um
I would like some more information about
conscious commandment which my question
has something to do with and also
excitement. All right. And it is I the
question involves something between my
husband and I because I feel that
marriage becomes another energy in a
sense. Yes. It is representative of an
energy and with that other energy for
example I had a message the other night
to give up the job I do that gives me my
income and make room for something new.
I've already created new work in my life
that excites me. It just doesn't pay me
any money. I ran home to my husband in
great excitement and I said, "I can give
up my work now. Isn't that wonderful?"
And he went, "No. Um, it's not a really
good time to do that." And I was
thinking, "Well, I would really like to
do that. It does excite me." And I and I
have trusted before. And how does that
work when you have two
people with a third energy and then if
you know you are operating within your
integrity? If you know you are following
what excites you then any polarity you
are presented from another individual is
simply your opportunity to decide
whether you truly do believe in yourself
or not. I see. Yeah. Because you first
and foremost you
yourself with yourself with creation you
are the primary marriage.
The question was to do with community. I
was thinking well this is great for me
but is it great for my community? And
that was an earthly question. Do you
believe that you function with an
integrity? Yes. Then by definition do
you not understand that anything you
could attract yourself to will obviously
serve all concerned?
I hadn't known that. But yes, does not
the definition go hand in hand? If you
know that you are willing to be of
service by being who you are, then why
not simply assume that the only
circumstances you will attract will be
those that will allow you to be of
service and that it will benefit all
concerned. Good. But that that doesn't
mean that other individuals may not
express other opinions that are contrary
to
yours. Even that your willingness to be
who you are and allow them to experience
who you are, whether they go along with
it or not, may still be representative
of being of service to them by allowing
them to see yet another way that someone
can exist by following their trust.
Well, that trust is the way I've lived
my life as long as I can remember. So,
it is a new a new way of being for the
other person. True. Not really. But
maybe perhaps in the way they are
applying their trust, maybe that is
something they simply have not recently
considered or not considered for a long
time. Okay, but it is not new. All of
you use your trust to create every
reality you experience. It just depends
whether you have trust in negativity or
trust in
positivity. Where do you have the
greater trust? That will determine the
type of effects you get out of your
life. That's all. You all use trust. You
all trust in something. Depends upon
whether you prefer what you're trusting
in or not.
Does that assist you? Yes, it does.
Thank you very much. Well, find you and
find him. Oh, I do. I was we thank you
too. I do have something else. I was
given a tape about hydro the internal
use of hydrogen peroxide. Are you
familiar with with what that does? To
some degree it can be of benefit in
extremely small amounts. Very rarely.
Uhhuh. I was advised that it would help
me perhaps by it by its youth. And the
tape that I heard on it today just
sounded wonderful. I was why does the
world not know about high? in because
not everyone needs it. Uhhuh. Trust your
instincts. It is an idea that is finding
more and more momentum within your
overall mass consciousness. But like any
other tool, it is not an end all be all.
It is one way and it can be applied in
many ways. Certain individuals may
simply find the invigorating activity of
its chemical components as stimulating
even just to the energy field around
them and that may be enough.
You following? Yes. Yes. So, follow your
instincts. Mhm.
Mhm. Does that assist you? Yes, it does.
Does that assist you? Yes, it does.
Thank you very much. Thank you.
Greetings, Bashar. And do you? I've been
in contact with an extraterrestrial for
about uh four or five years now. And uh
can you shed some light on on an
incident that happened over a year ago?
Maybe. I have a replica of this planet
that he comes from. In fact, he led led
me to this replica. And uh since I've
had this planet, u a little black hole
has appeared on the planet itself. And
in the last year, it has grown in
circumference. Uh since a year ago, I
have had no contact with the ET. Uh can
you shed some light on this? And the
planet is called Gamil. Uh can you uh
tell us what role this planet plays in
the association?
First we will ask in what way was your
contact accomplished? Through dreams.
Was there an identification or at least
what you might call a name provided for
reference? Yes. Elen,
did you receive an indication as to the
so-called purpose of the contact? Yes,
it was. It was to enlighten me uh to
enlighten other people through his
information
about about spreading uh love about um
the new age about also getting ready for
uh UFO contact.
Did it in your terms
commence just the five of your years ago
or were there previous connections? I
have had previous connections with the
CT. Yes. In many lifetimes
within this lifetime. Are there
incidents that stretch back at least as
far as 10 of your years previous to what
you perceive to be the dream contacts?
Possibly subconscious, consciously no.
Consciously I came in contact 5 years
ago. We would first of all suggest that there
We would first of all suggest that there
may be individuals who can be of
assistance to you in recalling that
there may have been earlier contact that
you simply are not aware of now and this
knowledge may assist you. They may be
able to bring it out of you in a sense
in what you might call hypnotic states
or relaxed or meditative states. You
follow me? Yes. We might suggest this if
it interests you as an endeavor. Very
much. Now Now
imagine your
brain. Picture your brain. And picture
that right at the center of your brain
also is a black hole, a gate, a
door. At this time, in your
estimation, what percentage of the
replica of the world is covered in
black? Maybe a third. All right. Very good.
Maybe a third. All right. Very good.
Then to some degree you can consider it
like what you might call a
call a
clock. And it is to some degree an
indication of the
rate at which your planet and other
civilizations of the
association are coming into an
opportunity to interact more and more
obviously. Let us say therefore, not
that it cannot accelerate greatly, but
specifically with regard to that
energy, you and your world are
approximately onethird of the way
towards full contact.
Now, as you describe the
idea, and this will fit in with a timing
we
understand of already having passed
through five of your years, then
recognize again another
decade will represent the final 2/3 at
this time. And within that decade is
when our ability and the ability of many
other members of the association will be
at a peak in terms of being able to
physically interact with you. I see. So
it is like unto what you call a sand
clock. The blackness represents the
gate, the contact gate, the absorption
gate through which you are stepping as a
society. And as you watch it engulf the entire
And as you watch it engulf the entire
replica, that will literally give you a
specific physiological time
frame, a representation of how your
energy as a society is accelerating
towards being equal to that society, to
our society, to all other societies
within the
association. represents the time frame
that makes it more available for you to
consciously join if you wish the
association of
worlds. You follow me? Yes, I
do. It is much like your hourglass in
that sense. And the blackness simply
represents the doorway through which the
connections are being made and the
mental linkups that are being
made and indicating the percentage of
the society with which those linkups are
being made.
fully. Now therefore you can understand
that whether it appears on the surface
or not collectively in all the different
ways you have of expressing it fully
onethird of your society is aimed in the
direction we are
speaking. It will not be too long before
the majority is aimed in that direction.
for you have long since passed the
threshold point and it is now on
automatic so to speak logarithmically
accelerating. Does this assist you? Oh
very much so.
Also continue pay attention to your
dreams in this way. There is not much at
this time that we can specifically tell
you about that particular civilization
other than for now there are many
interactions and there are in this way
specifically the timekeeping aspects
that will allow you to always see the
progression of how the energy in your
society is accelerated.
We thank you. Thank you.
Shanning. Hello. Hello.
Hello. Hello.
Regarding the uh laws that we agree to
abide by within our universe, does
functioning within your integrity mean
living up to those agreements?
It
depends. The overall agreements do not
necessarily have to be restricting. If
something that you know represents your
excitement and integrity can alter them
in many ways. If they are then
alterable what you are referring to as
laws, then that in and of itself may be
a sign of your ability to express your
integrity by being able to allow them to
transform into something else. Because
when you are totally integrated as a
whole, then there are fewer and fewer
limiting specifics. You follow me? So the
specifics. You follow me? So the
alteration of those so-called laws may
actually be an expression of your
integrity in certain
circumstances. Suppose an individual
were to go out and kill a 100 people
because that's what excites them. But
understand the idea again is that with
integrity means that you are functioning
as an integrated
being. Integration is functioning as a
whole. Meaning there is no separation
between you and the beings you are
killing. In other words, the recognition
that all murder is suicide.
And if you wish to truly be
empowered, then killing off those beings
is like hacking off your own arms and
legs. And that is not an expression of
integrity or power. And also when you
use the term excitement in that sense,
usually you will find that it is not
precisely excitement that motivates
individuals in that direction. It is the
negative polarity of the same energy
that creates excitement. But the
negative polarity is usually expressed
as anxiety.
You follow me? Yes. Suppose the the
victims agreed to be victims. That does
not excuse the perpetrator for not being
strong enough to not fall into the
victim's game.
What would be the consequences then of
uh violating integrity in this fashion?
Perhaps you will create another scenario
wherein you will have learned that the
violation of integrity in that sense
does not serve to empower you and then
you will express a lifetime maybe or an
experience where you will be the
expression of integrity. Some
individuals may choose to have other
individuals attempt to violate them as a
sort of what you call quidd proquo
exchange. That is not necessary all the
time. An individual who murders an
individual in one life does not
necessarily have to be murdered in
another life, although many have sought
the balance in that way. An individual
can perhaps talk someone out of
murdering someone else and fulfill the
same balance.
You follow
me? But the overall idea of course on
every fundamental level is that to the
oversoul all experiences are learning
experiences. And since you truly are
infinite, indestructible, no matter what you have
indestructible, no matter what you have
done, whether it be positive or
negative, whether it be an expression of
integrity or an expression of lack of
integrity, you will still exist. You
will still learn. You will still grow.
You will still change. You will still
have new experiences. So in the overall
sense, it does not really much matter
what you have done. But it is simply up
to you to understand that your own life
with the expression of integrity will be
far more joyful, far more connected, far
more effortless, and you will be able to
effortless, and you will be able to
create without any struggle whatsoever
all that you desire. In expressing lack
of integrity, you will find that an
individual who does that will struggle,
will suffer, will feel powerless, will
feel out of
control, and will create many, many,
many versions of their own expression of
versions of their own expression of
negativity within themselves and not
allow them to enjoy
life. You follow me? Yes. Um, is
self-imposed karma then a way
to balance out the integrity agreements?
Sometimes although again karma being
completely self-imposed does not have to
manifest in a
retribution style manifestation. Again
the analogy that karma itself is simply
the carrying through of a momentum to
create a balanced experience. Again, if
you have been a murderer in one life,
your self-imposed karma does not insist
that you be murdered in the next life to
atone for that. You may be able to
assist someone either who has had
someone close to them murdered or
someone who wants to murder. You may be
able to talk them out of it. And that
will be just as much of an expression of
your balance and karmic imposition as
being murdered in that way. And many
times just being murdered is not
necessarily a true balance.
The balance is something that's like an
absolute that has to be maintained. But
the karma does not that's that's
something that you don't have to have if
you don't have that belief system.
Correct. In a sense. Correct. But the
idea simply is in the fundamental
understanding of karma is that you will
usually since you are a collective event
balance the idea out somewhere within
your experience on some level and that
is all karma really
is of all the balance that you are all
the polarities that you
are where did someone like Adolf Hitler
come from I understand came from your
society came as an expression of the
combined and collective fears and
perhaps some self-imposed karmic
balances in a negative way that your
society placed upon itself. It was an
individual who did not feel their own
self-empowerment and so in your terms
fell into the adoption of the negativity that
into the adoption of the negativity that
was sensed in the society and expressed
it as a reflective negative mirror back
to the society to show the society what
the combined ideas of its fears and
negative attitudes had been able to
create. But that was not functioning within
But that was not functioning within
integrity. No.
because it was segregative, separated,
doineering. That which needs to dominate
does not believe it is in control
already. Okay. Thank you very much. Does that
Okay. Thank you very much. Does that
assist you? Yes, very much. Thank you.
Sure. Good evening, Bashar. And who to
you? Um, my question has to do with
um I feel like a black kind of heavy
little space. Black kind of heavy little
space. Very creative.
Very creative.
And it it gets in my way of
relationships and of it gets in your way
a lot, right? and of surrendering
completely to the moment and to
um taking all of my power and just being
all right. May I ask you a question?
Yeah. Are you sure you do not sound too
sure that you wish me to ask you a
question? I know I'm scared to death.
Oh, all right. It is all right if you
want to be scared to life, too. Okay.
Now I do. All right. This question
simply is why do you
assume that what you are describing
actually gets in your way as opposed to
being a part of the path you are
choosing to
be? Why do you think it is not a part of
your path? Well, I guess that's what I
want to know. It's what's the agreement
to to have that? I'm I'm I want to be
I'm finished with it now. I want to be
done with that. I want to be able to
um let that go a different process. All
right. Can you do me a favor? Yeah.
Yeah. All right. Can you define
it in any more precise terminology than
simply the heavy little black face? Um,
for me in in this right now, it feels
like mom and feels like the unresolved
stuff with mommy or something. All
right. And um can be many of the beliefs
you were brought up with. Yeah. And I'm
sure that's what it is. And and so I
understand all the stuff of your reality
being what you created. And so I wonder
why I get myself just right up to that
point, up to that wall, to that window,
to the whatever, and
and why I just can't just go through it.
All right. All right. May I ask you All
right. I'll ask you.
Let me ask you this. What do you imagine
would happen if you did go through it? I
guess it comes down to um death. I think
if
I be or whatever who I am or engulf all
my power, maybe there's some idea that I
won't be loved. And then if I'm not
loved, then I don't exist because I am
dead or that stuff. One moment. Your
definition contains a contradiction.
How can you be all you are and not be
loved? That is a contradiction. It is not
That is a contradiction. It is not
possible. You are made of love. How can
you be all you are and not be loved?
Because someone told you that or
something. So why why do you believe it? Why do we
So why why do you believe it? Why do we
believe it when we're I don't know. Why
do you believe it?
Why do you choose to exercise your
conscious commandment to continue to
believe it even though you know what it
is you don't want to believe in?
Um perhaps one of the beliefs you have
been taught is that it is not that easy
to transform it. Right? It's always the
hard way. The hard way. The hard way.
The hard way is the best way. I don't
want the hard way. I want the easy way.
I'm trying to find the easy way. You do
not have to try to find the easy way.
That's not an easy way to find
it. An easy way to find the easy way is
to simply do the things that are
representative of what you imagine the
easy way to
be. regardless of anything you used to
believe in. Also, what may be in your
terms hanging you
off is simply the belief that you have
to dig out all of the old
beliefs before you can place new ones
in. If you simply act upon whatever new
belief you prefer to be true for you, it
will automatically replace the old one.
Whatever it was, for whatever reason it
was there. It is also that
easy. You do not necessarily have to
dredge all the reasons up as to why the
old beliefs are there. You may find it
difficult to go on simply because
you are standing on the threshold not
believing that just activating the new
belief will be enough to cancel the old
one. But it is.
Is there any like exercise or
affirmation or something that can help
me let go of this? There are probably
2,578,934 of them.
Okay. Now, we could give you any number of
Now, we could give you any number of
them. However, your imagination will
always alter it to fit your best
understanding anyway. So, why not begin
with your imagination when you say, "Is
there an exercise? Is there a
technique?" Why not ask your imagination
for one? Since your imagination is the
primary tool, the reason you have an
imagination is for just such a
question. What can I do to change into
what I desire to be? Imagination. Give
me a sign. Give me a picture. Give me a
feeling, please. It always will. It's
the tool that is specifically oriented
to the vibration of the person you are.
For whatever your imagination gives you
will work for you. if you
trusted. So in your picturing of what
you would prefer to be, how do you
imagine if you were that person you
prefer to be? How do you imagine you
would act that is different from what
you are doing now? I would be more um
active. I would just get things done.
Boom, boom, boom, boom. Then understand
all you need to do is act that way and
that action will completely cancel any
other habits you have.
Okay. So all that stuff about karma with
this person or that person or agreements
that it's all valid and it's all
relevant, but in no way, shape or form
does it
control what you decide to be now. It is
all a part of what brought you to this
point, but it has nothing to do with
preventing you from being anything you
want. You right now just by whatever you
define yourself to be right now will
change all the focus of all the past
connections to validate what you choose
to be right now. The past does not
control the present. The present is not
a result in a controlling way of the
past. You define yourself to be whatever you
You define yourself to be whatever you
believe you are at any given moment. If
you find that a certain linear idea of
your past connections no longer serves
the definition you prefer to be, why
hang on to that
connection? Sever it by redefining
yourself and believing in the definition
you prefer now. Believing in the
definition you prefer now will change
your past to accommodate whatever
definition you choose to be in the
present. And believing is just your imagination.
And believing is just your imagination.
Just your imagination and your
willingness to act and trust that by
acting upon your instinct and following
what excites you the most, your physical
reality will always reflect that
certainty. back to you. That choice back
to you. That is how the universe works.
It works for everyone. No exceptions. It
is working for you right now. But it is
only reflecting back to you what you are
choosing to believe is most true for
you. Change your definition. Believe in
your new definition. Act like you
believe in your new definition. And your
physical reality has no choice but to
reflect your belief, your action, your
new definition. That is all it really takes.
definition. That is all it really takes.
Now, if you believe for any reason, and
it does not matter why, if you believe
you need a process to acclimate you into
the understanding that it's all right to
believe you're that powerful, and that
it's all right to believe it's that
simple and that easy, then by all means,
attract to yourself
a process, a exercise, whatever you find
most enjoyable, just because you enjoy
it. Okay. And that will work for you. Now,
Okay. And that will work for you. Now,
one exercise if you wish that we did
share with you of recent time already
exists in what you call your tape form.
And there are individuals who can refer
you to this exercise which deals
specifically with converting fear into
power. And if this works for you, use
it. If it doesn't work for you, don't.
The idea is to simply trust that you
will attract into your life whatever
truly will work for
you and lighten up on yourself. Okay?
There is no real heavy small black thing
in your
way. Only your assumptions that there is
something in your way creates there to
be something in your way. And the only
thing that's in your way is an
assumption that there is something in
your way.
That's it. Truly, it beliefs are what
create your apparently solid physical
reality. So a solid strong belief in a
very lightweight
assumption will create that assumption
to seem as if it is made out of steel
and it will seem to be immovable just
because that's what your belief
does. It solidifies your assumptions.
That's it. Is there any purpose in in
these beliefs? I mean do we you can
extract a purpose from anything perhaps
if you wish again to keep it simple. The
fundamental purpose in experiencing
limitation is to recognize that you no
longer prefer it and then you will not
be
limited. You can keep it that simple.
All right. I've gone through all of this
to recognize now by being able to
compare the ideas I no longer prefer to
what I now know I do prefer. I went
through all this so I would know beyond
a shadow of a doubt what I really
prefer. Now the last step is to simply
believe that if you act upon what you
prefer that will be from that point
forward the reality you will experience.
Plain and simple. So you always know
what you prefer. I mean really yes you
do. You can create a scenario in which
it seems you can hide your preferences
from yourself. But then in a sense to be very
yourself. But then in a sense to be very
basic about it obviously at that moment
that's what you prefer to
do but it is always a matter of
conscious commandment. If you are out of
control then you are preferring to be
out of control but you are controlling
that scenario. So you are never really
out of control. Okay? Simply know that
you cannot be truly out of control. You
cannot truly be off of your path because
you are not on a path. You are a path.
You can't be off
yourself. You are who you wish to be.
You are what you are. You are the
creator of your reality. Prefer what you
prefer. Believe in it. Act on it. You
will always get the reflection back of
what you truly prefer. Okay. Thanks.
Thank you very much for your boldness.
Hello, Buzzar. Hello. How are you?
Perfect. And you? I'm fine, thank you.
Thank you. I have a question relative to
a mental disorder that my son's
afflicted with called schizophrenia. Ah,
if you have any insight into maybe the
origin, possible potential cures that
may be forthcoming in the uh ongoing
years, I would appreciate your insights
into that. Oh, thank you. I have no
insight upon it. However, I
do while he is taking a
break, I will be glad to share our
perspectives on this idea.
Fundamentally, fundamentally, what you typically call
fundamentally, what you typically call
schizophrenia will usually be indicative
of the consciousness's
awareness that it is many different
persona coexisting at the same time,
overlapping in many different lifetimes
and dimensions of experience. For
whatever the reasons are that are
germanine to that particular individual,
they have chosen to experience more than
one of them seemingly within the same
time frame structure. Or they have not
been given the opportunity to understand
how to
communicate those two aspects of
themselves in a blended way because you
exist in a society that only recognizes
one persona at a time and not two
existing in that sense.
It is not truly in a sense a disease
fundamentally. The fact that that
particular manifestation exists in a
very limited type of
society makes it diseasing because there
is no way for that individual to learn
that they can communicate their
experience to the society because they
know it is not acceptable. That's what
locks them into the self-perpetuating
cycle that allows them no way to truly
communicate and understand that their
experiences are quite valid and quite
real and that that persona the different
personas are real distinct personas that
do have their own lives their own
validities. It is simply that they are
manifesting through what you typically
call one expression of embodiment.
It is to some degree, this is extremely
colloquial and not necessarily precise,
but it will serve as an analogy. To some
degree, it can be said it is like having
twins in one
body. You follow me? Yes, I do.
Now, many of these
individuals become what you typically
regard as negatively
schizophrenic simply because they are at
a very early age aware that there are
other levels and dimensions of
consciousness and they have free
communication with them. Not only do
they have free communication with them,
but they understand that since every
being is every other being, they have
free communication as them. All
consciousness is the same one
consciousness and can express itself in
any degree as any
persona. This individual is integrated
in a different way than the majority of
your society. They are integrated in a
way that allows them or creates in them
the desire for full expression of both
of the fragments of their total being
that they perceive themselves to be that
are overlapping at this time. But your
society has not had a niche for that
particular type of expression and so
they become their own society locked
into their own world. You follow me?
Yes, very much so. When your society
begins to understand that every
individual is the expression of every
other individual that has ever lived or
will ever live and is living now on
every different dimensional level. Then
they will be able to facilitate these
individuals by manifesting a type or
style of
communication that validates the
experience instead of invalidating the
experience of that
individual. All they require first and
foremost is unconditional love and trust
and validation that their experiences
are just as real as anyone else's chosen
form of expressiveness.
Because many of those individuals, if
they are loud lines of communication
into your society, can express
themselves in the terms you call
channeling. In a sense, you could say
that the physical channel before you is
schizophrenic in the sense that they
exhibit more than their allotted
personality quotient from time to time.
It is simply that this individual has
understood the trust that this is
something that can be utilized in your
society and never believed your society
when it said it had no reason or place
for that type of
expression because we are all fragments
of each other's consciousness. I am my
own being and I have my own validity.
The channel is his own being and has his
own validity but we are at one and the
same time the same being in many ways on
time the same being in many ways on
different levels. It is simply how it is
chosen to be
expressed. Individuals that avoid the
schizophrenic label perhaps simply go
about it more cleverly than others.
You follow me? Yes, I do. Uh question
regards that then the best way of coping
with that would be to surrender to it.
Would that be true? But this does not
mean that you cannot actively
investigate and involve what the
personality is all about. Dialogue with
it. Find out what all the likes,
dislikes of the different personalities
are, where they feel at home. Find out
where each persona feels at home. Allow
them all to be validated. One of the
fundamental reasons that this is a
difficulty in your society is because
your society has the strongest habitual
penchant for determining that something
must either be this or that when in fact
everything is this and
that. So validate each of those
expressions, each of those experiences
on their home ground. Find out who they
are and where they are comfortable and
let them know that you know they can
coexist. They do not have to fight for
domination of the one gateway body that
they have to express themselves
in. Now whether or not this will be
something that may occur soon in your
society, we do not know. But there are
societies that do express themselves in
the following way I'm about to describe.
And this is something that may actually
be possible in your society and it has
happened from time to time.
Briefly, individuals expressing more
than one persona as you recognize it in
that way may actually be able to create
a physical bill, a duplicate body so
that both personas can coexist and then
you would simply see them as physical
twins and then your society would say
that's okay because there is a society that
okay because there is a society that
actually creates themselves In that way,
any persona they imagine themselves
wishing to become, they actually project
another physical body to house that
persona. When they decide whether or not
that's truly the direction they wish to
go in, then either if they decide no,
then that extra body vanishes and they
pull the personality back in. If they
decide yes, then the original body
vanishes and they continue in the new
one as the new persona.
You follow me? Yes, I do. And then
dealing with that then the key word
would probably be acceptance. Oh yes. On
every level, but also
imagination, curiosity, exploration,
true dialoguing. Bring these personas
out for understand true unity of any
being is the result of the complete
equalization and validation of all of
its personality aspects.
Then the being can function in a unified
way when all of its aspects are equally
validated and accepted regardless of the
negativity that's hidden in some of
those personas.
When you allow them all to be validated,
they will not need to express themselves
in negative ways because they will know
they are worthy of love and then they
can start loving themselves and that
will form an integration within the
being and you may no longer see a
manifestation of either persona. you may
see a third new integrated persona. So
our traditional way of dealing with that
particular uh dysfunction is absolutely
probably incorrect. It is simply
indicative of many of the limitations
you already believe in as a society. But
let us simply say it is not conducive to
the birthing of the third personality
that could result from the blending of
the other fragment personas when they
are each allowed to know they can love
themselves for who they are. They will
not need to express themselves in
negative ways. They will learn to live
in harmony with themselves. That will
allow the being to reintegrate and
blend. But it will not be that it will
become one or another of the personas
already there. it will become a totally
new persona. It's extremely helpful. I
thank you very much. Thank you. And also
remember you are very capable of
dialoguing with this individual
consciousness in your dream reality.
Simply make the conscious decision that
you will do so when you go to sleep and
you will also begin to see results from
that because on that level you are both
wholly in communication as each other.
All right. All right. Again I thank you.
Exciting green. Thank you very much. At
this timing, we will allow a short break
and we will resume.
How's it going? Great. [Music]
[Music]
There's pink over here. And if anybody
wants tapes or videos, you can see Lynn.
Wave Lyn.
All right. I'll say sharing.
How's it going, Mr. As you create going
to go
is going rather well as we create going
to go. Thank you. How has everything
gone for you?
It's gone fine. Fine, too.
Um, a few questions ago, somebody was
asking about complete encounters where
we
would meet UFO beings on a onetoone.
Speak of some guys. Yeah,
please. A few questions ago, we were
talking about uh face to face encounters
between beings of your world and beings
of other worlds. Yes. Um, what's holding
that back? Nothing is holding it back.
It is progressing nicely. Thank you. Oh
well well the uh the obstacles to be
removed has has uh as we create them
because they would sort of uh I'm just
guessing at this we must have created a
delicacy to our situation to not have in
a sense other people come into our
reality what would they do would they
blow our chakras or in a sense yes blow
our minds and in a sense the idea simply
put is that because you still consider
consider yourselves to be segregated
beings in many ways and do not function
as unitized individuals. Then to some
degree the vibratory frequency upon
which you do exist is somewhat let us
say not meaning to be
derogatory slower than the vibratory
frequency of an integrated being. And in
this way therefore bringing a higher
frequency in proximity to a lower
frequency like a faster gear and a
slower gear. The faster gear will have a
tendency to overwhelm the slower gear,
forcing it to go faster than it is at
this point built to go or take all the
teeth off. Yes.
And therefore, we simply proceed at
whatever rate will
determine the amount or lack of friction
in that gear as we perceive you to be
adding more and more lubrication that
will allow it to turn faster and faster
and faster. That lubrication is your
willingness to simply know that you
create your own reality and to act that
way. In joy, light, love, service,
integrity. That is the lubrication. Will
allow you to spin as fast as you desire
to spin. Allow you to meet headon and
face to face any other gear spinning at
any speed.
Does that assist you? That that's fine.
Thank you. Um, another question or two.
I see. The um crystal generator with the
Fibonacci grid. Nice. the um the wires
coming out of the uh X and Y axis, Z
being up and down. I see. Would they be
insulated or would they just
be copper bear wire? Insulated.
Insulated.
They're insulated. So when they form the
Fibonacci grid, they're they're actually
touching each other or are they They are
insulated but touching. Insulated but
touching. as and then on the on the U
anti-grab device where you have those uh
coils going around the copper disc, the
wire goes to one coil, goes around it a
thousand times and it goes to the next
one and goes around it a thousand times
and it goes to the next one. That is one
methodology. You may also find it of
benefit there are many different
configurations that the whole external
idea the whole external ring can be one
coil of many thousands of windings.
So it doesn't need individual coil
pieces but that is one configuration
like a two. Yes.
Okay. That's neat. And um a while back,
I don't know, a year ago or something,
three quarters maybe, the uh we talked
about some flood stone that I had gotten
and it was reshaped in like a a double
cababashon teardrop.
Um which I I had made and and it was
um you said it might work the same as
one of those
board very low frequency watches.
It is to some extent. a grounding
frequency in many ways. Is it working at
that capacity? Is it? Yes. It's helping
my vibration stay at the rate of the
earth's vibration and all that to some
degree. Yes. on and off or when I there
is still some fluctuation but generally
yes it will allow you to
assimilate certain types of activation
energy ethereal energy and blend and
harmonize and balance that with the
lower magnetic frequencies of earth
energy as
well. It is also in many ways to some
degree transformational through a
certain path in specific ways allows you
to become familiar with some of the
radio frequencies of your planet in that
sense to become intuitive in many
subsonic ways many lower vibratory levels not
ways many lower vibratory levels not
lower in what you might call a
judgmental way. Mhm. The blood stone
actually um put iron into the blood or
put iron into the ethers which trickles
down into the blood or it is that idea
to some degree but not just specifically
that element. What what other elements?
Not that there is inherent within what
you call the chemical composition of the
stone, but it activates within the
electromagnetic atmosphere also some
attraction for silicon, sulfur,
magnesium, manganese,
leads from like an astral level or an
etherical level in a sense. Yes. And
then represents later on in a physical
level. Not always, but will represent
perhaps what you might call the
emotional symbol. Act if you have it.
Yes. Okay. Super. Thank you. Super.
You're welcome.
Super. Thank you.
Sharing. Hi. I feel really open with my heart
Hi. I feel really open with my heart
with you tonight. And I did something
really exciting yesterday. Oh, not you
too? I did. I walked in and I told um my
associates that I worked with that I was
no longer excited like I was a year ago
um to work there to do the things that
um excited me when I first got there.
And coming to that decision, uh I
suppose like five weeks ago, I began to
feel that I definitely was walking into
just another initiation phase. And it
was like um I could really feel a door
closing. And the thought of that because
of an old thought pattern or the old
habit of worry and fear, the thought of
a door closing really panicked me. And
it was just yesterday that I really
allowed myself the responsibility of to
continue walking through the process and
to realize that yes, when one door
closes, another one opens and to take
the responsibility and grab hold of the
door knob and open the door and walk
through. And oh, extremely super
thanking.
Um, it was really interesting when I did
this because,
um, being honest with myself, u, I was
able to release some stuff that I was
caught up in the last five weeks by not
being honest and willing to look at the
situation and to see that I was not
happy and to allow transition and
change. Change has always uh, frightened
me somewhat because of of the
unknowingness of what was beyond. And it
was really interesting because today
they were coming to me and they were
saying, "Well, what are you going to
do?" And and I I said, "I don't know.
I'm uh going to go home and I'm going to
heal and rest and relax and I'm going to
locate what really excites me and I am
going to go with my excitement this
time." Why? And um a friend of mine gave
me a book and she said, "Uh if you take
this book and ask it a question, just
open it up, it'll open up to the right
page." And I said, "Oh, really?" And
decided to give it a try. And so I
formulated the question and I thought to
myself, "Now I've gone with this
decision and I would really like to
trust it and I'd like a message of
trust." And this is what I got when I
opened a book and it says, "Go in
confidence in the direction of your
dream. Live the life you've imagined. As
you simplify your life, the laws of the
universe will be simpler. Solitude will
not be solitude. Poverty will not be
poverty, nor weakness weakness. And I
looked at the bottom of it and it was
written by Henry Thorough. And it was
just really appropriate and it just felt
like cosmic divine guidance that I
opened up the book and got that. You
mean to tell
me that it's that
simple? That it's that synchronistic,
that coincidental, that easy?
What I learned from it is that it's only
that if you allow it to be that. My my
and I did everything.
I I I also came to the realization that
um uh not that I want to do this, but
that I would be a wonderful um fear
instructor. I I really learned that very
well and I could could be a wonderful
teacher, but that's not what I want to
teach. Um but as being an actress of it of fear
Um but as being an actress of it of fear
and doubt and worry I I do the role just
magnificently. Um the other thing that I
wanted to to really get your assistance
on uh was last week within a period of
three days I had two what I call um
accelerating dolphin dreams. Um in the
past with all my dolphin dreams there
has always been a a state where I've
witnessed the dolphins in the water.
I've been in the water with them. Uh
they've swam around me, dolphins and
whales and humpbacks and orcas. And I've
always uh watched it with a little bit
of um of wanting to stay back just a bit
because I was afraid. And last Friday,
um I had the dream that I was in a
cave. And inside the
cave, I was with several other people.
And the energies were very similar to
the energies that I went to Hawaii with.
And next to my side swam up two
dolphins. And I had what I can only
describe is very, very
intense eye contact with this particular
dolphin. And he looked at me and what he
said through his eyes, "Go ahead, take
my fin." And I was frightened. And I
realized that and it was like having a
lucid dream and realizing, "Yeah, you're
frightened, but go ahead and take a
spin." So I did with my left hand and
then he opened his mouth a little bit
and I put my right hand inside of his
mouth feeling frightened about that. And
he closed on it very, very gently and we
swam. And as we swam, I was so elated
and so excited that I I hollered out to
the energies that were in the cave with
me, "Look, a dolphin. I'm with a
dolphin." And then at that time uh other
dolphins came in and they were with with
the other people. What was so strange
about this particular dream was after I
concluded the swim with the
dolphin all of the dolphins that were in
the cave turned into uh very tiny little
puppies. And we began to nurse the
puppies and I I woke up and I thought
that was very strange. Not so. Three
days later had another dolphin dream. I
was in the ocean this time with two
other people and swam with more than I
suppose maybe 10 or 12 dolphins. And
this time they turned into dogs. They
were already mature. Very good. Very
stately looking dogs. And they lined up
in a straight row just looking at me and
I would like your assistance in in the
dog in your society is the symbol of
service. Uh tell me more.
Uh tell me more.
[Music]
Sirius the star, the dog star,
right? I get that. But is there more? It
is the symbol of service and it is
representative of that which was begun
as an infant in your concept has now
matured into full service. And therefore
full service from you means from the
universe full service to you.
Okay. You are supportive of the whole.
The whole supports you. Mhm.
Okay. Well, those are nice messages in
times of this particular
transition. It's it's been
um because of my resistance, it's I've
had pain and a resistance which no
longer exists. Yeah, I agree. Okay.
Thank you. Thank you very much. One
moment. Are you planning to move about
in the near future? Geographically,
uh, I'd be willing
to. Our perception at this time is that
you may get an offer
to which will only be an extension and a
representation of the excitement of the
service you have
begun. Enjoy. Thank you.
There is also an
aspect of the total being that you are.
That in listening
in and having received your
understanding, your labeling of
yourself as a fear
instructor found this most enjoyable and
enjoyable and
delights in your awakening unto
yourself. You're awakening as a portion
of
creation. And to some degree, this being
represents the idea of your future
self. The future self you are now
willing to express yourself to be here
and now. and the future self that you
are rapidly also at the same time
becoming in more ecstasy and
joy than you may even think possible to
handle. But which you
But which you
will by all means
continue your stellar explosion.
Oh, thank you very
much. Delightful
dreams. Delightful dream
life. Delightful
delight. Thank you, Michelle. I'm really
touched by that.
Um, I would wanted to briefly say that
I've been investing myself heavily in
the accuracy of things that you have
told me about following excitement and
trusting that it will that I will be
automatically supported by. Are you
receiving dividends for your investment?
It seems that way. All right. Yeah.
Um, I wanted to tell to to share that
Paul Harvey on the on his broadcast
today mentioned having previously mentioned it
mentioned having previously mentioned it
back in December the sighting of the
spacecraft in Anchorage, Alaska, I
believe it was. Yeah.
Uh and he pointed out to the entire
American audience that transcripts of
communications between the air traffic
controllers and the pilot and witnesses
that were on the plane and so forth and
so on are now available from the Federal
Aviation Administration. Nice.
Yeah. And radar images. Ah, good. You
were listening in.
Um I also wanted to share with you that
uh that I've we've made a a milestone
step in getting the new metaphysics book
completed and in printed form. We thank
you. Yeah, it's my pleasure. And one of
the main things that I wanted to find
out about um I recently have become
aware as you are aware of another aspect
of the same oversoul of which I am um
who whom is in my physical surroundings
guys and it's brought up ideas questions
within me about that relationship.
One viewpoint might be
that beings exist or and let's say that
an oversoul exists and then chooses to
have different experiences so divides
itself up. Yes. And sends these
different aspects out into different
places. Nice. Actually my question is
then is are those aspects
rehomogenized at the end of the physical
life or is it a much
once something is created it continues
forever in many different ways. It is
more although all of this in your
language is rather arbitrarily being put
but it will suffice. It is more the idea
that the
reabsorption always seems to take place
from the point of view of every single
aspect. In other words, as each and
every aspect becomes more and more and
more expanded, more and more and more
aware of itself as its own
oversoul, this seems to happen from the
point of view of all the different
aspects that the oversoul created.
Each thinks it is becoming its
oversoul and so the oversoul is expanded
even from
that it becomes many oversouls in a
sense it plants many seeds which then
grow into blossoms that allow the
original single flower that gave all the
seeds to the soil to turn into a vast
garden. Each now its own oversoul and
Each now its own oversoul and
collectively the garden an
oversoul and so on and so on and so on.
Does that assist you? Yes, it does. One
last thing. Um I'm getting ready to
leave in the morning to go back to the
Monroe Institute and have a good time.
Okay. I was going to inquire whether
there was anything else that you might
wish to say to me before I go to do
that. If you see what you recognize as a
gate, go on, jump through
it. You don't have to hesitate. There
will be nothing that you could possibly
encounter that you wouldn't be able to
use in a positive way. And like another
individual said, if you might for a
moment experience a little
anxiety, enjoy it and it will turn into
excitement. Ride it. Flow with it.
Jump. You will be
supported. Jump through that
gate. You will discover many ways this
time that you can translate the gate. So
you will begin to recognize the gate in
its many forms. For you have seen it
many times but not necessarily
understood it for what it was simply
because of the previous definitions you
might have had within you. This time
many of those definitions are no longer
with you. You will begin to see the gate
and the doorway to your higher self in
many different forms and recognize them
all to be the same gate. Enjoy. Okay.
Thank you. Well, thank you very much.
Shedding. Hi. Hi. Uh, wanted to ask you
about the whales. Yes. When they're
doing their whale songs, are they doing
it to the other whales? Yes. Many times.
And if and when they're doing it to us
or our consciousness, what is their
message to us?
Whatever you feel it to be, however it
sweeps you
up, however you wish to discover the
totality that you are. Again recognize
by your analogy, a whale is a
physicalized embodiment of a dolphin
over soul. Many dolphins are a
whale. In a sense, it is as if you had a
physical being to represent your
oversoul at the same time that all of
its fragments existed as well. It is
simply that in your land environment
this will not necessarily need any other
symbol other than your own physical
body. In the water environment where
there is more expansiveness they have
been able to create a physical
reflection and interpretation of their
own higher consciousness to be embodied
in the form you call a whale.
So, so it puts you in touch reflectively
with the fact that you while in that
energy and anytime you wish to create
that energy for yourself are in the
vibratory frequency of and as your own
higher consciousness, you are
experiencing the scope of your power,
the scope, the distance of your express
ability. As rapidly as that song travels
through the water to all the ears to
which it travels, you also exist in a
etheromagnetic medium through which your
thoughts are always traversing and
always singing to all the other minds
upon your world. Sing your own song if
you feel so moved by the song of that
whale and you will be expressing the
harmonic vibration of your own higher
self and you will be that expression.
That is what it is a reflection of. It
is like being in the presence of a
reflection of you as your total higher
self. So sing the song you are moved to
sing. Does that assist you? I just want to
Does that assist you? I just want to
clarify it. So it's more like their uh
their messages in their symbolic form
that they're there than actually a
message like the dolphins have for us.
From time to time there may be a
specific message but generally speaking
the oversoul will communicate more in
generalities in feeling in emotion in
mood in tone in quality in light in
love. Okay I have a question. I'm reading a
Okay I have a question. I'm reading a
book called I Remember Lamoria and it's
an older book and the main character is
uh Mutan Meon or Mayion and uh they're
talking about Atlantis and um hell of a
lot of Lamoria but they were talking
about the sun's rays effect on people
and that's why they didn't grow as big
as they did on dark planets. Are we
talking about the same sun as it does it
have the same effect on us? In a sense,
to some degree, you will recognize that
certain vibrations you have created
yourself to be allow you to experience
certain vibrations from your central
star that has actually removed enzymes
and acids from your system. That has not
only in many ways in the past stunted
some of the physiological growth you are
capable of, but also reduced your
physical longevity.
Now you are regaining that again because
you are becoming a vibration that
automatically screens out the idea of
what you might term the harmful rays and
allows you the benefit of the light in
other ways. So you are as you have been
observing in generations not only
growing taller but also living longer as
you used to long ago. Okay. and he said
that he did made a lot of tablets, not
tablets, but something on metal that he
put all over the place. And uh at the
time the book was printed, they said
none had been found yet. I was wondering
if there was uh any found yet or in the
near future. Some have been sensed, some
have been understood, none have been
unearthed directly. Not yet.
There are still changes, timings,
encounters that must come to pass before
you will be able to decipher with your
own senses where these tablets
lie. When you can find them in that way,
that is when you will be able to read
them because you will only be able to
read them with your
heart. There will be nothing for you to
be able to translate physiologically,
linguistically. Okay. Thank you. Thank you very much.
Okay. Thank you. Thank you very much.
Sh.
Greetings, Bashar. And to you. I just
wanted to share with you uh that this
gives me great joy to share this
vibration with you. Uh my first question
is
uh the best way to handle or to cease uh
negative thoughts that I suppose come
from what is known as the alter ego or
the antichrist. What would you suggest
in that area?
Allow yourself to recognize that as you
become more expanded, as you contain
more of creation within you, you're
obviously going to become aware of more
of it. And that includes the negative as
well as the positive. But just because
you are aware of it doesn't mean you
have to put it into practice. Again, the
idea is to go back to your conscious
commandment. And we can now couple this
with the concept of the library analogy
that we have used and shared with many
of you from time to time. Think of all
of these ideas, all of these thoughts as
the books in a library. They are all
sitting up on the shelves. You can go
into the library. You can take any one
of them off the shelf. You can open it
up. You can read it. All of the joyful
books, all of the scary books, you can
read them all. The only one that goes
home with you is the one you consciously
decide to check out. So it does not
matter how many of these thoughts pass
through you or where they come from. You
are going to be cognizant that it is a
probable way to exist. But if you simply
know that it is not the way you prefer,
then you will not put energy behind it
and you won't have to worry about it.
Worrying about the fact that they are
there puts energy behind them. If they
occur, let them occur. Examine them for
what they are. Use them from a
perspective that you can get something
out of them. Maybe some scenario will
occur in your life that will allow you
to hearken back to the thought you had
so that you will have a perspective, an
experience that may assist you in
assisting someone else. When you become
familiar with the idea of what
negativity is, then when someone may
seek your assistance, you will have a
frame of reference to discuss the idea
from. Simply use it in whatever way,
shape, or form allows you to continue to
express your service in light and love
and integrity.
Does that assist you? Very much. Thank
Well, thank you very much. Uh, my next
question is I wish to visit uh inner
earth. Go right ahead. Thank you. Can
you give me an approximate way to optim?
Not really. Okay.
However, there are many areas upon your
planet that are relatively conducive
that contain energy vortexes that may
allow you at least the beginning of a
communication with that particular
dimension of experience. For do remember
it is another dimensional plane and in
your dimension is not literally in your
planet. That is the apparent direction
you will appear to go in encountering
those beings. But it is on a slightly
different vibratory plane. You're not
physically in your dimension inside your
planet. You follow me? One very strongly
conducive area to acclimate to the
energy that can put you in touch with
their consciousness is in what you call
the Shasta area or the Sedona area. All
right. Thank you. find you very much and
enjoy all the surprises and the
unexpected way in which they will
appease. Got it. Uh I have two more questions if
Got it. Uh I have two more questions if
you don't mind. You make them uh just
one or two so many people. Sure. Sure.
Sure. Um let's see which one. Oh, decision.
Um let's see which one. Oh, decision.
The shortest one. All right. The
shortest one. If you if one wishes to
channel a wondrous entity as yourself to
a wondrous entity like wondous what
could we do anything be
yourself and any agreements you have
made will express themsel in whatever
way they need to to allow you to
continue to be who you are. Do not
forget that when it comes right down to
it a of course as you have said you are
a wondrous being and channeling is only
doing what you love to do. Have a good
time. Thank you. Happy channeling. Sure.
Hi. Hi. Could you tell us the or the
significance of pi?
Helen. Yes, we can tell you our
perspective of the significance to us.
Okay. It
is the gate.
It is representative mathematically if
you wish of that factor in the universal
web in the universal matrix in the
so-called universal structure. It is
that factor that always allows you to
expand that structure so that it does
not become
fixed. It is the doorway out always
because it has no settled fixed value.
And yet it is the product of all the
other settled and fixed values in
creation. And it is also the seed of all
the settled and fixed values. But it in
and of itself is the elusive principle
that always allows you to expand upon
any structure that you have taken and
created out of it. Will that suffice?
Uh is there more that you could say that
is a good Well, it is no accident that
it is connected most often with the idea
of the circle because that lets you know
that there is no beginning and no
ending. It is perpetual in that sense.
It is perhaps one of the most precisely
representative symbols, if you will, for
eternity itself.
It is the factor that allows eternity to
always exist. It is the expression of
the fact that eternity always will
exist. Good. Thank you. Thank you very
much. It is the open-ended door and it
goes in all directions. Good. It
suddenly dawned on me today or I seem to
become aware that I've probably been in
touch with extraterrestrials of some
sort. Many of you in a sense have had
many dialogues with different levels of
consciousness. Some of what you may call
extraterrestrial. Yes. Well, fairly
continuously. Yes. I was wondering
specifically of your perception of this
awareness I just had. It is very
strongly there.
Could you have a sense of what level or
region or not at this time at this time
we would simply suggest to you that you
glean the information for the
information's sake. See if it works for
you. learn how to work with it and that
will bring with it all the recognition
that is necessary. Okay. Thank you. And
this process you speak about of blending
the feminine and masculine energy within
each of us. Nice. I can't seem to come
up with a sense in my imagination of
what the result will be after it's
blended. So I would like that. If I
throw a ball to you, will you catch it?
Yes. If I ask you to throw it to me,
will you throw it back? Yes.
Receptivity, sending off assertiveness,
receptivity. I understand them
separately, but it is the same thing.
You contain them both. Now, blending
them in a sense will allow you to use
whatever aspect, whatever polarity is
needed to be used in whatever situation
is conducive of using that particular
aspect. So the idea of blended doesn't
mean that it's sort of a neutral smoosh.
No, no, no, no, no. It simply means that
you have the capacity. It is more of a
certainty to allow them both to be
utilized when they are
needed rather than a suppression of one
or the other of them because you refuse
to acknowledge that you contain that and
can interact in that way. But at any
given moment if you're expressing what
is called masculine or uh that would be
you what you're expressing and if you're
expressing more feminine that would be
what you're in a sense. Yes. But also at
the same time your willingness to
express either of them will also change
the quality of your expression of any of
them. Good sister. Yes. Thank you. Thank you
Good sister. Yes. Thank you. Thank you
very much.
Hi Vishard. Hi. Uh I'm working in the
capacity as a healer and uh oh joy
assisting people in healing themselves
and Oh thank you very much. And I'm a
student and I still have a lot to learn.
So do I.
We are all students and we are all
teachers. That's why it's so much fun.
Yes, it is.
But um one area that I still am having
difficulty with is uh Oh, one moment.
One moment. Yes, sir. Oh, sir.
All right, Mom.
Would you Now, you do not have to, but
would you do me a little tiny favor?
Sure. Oh, thank you very much. Instead
of expressing the idea as something you
are having difficulty with, would you
care to say something? I am still
exploring with my curiosity.
Okay.
Yes, I'm exploring.
Uh well, when people have uh have
created a a disease. Yes. Obviously
there if it's the more intense the
disease, the more resistance there is in
healing themselves. Maybe it seems
maybe. So my difficulty is is trying uh
well listening to a certain extent I
need to work on the listening aspect of
these people but also the sometimes
simplistic view that uh just by even
though I believe myself you know that uh
if you're perfect that you will overcome
these blocks that you created
uh people who are who are already caught
up in that process. Yes. It's very
difficult to express any any ideas like
that to them. Well, that is all right.
Yeah. Okay. It it would uh letting that
be all right is the first step toward
truly helping them because you are
letting them be who they are. Yes. Then
what? Then they see the unconditional
love in you and that is what allows them
to relax about themsel and not judge
themselves so harshly which is what has
created the disease usually in the first
place. Then uh what
Then uh what
is if I get to the point where I can
explain to him what how can you how
about this? Why not trust that any and all
this? Why not trust that any and all
individuals if you know you are being of
service as a healer any and all
individuals that you attract into your
life will only be the ones that no
matter whether you see how you are
helping them will only be the ones that
you are helping.
Yes. And follow me. Yes. That trust also
will allow them the opportunity for more
freedom of movement as to how they help
themselves because you will not be
placing upon the expectations upon
yourself as to how you think you must
help them. So simply assume that if you know
them. So simply assume that if you know
you are a healer, then whatever way they
are interacting with you is the type of
healing they need. Even if it is just
reassurance of your presence, your love,
your faith in them, your belief in them,
your willingness to simply be with them,
whatever it is, that's what they needed
to get out of it. And you did your job
perfectly that I'm very successful in a lot of
that I'm very successful in a lot of
times, but then there's still that need
sometimes to have to explain things. And
well, explain what you feel like
explaining. Yeah, explain. But again do
it simply because it gives you joy in
explaining it not because they have to
understand
it. It is all the attitude that will
make the difference and they do
understand it on some level. Again they
don't have to have an intellectual
understanding an analytical
understanding to understand it when and
where they need to. You may simply plant
a seed that will blossom later. Okay.
when they are willing to shine the light
of their own soul upon that seed to let
it grow. But at least you have helped
them plant it. Even if you plant it in
the darkness for now, eventually they'll
walk into the light and it will grow.
You do not have to demand that you see
the results exactly as you think you
should. Does that let you lighten up a little
Does that let you lighten up a little
bit on yourself? Yes. Yeah. All right.
You are doing just wonderfully. Your
desire speaks for itself. and you are
willing to be a loving being. What more
do you really need to be? You are doing
the best you know how to do and that is
all you need to do
and that is what makes a difference.
Thank you. You have an impact you know.
Mhm. Oh yes. All right. Then enjoy the
impact you have. And that paradoxically
is what will allow you to expand and
experience more of the impact that you
are co-creating with other individuals.
Does that help you? Yes. Well, thank you
for allowing you to heal you.
Thank you for You are most welcome.
Do you by the way?
Do you
like gardening?
Yes. Have you given much thought to doing it?
Have you given much thought to doing it?
Yes, I have gardened before
and I have thought of moving out of LA
to do more of that type of
A off with who then?
It will give you the centering that will
allow you to know you are expanding in
many loving ways. And the energy you
will feel in being in touch with your
earth will allow you to truly beam that
from your
heart. You will learn much about healing
and centering simply from nature itself
which after all is a reflective aspect
of your own creatorhood. Thank you very
much. Thank you. chatting.
Aloha and mahalo. Aloha.
I'm so happy to hear the previous
conversation went directly into my heart
and now I have my own questions. Of
course. All right. Oh, of course. Yes. I
um am from Maui. All right.
And since December,
uh, it seems that we've had a lot of
space activity on Maui or has been there
longer than that, but yes, there has
been an acceleration. Yes, very much
increased. Yeah. And at the same time
for myself, I guess what I want to hear
from you is whether I'm on target. Of
course you are. Yeah. You do not need me
to tell you that. Well, with my thinking
is that what's been going on for me and
not only just me, but several other
friends is that it seems that we've been
being taken out of body at night. You
have been choosing to go. Yes. And
waking up between 4 and 6 a.m. in the
morning. Typical. Wide awake with
tremendous surges of energy. Yes. Lots
of nice. Um, you find it enjoyable? I
do. I'm really so thrilled for the
contact. Oh, thank you. Do not forget
that from our point of view, you are a
contact, too.
Thank you.
This is not just one way. You are aliens
to me.
We thank you for your contact.
Well, thank you. Well, I' I've asked to
be of service and it certainly has been
happening in of course the most unusual
ways. Um, but this particular energy
that seems to be moving through me,
uh, I I'm assuming that my vibratory
rates have been speeded up a lot with
this. You can only experience the
vibratory energy of the level you are
on. So, yes. Okay. Well, what's been
happening is that I've been going
through a lot of energy changes. Of
course, tremendous energy changes and
typical of the times. Well, including um
I at first I thought it was hormones and
it doesn't feel like it's the hormones
alone. Well, do understand that any
energy change you go through will affect
every single idea of your physical body
as well. So, it is that too. Well, I'm
experiencing mostly it is your enzymes.
Okay. Well, I'm experiencing tremendous
energy rushes and including in that is
um a lot of preparation. Oh, yes. Some
of it seems like fevers. Yes. Yes. It'll
come on all of a sudden. This is a
typical fourth density.
Yes. Typical fourth density symptom.
Okay. Is there anything that I can do to
um help to balance that because I don't
want to not bring in the vibration. Oh
no, no, no, no. You are you are doing
just fine. The idea is to simply use the
energy in whatever way excites you the
most and you will balance that idea out.
The only reason you are feeling it as
the fever is again because of the
comparison between the idea of the old
youth, the slower vibration, the idea of
the new youth, the faster vibration. And
when you bring these two ideas together,
the different rate of vibration causes
friction in your body that causes fever.
Mhm. So when you simply use the energy,
when you allow yourself to become that
higher vibration and stop comparing
yourself to the old you and comparing
yourself to the new you, just be who you
are right now. All the vibratory
frequencies will balance, blend. You
will acclimate to the energy by simply
doing more with it and then it will all
balance out.
Okay. So I I You are not alone in this
symptom by the way. No, I'm aware of
that. Thank you. And that did make me
feel better too. Actually what happened
was I was working with someone with
healing and in doing that I found that
they were having the same symptoms that
I was and we were it is only indicative
of the flow of energy through you but
through a system that you still perhaps
a little bit here a little bit there
don't think can handle it. So it heats
up from the friction of the speed of the
passage of the new energy. Okay. Well,
now since I've been here on the
mainland, which has been for about the
past month, I haven't been experiencing
the same nighttime contacts that I was
experiencing in Maui. It is time for you
to experience other things. You are
still experiencing them, but now they
are translating in different ways. Not
in the same. The idea is to translate
that into action, into doing, not to
simply have conversations for the rest
of your life.
Mhm. Well, on the visual level, um, I've
had a lot of experience with ships and I
haven't found that in this area, and I
wondered if there was a reason for that.
To some degree,
yes, the amount of population will make
it usually less likely.
The type of energy going on right now is
a different sort of energy, much more
accelerated in a different way than what
you call your Hawaiian
area. The Hawaiian gate is usually, let
us say, simply more conducive to casual
sightings. Mhm. Many individuals
here really would find that there are
many sightings around, but many of them
in many ways are simply too busy to
notice.
Very true. But again, the timing of any
particular place being what it is is
simply conducive to a different rate of
interaction. That is all. when in Rome
as you
say. So simply allow yourself to
understand that there is a different
expression of the energy where you are
now than where you were. Not that the
energy has gone anywhere, not that you
do not have it. It is simply different
terminology which you may not recognize
because you're not familiar with it.
Doesn't mean it isn't there. The signs
come out in a different
way. This particular area you are in now
is an area of more physical action. And
so many of the signs, many of the
conversations will manifest themselves
more likely in the actions that people
do. You follow me? Yes, I think so. All
right. Okay. Thank you very much. I have
one other question and I'll make it
fast. And that is I deal with crystals a
lot and I've recently found myself very
drawn to counite.
Define. I wondered what I'm the
information that I got was that the kung
faded is a bridge uh of the levels and I
wondered if you could express a little
bit on that.
We can perceive the connotation also of
what you call a ladder in a
sense. It is an ancient symbology. It is
connected as we perceive the definition
you are giving us, the energy you are
giving us into many ancient
descriptions. Some of which stretch
through the ideas, the areas you call
the Himalayan gate, Indian gate in that
sense. Some of which also connects
through the what you call Native
American gates. some of which connects
into Lamorian gates.
Let us say if we were to express an
embodiment, there would be a very
large but very soft
being or
energy connected with that particular
symbol that can easily
carry you through different levels.
It spans all the
levels and so functions as a bridge in
the sense that if you rest within the
archetypal hands of that
concept, it can very easily elevate you
from level to level since for that
energy it is no great distance at all. A
bridge in the sense that it compacts all
apparent linear
destinations into the here and
now. A bridge that has no
length because it needs
none. Because it is a bridge that
recognizes that everything is here and
now. Does this assist you? Yes. Thank
you very much. Thank you very much.
tender and
strong gravitational dreams to you of
the earth itself.
Thank you very much. Who are you?
Hi Bashar. Hi. Hi. Um a few months ago
uh I in speaking with you had uh
expressed a lot of uh questions and
exploring that I was going through about
my whole life in general and you told me
to cloak myself uh with abundance right
and that the doors would start opening.
Well, I've taken your advice. Um I've
done that and the doors are opening and
it's wonderful. Well, I do. Um you wear
the cloak. Well, thank you. What's
really interesting about it though or um
is that the walls around me in my house
are falling apart and um the old symbols
will break down. Yeah. Well, I've
thought of a lot of um I thought of of
course the first thing was I've got to
move. This means it's time for me to
leave this place. I've been here long
enough. Then I thought of the Oh, by the
way, water was dripping through the
walls which caused the walls to start
falling apart. light itself and the flow
will break down old rigid concepts.
Okay. Well, that yeah, that's basic I
that's what I wanted to know if that's
kind of your idea of what Yeah. Many
times you may interpret these things as
negative but they are actually positive
in that sense. No, I thought it was a
positive thing. I real Oh, I did not
mean you specifically. Okay. I I also
wanted to know
um when symbols like that start
presenting themselves to us are those
little divas are doing things like this
for us or in a sense but it is still an
extension of your own consciousness.
Divas are extensions of the archetypal
substream of your collective
consciousness. Okay, great. Great. Thank
you. Um, the other thing I wanted to ask
you, um, is my cat Luchina has leukemia
and I've been treating her, uh, with a
homeopathic vet. Oh my god. Um, I see
her increasingly get better. Uh, but I
was wondering if you have any um, well,
generally the cat in your world is the
fourth density symbol and many times
will take upon themselves the diseases
that represent some of the
transformations you are going through so
that you will not have to be
incapacitated yourself. Yes, I
understand that. Thank you. So, as you
strengthen the animals, reflection in
that sense can also strengthen. True.
Um, aside from that, I do realize that
she's reflecting a lot of what I have
been going through or went through.
Um, aside from that, is there anything
um any anything that you have to suggest
in terms of potions or liquids or herbs
or any kind of remedies uh that I could
give her aside from what I'm doing with
my homeopathic uh vetinarian? At this
time, because of the nature of the
interaction, what we find we can suggest
is perhaps to present several herbs to
the animal and see which one the animal
responds to.
the animal will know. Okay. And that way
you will develop a type of communication
with the animal that will let you know
that there is a clear and conscious way
in which you can communicate in your
terminology. How would I give them to
her in liquid form? What we are
suggesting is that you simply show it to
her. Oh, great. Okay. Well, that's easy.
Let the animal smell it. Let the animal
sense it. The animal will know. Go
through the different varieties that
your imagination suggests to you. Great.
one can become free. Okay, you may begin
there. All right, thank you. Thank you
very much. And we will find the animal
as well that has been with you through
so many lives. Yes. Yes. You said she
was from an Atlantean lifetime all the
way back even before that. The energy
has been with you. Uh-huh. You said she
represented something very magical. Um,
all cats do in me. Oh, all right. Is
there something more that you can give
me besides all besides the idea that
that all cats do or something more
specific?
Henry, walk in your dream with this
animal through the fertile
jungles of your
imagination, and you will allow you and
she to express the true fundamental
power of your stature.
Your abundance, its abundance, her
abundance. Let it suit you well. Walk
through the abundance of
nature. Let nature balance you. Thank
you. Let you being nature balance you
automatically. Enjoy the power of walking in your
Enjoy the power of walking in your
natural state together. that will
revitalize and blend and balance the
symbols and in a sense draw you together
as
one. Great. One more very small
question. Francesca, uh, Daniel's daughter, would
Francesca, uh, Daniel's daughter, would
like to know if her
greatgrandfather, if she is her
great-grandfather, if she has
reincarnated as her great-grandfather,
Franchesco.
It is our perception that there are
connective lines in this direction.
For now, we can say no more. Thank you.
We thank you. At this
timing, allow us to extend to each and
every one of you once again our
unconditional love and our
joy in allowing us to experience the
gift of your consciousness individually
and collectively. Thank you for being our
collectively. Thank you for being our
teachers and our
sharers and for being willing to be our
equals.
We thank you for co-creating this dream
with us this day of your
time. Exciting dream lives to you all.
Once again, conscious again, conscious
commandment.
Choose then live what you choose
trusting that all the details will take
care of themselves. Fall into place
according to your conscious commandment.
You are in control right
now. You never have been out of
control. Wake up and live your dreams.
We thank you. Bond and unconditionally
loving. Good day to you all. Good night.
Good night. Hi Don. Hi Don.
Hi [Music]
How'd it go? Great. Thank you, Daryl.
Thank you all for being here tonight.
Few quick announcements. Uh you if you
want an audio tape, you can have it
tonight at tonight's session. We have
two high-speed tape duplicators. You can
have it tonight.