iting was his way of sort of tapping me
in the subconscious memory to get me to
start learning about the things I needed
to learn about in order to fulfill the
agreement that I had made. So spurred on
by that sighting
uh I began doing more reading about UFO
phenomena and metaphysical phenomena and
um eventually I read you know about
mediumship along with many other things.
Ultimately, I was introduced to several
mediums who were practicing at the time
and one of the entities coming through
one of those mediums offered to teach
mediumship for whoever was interested.
Now, even then, I took them up on the
offer and went into the class not
thinking that this is something I was
going to wind up doing. I had just read
all the books I could find and I wanted
to learn more about it. So, I thought,
well, if I go into a class, I'll see
something in action. Maybe I'll see
someone become a medium and uh I'll find
out more about what I want to find out
about. When I was in that class in a receptive
When I was in that class in a receptive
state under the guidance of the other
entity through the other medium is when
Bashar and his people made the
telepathic connection with me. And as
soon as they did, then the memory of
having made the agreement came back. Who
they were, who I was to them, why the
ship sighting had occurred, dream
conversations I had had with them at
night that I had totally blocked out of
my memory up to that point, all came
flooding back in that one memory at that
one point. And what came with it was the
first, let's say, real time message from
them telepathically, which was, "Okay,
now that you remember all of this, now's
the time for you to start doing this as
you agreed to, if you still want to. Do
you still want to?" Um, cuz it's always
a choice. And obviously, I said yes. And
I've been doing it now for the last four
years. This happened four years
ago. Now Bashar presents
himself as an extraterrestrial
consciousness and as I was saying
because of the ship sighting and a lot
of other things um I have my own
validation that he is who he says he is.
But one of the things I would like to
absolutely make very clear at this point
to everyone is that there is nothing at
all about this
particular channeling, nothing about
this experience that insists that you
have to believe that it is what we say
it is. That's not what this is about.
And there's no way we can prove it to
you right now anyway. From time to time,
other people have seen his ship, but
it's not something that can happen on
command. And he says that in a short
time, perhaps within the next decade or
so, it might be something that will be
possible to do on mass. But right now,
they have their reasons for remaining in
the background. And one of the reasons
is that in observing our society, they
have basically noticed that we have a
tendency to listen to the to follow the
messenger and not listen to the message.
So they're remaining relatively
unobtrusive so that people will hear the
information and so there will be no
proof as to who they are at this time
because they don't want the focus to be
on them. They want it to be on the
information because it's the information
that is being used to serve us. So
primarily the idea behind this is to
really get out of it what you want to
get out of it. If the information that
comes through that Bashar shares with
you in your questions and answers is
workable for you, use it. If it isn't
workable for you, don't use it. go and
find what does work for you. That's the
whole point of this thing. I don't care
what you do with it. I'm here to do this
because I recognize that it does serve
people. It serves me. It's changed my
life drastically in terms of applying
the information that Rashard has shared,
but different things work for different
people. So, you know, the vibration of
this particular channeling may not be
for everyone, and that's fine.
Um, Bashar is not literally his name. in
their society, they're pretty much
telepathic and they don't really have
names per se. It's a word that he chose
when he first came through so that we
would have something to represent him by
since he knows we use names. It's a
little bit better than hey you or
something like that. But it's an Arabic
word which is partly my background and
he chose it. I had I don't speak Arabic.
I had no idea that it even was a word
when he chose it. It has several
meanings which other people have have
informed me about who do speak Arabic
over the years. One meaning is that it
simply means commander which is
something similar to what he is in his
society. Another meaning is simply the
man or the being. And the third meaning
in an Armenian dialect is that Bashar
means messenger. So even though it's not
his name, he obviously chose a word that
represents in all different facets what
he's doing. And it may have other
meanings that I don't even know about.
Um two things that I would like to lay
down before we begin and especially with
in a sense a new group. I know many of
you have heard the tapes or seen the
tapes, but um in terms of a live
interaction, it can be a little bit
different. And one thing, two things
that I'd really like to point out most
importantly, and I can't stress this
enough because I find that people are
still hesitant to Bashar. There is no
such thing as a silly or a stupid
question. Don't be shy. Don't hesitate
to hold back if there's something you
want to ask because you think it's a
waste of everyone's time. There's no
such thing. Out of some of the most,
let's say, mundane things that people
might have asked in any of the sessions
we do have come information and
interactions that have served almost
everyone. So, don't hold back on that
account just because you think you'd be
wasting everyone's time. It's never a
waste. If it's really important to you
and it's something you really want to
know, talk about it cuz a lot of other
people will usually find that they want
to ask the same thing and you've asked
it for them, so you've done them a
service. Secondly, in the trans state, what I'm
Secondly, in the trans state, what I'm
doing is sort
of defocusing the consciousness that I
typically am as a personality and
letting Bashar's personality sort of
interlock with mine. So my consciousness
starts to take on the vibrational
frequency of his. That's what allows me
to function basically as a translation
box or as somebody once said literally
as a human telephone. There's no
thinking going on in what I experience.
I only see I I am conscious, but I see
pictures. I feel energy. I feel
emotionality. But a lot of it is
extremely abstract for me. It's like
being lost in a daydream. And time is
very accelerated for me. What may turn
out to be a typical 3-hour session will
only probably feel like about an hour to
me. So because Bashar is not actually
So because Bashar is not actually
speaking our language but because his
thoughts are just simply evoking from me
whatever words I'm programmed with to
fit the concepts that he is sending
telepathically. Sometimes the words or
sometimes the concepts may sound
unfamiliar to you. So the second point
is is if ever you hear anything coming
from him that just for some reason
doesn't make sense, don't let it slide.
Say Bashar, wait a second, I don't get
it. Can you back up? Can you use another
word? Can you explain it another way?
Can you use an analogy? Again, to him,
everything is the first time, every
time. He is never bored. He is always
excited. This is what he's chosen to do.
And yet, he wants to know that you are
getting out of this what you want to get
out of this. So, don't let it slide.
It's your time. Use it in the best way
you can to understand the most out of
this that you want to. So, whatever you
put into it is what you'll get out. He
is very willing to talk about anything
and everything. There are no taboos on
subject matter, but he's not going to
pull things from you. So, if you're
hesitant to talk about it, you don't
want to touch on it, he's not going to
force you to do that. He's going to put
out exactly 100% what you're going to
give to him and probably very much in
the same way that you give it to him cuz
he's acting as a mirror showing back to
you whatever it is you're putting out.
That's his
service. Um, so those two things
primarily. All the other thing I will
say is that when I'm going into the
trance and when I'm coming out of the
trance and I assume there will be a
break because there usually is and at
the end of the session tonight when he
says goodbye or take a break or what
have you, I'll just ask you please don't
all start talking at once and don't get
up and move around until I'm actually
reoriented. It's not draining. It's not
painful and it's not depleting for me.
It's actually always energizing but it
is very disorienting. So, if you just
give me a second to reorient before you
start talking and moving around, I'll
let you know when I'm back. Um, the
analogy I usually use is that if if he
says good night and you all start
talking at once, it's like having 60
people screaming at you in the morning
when you're trying to wake up out of
your bed. So, it's just a little bit
disorienting. Let me reorient and then
you can run around and scream and do
whatever you want to do after I'm back.
Um, you will notice a few bodily changes
occur when the energy comes on. And
again, I only say this is not painful
just because people have said it looks
painful. It's just an automatic
adjustment to the energy. So don't worry
about that. The basic bottom line to all
of this is to have as good a time as you
want to have. Have fun. Bashar, in many
cases, the more willing you are to
lighten up will lighten up right along
with you. And again, as I've said, he's,
you know, don't be shy cuz he's not he's
a real chatter box and he'll go on about
anything you want to talk about. um then
he will help you understand the
mechanisms for how to get in touch with
those things that are important to you
and use them in your life in the way you
want to. So that's up to you. It's
absolutely your time.
I noticed that there aren't a lot of
questioners up here. In case you don't
know, these are the seats for questions.
Um and as the seats are taken up and the
people go sit down in the audience, more
people can come up and ask questions.
I'm going to ask people to only ask one
question at first. If there's more time,
they can go back and ask. We have this
room up until 11:00 and so if you want
to continue conversations afterwards,
please take them outside because we need
to be out of here by 11. Other than
that, please I encourage you to answer
questions. I mean to ask questions
because that's how long this is going to
be. When the questions are gone, the
channeling's over or sooner than that.
Thanks. Um Okay. Yeah, we we do that
sometimes at the sessions we do in LA
and basically not only as a matter of
time but trying to focus on the single
most important idea to you will help
consolidate. Now if Bashar takes it
further then by all means go with him
but I guess for the sake of allowing as
many people as possible to ask questions
try to keep it to you know one idea.
Yeah.
Bashar is an extraterrestrial being from
a planet, a civilization they call
Esasani. Uh they consider like
everything themselves a part of of what
they call all that is which I guess is
their reference for the creator. You can
ask him about that in terms of the
specifics of how to apply that that
particular label to it. But um he has
simply explained that he's here to be of
positive service to allow us to live the
lives that we want to learn how to be
loving and live in light. So whatever
analogy you want to draw from that you
you can and and anything you want to ask
him for more clarification you can. Are
there any other questions about
procedure before we
begin? Okay. Have a good time and I'll
see y'all later.
One last uh little thing for people,
especially in the front row, there will
be a volume change, so don't be too [Music]
startled. You don't need to adjust it. [Music] Heat.
Heat. Heat. Heat. A [Applause] Oh.
All right, I'll say how are you all this
evening of your time as you create time
to exist.
Are you all alive? Thank you. Allow us
to begin this interaction, this evening
of your time with a reminder of the
reasons for why this interaction is
taking place.
Your world now as we have perceived it
is beginning to go through
transformations and discoveries and
explorations of what you have for so
long called the different aspects of
your consciousness. You are now
redefining the idea of what it is to be
a consciousness of what it is to be a
part of creation.
The idea is that any civilization that
begins to explore the different realms
and levels of consciousness as you are
now doing will start changing the
frequency of the consciousness it has
been and will radiate at a particular
vibration and that vibration will
attract other levels of consciousness
that are also functioning on the same
idea exploring many of the same things.
And thus you have by your explorations
extended in a sense to us an invocation
to interact with you at this time to the
many worlds and dimensions of
consciousness that we represent. Our
interaction with you will be indicative
of our recognition that you are now
expanding within your consciousness in
such a way to allow your senses, what
have been called your dayto-day
physiological senses to become aware of
more of who and what you
are. You in a sense are spirit. You are
light itself and you are in an overall
sense fundamentally complete. But you
have created the idea of your
physiological existence. And that
physiological existence carries certain
definitions with it that may have placed
limitations upon your ability to
remember and be aware of consciously the
totality of who and what you were
created to be. In having, shall I say,
played this game of forgetfulness for
tens of thousands of your years of time,
you have created many habitual rituals,
consciousness loops that continually
allow you to create the habit of
forgetfulness over and over again, the
habit of limitation and focus over and
over again. But now, now the timing upon
your planet is representative of the
fact that you have more or less played
out almost every single way there is to
play out of limitation upon your planet
within the particular game you have been
playing within the particular focus of
consciousness you have existed within.
And so you are waking up in a very real
sense. You are beginning to remember
more of who and what you were originally
created as the idea of spirit and light
itself. And as you now come out of the
ancient cycle of forgetfulness and begin
to move into the new cycle upon your
planet of awareness and
integration, then you are beginning to
find that your senses which have been
confined to physiological reality for so
long are beginning to become sensitized
to energy of different forms. Forms that
are more rarified than your senses have
been able to perceive. You are now
extending yourself into the vibratory
frequencies of electromagnetic light
that you have hereto for allowed only to
be invisible to you. And as you expand
your senses, you begin to see and hear
things you did not hereto for see and
hear. These things do not have to be
taken as strange. They do not have to be
taken as negative in and of themselves
just because they are happening and you
are not used to it. It is simply that
you are not used to it because you have
been in a habit for tens of thousands of
years of not paying attention to the
existence of those realms of those
levels of those dimensions of experience
even when they have been all around you
all the time since time immemorial as
you say. Now you are waking up and as
you open your spiritual eyes, you will
be able to be cognizant of more and more
reality that exists around you on more
rarified levels of energy. Recognize
that in an overall fundamental sense,
you are not really learning anything
truly new. But newness comes from the
creation of a different perspective of
what already exists in its total form.
So as you wake up, as you become more
aware of more and more levels of reality
that already exist, then that is a
newness that creates different effects
in your life and allows your
physiological reality to become far more
representative of a malleable,
flexible reality that allows you to
understand that you, each and every one
of you, were created to be doorways,
gateways through which a different view
of the infinite creation has been
expressing itself. And that as you
change your idea of what view you choose
to be, so then does the physical reality
around you change. Because your physical
reality has only been the product of
what you imagine it to be, of what you
have been taught to believe that it is.
It is only a point of view. It is one of
the ways of all the infinite ways that
all that is has of looking at itself, of
creating itself to be within creation.
Our civilization is another way. other
civilizations, other dimensions of
consciousness are yet more ways that
infinite creation has of realizing and
manifesting itself within the creation
that it
is. But you and all portions of creation
in that sense are created with what you
call free will. And that free will means
you can change the perspective that you
are at any given moment. And as you
change the perspective, as you change
the idea, you change your beliefs. And
as you change your beliefs, you change
the blueprint, the filter, the doorway,
the gateway through which the energy of
infinite creation manifests as the
physical reality you perceive to be what
you experience on a day-to-day reality.
So our service to you at this time is to
put you in touch with yourselves to
allow you to understand the
self-empowerment that is within you to
transform your point of view in any way
shape or form you really desire to
transform it and to understand that in
transforming that point of view you will
literally physically change the reality
the physical experiential reality you
find yourselves elves interacting with
on a day-to-day basis. Some of this some
of the ideas that we will be discussing
with each and every one of you may sound
like what you are used to calling
philosophy and in a sense yes it is
since it is a different point of view.
It is a
perspective. But the ideas that we are
also discussing actual mechanical ideas,
physics if you
wish, methodologies if you wish by which
you can alter the physical reality that
you experience yourself to be because
you are creating it now just by what you
believe to be most true anyway. And when
you change the definition of your
belief, you change the physical reality.
It changes your emotions. It changes
your thoughts. It changes all of your
experiences. And your experiences can
can be changed in the direction you
prefer them to be changed. It is up to
you. Completely up to you. You have that
free will. You have that ability. It is
a part of your inherent right as beings
as all beings are as you say in your
literature made in the image of the
creator. What does that mean? It means
that you are also multi-dimensional
creators. That is what it means. And we
are here to assist you to remember that
you are multi-dimensional creators as
far as your immediate experiential
reality is concerned. And that you can
exercise that ability, exercise that
flow in an effortless and joyful manner
and manifest the reality that is more
synchronistically in harmony with love,
with light, with peace and ecstasy upon
your planet. At this
planet. At this
timing, we will always extend to you our
unconditional appreciation and love in
your willingness to interact with us
this day of your time. In your
willingness to function literally as
ambassadors of your society because that
is what you are. And allowing me to
function as an ambassador of my society.
So that bit by bit, day by day, your
society and our collective societies in
the association of worlds may create
more conductivity and conducive
atmospheres in which we may interact
face to face for that time as we
perceive your energy is close at hand.
But for now, it is simply that we
interact in this way to allow you to
recognize yourselves as equals to us. We
are not your betters. We are equal to
you. We may have expanded points of
view. We may have different points of
view. But that is all we are is
different. In the infinite creation, all
is
equal. We thank you for allowing us to
experience the gift of your
consciousness. Because in sharing who
you are with us, you give our society
that much more opportunity to perceive
all the different ways that infinite
creation can manifest itself to be
through the unique manifestations that
each and every one of you are and have
chosen to be. In return for your loving
willingness and your loving gift, I ask
you now, how may I serve you?
Can you please tell me what kind of
changes, physical changes we're going to
see in our world in the next Can you all
hear this individual?
Do you wish to make an adjustment?
Yes. Could you please tell me what kind of
Could you please tell me what kind of
physical changes we're going to see in
our world in the next 15 to 25 years?
Thank you. To some
degree, the idea of physiological
changes that will occur upon your planet
will be as follows. As we perceive your
energy now, there will be strong
electromagnetic shifts both physiologically and in your
shifts both physiologically and in your
consciousness. But remember this and let
us lay this as a foundation. There may
be isolated pockets upon your planet
that will experience some of these
changes in what you would call negative
or catastrophic ways, but by far it does
not have to be that way. All
transformations in that sense are
neutral transformations and whatever
vibratory reality you are most closely
aligned with will be the way you will
experience the transformation. So some
individuals will experience the
transformation in positive ways. Some
individuals will experience it in
negative ways. It is up to you to decide
what vibratory reality you are and then
that will determine where you will
automatically be and in what way you
will experience the changes in the
electromagnetic fields upon your planet.
The change in the electromagnetic field
is indicative of an acceleration in your
mentality and in the timing of what your
world is going through at this time. For
your mentality is created from the
electromagnetic field. Consciousness
intersects with what you call the
electromagnetic field of physical
reality. And from that intersection is
created the phenomena you call mind.
physical mind mentality in physical
terms. So your mind patterns, your
mental patterns will ultimately
determine the way you experience the
electromagnetic shifts and accelerations
that are going on on your planet now
positively or negatively. You
understand? Does that serve you?
Remember also that with the idea of
prediction, there is no such thing as a
prediction of the
future. There are many probable
realities. It can go many different
ways. Now, there may be one or two
realities that have a great deal of
momentum behind them. Let us say a great
deal of popular support, a great deal of
energy behind it. And it may seem
unlikely that it will divert or change.
However, when you hear a prediction
about what is going to happen or not
going to happen, that prediction is
simply representative of a sensing of
the energy that exists at the time the
prediction is made. The very next second
could be different. And very often when
a prediction is made, you are now made
aware of where the energy is. A
prediction is simply saying, look, this
is the probable future behind which you
have most of your energy. If that energy
doesn't change, it is likely to manifest
into physical reality. But now that you
are aware of the prediction, if you
don't prefer the outcome, your awareness
of the energy, your preference of a
change in the energy will render the
prediction obsolete. So being made aware
of a prediction many times will actually
cancel the prediction itself. You
understand? Does that serve you? Thank
you very much for your sharing. Sharing
sir, I would like to ask you a personal
question if that meets with your
approval. All questions in that sense
are allowable. You do not have to ask my
permission. Okay. July the 12th, we had
an experience where we experienced 19
UFOs. my wife and I and they seem to
form symbols for us and we can find
nobody else that has seen this. Is there
any special meaning to my wife and I for
these UFOs? Can you find it in my aura?
Recognize first of all that many
individuals collected in what you would
call groups may not necessarily indicate
that their vibratory reality is all in
synchronous alignment. And therefore
some individuals can see things in other
dimensional planes that individuals
right around them will not be able to
see. And in this case that is what you
are describing. The idea is that your
vibration was simply oriented to the
appropriate frequency to be able to
perceive into a slightly different
dimension of experience. It was in your
terminology, let us say aware on the
part as we perceive that energy of those
individuals that they were simply giving
you intuitive symbolic communication.
What we call
identification. Identification is simply
aligning vibration with vibration.
seeing who is aligned to particular
frequencies and taking note of that in a
sense locking them in to simply take
stock of what percentage of your
individuals upon your planet are
aligning with a vibration that would
allow us to interact more and more and
more with all of you. So you were
noticed in that sense and you were given
the idea of recognition. You were shown
ideas of symbols that translate directly
into your unconscious and subconscious
minds to awaken within you whatever you
are willing to allow to be awakened so
that you can then be assisted with more
momentum and more energy to do the
things in your life that represent the
strongest of who and what you are. May I
ask you a question? Yes, sir. Are you
doing in your life what excites you the
most?
Um, I'm getting to it. Little by little.
Little by little. Yeah. Why are you
waiting? Oh, it's it's just taking a lot
of time for me to get open to what I was
supposed to do in this lifetime. Not so.
Not so. It does not have to. Now, the
idea may be that when individuals are
asked, well, are you doing the thing
that excites you the most? They conjure
up an image of something that will be
the most exciting thing they will ever
do in their life. and they work towards
getting to that point not enjoying the
rest of their life at all. But the idea
you see is that when we ask you are you
doing the most exciting thing we simply
mean are you doing the most exciting
thing you can be doing in the moment now
right now of all the things you are
capable of doing if you simply do the
one that excites you the most with
integrity very important then you will
be fulfilling the path you chose to be.
You will be fulfilling the purpose you
chose to be in that sense because the
fundamental purpose to all of your lives
is to simply be as fully as you can the
life you are living now. And the way to
most easily do that is to do what
excites you the most because excitement
is the vibration that lets you know who
you are. That's why it's exciting.
So if you simply do at any given moment
the thing that excites you the most out
of all the things you are capable of
acting upon, it will automatically lead
you into the circumstances necessary to
be able to do the next most exciting
thing that will come along and the next
and the next and the next. Excitement is
a string is a thread. It leads to all
other excitement and it constantly
allows you to accelerate your momentum.
You do not have the idea necessarily of
just a specific thing that you will have
to do in life and then that's it. There
are many things you can do that are a
part of the overall life you chose to
be. Remember all of you, even though you
are reincarnational beings, the you you
are now only does have one life to live.
So the fundamental purpose of the life
you are living now is to live it to the
fullest. to be the fullest you you can
be. And if you simply do that and are of
service, with doing what excites you
with integrity, with love, with joy, you
will fulfill your purpose. But you can
start right now by doing at any given
moment whatever you are aware that you
are capable of doing that excites you
the most out of all the things you are
aware of. You understand? Yes, I
understand. Does that serve you? Uh, I
think so. Do do you are you kind of
saying that because of the sightings and
things uh I've had I have had a desire
to meet with space people. Is that
because the sightings and things are
coming around because of my desire? It
is because of the vibratory frequency
you have placed yourself upon. But those
sightings are indicative of the level of
energy. It is a reflection, let us say a
mirror to you, of the level of energy
you are operating on and therefore
should be quote unquote should the idea
of a reflection of exactly how much
energy you have and a reflection that
you can do anything you want to with it
right now and you don't have to wait
understand okay thank you thank you very
much
hi Bashar hi um I have a personal
question all right a phenomena that I
experienced about seven years ago You
know, I was doing some meditation with
uh some tapes, some tapes that you send
in for and I was just at home and
experienced a spiritual awakening and
did not have anybody to relate this
experience with at that time. I saw and
for a long time I felt the love of God
and the oneness with the creator and
then I came to a point where my ego took
over and I became very afraid and just
turn one moment. One moment it did not
take over. You placed it in charge.
Right. Exactly. I put it above I put put it
Exactly. I put it above I put put it
above the spiritual experience above the
spiritual process.
And uh after that I did a lot of other
things in which
uh made the process even more difficult.
All right. What did you learn from that?
That you can't control the spiritual
process for one thing. Not that way. But
that you actually are always in control
of it when you allow it to flow
naturally. Right. Nice. But that's sort
of hindsight because that's all right.
Because of the experiences in
controlling and manipulation of other
processes, yes, I am left over with uh a
great deal of metaphysical discomfort
which I experience only because you
believe you need to hang on to it. Only
because you believe in guilt and regret.
Right? Okay. You don't need to believe
in that. If you recognize that you have
now chosen which way you prefer, which
way represents the positive energy, then
if you will allow yourself to know that
simply by making the choice to recognize
which direction is positive and then
acting accordingly, that that right then
and there will absolve you of any guilt
and regret you need to hang on to. Mhm.
Understand? Yes. I I believe I I grasp
that aspect of it. However, when I am
actually experiencing the physical
phenomena of being uncomfortable
or disconnected as it were, then I
psychologically bring my my vibratory
level down. Why? And uh because I say to
myself, this is terribly uncomfortable
and I wish I could get through this
period and what is my learning lesson
with this? And uh you know I put myself
in a little bit of a
uh boxed in place. All right. Then why
do you create the definitions that
create the box?
Why not change the definitions? So do
you have some suggestions that I could
follow? Yes. Okay. Are you paying
attention? I'm Yes. The best of my
ability. All right. We have it on tape
so I can listen later. All right.
But let me remind you that you are the
recorder. Understand? Right? Now this
can function for all of you. It is a
very simple understanding. We have
discussed it many times and some of you
may be familiar with it. But perhaps
some of you have not allowed it to sink
in as you
say. The idea is as
follows. Are you familiar with the idea
we have discussed that all circumstances
are fundamentally neutral?
Yes. No. Maybe. Yes. Yes. It's the
belief that creates the positive or the
negative. Is that right? Yes. Okay. Then
why if you are familiar with the idea
that all circumstances are fundamentally
neutral until you assign a meaning to it
which then creates a negative or a
positive effect, why do you say that the
feelings you are having are
terrible? Why are you automatically
assigning an inherent negative meaning
to them?
because of probably because of the
physical discomfort that manifests
through my body at at the particular
time. We understand that for you that
can be a very strong motivation or
incentive to continue to label it as a
negative idea. But what if you didn't
just in other words just allow it to be
just totally neutral and and then just
not label it at all. You see, here's the
paradox of the situation. We are not
telling you to tolerate your pain. No,
no, no. Because none of you need pain.
No, no, no. The idea, however,
paradoxically, is that very often as
soon as you allow yourself to
acknowledge that if there is pain that
you are choosing to create it, that it
is under your control because it is your
choice to experience the reality in a
painful way. It will bring it back under
your control. And as soon as it is, you
can then transform it in any way, shape,
or form you want to. But you see the
thing of it is is that because you are
many of you in the habit of denying that
you own the pain in your life, you will
not allow yourself to change it because
you cannot change what you do not
own. So first you must own it. You must
acknowledge all right. I am creating the
pain. Therefore I must have a good
reason for it. I must have a positive
reason for it. How does it serve me to
have created a negative experience? What
positive idea can I learn from it? The
sooner you are willing to understand
that it is there for a positive reason
and not a negative one, you will cease
to reinforce the negative aspect, you
will instantaneously begin to transform
it into a positive energy and the pain
will vanish.
All pain, all pain, mental pain,
spiritual pain, emotional pain, physical
pain, all pain is
resistance to the energy of flow of
light. All pain is the cutting off of a portion
All pain is the cutting off of a portion
of yourself from the
totality that can supply you with the
support, the flow that allows you to
function ecstatically,
naturally. Remember that this whole idea
of the transformation taking place upon
your planet now is not to learn how to
act normally, but how to act
naturally. You have acted normal for
quite a long time. all of
you. Now you are learning to act
naturally and so you will simply find
that much of the pain that you have
created in your lives comes from your
pressuring yourself to try and be normal
rather than natural by going with your
flow on all levels by trusting it on all
levels. The signature vibration that you
are is the fundamental being you have
been created to be. flow with it. Are
you doing what excites you the most in
life? Yes. I I believe in my work world.
Are you speaking of that? All of it.
Everything. Is there any area you are holding
Is there any area you are holding
yourself back? Well, probably in
relationship and then I'm I'm copying
out again because of physical, you know,
occasion the physical discomfort. I I
feel if I can
sometimes physical pain can be an excuse
to not have to do something that you may
be afraid to do. Mhm. Is that the case
with you? What do you imagine would
happen if you didn't have the pain?
Would there be something that you would
be doing that perhaps you are afraid of
doing that the pain doesn't allow you to
do? uh at this time I don't believe there is
uh at this time I don't believe there is
there may may be eventually I think I
have to take well you don't have to
create it and you don't have to wait for
it
I think if I if I do assimilate what
you're saying and and uh not label the
discomfort as being negative or positive
but just flowing with it and just own
like you say owning it well remember
that many of you do have what you call
habitual rituals and it may be your
habit to use energy to create pain. But
the idea is that as soon as you begin to
redefine it, it will not come with the
same effect, with the same meaning. You
will be able to redefine it and define
it into another experience all together.
But you must begin to redefine it now if
you wish it to change. Yes. And then if
the vi if I can create a better
atmosphere for myself, so to speak, that
I can become on a higher vibrational
plane because that's what I miss. I miss
that experience, the oneness. But you
don't have to make a chore out of it.
Mhm. Understand all of you that in all
reality now you can allow this to take
as long or as short as you wish, but the
process that you create is up to you.
Your imagination is real. It is not unreal.
imagination is real. It is not unreal.
It is representative of reality. It may
be on a different dimensional plane, a
different vibratory level, but there is
absolutely nothing you can imagine that
is not real. You are incapable of
imagining non-existence. Anything you imagine is
non-existence. Anything you imagine is
somewhere, somehow, somewhere
real. Some of it may not have immediate
application into your particular
physiological dimension, but that
doesn't mean it is not real. And
generally speaking, generally speaking,
especially when it comes spontaneously,
the ideas that come into your
imagination do apply to your physical
dimension. Otherwise, it is unlikely
they would have popped up first. So the
idea first of all and one thing that
might assist you maybe and any of you
that wish to apply this in your own way
is that if you have an idea of who you
are now and you have an idea of how you
would like to
be then recognize that your picture of
who you would like to
be is being created in the present.
It is within your imagination vibration
now. And all you have to do is allow
yourself to be that person now rather
than assuming that it takes time in
order to become that
person. The second you conceive of it,
you are the vibration. But the habit of
your society is to say, "All right, now
I have the idea of who I'd like to be.
What do I have to do in order to become
that idea somewhere down the
road most recently is that I have the
dreams that I remember which are the
ones that occur most recently to my
waking up prior to my waking up are ones
that are very much like my waking
reality very Um, I have a sense that
there are dreams that are in a deeper
sleep that I don't remember in which I'm
learning. Yes, in a sense, but not so
much as a difference as there used to
be. The idea that you are or seemingly
are remembering things that seem so very
common to you is that what was once
uncommon is becoming more familiar.
Understand? You are simply getting used
to the idea of different dimensions of
experience and so the dreams you
remember have a degree of commonality to
them. It is not that they are truly
common in that sense or mundane as you
call it but simply that you are getting
used to uncommon changes in your
reality. And so your analytical mind
upon awakening is interpreting those
experiences as very common experiences.
Remember that when you wake up, you're
not always literally remembering the
experience, but you are aware of the
symbology that has been applied to the
experience by your outer physical ego
structure to make sense out of it in
physical terms. So, it will use common
building blocks, common representational
symbol to show you that what was here to
very unusual is becoming quite natural
to you in a sense. Yes, there are still
other levels of information that are
coming to you that you are not in that
sense consciously aware of. But you do
not always need to be because as we have
discussed many times, many of you don't
need to be consciously aware of what
that information is so that you will
allow yourselves to live your physical
life spontaneously without having the
structure laid out before you that would
make you hesitate to act in any
direction for fear of getting it wrong.
I understand what you're saying.
Continue. You knew that was coming.
You knew that was coming.
Um I have been I was advised by an
entity other than yourself that if I
wanted to create the dreams this dream
symbology that I preferred yes uh what I
could do would be to 20 times in a long
written handwriting
um to say for example I am for an
example of a dream that I would wish I
am flying to a golden temple where I
meet my guides
and did that 20 times. You know why that
was recommended for you? No, because you
place a lot of belief in the written
word because you have in that sense been
a writer many
times and therefore since it has been
your stock and trade so to speak, it was
perceived that writing it down would
make it more believable for you as a
tool. I did it three nights and then I
stopped. It didn't work. Then I
remembered. Yes. Um, if you were simply
trying a little too hard, I tend to do
that. How do you not try too hard? Stop
trying to do it. Why is it so important?
Cuz I really love flying dreams. All
right, but let me put it this way. Why
is it so much more important than
anything else? It isn't. It's just fun.
You say, "Do what excites you the most."
And that is when I wake up from dreams
that I remember like that. It excites
me. All right. But remember also that
when we say do what excites you the
most, very often we are also referring
to things that individuals in your
society are negligent to do in physical
reality. You understand? Because that is
usually where most of you stop short of
the whole idea. You keep yourselves in
the idea of the spiritual non-physical
realms because that is exciting to you.
But you do not think that the idea of
action in the physical world is just as
exciting. And so many times you will actually stop
And so many times you will actually stop
yourself from remembering what is going
on in the non-physical realm because you
start making the non-physical that much
more important than the physical. I
don't feel it's more important. I just
love both. I'm really I'm very excited
by my awakening. This idea in general.
We have not gotten to the specifics
about you yet. Okay.
Now imagine the idea right now. Right
now. Right now of that golden temple.
All right.
Yes. What does it look like? Define,
describe. It has um steps up to it. Um and then um
It has um steps up to it. Um and then um
a
plaza area. What color? What color?
Golden. All of it. Uh some of it is
stone. What color? What color? Um gray
and pink. Granite like stone. Walk up to
it in your imagination and feel it. What
does it feel like? Is it hard? Is it
cool? Is it smooth? Is it rough? It's
smooth and cool. All right. Anything
else attract your attention? There's
um there are pillars in the front of the
the entrance way. And the entrance way
is oversized. What are they made of?
Gold. Go up to them, touch them, smell
them, taste them.
Okay. Describe. Define
metallic and cool.
All right. Smooth. Stop there for an
hour. Okay. Are you getting the picture?
Okay. Are you getting the picture?
The idea is to allow yourself to utilize
first of all and this is one of the
reasons that the writing was recommended
to utilize all the ways all the senses
all the belief systems that you have
that you would use in physical reality
to define and describe the non-physical
reality you wish to retain memory of as
well. Use all your senses.
Many individuals do not allow themselves
to retain the idea of the non-physical
reality because they become ethereal
about how they are to be experiencing
that idea. Let yourself understand that
if you wish to retain what seems to be a
solid recollection, then do an exercise where
recollection, then do an exercise where
you imagine it to begin with, lay out
the steps that you will take and go
through it using every sense you have.
Make it real to you on all levels. On
the levels you are most used to having
reality upon the physical level. Make it
solid. Make it real until you can feel
it. Until you can hear it. Until you can
hear the distortion of the metal or the
stone. Until you can feel the coolness
or the heat. Until you can feel the
solidity, the smoothness, the roughness.
Until you know it. Until you absolutely
know it. Just the same way you know what
it would feel like to place your hand
upon the wall of the building you are
in. Make it real for you. And as soon as
you become completely absorbed in its
reality, you will start to blend the
physical and the non-physical reality in
a very real way. But you are simply
going about it very ethereally.
Understand?
Yes. Are you sure?
Well, it's like this. Yes. How is it?
When my eyes are opened, it seems I'm
able to go through that process that you
said easier than when my eyes are
closed. Then that's your clue, is it
not? I guess so. Let yourself begin in
whatever way is easiest for you and let
the natural inclinations take over when
they need to. Eventually, your eyes may
close, but do not force yourself into a
pattern that is not the most workable
pattern for you. Do not assume that
whatever is the most workable pattern is
not workable. Oh, I can't do that with
my eyes open. Everyone knows my eyes
should be closed. Why? Don't make
assumptions. Do it in whatever way is
easiest for you and let the natural path
follow. Understand? Yes. So the idea of
writing it out also was an indication
that you rely on your visual senses and
you would start to daydream with your
eyes open in writing it out repeating it
over and over again. It is simply that
you place the expectation in another
area rather than in the present. You
said, "All right, I'll write it out and
I have better experience this later in
my
brain." Instead of understanding that by
writing it out, the whole purpose you
were given that exercise was to allow
you to start experiencing it while you
were writing it out. Uhhuh. Yeah.
Understand? Yeah, that I understand.
Thank you. Does that serve you? It does.
Then let me just clarify one point then.
All right. Then is it so that the dreams
in which um I would be forgetting some
information perhaps or not bringing it
back um those dreams that information is
not needed to be conscious and it
sometimes sometimes not and it will come
forth into my consciousness when it's
appropriate. The more you relax into
that understanding the quicker you allow
anything that is supposed to be there to
be there. Relax. Okay. Relax. Thank you.
Don't try so hard. That's what pushes it
away. Be in the moment. In the moment. In the
Be in the moment. In the moment. In the
moment. When? Now. When? Now.
Thank you. Thank you.
Sherry. Hello, Bashar. Hello. I had a dream that
Hello, Bashar. Hello. I had a dream that
I was wondering um you could tell me
what it meant. Maybe.
Um I was in first grade when I had this
dream. And it took place when I was in
first grade, too. And I was with my
first grade class and and um we were at
the zoo for a field trip and we were at
looking at the seals and my friend her
name was Amanda and she said there was
this door and there was this guard and
he was asleep and she said um I wonder
what's in there and I said well I don't
know and she said why don't we go in and
said okay and so we went in and there
was it's like a big tall and there was a
refrigerator and and we were real hungry
so we started eating. Nice. And then
this really big fat guy with this crown
on he he comes by and he chains us to
the walls by our hands and legs. Nice.
And then the guard that was sleeping
woke up and unchained us. And he took us
into this room where there was a whole
bunch of people sitting down. And they
and as we were walking by, they all gave
us little presents. And then we opened
up the door and our first grade class
was there and it seemed like he knew the
class was coming so that we could just
fit right in when we walked out. As this
guard represents symbolically to you
what is typically called a spirit guide
and simply took the form that fit in to
your dream experience to allow you to
understand that the old ways the ways
that chained you to the wall were
already behind you that you had now
entered a new reality with grade one.
You have begun life in a new world, a
new earth, far different from any of the
old earths you have ever lived in
before, of any of the other lives you
have had. You are now far freer to go
where you need to go because you know
you are doing it with
integrity. The idea of chaining you to
the wall is simply the old idea that you
might have been
stealing, not using your integrity in
past lives, but that dream was an
indication that you had already worked
that out. that in the first year of your
physical life, the idea, the first grade
as you call it, upon that point, upon
what you call the age of reason,
approximately in your terms, the idea of
5, 6, 7 years of
age, then you would understand you had
already in that time worked out all of
your past associations to negativity,
all of your past associations to
limitation, and your spirit guide
unlocked you to show you that you are
free now to go where you wish and that
you do in fact fit in. And that as you
accelerate in this physical life that
you are now living, you will learn
possibly to be of service to other
individuals by letting them know they
are also very free. And that the old
limitations and the old expectations do
not have to chain them to the walls of
the reality they have created. That they
are free. That they always have
assistance. They always have guides.
They always have love. And they always
understand that they are as innocent as
you say a child in your society is that
simply goes and knows that everything is
for everyone and that there is abundance
represented by the food for all and that
you are going to partake of great
abundance in this life because you have
already worked out the ideas of your
past limitations. Are you understanding
what we are saying? Yes. Does that serve
you? Uh-huh. Except um the only thing is
that I had this dream two or three times
and I was wondering why that was because
you have more than one encounter with
your spirit guide and you simply use the
same dream symbology to allow yourself
to represent who that is to you. Now
that you are aware that it is the same
being that you are dealing with as a
spirit guide that is assisting you, you
don't have to have the same dream in
which you interact with them. You can
change the dream. Allow yourself to
remember perhaps next time while you are
dreaming that you are in fact dreaming.
And as soon as you remember that you're
dreaming while you're dreaming, you can
change the whole aspect of the idea of
the interaction and you can see the
spirit guide more for what it is.
You follow me? Yes. Thank you, Bashar.
Thank you very
much. Shing.
Greetings, Bashar. And to you. Good day.
Um would you please comment on this
coming period called the harmonic
convergence? As harmonic convergence
simply is the recognition of the overlap
of the old cycle of negative vibration
and the new cycle of positive vibration.
The overlap of old ways and new ways. It
is let us say the quote unquote official
center point of the transformational age
which has been going on on your planet
for approximately 40 of your years give
or take. and will continue for
approximately another 40 of your years
give or take day. And that this
represents the actual midpoint, the
fulcrum, the doorway that is the center
of the overlap of the old reality and
the new. It is the limbo point, the
balance point. It is the analogy of the
dive, the jump where you jump up and
then that moment of hanging in
suspension before you slide down the
other side. That is what it represents.
the ability of all vibrations of all
probable realities that allows you to be in a
realities that allows you to be in a
neutral state, a limbo state, a
disconnected state to pick and choose
what reality you
prefer. So that when you decide and then
lock yourself into that frequency from
that point forward, you will begin to
accelerate around you that experiential
reality. It is a gateway. It is a tunnel
from one reality from one earth to
another earth in a sense to whatever
earth you prefer to be a part of. It is
a limbo state. That is why many of you
are beginning to experience the idea of
disorientation of limbo in your lives of
disillusionment.
It is because you are placing yourself
in neutral, unlocking yourself from one
reality, the reality you have lived for
thousands of years, and allowing
yourself the opportunity to assess what
reality you now prefer. A convergence of
harmonics because all realities are the
product of harmonic vibrations. That is
what it is. It is a library of all
probable realities for you to decide
which you prefer. You follow me? Yes.
Does that assist you? Yes. Then enjoy in
whatever way excites you the most. And
remember that many of you are doing
similar things at the same time across
your entire planet. And that will add
momentum to the ability of the majority
of your planet to create the reality you
desire upon your planet of peace and
harmony. Thank you for your willingness
to participate and create that
particular symbolic recognition of the
transformation that you are all going
through. Does that serve you? Yes. Thank
you. I have another question. All right.
Um, could you comment on the role of
crystals for some people at this time in
uh facilitating their own
transformations as well as the
transformation of the earth? Yes. Well,
the earth is a crystal like any planet.
You understand? Yes. The idea simply is
that crystals in a sense are tools. All
tools are valid. They do represent a
form of electromagnetic power or
vibratory energy. But they are actually
mostly triggers for you for the
representation of all that is an
infinite creation that you are. They are
tools that are now more symbolic of the
integration you are creating upon your
planet because they have less different
materials few moving parts. In that
sense you are integrating yourself into
one simple understanding. Crystals as a
solid material form are not that far
removed from the natural energy state
out of which all matter is created. So
they are the symbolic representation of
how your consciousness is
crystallizing. So that there is more
communication between you. So that you
are getting in touch with all the
different layers and levels of
dimensionality by literally creating
patterns of crystallin consciousness. By
arranging the energy that you are in
crystallin matrices to be what you call
superconducting. It is no accident that
your science is now breaking through
what you call superconductive materials.
It is because your consciousness is
becoming superconductive. Understand? Yes. The
superconductive. Understand? Yes. The
crystals represent this superc
conductivity. Crystal and alignment
allows energy to flow through it.
Absolutely. Without resistance. Does
that tell you something? Yes. Does that
serve you? Thank you very much. Thank
you very
much. Shimmy.
Hello Bashar. Thank you. Goodbye. I am
wondering if there is any truth to the
idea that the government created the
disease AIDS.
No, not directly in that sense. All of
you have co-created it. Basically, it is
representative of the following idea.
Now, there are many specific ideas
within this, but we will give you the
general foundation as we perceive it in
your energy. Your society has for so
long been refusing to blend and balance
the masculine and feminine energies
within each and every one of
you. You have been refusing to marry
that energy within each and every one of
you. That you have created factions in
your society that then are forced to
represent the idea that each and every
individual creates and has the ability
to create either energy within any
individual. Lack of willingness,
Lack of willingness,
fear to absorb, to blend and
harmonize the assertive and receptive
energies within each and every male and
female has created most of the different
forms of disease upon your planet. What
you call AIDS is simply the one that is
most symbolically representative of your
fear of self-intimacy.
For now it has forced you to begin to
drop all your barriers to deal with the
portions of your society and your
consciousness that you have as a
mainstream society refuse to deal with
to integrate those ideas and energies
within yourself. And when you center
yourself in that way by blending the
masculine and feminine energies within
each and every one of you then there
will be in that centered place no
disease whatsoever. It is simply one
more step in the acceleration of disease
out of the refusal to blend and balance
yourselves in the polarities that you
have expressed upon your society for
thousands of years. It is your breaking
point. It is your
threshold now. From time to time, the
idea of what you call your government
interaction has played some part in the
generation of some ideas of what you
would call making it easier to propagate
some of the idea of the disease upon
your planet or initiating some of the
conditions that allow disease to spread.
But remember remember you all of you are
your governments. No separation.
What you call your governments are only
what you have created and support them
to be. When you blend also the idea of
your public and your government and
allow there to be a flow of
communication between you because you
are your government. Then there will be
no mystery. There will be no secrets.
There will be no coercion. There will be
no covert activity. There will be
blending, service, sharing, allowance,
willingness, love, trust, light, no
disease, no fear. Remember that you have
in a sense perpetuated what you call
your governments out of fear. Protect
me. Protect me. You say, protect me from
what I
fear. Any consciousness that you create
out of
fear must continue to generate fear in
order to stay
alive. It doesn't want to die anymore
than any other
creation. The idea is to take back
responsibility for the creations in your
lives to own it and then change it. And
in that sense then to allow your
government to serve you not to rule you.
So they no longer have to protect you
from what you fear. Understand? Yes.
Does that serve you? Yes. Thank you,
Bashar. Thank you very much, Shannon.
Good evening, Bashar. And to you, good
day. Um, I'm still not clear uh about
pain. Uh, all right. I have a problem
with uh chronic pain in my low back, and
I'm wondering uh what it is that I can
do to help relieve that. Have you
already in your
terminology, let us say, acquire the
assistance of your medical practitioner?
Yes. What have they told you? Nothing.
They can't tell you nothing at all.
Well, nothing that seems to help. All
right. Do they attribute a particular
reason to it?
Uh, there's a problem with some
scoliosis in the upper back, although
the pain is in the lower back.
For how long have you had this
manifestation? Uh about u 5 years chronically. A little
Uh about u 5 years chronically. A little
bit longer than that
intermittently. I do not wish this to
seem as what you would call a
panacea but to initiate a foundation
first of all so that we may explore in
more detail. Are you doing what excites
you the most in
life? Yes. No. Maybe. Yes. What is it?
Uh, are you sure you're doing it?
I'm doing some of it. All right. Some of
it. What would be all of it?
To be doing what I'm doing, but doing it
better. Better? You mean more expanded?
More expanded. In what way?
uh to be uh to be the best healer that I
could be. The best healer? Yeah. Have
you applied any of these principles to
yourself? Yes.
Yes.
And and doesn't seem to be helping. May
I ask you a question? Yes. Do you
believe that the individuals that come
to you for
healing deserve to be healed?
Yes. Are you sure? Yes. Do you believe
you deserve to be healed? Yes. Are you
sure? I hadn't thought about it before now.
I hadn't thought about it before now.
All right. Think about it. Yes, I do
believe that. All right. Why?
Because I don't think anyone needs to
live with pain. No. No one needs to live
with pain. But do they believe they can live
pain. But do they believe they can live
without it?
May I ask you another question? Yes.
Just playing around here for a moment.
Okay. Do you believe that you are taken
Do you believe that you are taken
seriously as a healer? Yes.
By the individuals that you assist in
healing? Yes. Do you understand what
healing is?
Can you define it? When another
individual is healed quote unquote by
you, can you define the mechanism that
is happening?
Well, I don't think they're being healed
by me. Correct. Uh to me, uh uh being
healed means becoming integrated with
body, mind, and spirit. And and
resonating with the pulsation of
creation in the universe. And as a
healer, then what are you doing for
them? Helping them to resonate. All
right. Right. So you are saying you are
creating a conductive or conducive
atmosphere, a frequency that they can
align with that will allow them to see
how they can heal themselves. Yes. Yes.
All right. How do you go about healing
right. How do you go about healing
them? What do you use? What techniques?
What methodologies? Uh I use acupuncture
and uh I use counseling, some diet and
nutrition. All right. Now may I ask you
another question? Thank you. I will.
Do
you do you have in your imagination
other methodologies that have occurred
to you that perhaps you are not willing
to try? Yes. For one reason or another?
Yes. What are those methodologies and
why are you not willing to try them?
Uh a little scared of the unknown
methodologies. Scared of the unknown.
Methodologies like homeopathy crystals.
Yes.
um more more expansion of visualization
techniques. All right. These things have
come to you in your imagination as ways
that you could possibly expand the idea
of your healing. Yes. And yet you have
refused to incorporate them. I haven't
refused. I I've I've procrastinated.
What's the difference?
Not sure. There is
none. Okay. It is simply a lack of
willingness to trust what your
imagination is giving you.
Do you believe you are a healer? Yes.
Why don't you believe your imagination?
Then do you not think that your
imagination is the imagination of a
healer? Yes. Then why not trust the
images that it gives you as what is
representative of what you can actually
best be of service in?
Okay. Okay. Well, all right. It is a
suggestion. You can do it. You can begin
to trust that whatever you get from your
imagination is what needs to be provided
to you to allow you to be the best
healer you can be.
You begin to trust your imagination
because you understand that your
imagination is the key to any
methodology that will work best for you
in doing the thing that excites you the
most. That's what your imagination is
for. It's key to your vibration. When
you say, "Well, let's see. I'm a
healer." Yes, that's what excites me.
How can I heal best? Your imagination
will say, "Pop pop here. Picture this.
Picture this. Picture this." But if you
say, "I don't know. I don't know. I
don't know. Well, maybe maybe
maybe then you are resisting your own
flow. When you resist your own flow,
you're going to block up in your body
and you're going to create the type of
pains you're
feeling because all pain is
resistance. Resistance to your natural
self. lack of willingness to trust the
information you are getting from your
higher self, from your imagination as to
who and what you are and how you can
best be of service. When you let
imagination in that sense create the
image that represents who you are, trust
it, act upon it and let that energy flow
through you. Then it will not block up
in you and will not create the pain.
Many healers who do not use the energy
to allow it to flow will feel the pain
generally in their lower back because
that is the seat quote unquote of the
idea of what you call the condalini
energy. That which from all energy in
your body deres its source and origin
the spinal cord the connection between
your brain and all the neural system of
your body and it will tend to block up
in the
base. Understand? Yeah. Has this served
you so far? Yeah. I'd like to ask a
question about channeling. All right. I
I use channeling to get
uh answers to questions in a yes and no
form using muscle testing in my fingers.
All right. Any tool is valid. And and
however, and I've been doing it for
about a year, a little bit longer. And
uh but I've been finding more in the
last 6 months that that I don't trust it
anymore. that the answers that I get
don't seem to go along with with uh my
my observations. Then what methodology
does your imagination tell you would
work best for you? Now
and while you are pondering that, do you
have a definition of what channeling is?
Receiving information from a higher
source.
No, I give up. All right.
Fundamental definition of channeling
doing anything you love to
do in total
trust. Understand that is channeling. Okay?
Understand that is channeling. Okay?
So do what you love to do but do it in
total trust and trust what comes to you
and when things change in your
methodology trust the change. The change
is there for a reason as a part of the
path you chose to be, not as an
interruption in it. Understand? Yes.
Then when you flow that trust, you will
then release that energy and begin in
that sense to lighten up and not be so
tense in that portion of your
back. In a sense, it is resistance.
Resistance is all it is fundamentally.
Do not resist who you are. Trust what
your imagination gives you. It is there
for a reason. I guarantee it. You will
always see that it works. It never
doesn't work. And there are no
exceptions. Not even you.
Understand? Yes, I do. Thank you. Does
this serve you? Yes, it does. One
moment.
Have you utilized just as an assistance,
just as a focus, the idea of what you
typically call a blueish violet fluorite
crystal? No, I haven't used any crystals. Play
No, I haven't used any crystals. Play
with that idea and see if it changes the
energy in your neural pathways. A bluish
violet crystal. Fluorite. Bluish violet
fluorite crystal. Fluoride crystal S.
Okay. Individuals will point you in the
direction. Use your instincts and pick
the one that feels most correct for you.
And this is to be used. Use your
imagination. Okay. Apply it to your body in whatever
Okay. Apply it to your body in whatever
way, shape, or form your imagination
tells you. In whatever way you picture.
All right. All right. Thank you. Thank
you very
much. Sh.
Good evening, Bashar. And to you, good
day. Good day. Thank you for co-creating
this evening with us and you as well.
Uh, I have a question about my mother.
She went into the hospital today. She's
having some kind of discomfort in her
chest area around her heart, and
nobody's really quite sure exactly what
it is, but she's not sure anyway. And I
was wondering if you could give me some
information about that and possibly some
information on how I might be of service
to her in that way. One moment. Have you
taken flowers? No, not yet. When will
you? Tomorrow.
Will you do a favor?
Yes. Remind that individual that they
are as the
flowers that their roots are
deep and they draw nourishment from the
earth. That the earth
sustains that creation
sustains and they do not have to
consider that they do not
belong. They do not have to think that
they are not one of the flowers of the
garden. They do not have to work so
hard trying to expend so much
energy to be where they naturally fit
in.
Anyway, what do you think? That's my
mother. I'll tell her. All right. She
does not have to believe it. But you can
send your unconditional love and that
will be of best service to an individual
who simply in that sense basically needs
to loosen up a bit. Needs to open the
pedals up to the sun to relax to soak up
life because because most important most
important reminder she deserves
it just because she is who she is. She
doesn't need an extra
reason. Understand? Yes. Thank you.
Also, perhaps a little laughter would
lighten things up. Okay.
And think orange for her. Orange and
suggest she think
orange the emotional vibration to
attract those who can be of best
assistance to her. for there are others
around her who can be of assistance also
in non-physical form in dream
reality to soften her up.
Okay. Thank you. Thank you. I have
another question. Thanks. I had a dream
a couple of weekends ago. I was up on
the mountaintop near Grass Valley. Hi.
And I had a bunch of dreams that night
that seem to relate to extraterrestrials
or UFOs. It is a highly magnetic vortex
as we have outlined before that is very
stalling connected to different
dimensional planes some of which connect
directly into those in which we exist.
Yes, it is like plugging yourself into a
live stream alive energy. Yes, I had as
I said multiple dreams. One of them in
particular was was actually a waking
dream. I was I had awakened between
dreams and I had this experience where I
closed my eyes for a second and I saw
while my eyes were closed my arm
reaching out and resting on the shoulder
of someone else. I couldn't see myself
or someone else only my arm and the
space that it was crossing and then a
moment later an arm came back and rested
itself on my shoulder. This is an astral
experience. Okay. Could you explain the
arm because it wasn't of this planet
that I could tell and I simply that it
was made out of what you call astral
material. could go as far as you wish,
stretch anywhere, anywhere.
It is your indication that in that
vortex and as is becoming common to your
entire planet. Now, physical reality and
dream reality are merging or blending
because physical reality is only a
dream. And as you allow the astral
reality to contain them both, your
physical reality will become as
malleable, as flexible. You are simply
encountering consciousness and
intelligence that was aware of you and
identifying with you, reassuring you,
letting you know you have literally
touched other dimensions. Do you
understand that is where the original
term touched comes from? I wasn't aware
that you are literally
touched by spirit now that you are
becoming more spirit in vibration. You
can feel it. Your senses now can feel it
as if it is more solid. You are becoming
more astral, more fourth density, more
light. And light will then feel solid to
you. Mhm. Understand? Yes. So you have
given yourself an opportunity to be
presented with a mirror reflection that
you are now touching into other
dimensions and therefore can be touched
by other dimensions.
Understand? Yes. One more question. I
had a meditation the other afternoon
where I uh during my lunch break and I
took my crystal and I laid it on my
heart and while I was meditating it was
actually your voice that I was hearing
or my interpretation of your voice. I
assumed it to be my own higher self or
something that way. Yes. Because our
vibrational frequency is always in a
sense being beamed to your planet and
when you think of us you will simply
acclimate yourself to that particular
frequency to reflect it back to yourself
if that is the symbol that you require.
Okay. But in that sense it is you and it
is us. get his boat. Okay. Um what what
you said or what the voice said at the
time was uh for whatever I was thinking
about was to look into the crystal skull
which I did. Yes. And it at least I felt
that I was sort of transmigrated into a
fourth density kind of awareness at that
point and stayed that way for the rest
of the day. That is what the crystal
skull is for. You know, all the ones
that exist. I was aware of that. And you
were in a sense a part of that
civilization too. The May civilization.
Oh, very interesting. And Atalantium.
Okay. From where some of the original
technology came from. The idea of the
crystal skull is a dimensional gate. It
has within the skull in what you would
call magnetic crystal and alignment the
patterns of recognition necessary to
open a dimensional gate to the dimension
in which that civilization transferred
themselves. But it is in a sense
encoded. And someone who looks into the
skull's eyes if they cannot face all the
ideas of the different levels of their
consciousness if they cannot come to
terms with that will not be able to
integrate and will not be able to open
the door. So that is the lock on the
door. Anyone who is not integrated
enough to follow will not be able to
follow. Okay. But you are remembering
who and what you are. And so you are
remembering those patterns, those codes,
those keys and that is the way by
looking into the eyes of the crystal
skull. You will evoke from yourself and
pull from yourself all the different
fragments you have created yourself all
the different compartments you have
created your consciousness to the if you
cannot stand the idea of them
integrating back together into one
homogeneous consciousness then you will
not be able to face that skull which
represents transformation which
represents death but not in a negative
sense. Understand? Yes. Does that serve you?
Understand? Yes. Does that serve you?
Yes. Thank you very much for Thank you.
Would you all enjoy a short break?
Then we will resume contact in
approximately 15 of your minutes. Okay.
How's it going?
[Applause]
Are we on a break? All
right, sir. Continue.
Good evening, Bashar. Unto you. Good
day. Uh, for the last h 100red years,
our society has been based on petroleum
products. I see. And it's it's a it
seems to me it's a a dirty form of
u
uh of
energy. And can we expect any clean
energy to come into
uh our society as a main form of as
understand that many times it has been
attempted in your society to utilize
what you call the electromagnetic field
of your planet. This is what we utilize
light itself gives you all the power
that you need if you will apply it in
that way. These many attempts to utilize
the electromagnetic spectrum in some of
the inventions that have been created
upon your society simply because of what
you have created your society to be has
as inventions been
suppressed. But you can use that
technology anytime you wish. And it is
our perception at this time that within
what you call the next 30 of your years,
you will begin to utilize that
particular type of technology almost
exclusively. Do you see the Persian Persian Gulf
Do you see the Persian Persian Gulf
crisis as a a beginning of the end of uh
our petroleum base?
There will be in our perception many
particular factors that will in your
terms come to a focus in approximately
what you call your year
1,997 within that entire area you call
your Middle East.
It will revolve around the idea also of
one factor of energy and also one factor
you would call
religion. But the idea in this sense is
that you are now as a whole society
bringing all these ideas bubbling up to
the surface so that you can display all
the opportunities out in the open
overtly rather than covertly so that you
can all decide as a society what
methodologies you prefer to utilize upon
your planet. It is one of the factors.
It is not necessarily the only one nor
even in your terms the strongest one
that will occur. But it is one of the
factors that will in your terms bring
all of the idea to a focus. You follow
me? Mhm. Does that assist you? Yes.
Thank you. Thank you. Shutting.
Hi Bashar. Hi. I'm so happy to meet you.
I wanted to ask you what my connection
with dolphins are. I I love dolphins.
I've always loved them. I dream about it
all the time. Recognize first of all
that in your terminology, if we may use
your word alien, since you are to us
alien, you as humans are not the only
alien species upon your planet. The
dolphins and whales, the citations are
the other alien race upon your world.
You have two, not one,
two. They are in your terms sensient
like yourselves, although they express
themselves of course very differently.
But they have been in telepathic
communication with many civilizations
for quite some time and recognize that
you, the humanike form upon your planet,
is now waking up and tapping into the
same communication. So they are willing
to involve themselves, to play with you
in your dreams, to assist you, to learn
how to love, how to share in loving
ways, to open you up into that
telepathic or what we may term
telempathic receptivity to other lines
of communication going on. They are very
strongly connected to the civilization
you call by the name star
Sirius. And in this way, you will find
that many individuals that find
themselves strongly attracted to dolphin
energy may have strong serious
connections in many different ways. Part
of their energy will be locked into or
focused into that particular dimension
or density of
consciousness. But dolphins in that
sense are the other alien species upon
your world. And now they invite you
openly to play with them in their own
environment so that you may learn to
telepathically share with each other.
They are in many of your dreams all the
time speaking with you in many different
ways. And one of the strongest things
aside from dream communication they are
doing upon your planet is giving you
assistance with the actual physiological
births of your children taking place
upon your planet now to alleviate the
idea of the pressure and the pain that
you think you have to go through. Child
birth in no way, shape, or form needs to
be painful. Calling upon the dolphin
energy can assist you. Also, allowing
the child to help with the birth can
assist you so you're not taking it all
upon your own shoulders, so to speak,
which is the only thing that creates the
pain, the responsibility that you place
upon yourselves in a negative fashion.
Dolphins will assist on all of these
levels and will be very conducive to
teaching you how to remember to play to
teaching you to remember how to be
children again. You follow me? Yes. So
you have that connection simply very
strongly. It is our suggestion that you
go and play. Thank you with them. Thank
you. Okay. Thanks. Sharing.
Hello Bashar. And to you. Good night.
I'd like to share a Can you all hear
this person? I'd like to share a vision
thing I had. All right. A vision thing.
Speak up. I We had a meditation on
Friday. Hi. And in the meditation, I had
a quick flash of seeing in the middle of
the ocean um a crystal um like circle
that was in the water and there was a
flag from each of the countries all
around it of everyone that is on the
world and there were dolphins um jumping
all around it. This is a symbolic
representation of your harmonic
convergence. The idea of a true unifying
of the idea of nations, of realities, of
all beings upon your planet, a
crystallization of your collective
consciousness as a world. It is your
recognition of the vibration and your
translation of that vibration into your
symbolic crystallin format. You follow
me? Yes. Does that assist you? Thank
you. Thank
you. Shutting. Remember, remember every
Shutting. Remember, remember every
individual makes a difference. And when
you put your energy in that direction,
you make it that much more possible for
the collectivity of your world to
accelerate in that positive direction.
Thank you. Yes. Good evening. I wondered
if you could um speak up. Speak up.
Speak up. Be bold. Describe your
relationship and understanding of those
beings that we call ascended masters.
Ascended masters. All right. Now, not
meaning to be flippant, the idea of an
ascended master is simply the same as
you. Someone, however, who has simply
woken up and recognized what they are
and acts like it. Important point, acts
like it, knows that they are a part of
infinite creation and acts like it in
the moment. You are all masters in that
sense. Ascension is simply an
acceleration of your energy into a
format that allows you to act like the
idea the reflection of creation that you
were created to be. You follow me? Some
of them can be of assistance to you in
many ways by functioning as mirrors as
reflections for what you yourself are.
Remember that a master is the first one
to let you know you are also a master.
So ascended masters are mirrors. mirrors
for each and every one of you to show
you that if you can see the attributes
in them that you prefer in yourself
because you can see it in them, it means
they already exist within you. All you
have to do is act like it and you will
be an ascended master in that sense
through whatever process is relevant to
you. Understand? I believe so. Am I
clear to understand then that those who
have interactions with so-called
ascended masters on the physical plane
are therefore vibrating at their
resonant frequencies basically or enough
of a third commonality to at least give
them the opportunity to recognize their
own mastery within so they can manifest
that if they wish to understand? Yes.
Does that assist you? Yes. May I ask
another question? You don't have to ask
if you're going to ask. Um, could you
clarify the belief that I've heard of a
astral belt around the planet Earth?
Ice, a psychic belt which
um much of our consciousness gets locked
into and that in clarifying and
vibrating at higher frequencies, we're
able to move beyond this. In a sense,
yes, it is an analogy, a convenient
label. Yes, it is experienced literally
that way as if there are levels and
layers, but it is still ideas within the
one homogeneous collective
consciousness. All of you are physically
and non-physically. But yes, you have
created layers within that idea. And
those layers simply represent different
levels of refinement, different levels
of acceleration, higher and higher, more
rarified, less physical frequencies. So
whatever level, whatever frequency you
are operating on in the physical will
usually determine what level you reach.
And if it is in your terms insufficient
to go farther or higher, then you will
not have quote unquote, as you say,
achieved escape velocity. And so you
will fall back down in a reincarnational
format over and over and over and over
and over again. The idea however is when
you begin to realize that you have
created these levels then when you are
in that level non-physically you can be
aware of that aware that it is your
creation that it occurs in levels and
that awareness in and of itself can
accelerate your vibration above and
beyond up to the higher levels and
remove you from what you call the karmic
cycle. You follow me? Yes. Awareness in
and of itself of the karmic cycle of the
belief systems that perpetuate the
karmic cycle. Awareness is enough to
break you from that cycle because all
karma is self-imposed. Karma is simply a
momentum that once generated always
seeks its own level. So whatever
vibration you leave the physical level
with will determine how much momentum
you have to go to whatever level you can
go to and if it is insufficient to take
you beyond a certain point it will float
you back down again. You follow me? Yes.
It is again simple physics that is all.
Am I understand to understand that this
belt will be that the light intensity of
those beings like yourself that are
assisting our planet and those beings on
our planet who are raising their
frequency will help to eliminate this
spell within the next 20 years. It will
help to homogenize it. Yes, in that
sense you may perceive it as an
elimination but it has been a
homogenization. the removal of the idea that there are
the removal of the idea that there are
levels within it so that all the
realities become one reality and then
there is nothing to keep you anywhere
you do not want to be. Understand? Yes.
Does that assist you? Yes. But remember
that the strongest impact will come from
you because it is your world.
I understand. Thank you. Thank you.
Sharing.
Hello Vishar. And to you good day. I
wanted to ask you about uh telepathy.
Teleathy. Yes. Telepathy. Does it
emanate from the heart? Very good. That
is why we call it telempathy.
Understand? Telepathy in that sense does
utilize the electromagnetic
mentality. But it is emotionally
activated. It is identification. In a
very real sense, telepathy is being in
love. Do you not recognize that the
Do you not recognize that the
individuals who more often than not on
your planet know each other's thoughts
are individuals who you say are in love
with each other? Well, there is a reason
for that. Telepathy is absolute
identification with another being. If
you are identifying with another being
very strongly, then you begin to operate
on the same wavelength.
You begin to interpret creation in the
same way, in the same thought patterns.
You're on the same frequency. So you
have the same types of thoughts
synchronistically at the same time.
Telepathy is not literally mechanically
speaking reading each other's mind. It
is creating the same thought patterns in
your mind that someone else is creating
because you identify with them so
strongly. That's telepathy. Understand?
Yes. And that is why when you allow
yourselves to be in love with each
other, your world like ours will be
completely teleathic. But first, you must be in
teleathic. But first, you must be in
love. You must identify, you must
cherish and validate the differences
among you. By validating and equalizing
those differences will you then create
the unity that you seek upon your
planet. Understand? Yes. That is
telepathy. Does that assist you? Yes.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
You see to add what you call a
footnote. That is why many of your
scientists have not been able to measure
it in the terms they are used to
measuring physical reality because it is
emotionally activated. and much of what
you call your science will not allow
emotion to figure into the equations or
consciousness to figure into the
equations. But you see the idea is that
all psychic functioning and all
telepathy does follow its own rules and
they can be measured but you must use a
different measuring tool. You cannot use
a measuring tool that belongs in another
system to measure the idea of telepathy.
You must use the measuring tools that
belong within that system. The idea
first of all is that all telepathy, all
psychic functioning will always take the
path of least resistance like
electricity. It is very similar in that
sense always take the path of least
resistance. And many times when an
individual already knows what needs to
be known, then another individual
doesn't need to know that. And that will
shortcircuit the ability of another
individual to be able to telepathically
receive the information because within a
particular framework the information is
already known path of least resistance.
Second, it requires a great need or
desire to have the information or to
connect into an individual and generally
it is
spontaneous not planned out not
analyzed. For if it is an emotionally
activated idea, planning it out and
putting it in a rigid framework that
many of you call scientific will
actually kill the ability right then and
there. It will be analogous to the
following idea. Individuals who pull people into
idea. Individuals who pull people into
what you call your laboratory
environments and wire them up to many
machines and say all right now on the
count of three be psychic and if you are
not psychic on the count of three then
that will prove that psychic functioning
does not exist. That is analogous to
pulling an individual into a very cold
and what you might call sterile
environment surrounded by individuals
they do not know, are not comfortable
with, are not familiar with, wiring them
up to machines and in that sense
expecting them on the count of three to
fall in love with you. It just simply
usually on your world will not happen.
And the similar analogy is made by the
scientist is that if the individual
cannot fall in love by the count of
three then love doesn't exist. But the
idea is to understand that it does have
its own rules. It does have a measurable
quality and it can be repeatable but
only in the laboratory for which it was
designed. Spontaneous life
itself and or a much much
much stronger confidence level on the
part of the individual doing it. It
requires an absolute trust or
spontaneity. Either will do.
Thank you.
Shing.
Hello Bashar. I'm to you. Good day. Um,
you talk about the third dimension.
Third density, fourth density. Yes. How
many densities are there? Infinite in
all senses. But the idea of within what
you call your particular universal
reality, there are approximately seven
levels. And then there is another octave
and another reality and another octave
and another reality and so on and so on
and so on forever. But within the
universal reality you call your own,
there are approximately seven
levels. Understand? Yes. When we
supposedly were in Atlantis, what level
was that? You are operating in a sense
in fourth density. Fourth density is the
last level in which you can experience
physical and non-physical reality. Above
that there is only in your terms
non-physical reality. So we slip that to
the third level in a sense by playing
the forgetting game. Yes.
Are there planets that have a one or two
dimensional? Yes.
So there we are more knowledgeable or
what? You are simply different. You are
expanded in a different way. To utilize
a phrase that has been used on your
planet, you are in that sense nowhere
near the bottom of your totem pole if
that is what you
mean. You are actually quite close to
spontaneous transformation into light.
That is why there is so much
acceleration even on the negative side
on your planet now. Because
transformation is not the product of
mediocrity. And the stronger you have,
focus yourself in one direction. When
you decide to change as you are doing
now, you will change that much more
quickly because you have that much more
energy as your disposal. And when you
change, you will flip over very fast.
You follow me? Yes. Does that serve you?
I have just one more question. All
right. Uh I read an article that there
were other entities from other planets
that were afraid of us. Is that true?
Not in the sense you understand it. Let
us simply say that there are many
civilizations that choose to be cautious
of
you because you are quote unquote so
random and in a sense in your terms
liable to well not meaning to be
derogatory fly off the handle at a
moment's
notice because you are not yet as a
society fully in touch with all the
different attributes of your
consciousness. The idea simply is a
caution because in doing yourselves
harm, it is possible for another entity
that is in proximity to you to be
involved in that same idea if they are
not certain about where your vibratory
awareness lay. You follow me? Why do we
think there's going to be like something
like Star Wars? In actual fact, the idea
that you have symbolized in that
particular play is something that has to
do with your past more than your future.
It is a recognition of many of the
connections and civilizations and areas
of negative consciousness in your
history that you've already passed
through. You are simply applying it to
what you would call a futuristic format.
But recognize as we perceive in the
consciousness of the channel that
instinctively instinctively the
originator and creator of that
particular play understood that it was a
representation of your past and not your
future. Does it not begin a long long
time ago?
You follow me? is it is a representation
of the old cycle of negativity and it is
a connection to many other star systems
through which you have all come. None of
you are original to your planet. None of
you and many of you have connections in
old planetary systems that were very
heavily steeped in negativity and it is
from some of that that you have still
been playing out the negativity upon
your planet.
Understand? Thank you. Thank you very
much.
Hello Bashar. Hello. Uh, what you just
said to the last person that asked a
question kind of flows into mind. All
right. All the time I was growing up, I
always felt like I wasn't from here. And
I had dreams about um flying saucers and
uh being connected in that way. And as I
was as I became a teenager, I would be
awakened in the middle of the night and
be drawn to the window and see things
out my window at 3 or 4:00. what you
call your adolescent years. All of you
are high psychic connection ties.
My question is what is my connection and
also I sense my son's connection to uh
extraterrestrial life or UFOs. I cannot
be specific for you at this time but the
idea is that again all of you are
connected in various ways. All of you
are having conversations and making
agreements in various levels. And the
idea is that you are playing out your
agreements in your physical life along
the paths you need to. You are all
connected in that way. Some of you
simply have more conscious recognition
of it than others. That is all. Oh,
okay. But the idea is to be be be who
you believe you are representationally
speaking relative to that connection
upon your planet now. And you will
create the vibration on your earth that
will make it conducive for us to be able
to interact with you as equals upon your
planet. You follow me? Yes. Yes. One
moment. Is there a particular area you have been
Is there a particular area you have been
attracted to that you wish to go to upon
your planet? Uh yes actually two. One
where where one is Tahiti and the other
is in uh Costa Rica I believe.
Are you going to travel there? I hadn't
planned on it. Do you want to? It's been
a fantasy or a daydream of mine for a
long time. Does it excite you? Yes, it
does. in kind of a scary way. I don't
know what I don't know what lies in
store for me there. All right, then.
That is one of the reasons why we are
not allowed to be specific at this time
of what the connection is because you
are still afraid of it. Okay.
Doorways are closed to us when it will
interfere with your process. We place
these inhibitions upon ourselves
willingly so that we will not, as you
say, spill the beans.
Okay. Okay. I I get the message. Okay.
The idea is to move in the directions
that you feel most magnetically
attracted to move
within. There is, if I may be of
assistance on this level, nothing you
could ever discover about yourself that
cannot be applied in a positive way to
you. Nothing. If you are willing to trust
Nothing. If you are willing to trust
that, you will move a little bit faster.
Understand? And then you can attract the
circumstances and situations in your
life that will automatically allow you
to flow wherever you need to
flow. There are at least three other
places upon your planet where you may
find some associations that will benefit
you. One of them may be in what you
would call your South England area. One of
call your South England area. One of
them may be in what you would call your
American Southwest.
One of them may be what you would
call in our perception this is a
fluctuation of energy but the general
area you would call the orient. Mhm.
There are many aspects, many connections
and many lives that you have connections
to there and you have not yet decided
which one of them, which connection,
which symbol will serve you best. It may
be in your terms
China. It may be somewhere farther
south. Mhm.
And potentially for you potentially
though this may not yet be formulized or
solidified there may be some very strong
attraction to what you would call New
Zealand. You will see in time but let
yourself flow. Do not fear yourself.
That is all you're discovering is
yourself anyway. Understand? I
understand. What is what would help me
the most to release that um that sense
of unsuress or the the fear? What do you
believe me when I tell you that there is
nothing you can ever discover that
cannot be applied in a positive way?
Yes. Then that's it. That's it. Okay. If
you really believe it, you will need
nothing else. You will trust it.
Understand? Yes. One moment.
what you call
a.m. 3:15 a.m. in your morning. This
morning of your time, be open for
information from someone who can assist
you. All right. Yes. Thank you. Thank
you. Shooting.
Hello, Bashar. I have Hello. I have two
questions. All right. The first one.
Speak up. Speak up. Be bold.
Okay. I'm shaking. All right. Feel
excited. Feel the whole thing through
you. Yes.
Share the excitement. My first question
is on Friday my father was admitted to
the hospital. And he has spinal menitis.
All right. And the doctors can't tell
how far along it is. And he's just been
newly married. And my stepmother is very
scared. And I'm wondering what I can say
to calm the her down and say to my
father also cuz I know this is something
he's choosing to bring upon himself.
Does he know that? No, he doesn't want
to believe it when I tell him that. Then
you may not be able to change the belief
system within that individual and they
may need to play out what they have
agreed to play out. And all the fears
that they may face within this
interaction, we perceive may need to be
played through. For it may be, this is
not a solid prediction, but it may
be what you would
call the discovery of what you may say
to be a
75 point out of 100
point creation of a manifestation that may
creation of a manifestation that may
seem to be so overwhelming it will not
reverse. Now it
can but we perceive there are many
things that those two individuals your
father your
stepmother have agreed to face and they
may have to go through playing this out
if they will not believe that it can be
done in any other way. We may not be
able to be of much assistance to you in
this because their determination to play
this out at this point as we perceive
their energy is very strong. Okay. The
best you can do is still love them
unconditionally and at least see what
they have chosen as a sign of their
strength and not a sign of weakness. You
understand? I understand. Because
everyone is eternal. Everyone is
infinite. Understand? Yes. Now one moment. One
moment. I am going to suggest some
symbolic words to you which may open and
unlock some doorways within you. I
cannot necessarily give you an
analytical understanding of this except
to say that it is our perception that
some of the lives you have had together
with them that have been the strongest
involve some of these symbols and
sending some of these energies to you
may unlock certain things that will
allow you to help them later and help
you now perhaps though you may need to
assimilate them in your dream reality.
Nile, Egypt, Russia's violet light,
waters of
light, crescent
moon, white
energy, papyrus, papyrus,
oirus,
Isis, boat of moon, boat of
sun, waters of
Nile, wisdom, Aged
aged chamber
focus fire awaken. In that sense, you have
fire awaken. In that sense, you have
what we can give you as a key at this
time. Thank you. Well, thank you very
much. Allow your dream reality to
assemble this idea into some format that
will make sense to you. Yes.
Um, my second question is when I go to
my meetings and I come to the Sunday
night meeting to listen to your tapes
from Los Angeles, I am falling asleep
all the time. Yes. And I'm getting tired
of doing this. It's just No, no, no.
It's all right. It's all right. You're
getting the information. I know. That's
why we are telling you now that some of
the symbologies we had to give you have
to be assimilated within you
unconsciously. For now, it is where you
are doing your quickest work. It is the
way that will allow you to assist the
other individuals in your life in the
best way. Do not worry about it. You are
getting the information. You are getting
it. Okay? Trust it. Relax. Relax. It
will begin to come out in the actions in
your life when you allow yourself to be
fully spontaneous in that sense. One
more word. Scarab.
Okay. Thank you for Thank you very much.
Understand that part of the connections
you are making now in what you would
call your sleep state will allow you to
begin to truly wake up in the dream
reality and wake up in the physical
reality in the physical dream. You
follow me? Yes, I do. Relax. It is all
right. Many individuals react that way
right now. That is the way they best
absorb the energy and the information.
To us, you are not asleep. Understand?
Yes, I do. Thank you very much. Pleasant
dreams. [Applause] Shedding
Bashar. Yes. My my question is twofold.
First, all right. Fold number one. Okay.
Fold number one. First of all, would you
just briefly mention what you foresee to
be some of the changes in the field of
education in the near future? All right.
Some of them will hearken back to what
you call Atlantean times where
environments and atmospheres will be
created in which those being educated
will have all senses utilized. They will
not be the high analytical focus but
direct experiential absorption so that
an individual will be allowed to
identify literally identify with the
concept as the concept. They will be the
concept and will know it innately,
intuitively, automatically. Understand?
Yes. Some of this was accomplished in
what you call Atlantean times through
the use of drum beats, setting up a
cadence, what you might call a hypnotic
state, not something that does something
against their will in that sense, but
just the creation of a conducive
atmosphere to allow them to absorb in an
easy manner. Breathing. Breathing in
learning is very powerful. very
powerful. You will find that there is
any concept you really want to maintain
intuitively an idea of. If you will take
a four count of four, four count of
four, allow yourself to breathe in 1 2 3
4. Hold the breath 1 2 3 4. And think of
the concept. Let the breath out. 1 2 3
4. Hold it out. 1 2 3 4. Clear for the
next concept. Breathe in. 1 2 3 4. Hold
it. 1 2 3 4. Have the concept. Again,
repeating the idea, but at this rate. 1
2 3
4 1 2 3 4. Approximately what you call a
second. 4 seconds. You follow me? very
powerful learning technique that will
begin to be implemented in your society
when you understand that regulating the
body as a whole will allow an individual
to absorb the information in a holistic
way rather than telling them to
concentrate with this portion of their
consciousness or this portion of their
consciousness rather than breaking them
up into pieces letting them absorb the
idea as a whole. Understand? Yes. What
else? I I can see that what you're
saying might also be related to what I
want to ask next, which is would you
talk a little bit more about dyslexia
specifically and how uh we may help
someone who appears to have this
problem. All right. There are a few
reasons for why we perceive that occurs
in your society. One is similar to the
format you call epilepsy. You
understand? Yes. It is a crosscircuiting
of the brain.
This is similar to what happens in the
type of channeling you are perceiving.
Now there is an explosion of neuronic
activity but coordinated in what you
would call a laser-like coherent
fashion. Epilepsy and to some degree
dyslexia are uncoordinated electrical
activity that is related to the idea of
channeling and perceiving different
dimensions and perspectives of reality
all at the same time. But they are
overlapped in a way that cannot be
filtered out. You follow me? Yes. So the
idea is to allow more
coordination as a whole unit within the
brain to understand whole concepts,
whole directions of motion so that the
crosscircuiting shortcircuiting will not
occur. an individual to some degree who
is epileptic, dyslexic or even what you
call stuttering. One thing that can be done
stuttering. One thing that can be done
just one. Now remember there are as many
reasons as there are individuals. This
will not work for everyone but this lays
a base
foundation. Have them look at you in a
relaxed and meditative state breathing
easily. Take your hands and have your
hands do this. slowly then slowly then
cross
cross. This effect on the optic nerve
will begin to assist the brain in
blending and balancing what you call the
left and right hemisphere to such an
extent that the short circuiting will no
longer occur.
Individuals who
stutter while they are watching you do
this, nine times out of your 10 will
stop stuttering. Individuals who are
dyslexic, while they are watching you do
this, nine times out of 10 will smooth
out at least what you would call 70%.
Individuals who are epileptic while they
are watching you do this may find
smaller and smaller firings going on in
the brain and they will be more and more
focused in specific directions. You
follow me? Yes. It can aid and assist in
the blending and the balancing of the
different hemispheres and the electrical
activity that goes on within them.
Understand it is no accident, not that
it has to happen this way, but simply
because of the way your society is and
the way it thinks it needs to get things
done. It is no accident that the
majority of what you call channels in
your physical reality before they
started channeling or becoming psychic
gave themselves a severe electric shock
or a strong blow to the head that
approximated what you call an epileptic
seizure. It was for the purpose of
realigning all the neuronic pathways to
open them up to be able to allow the
flow of energy to come through in the
way that it needs to to facilitate the
agreement of the channeling that they
have made. You understand? Yes. Yes.
Now, we're not saying you have to go
around banging yourself on the head, but
the idea therefore of allowing the
left and right hemispheres of the brain
to start acting like one brain, which it
is, it is not really a left and a right
completely. If you start treating it as
one idea, then you will begin to smooth
out some of that electrical activity and
it will not
shortcircuit because it is
shortcircuiting because you rely upon
the idea that one side serves only one
function and another side serves only
another function and you will not allow
those things to cross to blend where
they need to in the
center. Understand? Yes. what you call
the corpus colossum that separates the
brain halves is the seat of all the
origination of the electrical activity
cross filtering and blending that takes
place within all of the phenomena you
have mentioned. So allowing an
individual to center in that way by
involving both halves of the brain and
then crossing them will allow them to
utilize that center portion and begin to
balance and blend more appropriately the
polarities they have created themselves
to be for whatever reason understand.
Yes. Does that assist you? It does very
much it is one of the reasons not the
only reason but one of the reasons why
your infinity symbol is in the shape
that it is. It shows the polarities and
where they converge in the center.
Analytically, symbolically, this is in
the center of your brain. Right in the
corpus colossum in which there is
literally a type of black hole through
which all your consciousness pours into
physical reality as the persona you know
yourself to be. Understand? Yes.
Sweet dreams to you. Okay. Thank you.
You will have more information in that
state now that a certain door has been
opened. Thank you. Well, thank you very
much. Oh, one moment. One
moment. You have done similar things to
this before using what you call visual
aid, especially in adalantean times.
I've been an educator many times. Many
times, many times. Understand? Yes.
Use color, use light, use
sound, use what your imagination
provides. Enjoy, joy, joy, joy, joy, joy. Thank
Enjoy, joy, joy, joy, joy, joy. Thank
you. I will. Thank you. Shooting.
Hello, Bashar. Hello.
A beloved friend of mine has recently
experienced the death of her younger
brother. All right.
She has the belief that life on this
earth now is all we experience and when
it's over that's the end of that person.
She's experiencing a great deal of pain.
All right. Can you tell me how I can
best serve her during this time?
Do you mean within her belief system?
It seems as though it would have to be
my that her belief system is not mine.
I've experienced a great deal of
frustration in trying to know
how to be accessible to her. Perhaps
within her belief
system, can she believe that even if
there may not be a continuence that
there is a reason for
everything? Can she believe that?
Perhaps. Perhaps. All right. We will not
second guess. Okay,
that can be one way to understand that
there is a reason and therefore whatever
that individual contributed as the
individual that they were is what needed
to be contributed to your world to allow
it to be what it is. Now she will not
accept that there may not be much
assistance we can give. However, with
the idea of continuence, we may be able
to assist a little bit with the
following perspective.
Perhaps just from what you call a
logical point of view, the individual
might be able to understand that all
things continue in a different
form. Is the individual in any way,
shape, or form in your terms scientific?
I would say her mind works that way
more. All right. Does the individual
understand that energy cannot be created
or
destroyed? That it can only change from
form to form? I'm sure she's heard that
concept. Let her think about it because
it can be applied directly to
consciousness, which is energy. It
cannot be destroyed. It must continue to
exist. If it once existed, it must
always exist. Yes. It's in a
different consciousness has ever had the
ability to express itself
cohesively, then it will always express
itself cohesively on some level in some
way. Understand? Yes, I do. In other
words, to put it very simply, if
something has existed, it must always
exist because what has existed cannot
become nonexistent. What exists
nonexistent. What exists
is the idea that something can end
utterly and become non-existent comes
from your society's assumption that
existence can become non-existence. But
those two concepts are already complete.
They are the polarity of creation. That
which already doesn't exist fills
non-existence. That which exists fills
existence. They do not become the other.
There is no room in non-existence for
anything that already exists. It is
already filled with all the things that
will never exist.
I know this does not necessarily
translate very well in your language,
but perhaps it is the best that can be
accomplished. The idea is to simply
understand that if something has
existed, it must always stay on the side
of existence and therefore the only
choice it has is to change its format
because once it exists, it always exists
because time is your illusion.
Understand? Yes. Perhaps this can be of
some assistance. However, in no way,
shape, or form is anyone ever expected
to force a change in someone's belief
systems. And she does not have to
believe it if she does not want to. I
understand that.
However, one moment. One moment.
All right. No, we cannot share that.
Does that serve you? Yes, it does. Thank
you. Thank you.
Shooting. Hi Bashar. Hi. Uh I'm I'm
curious um in terms of
um Earth years. Yes. Uh how old are you?
158. 137 in my years. Uh have you uh ever
137 in my years. Uh have you uh ever
channeled down into another human being
before? And did it affect did it affect
uh the history of this planet? All
things that interact affect each other.
You have affected mine. I have affected
yours. We have affected each others in
the combined history that we are.
Do you plan on coming down in another in
the form of another human being at some
later date? No. The one life in that
sense that I have lived upon your planet
has been sufficient though we have
channeled through many of you at
different times.
Uh, I listened to a fellow that had
interviewed um many people that that
have been um had contact with aliens and
uh he seemed to have talked to several
people that had
uh been removed from the earth and part
of their um uh sexual reproductive
systems been removed and placed into uh
the bodies or whatever of the aliens and
then at later date brought back the
human being to show the offspring. Do
are you Yes, we are aware of the idea.
It is not our
civilization that is performing these
particular interactions. Is this really
going on in a sense but not exactly as
you have defined it. Remember that some
of what you are defining, some of what
those individuals in their experience
are defining to some degree are symbolic
interpretations that they pick up
telepathically that they think are
physically happening.
Understand? In other words, telepathy
can be so strong between what you call
an extraterrestrial and a member of your
society that a telepathic interaction
that involves an exchange of energy or
ideas can actually be interpreted by you
as a physiological occurrence when it
isn't understand.
I think so. In other words,
telepathy imagination is real but not
necessarily in the physical dimension
that you understand it. Also remember
that any interactions that are going on
between your civilization and other
civilizations, whether your civilization
remembers it or not, are all done by
agreement. And what is being done is a
part of the transformation taking place
upon your planet. To change the
vibration, to allow there to be more
conduciveness for individuals on your
planet to exist within the new vibration
that you are creating it to be. None of
these things are experiments truly in
your sense against your will. They are
co-created experiments, co-created
interactions. But because of what your
society has created itself to be, many
of your members at this time do not
remember that they have made such an
agreement. Understand? I think so. Does that serve
Understand? I think so. Does that serve
you? Uh, could I ask you one other
thing? Yes. Uh, do you have any idea who
killed John F. Kennedy and why?
We cannot share all the specifics, but
it is our perception that the individual
you have labeled in your
terminology never committed the
act. In our perception, the idea would
be that there were what you would call
interest groups that found the vibration of that
groups that found the vibration of that
particular individual inviable,
unsupportable, and unchangeable in any
way other than through the violence that
was
perpetuated. But the individual that you
have labeled as being responsible in
that sense was involved and was a part
of what you would call the
entire scope or
scheme but was never actually
responsible for the physical act itself
that caused the death. You understand?
Yes. The idea is simply a format to represent
The idea is simply a format to represent
the degree of separation that existed
and to some degree still exists between
what you call your public and your
government. Also, the energy of the
individual you refer to as
Kennedy is in a sense another fragment,
another aspect of the energy you have
referred to as
Lincoln. It is the same in a sense soul.
Understand? Yes. And that is why it
represented many of the same ideas and
why many of the synchronicities in their
life over overlapped and were similar
and it played
out in a sense ideas in your society to
illustrate the
state in which your society existed at
the time and the state of separation
that existed at the time in your society
that could create such an act of
violence and separation. Understand?
Yes. So they were willing in that sense,
not in the negative
sense, not in the complete martyrdom
sense, but willing to choose lie that
would represent those energies in your society
represent those energies in your society
not unlike the scenario that was played
out by what you call your collective
Christ consciousness upon your planet to
illustrate the state of affairs at the
time and to give you an opportunity to
smooth out, blend, and balance those
affairs rather than allow them to
perpetuate in the manner that could
create that particular type of
scenario. Understand?
Uh I think so. You lost me a little bit
along there someplace. We are simply
making an analogy between what you
recognize as the martyrdom quote unquote
to use that term loosely of Kennedy of
your Lincoln of your Christ
consciousness. The idea relates in that particular
The idea relates in that particular
event strongly to the same type of
scenario and the same type of reasons
for why what you call the crucifixion
scenario was played out upon your planet
to relieve your planet of the need to
take itself through suffering from that
point forward. and what you call the
Lincoln scenario and the Kennedy
scenario were aspects of a soul
consciousness, what you may call an
ascended being that chose to live a life
wherein it would place itself squarely
in the position of illustrating in no
uncertain terms the state in which your
collective consciousness as a society
existed at that point. They were willing
in that sense to give up their physical
lives to illustrate the state of your
society so that you would see quite
definitely where and when things needed
to change. You understand? Yes. Does
that serve you? Yes, it does. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Shutting. Hi, Bashar. Hi.
Hi, Bashar. Hi.
What I would like to ask you is that I
am in training to become a
hypnotherapist and I would I would like
to know how I can best use this tool to
serve people. How do you wish to use it?
What has your imagination told you?
Right now, I'm doing past life
regressions. All right. Does that excite
you? Yes, it does. All right, then. Any
other way you wish to use it? Hypnosis.
Yes. Uh, I am finding out there are many
ways that I can use it. Pick the ones
that excite you the most. Act upon it
with your integrity and you'll be doing
just fine. You will be serving the
individuals best by being to the fullest
who you can be. Because by being who you
are, you will only attract the
individuals by definition whom you will
be able to serve the best. Will you not?
Why would you want to attract someone
you cannot serve? I wouldn't want to.
All right, then don't. Okay, it is as
simple as that. Every single
person has the necessary audience that
they can serve and every audience will
find its server. If you are simply being
who you know you are, you will be of the
vibration to only attract those by
definition who you will be able to help.
Why would you assume that you would be
able to attract someone you wouldn't be
able to help?
Well, I wouldn't. All right, then. Does
that work for you? Yes, it does. Well,
thank you very much. May I ask one more
question? Yes. I would like to know what
the importance is of nutrition. As uh
the consciousness expands, it will
depend upon the belief systems of the
individuals, but it can be
representative of changes and
accelerations in your frequencies. You
may find that you will lose the urge for
more and more material sustenance and
start relying more and more on energy.
This does not have to be a forced
situation. You don't have to force
yourself to be more spiritual. But the
idea in that sense is that generally
generally higher accelerated energy will
require less physical bulk to maintain
it. You understand? Yes. So the simpler
forms may come into play for many of
you. But the reasons and the timing and
the actual substances in question will
vary from individual to individual. You
have to deal with each one instinctively
and distinctly. You follow me? Yeah.
Does that assist you? Yes, it does. Oh,
thank you very much. Thank you. Shing.
[Music] Hello, Bashar. Hello. I have two
Hello, Bashar. Hello. I have two
questions for you. All right. The first
is how will I know what my next step is
for my greatest or fastest spiritual
growth? Now, what have we been talking
about all night long?
I got it. What excites you the most? The
thing that you can act upon. The thing
you are capable of acting upon out of
all the opportunities that present
themselves to you. Choose the one that
excites you the most and act upon it
with integrity. It will always
accelerate you effortlessly and
abundantly in the direction that
represents the path you chose to be.
That's what excitement is. Definition.
Excitement is the physical translation
of the vibratory energy that represents
the path you chose to be at that moment.
So act upon the thing that excites you
the most and you will be right in step
right in step right in step with where
you need to be. Understand? I sure do.
Also, when you do that, you are living
in the moment, enjoying who you are in
the present moment. And when you live in
the present, you collapse the whole notion
present, you collapse the whole notion
of time and what you call your future
accelerates towards you at an
accelerated rate.
Understand? You all know what you say
happens to time when you're having fun,
don't you? Well, it doesn't really fly. The
you? Well, it doesn't really fly. The
idea simply is that when you are focused
on something that is in your terms
exciting and lets you be in the moment,
it is not only that you let time fly. It
is not only that you are not in a sense
paying attention to time. You are not
ignoring it the passage of time. It is
that you are literally not creating the
time because you create time. You create
it. Space and time are your projection.
They are the definitions of physical
reality but you create physical reality.
It is your
game. So when you live in the moment you
do not create as much time. Remember
many of you have had this experience.
You are doing something you really love
to do and all of a sudden you look up
and say oh well 3 hours have passed.
Where did the time go? Feels like all 15
minutes to
me. Understand something very important.
If it only literally feels
experientially like 15 minutes to you,
you have only aged 15 minutes, not 3
hours. You have reconnected yourself
into the timeline that your society
agrees upon and therefore have
reconnected yourself 3 hours later to
catch up to everyone else. But if you
have only experienced in your heart 15
minutes, you have only aged 15 minutes
because you only created 15 minutes of
time. So the idea of how to accelerate very
So the idea of how to accelerate very
quickly is to live in the present
totally. Then you won't create as much
time. You will literally become ageless,
timeless, and everything will collapse
into the present. Understand? I sure do.
Does that assist you? It does. I have
another question. All right. I have a
situation in my life that's
not too much fun to look forward to that
might be happening in October. All
right. And I wanted to know how do I
know what there is for me to do to
disappear that situation or is there
anything that I can do to transform it?
Make it disappear. Transform it.
Transform it.
So that I don't have to experience it as
I now see it. All
right. Why would you create that
experience? And if you did experience
it, what would you learn in experiencing
it? If you can allow yourself to
determine what it is you would be
getting out of it if you were to
experience it and allow yourself to
learn it now, you will not have to have
that experience in order to learn it.
Understand? I do. Plain and simple.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
act this
timing. Allow me once again to extend to
each and every one of you individually
and collectively. Everything is in perfect
collectively. Everything is in perfect
timing.
Trust yourself. Wake up and dream.
yourself. Wake up and dream.
Wake up and live your dream for your
physical reality is only what you dream
it to be. What you believe most strongly
or fear most strongly that it might be
is what it is. Redefine the belief you
will redefine the
reality. Remember your feelings do not
happen by themselves.
There is no such thing as I just feel
that way. I don't know. I just do. All
feelings are
reactions. Reactions to something you
already believe to be
true. So if you have a feeling you don't
prefer, it's because you have a belief
that you may not prefer. Let the feeling
put you in touch with what the belief
would have to be in order to have that
feeling. define what the belief is that
you don't prefer. Don't judge it. Just
redefine it. For in having had the
belief the way you had it, and in having
had the feeling the way you had it, it
pointed out to you what you preferred
instead. So, it has served you in a
positive way. Anything you have ever
done, positive and negative, has brought
you to where you are now. Don't
invalidate it. It is all a part of you.
Redefine the belief in the fashion you
prefer to define it without invalidating
the way it used to be defined. And you
will allow, not make, not force, allow
that reality to manifest in the quickest
possible way, the path of least
resistance. Do what excites you. It is
your strongest signal. It is the
vibration that allows you to know you
are all living
light, coherent lasers of
consciousness. Whatever vibration you
are is what reality you pull out of the
holographic matrix that is formerly
invisible and make it visible to
you. All that you perceive with your
physical senses is the vibration you are
on. Change your vibration. Change your
Change your vibration. Change your
reality. It is as simple as that. Let it
be that simple. And remember, nothing is
too simple or too good to be
true. Oh, how long will this last? It's
got to end sometime. And
sometime. And
finally, lighten
up. Lighten up on yourselves. You
deserve ecstasy.
Just because you
exist. You don't need another reason.
You deserve
it. I believe
it. You don't have to, but you can. It
is up to
you. We thank you for allowing us to
reflect back to you what you already
know. To remind you of who you are so
that we may learn to play together as
equals. Our unconditional love to you
all. We bid you all exciting dream life
and light dreams. A fond and loving good
day.
Let it go.
[Applause] Thank you all for being here tonight.
Thank you all for coming tonight.