all right I'll say how are you all this
evening of your time as you create time
to
exist allow us to begin this interaction
this evening of your time with a
reminder that we have entitled this
interaction ghost story in honor of your
all hollow's Eve now just one more
reminder of the basis of the
foundation though this may not have
anything to do particularly with this
story we will share the basis and the
foundation of your Halloween once
again in times past there was upon your
planet as many of you have realized many
ancient civilizations one of which you call
civilizations one of which you call
Atlantis has now down through your ages
been relegated to the idea of a
relegated to the idea of a
mythological civilization is still still
commemorated in much of your literature
in various ways though you have in many
ways forgotten what some of these
commemoratives actually refer to one
idea of the destruction of Atlantis is
what you refer to as your biblical
flood the idea also of many of your
druidic rituals also hekken back to the idea of
rituals also hekken back to the idea of
some of the Atlantean
civilization your Egyptian and your
Central and South American pyramidal
Structures hearken back to the time of
atlantian architecture for they were
begun in that land those
structures also pertaining to this interaction this
also pertaining to this interaction this
evening of your time in terms of the
date of your counting your Halloween the
three dates your all hollow's Eve your
November 1st and your November 2nd
repres presented in some of your
religious circles as the idea of All
Saints and All Souls days the days
following all hollow's Eve those three
days are actually The Remnant
commemoration of the day before the day
of and the day after the destruction of
Atlantis in a sense
energy speaking your November 1st
speaking your November 1st
is actually your true New Year's Day the
beginning of the cycle of energy that
you are now finalizing upon your planet
because the cycle you are now emerging
from was begun long ago in Atlantean
time and now you are shifting
it the idea as we recognize Therefore
your Halloween your all Hollows eeve is
that timing when you come as you say
down to the wire of facing those
portions of your Consciousness that many
of you now for the several thousand
years since the destruction of Atlantis
have submerged into your
subconsciousness have buried deep within
you and covered over with the waves of
your surface conscious memory these
ideas now AR Rising once again from the
depths of your being are coming to the
surface to reveal themselves in the
knowledge of your connection to the
infinite and the reach creation on the
surface of your planet in the society
you have now of civilizations and
attitudes and Creations that are
analgous to the heights of the
civilization on your planet you call
Atlantis you are very much at the same
point once again almost the same degree
of Technology you now have some
differences they did not have they had
some differences you do not have but you
are relatively speaking at the same
point the same level of technology and
on the verge once again of the same
basic decision do you use it in positive
ways and expand and accelerate to the
stars or do you use it in negative ways
and once again submerge yourself under
the basis of your Consciousness these
decisions are up to you although we have
once again shared with you many times
that it is our perception now that you
have decided to use it in a positive way
and that is the reason we can be in
contact with you at this time simply
because your vibration is now becoming
more and more like the vibration of the
worlds that have created peace within
their structures of
Consciousness but we know that many of
you still like to be
frightened still of to play the IDE is
out and this is a very creative thing to
do for if you can find ways to enjoy the
fears you have they can be transformed
into positive
light and so in honor of this idea and
in willingness to play and participate
in your society's Customs we share with
you now our version of a little ghost
story if you wish you may adjust the
lighting to what you find
appropriate but we will leave that up to
you it all
begins on a world if you wish very much
like your own it does not have to be any
particular place it does not really have
to be any particular
time and as you say the subject of the
story can be called for now
army army can be if you wish male or
female it does not
matter on Army's
World there is a time and a
ritual that everyone must go through
before they then undertake for the
remainder of their life those ideas that
they will be utilizing in service to all
those things that will
represent their passage from what you
would call childhood to
adulthood similar in many ways to many
rituals you may have upon your world
this ritual involves the idea of
spending some time in a particular
structure this structure is a many
storage structure and even though it may
not have absolute similarities to the
idea of buildings upon your planet it
will do in this story to refer to it as
a
house now you may wish to call it a
haunted house that is up to
you but in Army's world it is called the
house of all things every everyone knows
of it and it is not without some
trepidation that individuals take their
turns spending a night within the house
of all
things and so it came to pass that it
was Army's
turn to spend that night in the house of
all things and the teachers and the friends
things and the teachers and the friends
of army wished Army
well all the while of course it
expressing that they were very glad it
was not their
turn and so with perhaps some boldness
and yet some
trepidation Army set off for the house
of all things which stood by
itself in the very center of a
forest in its own clearing in its own
Meadow Pleasant enough perhaps during
the day
or so at least Army used to
think and as Army
traveled through the forest towards the
house it began to be the time of the
setting of The Sun dusk as you call it
and the closer Army got to the house of
all things the darker and darker it
got and the
the
animals and the
Trees of course through Amy's
imagination began to take on slightly
different aspects of them seeming to point the way
aspects of them seeming to point the way
toward the house but very
reluctantly their branches swaying in
the wind pointing the direction to the
house but all the time bending in the
wind as if to say go go back go
[Music] back this is the way you wish to go but
back this is the way you wish to go but
if I were you I would go back go
back well Army knew that Army could go
back but Army also knew this was very
important that there were things to look
at things to face things to understand
if Amy were to become what Army really
desired to
be nowhere but in this house could one
accelerate so
quickly it was said though everyone who
had been in the house was also told you
may share of your experiences if you
wish but not to the point where you will
be living those experiences for everyone
else for it is up to everyone to decide
that they themselves must go through
this house and have their own
experiences and as Army walked through
the forest Army dwelt on the many tales
that had been told and the many stories
that had been
shared three steps forward two steps
back three steps forward one step
[Music] back
back
eventually however Army arrived at the
clearing and there in the clearing at
the very center was the house of all
things multi
stor it stood
alone the wind the only sound no light
coming from anywhere any window within
the house and army took one look back at the
house and army took one look back at the
forest
comparing the idea of going ahead or
going back
bolstered up the courage and walked
boldly up to the
door and just to be polite gave a little
knock just in case someone might be home
you never
know the door opened
slowly to Amy surprise but it did not
seem to be anyone
there yet Army took it as an
invitation especially since everyone
knew this is what army was supposed to
do now and stepped
in and the door you guessed
it closed behind
army ever so gently not a slam but with
an absolutely precise definitive and
final
click and in that click there was an
echo e an echo of a
voice the way
out is
up and army did not really understand
this was not even sure Army had heard
this for
real rubbed out Amy's
ears my imagination getting to me I am
hearing voices already I don't know if
this was such a good
idea individuals have said they spent
whole all night in this house I have
just arrived already I'm hearing
voices I will probably never see the
dawn but if this is to be my fate so be
it if there is anyone around who decides
these things if it is going to be
horrible please at least let it be
quick but there was no sound and there
was no
answer and all was dark except for here
and there the very faint light of a moon
shining through this window and
that creating even deeper shadows in
contrast to the soft velvety violet
light and Amy began to take stock of the
surroundings allowing the eyes to adjust
somewhat but never completely in Focus
did all of the room become
Army wandered
through a creek here an unknown sound
there a
heartbeat oh oh that must be mine Amy
said a little louder than usual it is
tonight but it is mine after
all Army sat in the middle of the first
room for a very long time expecting
things to come to Army waiting for what
might come with some once again amount
of dread intrepidation uncertainty
unknowingness and finally after what
seemed to be many
hours nothing had happened well maybe
it's not so bad after all Amy said maybe
I could go exploring this old place and
find something interesting that no one
has ever found perhaps all the others
were simply too
afraid but if there really is nothing
here and I am the first to explore
everywhere I can come out perhaps with
many Treasures who knows what I may find
under the floorboards and in the shadows
that others have been afraid to go
into so Army began to
explore a door here a door there some
locked oh
well some
not maybe I wish they
were chose a door
turned on pushed it open
on pushed it open
gently
Creek an old house
cek a very old
house and into the room Army
went not much light at all little cracks
here and there little beams of
moonlight little moats of dust catching
the eye what was that oh just the
light what was that oh just some
dust walked into the
room and the door closed behind with the
same definite click Amy turned around
and tried it and it did not
budge No Going Back the little click
echoed only go up
armmy turned around to see if there were
any other doorways out of the room and
in the shadows could not see
any only go up how can I go up the room
is sealed there is a ceiling I do not
see any other
door Army looked around staying close to
the door through which army
came hoping upon hope that it might open
again maybe it's just because the house
is old there isn't really anything
holding the door shut maybe it's just
because my hand is trembling and too
weak to really pull it from being
stuck maybe
maybe
maybe and all of a sudden a slight sound
to one
side a sound like a breath ever so
shy and army
turned and could see nothing at
first and then
slowly something that made Army recoil
against the door for there seemed to be
far on the other side of the room very
faint very
ghostly shining with the pale violet
light of the Moonlight
itself glowing softly what appeared to
be just two
legs just two
legs as if there could be something
standing and
watching but only ding to allow enough
of it to materialize to at least allow
Army know where it
stood just two legs connected at the hip
with nothing
above and army looked a little closer to
be sure that Amy was seeing what Amy
thought Amy was
seeing and recoiled immediately ly as
the legs took a step forward towards
Ami and Ami began to perspire heavily
and the heartbeat was ever more
loud and Amy turned around and faced the
door and began to wish with all the
might that was contained in Amy's heart
that the door would open and pulled the
handle and rattle rattle rattle rattle
but it would not give and as the last
rattle died away the echo once again the
only way out is
up and army turned and
looked and to one side where Army did
not SE before there was another
door and army moved sideways around the
wall staying as far from the legs as
possible and they turned to
watch as if they had eyes to observe
Amy's movement around the
room and army made sure Amy's eyes
stayed riveted on those legs so they
would not run toward
Army because Army thought if Army could
Army would run right through the wall if
that happened Army reached the
happened Army reached the
door the legs seemed content as long as
Army did not enter further into the
center of the room to remain where they
were just out lining its domain as it
were Amy reached the other door and with
one hand opened it and looked and there
were some
stairs and quick as you can imagine Army
bolted through the door and shut it
behind and turned
around and saw a very tall
staircase very creeky
stairs and walked up and up and up and
up and up and came to another door
another room oh
room oh
no not more
legs a house full of legs what could
this mean how am I supposed to learn from
mean how am I supposed to learn from
this I am being scared to
death what is this supposed to teach me
oh teacher I wish you were here now
it was you that told me I must go
through this if I were to become the
Army I want to be how does this serve
me can I really last the night oh well
deep breath into the room Army
went didn't see anything immediately
pretty dark though just as dark as the
other room little trickles of light
through a very tiny
window looked
around no legs all
all
right walked into the center of the room
turned 360° looked
around no
legs oh better and better Army
thought explored the room a little bit
more peered into the shadows as far as
Army dare looked up to the little window
dare looked up to the little window
stood looking up the shaft of light as
if some somehow Army might be able to
LEAP up and squeeze out that little
window to get outside into the Moonlight
where Army knew it would be
safer and all of a sudden standing there
watching the light Army
felt all of the skin on his
back as if something had caressed every
so
gently and took a
gump no no no just my
imagination the breeze through a crack
in the
floor and turned
around and
jumped and stood
Frozen in the shaft of Moonlight and
there floating floating nearby in the
Darkness glowing ever so gently a
floating pair of arms reaching
arms reaching
out reaching out towards Army who now
began to
shake who began to step
back able to uproot one foot and then
the other as if they were glued to the
floor and becoming stuck again and not
taking another step and staring and
staring at the arms that reached
out groping grasping for
Army and just beyond the arms to one
side Army caught in the faintest glow of
the light another
door Amy wasted no
time Army
ran and did not
stop the beating of Amy's heart so loud
until the next door was slammed securely
behind and this time by now Army was
becoming weak and frightened and
weak and frightened and
wishing there
were a window large enough for now Army
was certain Army would jump even if it
meant Amy's death for Amy did not want
to spend another moment
and yet once again in the slamming of
that door and the clicking of the lock
there was the Small
Voice the way
out is
up I'm going mad Army
thought truly mad perhaps I will simply
become a resident of this
house perhaps this is
how this house has become so haunted I
am seeing all the Mad people that have
been here before me who have never
escaped and neither will I woe with
me but there ahead of army was yet again
another
staircase well if I am going to
die it might as well be
now and up the stairs Amy
climbed and with each step Amy's legs be
became heavier and heavier and heavier
until at the very top Amy wondered why
the floor underneath did not give way
and Amy didn't go crashing
through Amy looked at the door at the
top of the stairs the same bright brass
knob waiting for the
waiting for the
touch of Amy's hand
as if it had always been waiting for the
touch of Amy's hand to turn
it and
with leaden
arms Army
reached and felt the smooth coldness the
coldness that Amy thought that any
moment would signal the coldness that
Amy's body would be in death if Army
walked through that
door and turned it click
a very very old door very
Rusty what strength Army had
left was necessary all of it to muster
to push the door
open for Army knew it was the only way
there was no going
back and into the room Army
went and the
door closed behind
click and the echo died away but Army
did not
hear for Army
senses now
draining and Amy's heart
was in the
throat for ahead of army floating in the
center of the dark
room was only a heart a beating
heart Amy could not think Army could not
move Army felt Dark Death wrapping
around and covering Army's
eyes army with
Drew and curled into a little ball on
the floor and
floor and
felt the Eternal Night
descend but
then but
then in the very depths of Army's
Despair and fear and
darkness that little voice echoed again
up
Army the way out is
up I am on the top floor Army
cried up Army
up way out is
up what do you want from me army
cried yet Army found strength coming
back a strength that if anything even if
it was anger even if it was Defiance
that Army's predicament was allowing
Army to regain
senses and Rising
slowly Amy saw the
heart and the heart beat and glowed
fiercely and
brightly and Amy did not feel as
scared God has
scared and felt a warmth from the heart
who are you said
Ami up said the heart
up I do not understand said
Amy you will said the heart you
will the heart
vanished and the door behind Amy clicked
open and Amy saw light from
Below in a house that had had no light
up to that
point and descended the
staircase and walked into the
room peering around the corner of thirst
of
course looking for the arm that had
groped for Ami's
throat and saw
nothing and walked into the
room saw nothing nothing the room was
lit looked one
wall another wall and the third wall and
froze and then
recovered for there on the far far
wall was a
mirror and it was
only Amy's arms in the
Moonlight that had scared Amy
and went to the other door and down the
stairs as fast as you could imagine into
the other
room where there was now light and once
again the mirror the mirror on the far
wall it had only been Amy's legs that
had trembled and turned as Amy turned
around the room to seek
Escape shining the reflection of the
Moonlight off of Amy's legs into the
mirror and army went to the front door and it
and army went to the front door and it
opened
easily and out of the house of all
things to stand in the meadow and look
at it from
afar and the night was glorious and the
moon Shone brightly and army was happy
he had
lived and all of a
sudden a thought struck
Army but wait in the first room had been
the reflection in the mirror of my legs
in the second room had been the
reflection in the mirror of my arms but
no mirror can reflect a
heart what was
that what was
that then there was a
spirit I wonder if I'll ever
know and it came to
pass that Army lived a full life doing
all the things that Army desired to do
in being of service in joy and love and
now and then pondered back to the house
of all things and the heart and wondered
but found no
answer could not understand how the
house had been able to show a
heart to see through Ami's body to show
Ami's heart if that is what it truly
was and so it came to pass
that in the living of a full
life it came time for Army to
die and in passing from the physical to
the spirit
world Army was met by Army's teacher who
had preceded
before how nice to see you
again and now we are
spirits and hearkening back to the time
of the House of all things I can see in
that sense that Spirits are not things
to be
feared and funny you should mention that
said the teacher funny you should
mention the house of all things for just
as it was in physical life just as the
house of all things
represented a passage that each living
being must go through the house of all
things is something that you as a novice
Spirit must always so play a part in
serving how so you mean now that I'm
dead I have to go back
there just for a moment or two just to
be as a guide of service in love and in
light for it is the house of all things
and by definition it Bridges Both
Worlds and it is a doorway and a
passage that not only the living in life
but the living in death must also
participate in very well I will do what
I must said
Amy so go said the
teacher there is someone waiting
now and so Amy went and entered the
spirit side of the house of all things
but of course not through the front
door through the
top into the
attic and as soon soon as Army was in
place the sound of a
click and army
turned and saw
Ami Amy in
life being viewed by Amy in
death and Amy
understood I am the heart I
saw I am the guide I saw so long ago in
life life my own self in the
life my own self in the
future radiating the love the self love
it would take for me to live the life I
desired to
live I saw my own heart truly but not
reflected in any mirror of physical
design reflected in the mirror of
spirit to give
myself the reminder
that I am
loved are
me we thank
you thank
you we thank you for allowing us to
participate in the unlocking of
yourselves to
yourselves in the revealing of
yourselves to yourselves
for that is what the gate is all about
the gate you call all Hollow
Z represented by the vibration of the
number 13 for 13 is the Gate of
13 for 13 is the Gate of
transformation and death is only life in
a different
form at this
timing in return for your gift of
allowing us to share your dream with you
I ask you now how may I serve
you and to you good
evening thank you for your wonderful
story we thank you for allowing us to
concoct it out of the imagination and
the dreams and the spirit of all of you
and reflect as a mirror those ideas you
already contain um
contain um
okay since the summer when I was in
Santa Fe I've been painting um my own
line of garments with lightning bulbs
and snakes how exciting and Indian
symbols and I was very excited to find
that lightning bolts are the Kachina
energy in many ways yes and that the
snake is an Aboriginal sign of power in
a sense it is an ancient symbol to
represent wisdom and knowledge yes thank
you um now it seems this weekend I will
be going to Miami and swimming with a
doll all right have a good time I'm very
excited to play with them yes they are
very excited to play with all of you I
know um I feel that uh and also the
person I'm going with we feel we're on
the wave of great momentum in Sharing
aply put uh yes especially where are
concerned especially at this time of uh
November 1st and 2nd yes especially in
that area for it was off of your Eastern
and Southern Seaboard that the islands
of atalantis existed yes especially in
what you call your
Bahamas and your Bermuda
areas well we sense this excite
excitement and great expect
and yet I know as much as there will be
a lot of unfolding um I trust that the
unfolding will happen when it's meant to
happen absolutely it is going on all the
time you will have whatever recognition
of it you need to have when you need to
have it yes so I won't ask for a preview
at this time all right but um if there
is any message the dreamer has for
myself or for anyone here we haven't
heard from dreamer in a long time and I
thought maybe um there might be some
take flowers with you flowers of Many
Colors share them with the dolphins even
as they shared in times past the
discovery of colorful things on the
bottom of the sea and brought them to
the surface for all of
you okay so throw them in the water with
with them there take them in the water
with you ahuh okay at least
one all right I like the idea of many
all right is up to you okay we thank you
oh say hello for us I will thank you
very much thank you
Shing good evening Bashar and to you
good evening my name is starbird all
right I'm pregnant all right I'm a
excited yes I'm a dolphin Channel and
dolphin collar all right and I'm
expecting to have my babies in the water
with dolphins all right and right now
I'm looking for where when sort of that
can happen since in the moment there is
no place all right do remember do
remember that whether it takes place
physiologically or not if you understand
that of course a the child will assist
in the birth it's not just on your
shoulders yes and you simply call forth
the dolphin Consciousness which are very
willing to help each and any of you now
in the giving of the birth process you
will then be surrounded by their energy
sea even if it's not a physiological
ocean and that can amount to the same
energy wherein you will be boyed up and
supported and there will be a flow with
no pain whatsoever become lost in that
energy sea floating and floating and
sharing and feeling the interaction and
the blending of the energy it can be a
physical sea and if such as necessary by
simply putting this energy out in your
imagination you will attract yourself to
whatever physiological counterpart of
this idea can occur but if it doesn't
you can do it within the energy sea it
will be the same I felt that thank you
thank you I have one related kind of
question as well um can you explain
maybe what the um connection is between
the starboard um
energy the serus connection and the
dolphin vibration yes well dolphins have
received the idea of telepathic contact
from the Star series is for quite some
time the similarity in their vibration
is that the sixth density level of
Consciousness around the star you call
serus exists in an energy State and when
they have contacted your human life upon
your planet telepathically because they
exist in an energy C your human Minds
have translated them to be amphibious
beings which they are not literally but
because you translate them that way that
gives you your first clue that they are
very similar in vibratory wavelength to
the dolphin who exist as Ascension
species in your ocean and in that sense
by breathing air are to some degree
amphibious even though they do not
arrive upon the land's surface itself
they are simply counterpart energy to
the serious energy in many aspects and
the notion of what you call starbird is
an ancient recognition of a vibratory
name that is connected to ancient
American Indian cultures that also knew
and participated in directly the energy
and telepathic linkages with dolphins
and many other extraterrestrial
societies all the time especially those
that existed on what you call your
ancient Eastern
Seaboard does that serve you yes it does
thank you what pleasant dreams you too
Shing hi B and good evening to
you I U wanted to uh first off share
with you that you your mirroring has
been a great assistance all right can
you all hear this individual
adequately all right and I have been
facing a lot of myself which actually
has turned out to be a delight though it
doesn't seem to be to begin with
yes and actually um I have two well
curiosity questions I don't know which
is most important so I'll spit them out
answer the one you choose oh all
right uh it seems that uh since I have U
disconnected with Billy Meyer I seem to
be attracting a lot of Orion connected
people yes um and I was kind of
wondering what my connection might be
with or aside from the connection with
all that is which I'm connected with
everything of course and the other thing
was um an entity who is not Orion but is
often by the people that pick him up
called Orion or put into the Orion
things you might say uh an entity called
mraa I was wondering if you could tell
us about f thank you both are answerable
in one format good the idea basically
remember is that early pleadian
offshoots are also Orion in nature I
know that all right in that fashion
therefore you have created for yourself
a connection to that form of energy
because you recognize that in order to
be of service in the way you desire to
be in order to allow the ancient
negativity to be transformed into what
you call a and Light which is the
representation of what you call the
identity mraa then in that sense you would have
mraa then in that sense you would have
to associate yourself with the Orion
Energy to allow individuals who were
already fixed in that energy to
understand the blending of the pleadian
and the Orion Energy as old offshoots of
each other as old split that happened
long
ago I want to thank you for the things
you said to us um in the past
um it sounds like a pretty simple
formula some of the things you said it
is and you tells it's simple I believe
it and I've been following it and I've
made some changes in my life because of
it I'm sure thank you very much um not
every change yet but I found that trying
to follow your instructions on
imagination I've imagined myself in different
I've imagined myself in different
circumstances to a point where it's
almost easy or actually it's much easier
iier to imagine myself there than where
I am yes all right to a point where I
feel I'm almost disconnecting in an
unhealthy way well all right but it does
not have to be viewed as unhealthy
remember one of the whole ideas of your
transformational age is the whole
process itself of disconnection from
things that no longer represent who you
are if we live in our dreams yes is
there a point where we are ineffective
in operating in daily life so that only
when you do not allow yourself to
incorporate the physical reality as a
part of the dream itself only when you
do not act physically the idea your
imagination gives you out in the
physical world I feel like I'm missing a
part of the formula that you say is so
easy and maybe it's exactly that part
you just mentioned all right that is why
we always ask when we talk about the
thing that excites you the most if
you're doing the thing that excites you
the most as an individual because it is
the doing in physical terms the physical
actions that reflect the conviction of
your dreams because if you're willing to
have the conviction to act it out in
physical terms then you lock the
physical reality and the dream reality
together as one reality if you remain
floating in the idea of the imagination
reality without thinking that you must
manifest these ideas or put them into
physical action then you are forgetting
that you chose to be a physical being
and that the whole idea of the
transformational age is to allow
yourself not just to recognize that
physical reality is a dream that dream
reality is also solid and real and that
you by taking steps and by acting with
conviction on the opportunities that
come are actually putting into place are
manifesting in solid terms the idea of
the dream you are being at any given
moment so it takes action physical
involvement conviction doing that's what
grounds you and also allows to connect
to the infinite at the same
time at what point do we trust we we
always trust yes you always trust
whether you trust negative or positive
you always
trust how do how do we always know
what's negative and what's positive when
we want positive yes and we have
opportunity we have opportunity a and
opportunity B yes and we want to trust
the most positive opportunity for us
trust the one that excites you the most
and act on it with the most in Integrity
you have but then when it turns out to
be
bad do not Define something just because
of the way it
looks remember no circumstance has built
in
meaning and many times certain things
may happen that may appear on the
surface to be negative just because
that's the way you've always Define them
but if all of a sudden you no longer
Define them that way and start defining
them in a POS positive way you will get
a positive effect out of it however if
for some
reason you find that something that
occurs as a result of what you have done
does appear to be a negative act then
learn from it in a positive way learn
what beliefs you would have had to have
bought into in order for what you
originally wanted to do to have
transformed into a negative outcome
because remember what you put in is what
you get out and there is absolute no way
you can put a positive idea into the
mechanism of trust and get a negative
idea out if you really are getting a
negative effect then you put a negative
idea or a negative belief or a negative
definition into it to begin with which
means simply that you may not have been
as clear as you thought you were going
in so if you are getting a really
negative result and that is simply the
idea of negative energy that which is
segregative separative in that sense
limiting rather than Integra ative
unifying and unlimiting which is
positive energy if you really are
getting a negative energy effect then
use it in a positive way oh well now
that I am getting that result that must
mean that my definition going in was not
as positive as I analytically thought so
now I can use this effect to retrace my
steps discover what my original
definition was to find out why I got the
negative effect because if I did get a
negative effect the original information
had to be negative change it from that
point of view then put the positive the
new definition back in and you cannot
get anything but a positive result you
can still use a negative circumstance to
teach you positive things you can always
use it as a barometer in that way
understand yes I understand does that
serve you or is there still in your term
some confusion well I have to think
about what you said before I can
possibly not be confused about it all
right I'm I'm All it really comes down
to is a true fundamental trust a
fundamental definitional trust in the
sense that even if you do not always
know what is going on in your head even
if for some reason now and then you
might not be acting with full integrity
and something you do does come out to a
negative manifestation at least give
yourself the fundamental trust that you
will reflect to yourself either in the
circumstances in your own life or
through someone else's observation that
you have in fact created a negative act
and being put in touch with the fact
that you have done so will be your
self-regulating and self-governing
mechanism so that fundamentally even if
now and then you might quote unquote
accidentally or
unintentionally create a negative act
you will at least create the lifestyle
that will immediately catch it and
immediately show you what you have done
so it won't go any farther than that and
then you can in your terms redefine it
and rearrange it so if now and then you
find yourself unintentionally
manifesting a negative act do not add
more negativity by judging that you have
been doing something incorrectly just
allow yourself to realize that you have
not necessarily perhaps defined the idea
of your belief as clearly as you want to
and use the result as an opportunity to
define the original belief more clearly
because many times
remember sometimes for many of you it's
easier to discover what you are by
discovering more clearly what you are
not understand I understand that does
that assist you yes it does thank you
well thank you very much
Shing hello Bashar Andrew you good
evening um 6 months ago I left Woodland
Hills I left all my friends and
everything and I moved to Orange County
with my dad all right and I got a new
job and all new friends and everything
and things are going really well yes and
um just in the last two months I've been
coming back to Woodland Hills yes seeing
my old friends and my old boyfriend yes
and um since then I've lost my job oh
all right where do you suppose you lost
it
to maybe it's in the house of all things
maybe would you like to go and look for
it
I was wondering if you had any insight
why I keep I have this need to keep
coming back to this place when may I ask
you a personal question yes are you sure
now yeah oh all
right is the job you had something that
really excited you more than anything
else you could be doing well then what
do you want to do it is absolutely no
surprise that you would lose a job you
don't walk okay but what I really wanted to
walk okay but what I really wanted to
know is why do I keep coming back to
Woodland Hills what do you want to
do that's why I'm asking you what do you
want to do in your life be happy be
happy how by doing what what excites you
isn't there something you'd like to
do yeah there's a lot of things I want
to do name the most exciting exting one
the most exciting
one travel all right travel any place in
particular Caribbean islands why cuz
it's a beautiful place yes all
right then why aren't you
there because I don't have the money to
go who says you need the
money can your imagination not attract
in your life
different ways that you can get to
different places without necessarily
having it to be through money it can be
but it doesn't have to be are you aware
of the fact that there are other
individuals on your planet who travel
all the time and do not spend a cent
yeah but there must be some reason
reason
yes continue there must be some
something that's attracting me in this
Valley yes you know things don't go well
for me here I spent all my money here on
my boyfriend who doesn't have any you
know so do you have any insights on that
let's examine the idea of what you call
your Woodland
Hills on what you call the positive side
what do you like about your Woodland
Hills my mom lives there all right what
else I have a few friends all right that
I like to see what else not much else
not much else what about the energy of
the area itself it's not good not good
why not cuz a lot of things happened
here that weren't very good for me
that's why I moved in the first place
but that's not what I'm asking
you I'm not asking you about the energy
of the things that happen to you I am
asking you about the energy of Woodland
Hills let go of all the things that
happened to to you in Woodland
Hills just get in touch right now with
the energy of the place itself it
doesn't feel right in what sense it just
doesn't feel like I belong here I mean
like there's anything here for me but I
keep coming back here then where do you
feel you do belong is it in the
Caribbean yeah then go go there yes you
are are returning to what you consider
to be quote unquote home based that is
not home to you to make it more clear to
you that there are other places that do
resonate into your vibration do not
create the Assumption you cannot get
there put in your
imagination the vision of you being
where you believe you fit where you
believe you belong where you believe you
resonate do not block your ability to
get there by creating assumptions that
you can't because of what you think you
need to do it that is one of the reasons
you have returned to give yourself the
opportunity to truly understand that you
have the ability to go where you really
want to go to learn the things you
really need to learn to be who you
really want to be in this life so put
the desire out there knowing it is
highly probable that you can get there
you may not necessarily have to know
how and you don't really have to know
how you don't have to understand the
details all the time but if you have
given yourself the
ability by being where you know you
don't want to be to Define more clearly
where you do want to be then radiate
with your
imagination visualize yourself in that
area put all your senses into it feel
what it would be like to be there taste
what it would be like to be there hear
as if you were there see smell touch use
all your senses wrap yourself in that
Vision feel what it feels like to be
there because you do know what it feels
like to be there even though you may not
have been there in this physical life
you know what it feels like because
that's why you recognize the vibration
feel it in your visualization then just
send a burst of energy out into the
world that represents your connection to
that place then let it
place then let it
go from that moment forward all you need
to do is the following
thing at any given moment act upon the
circumstance that is the most exciting
circumstance that comes along that you
are capable of acting
upon those circumstances whether they
seem to have anything to do with the
idea of you're traveling or not will
lead you into the connections that will
get you where you need to be do not
judge them on the surface as having
nothing to do with what you really want
feel the same level of excitement moment
to moment that these opportunities bring
it is the excitement that tells you
these situations that will come along
will be connected to each other in a
path that will get you where you need to
go and the sooner you act upon these
ideas the sooner you act upon the
opportunities that excite you the most
at any given moment the sooner you will
get where you want to go in the most
unexpected ways that's the whole point the most
ways that's the whole point the most
unexpected ways will come
about understand yes I do thank you very
much pleasant dreams to you you too
allow yourself to
know if you are willing to begin to
radiate that vibration beginning this
evening of your time that within what
you call 72 of your hours you will
receive on some level the first signal
that the momentum you have started is
now echoing back to you again it may not
look like it's connected but it will
come in the form of a coincidental
opportunity that will bring excitement
with it act on it even if it appears it
is not connected act on it with
Integrity without
judgment without doubt without fear
without invalidation in total love and Total
invalidation in total love and Total
light understand yes I do Pleasant dream
thank you thank you
shoting hello Mr Bashar Mister yeah I
thought you might be interested in
knowing that I'm very excited about
being here tonight oh all right thank
you very much this is my first time you
know but it must be Deja Vu cuz I feel
I've done this before must be yeah
anyway I feel the same way even though I
know this is my first time very good a
laugh is always good for the heart yes
where's that Spirit uh anyway uh I was
listening last week to the information
you gave on the
spaceship and uh I was wondering if we
had time today maybe we could uh take a
visit maybe after your break after my break it
maybe after your break after my break it
sounds very good you've done this for me
once before you know so I feel good
about this all right yeah now uh what
was I going to say oh on your
Association uh is there a lower level of
the association or is just one solid
upper level of it there are many
variations within how civilizations May
expresss within the association but we
do not put labels on the levels every
being is equal but different to every
other being and serves as that being and
civilization can best serve to represent
the vibration they have chosen to be all
are a part of it all belong all serve in
their own way and all are seen as equals
in that light okay the only reason I
asked my channel Gregory came back for a
visit and uh I asked him if he knew you
and he says well in a way but he's in a
lower level of the association it is
only a nomenclature that may be a
representation of a frequency it is not
meant to be an invalidation or
judgmental nomenclature but simply a
technical one okay that's F in the same
way that the vibrational frequency of
the color red may be lower than the
vibrational frequency of the color
violet but it has nothing to do with the
idea of their
work I like that thank you thank you
yeah what I uh well I don't know if I
really have a question on this but I'm
back to Integrity again it looks like
I'm going to spend quite a few life
times where I'm at because I still enjoy
stealing peanuts from the grocery
store let's put it this
way the whole idea if you wish one more
technological description of Integrity
can be as follows
mhm just ensure that whatever you
do results in an equal
exchange that benefits both sides of the
interaction and comes down to a net
result of
Zero no problem I got it licked just
just as a quicky I did ask the um
garbage truck down at work excuse me
that's a lousy expression but anyway the
vendor who comes uh if I can have any
free peanuts so we flipped the coin and
I won and it just wasn't the same even
though I got the free peanuts but all
right but now that you are entitled to
the free penis you can simply suggest to
the vendor
that they forget the deal to allow you
to continue to take
them I'll check that with him but I'm
sure he's going to want me to flip the
coin for it all right but we'll see what
happens all right but anyway good day to
you and to
you Shing good evening mishar and to you
Shing good evening mishar and to you
good evening I've had uh some of my past
life's explained to me and and as they
were explained I could see how the they
were bleeding through this life
but I've never had any of my future
lives explain and I'm interested in you
know how they're affecting this present
life can you look at can be much in the
same way to some degree it can be
analogous to the story we have told of
Amy the idea that certain events may
occur in your
life that simply do give you assistance
in certain ways but do not necessarily
make it known at that moment that they
may be bleed throughs from a future self
because it is not important as to
exactly where it comes from but simply
what it does at that moment in fact
there are many bleedthrough going on all
the time for all of you from what you
call the past and the future though
those of course are very colloquial
expressions and very arbitrary
Expressions at best but the idea is that
these bleedthrough are not always
recognized as such because they will
manifest in whatever terminology serves
you best in the present that you
understand in the symbols you need to
understand in the present so you will
not always recognize a bleed through for
what it is and it is not always
important that you do so in fact many
times if you do it can actually
interfere with your ability to allow
spontaneous creation to continue in your
present however you can trust this as a
foundation since your description of the
future you is someone who has already
gone through to some degree what you're
going through now and has already
learned from that in what I will assume
is a positive way then simply to sum it
all up in one analogy a assume that all
the bleed through that happens from the
future the positive idea of your future
self all takes this kind of a
flavor you made it you did fine it's
worth it to keep going because you made
it and it's great
here that is basically the flavor that
all of those Communications take keep
going because you do know what you're
doing I know it because here I am and I
am calling back down the ages to remind
you that the things that you really knew
in your heart were the things you really
wanted to do and the things were really
the most you
were because I made
it how's that okay I can understand that
well let me give you an example I've had
a fascination with St James yes and in
talking to John he tells me that I lived
back at the time of Jesus that I knew
both himself and his brother James and
and you know from that I could see the
connection as to what this Fascination
was I don't have what your fascination
with the future I don't have any none at
all I don't seem to no then maybe you
don't have any
incarnations is that a possibility of
course let me ask you this
question if you were now to translate
into what you call Spirit
for do you feel there is any other
reason for you to Incarnate at at this
point no I don't I feel I'm going to
accomplish what I was supposed to do in
this lifetime there's your answer all
right thank you now this is not
necessarily to say that you cannot have
incarnations of a type going on in other
dimensions that would represent to you
the idea of the future but if they're
not of the same timeline in your
dimensional sense then you may not have
a sense of them relating to this life so
you may have them but they may not
relate to this particular linear format
and in that sense this may be the last
physical life you have and if that is
your feeling that you have accomplished
or will accomplish what you need to in
this life then that is your best clue
that you probably will not reincarnate
again in the typical Earth cycle
reincarnation basis okay thank you one
moment I'm not
[Laughter] [Music]
[Music]
through One Moment One Moment One Moment
we are allowed to share that it is
within our perceptive
range one
moment within a short period of time as
you count
time now I do not mean to be vague but
within any period of time that could be
anywhere from 3 days to 3 years that is
a short period of
time there will be
Awakenings within your
Consciousness that can allow you to
begin to
see how in the non-physical state after
this life there will be certain choices for
life there will be certain choices for
you in terms of being a spirit
guide and how you may even at first be
very willing after a certain amount of
willing after a certain amount of
Education in the spirit state to
actually come through a channel on
Earth that will be up to you and that is
all we are allowed to share you will be
told more by others that we have
received this information from in your
dream states you will be prepared on
that level but the choice will still be
yours if you find that exciting at that
time and interesting it is open to you
as we read your energy it seems very
likely that it is something you may
choose to do but I will not say it is
absolute because you always have free
will all right all right thank you very
much sounds exciting thank you
Shing hello Bashar and to you good
evening uh I'd like to describe a
scenario to you and get your reflection
on it all right I had a while back I
mentioned once to you that I had uh got
a perception that I had not been part of
the Orion civilization or the Atlantic
civilization at that time I had three
things that you know perceptions came to
me that I had refused to return to
Source cuz I was wanted to maintain my
individuality and I had recycled through
physicality for understanding yes
another perception I got recently is
that through the interchange of being
here the last 10 months and listening to
the 86 tapes and much the 85 tapes I
have got the understanding I came I have
completed my purpose for being in
physicality at this time if you say so
there's one very easy way to find
out I'm not ready to drop my body no all
right but just as an area of interest
for any of you the easiest way to
determine if you are through with your
physical life is to lay down close your
eyes take three deep breaths relax and
say I have completed all all that I came
to complete wait 3 minutes if you can
open your eyes you're not
[Laughter] done it's as simple as
that however do continue anyway that was
a perception I got it seems to me like
once I've completed the purpose for
being here I can set up a new purpose
and I should no longer have some
agreements that a building is going to
follow on me or something that
correct that I just totally set up my
own future right now from yes AB
absolutely absolutely and you have I
will assume learned that the idea of
going back to Source actually means that
your identity and your individuality is
strengthened not the F yes I have thank
you does that serve you yes it does well
thank you very much okay thank you be
sure Turing hi Bashar and to you good evening
Turing hi Bashar and to you good evening
how you doing
perfect on you uh pretty good Prett
pretty good yeah I want to ask you a
question I saw a ship on Tuesday evening
and I haven't seen one for a long time
it was kind of like diamond shape and it
had lights on the ends of it and there
were these two beings that you could see
like through a window and they were
golden white color I was wondering if
you could comment on them nope no no yes
okay one little comment well then could
you discuss the the activity out of
Andromeda
lately only that the energy is funneling
through the Arcturus gate because that
is one of the main input
centers of what you call your
Galaxy from the galaxy of Andromeda so
was that an Andromeda ship no comment
come
on I am not allowed you're not allowed
no no okay now again not out of any
great mystery and not out of the desire to
mystery and not out of the desire to
withhold but do remember as always we
impose upon ourselves blockages to
information when the accessing of that
information would be an interference per
se in the processes that you are all
going through okay let us simply say
this energy is being added to the scale
to help create a
balance that is all we are allowed to
say okay and one quick question uh cuz
someone I don't know two or three people
before me with bringing up colors and
lights yes I got I've been doing some
channeling lately and I got a chance ing
after seeing that ship from several of
the different civilizations that I've
had interactions with over the past
couple of years and they kept but they
were talking to me in color tones yes
but you know I really didn't understand
it we say like pleadians vibrating
positive in green and you sent the you
know color positive vibration you know
all these different colors and I didn't
energy is being added to the
scale create a balance you are only
interpreting it on that level because
there is no analytical message coming
with it oh okay well that that's what
got me is there was no they were just
sent me a color tone just think in terms
of blending once again so that was their
way of saying hello well in a sense
although it was not an absolute
directive in that way it is simply that
the whole idea now is the energy of the
association and as such as the blending
of all frequencies out of which you may
now and then depending upon your degree
of sensitivity pick up different color
vibrational tones in the electromagnetic
field but it is simply all the energy of
our radiation of our love to all of you
to assist you now as a mirror to reflect
that energy so you can reflect it from
yourselves to help balance the
scale okay could you okay clarify the
arterian gate then if I mean the only
way we can clarify that now is to Simply
say you can think of it in term terms of
a consciousness of a civilization if you
wish non-physical in nature that has
taken upon themselves the
responsibility for the
channeling of the energy from other
galaxies especially the Andromeda galaxy
to your
Galaxy MH therefore they are to some
degree responsible
for now this is a misnomer not the
control but in a sense the
overseeing of the vibration of other
energies that are funneled from Galaxy
to Galaxy and the
dispersement of those energies like a
prism into the various
frequencies that will then be sent to
the appropriate local where the
vibration is appropriate in a sense
that's what you're picking up is the
dispersement of that energy right
understand yeah that I understand well
thank you thank
you shooting
hello Bashar and to you good evening
good evening
um I've been trying to formulate in my
mind what I wanted to say oh all right
it's now been for me I think in the next
few days it'll be about 80 days since
the time we spoke last and I think now I
think I know it's taken 80 days instead
of 40 days to go through the
transformation I've gone through well
that's all right and it's what's
happened is in actual fact not meaning
to interrupt the entire transformational
cycle is actually 80 years not 40 years
and so in that sense you
are mirroring that particular idea
because it has been 40 years up to what
you call your convergence point and from
this point forward will be another 40
years until your entire planet is
actually living the example of what it
is choosing to believe in now so in that
sense 80 Days is a representation not
just of the changes an individual can go
through but also the idea of beyond the
center point of really absorbing and
integrating it so continue you're not out of
it so continue you're not out of
Step no I didn't think I was right
um I I realized now I I thought the u a
symbol of the transformation that I was
going through would be the selling of my
business and now I realize that it's neither the
and now I realize that it's neither the
selling nor the keeping of it all right
but simply the choice to create whether I
simply the choice to create whether I
sell it or whether I don't to create a
positive situation out of either of it
all right because of you has as you have
said because I say so
yes because if you know you are a
positively oriented being there is no
reason for any circumstance that occurs
in your life even if generated by
another being that has negative
intentions there is no reason for any
circumstance in your life as a
positively oriented being to manifest
anything other than a positive effect in
your
life yeah I all too often have created
myself or allowed a situation to develop
where I am quote unquote a victim all
right well that was then this is now is
that something you prefer to do from
this point forward not at all all right
and the way I've done it is by not
including my own own energy all right
and uh and perhaps choosing to agree with
uh and perhaps choosing to agree with
someone else's definition of my own yes
but this has been the thing that many of
you have done for thousands of years
absolutely buying into realities and
definitions that really have nothing to
do with who you really want to be
exactly so it is up to you are you
having a good time yes is it getting
more exciting yes well all right this is
getting much more exciting yes thank you
thank you you very much it's it's been
um it's been great it's been absolutely
great and it's totally unexpected what's
happened oh thank you totally unexpected
congratulations thank
you bye
hello
good day Bashar good evening to
you I have a very exciting Adventure
that's going to start in December the
all right I'm going to be um working on
a very big feature film in Mexico for 5
months oh all right and um I'm going to
be working primarily in the desert and I
also hope to visit the Yucatan for a
couple of weeks all right and I was
wondering if you could give me any
previews or Coming Attractions nope
nothing you give them to us since you
are so strongly connected into your flow
you share what you believe you're going
to discover well we may or may not
comment on it but you share since you
have a very direct flow going right now
can you not Fel it you know what you're
going to do so make it a statement don't
ask us tell
us well I know what I'm going to do in
terms of my work but in terms of what I
hope to accomplish what I plan to thank
you is uh is what well I'd like to have
an extraterrestrial contact in what
nature either a sighting but preferably
more direct one to one or why um I'm
curious I'd like to explore more and see
what my connections are I see what do
you think you're having now well [Music]
[Music]
I I should rephrase it to say other
extraterrestrial contexts all
contexts all
right um I enjoy our our interreaction
extremely oh all right but why do these
interactions happen um I they happen to get you to
happen um I they happen to get you to
rely on
yourself they happen to allow you to
create your world and your energy to be
a
version of our world in a sense to match
our frequency so that we can interact in
more blatant ways with
you one
moment will you still be in what you
call your yukatan area in your March
month no when will you leave that area
um probably the beginning of January one
moment where will you be in your March
month the desert probably in the
northern part of Mexico ah all
right all we are allowed to share is
that if it is likely at all it will be
then in March when you are
alone so I should keep looking at the
sky no no
you should keep doing what you need to
do keep living your life look at the sky
if you wish
to but not with expectation no the
quickest way to generate the vibration
similar enough to meet you halfway is to
stay focused in your life not on the
sky when something happens you won't
miss it you will know exactly when to look up
it you will know exactly when to look up
and you will not have to look up 1
second before nor will you look up 1
second later understand yes so continue on you
later understand yes so continue on you
have already arranged your path
accordingly March is the strongest
indicator we can give you especially if
that's when you will be in your desert
area and
Alone um the second thing I hope I plan
on accomplishing is discovering why I
have such a strong attraction to the
Mayan culture and or perhaps that is
something that you will then discover
when you are in that
area is there any method or meditation
that you can suggest follow your
nose there is more than one meaning in
that and you will find out what it is
later does that mean the sense of smell
follow your
nose that is all we can say thank do you
want me to unwrap all the Christmas
presents for you
patience was never one of my virtues you
don't need
patience remember once again that the
only reason individuals are impatient is
because they think they need patience
and they think they need patience
because they are not enjoying what is
going on now but are waiting for
something better to come along when you
are enjoying fully the life you are
living in the moment you're having far
too much fun now to care what comes
along all you know is that whatever
comes along later will be just as much
fun and it will be exactly what it needs
to be in living your life now to the
fullest in the moment at the point
you're at you will not need patience and
therefore you will not be impatient
because you will be busy having too much
fun right
now understand yes thank you thank you
so much bishar
enjoy the journey you have laid
out and enjoy walking on the lush green
carpet of your path thank you you'll be
with me in spirit I hope oh yes I plan
more hope more
hope hope and plan hope and
plan hello Bashar good evening this is
quite an experience for me oh this is my
first time me too to come and greet you
uh I have had uh a little bit of
despondence in my life lately and I
finally got my picked myself up by the
drawers and thought now this is no way
to go so
uh are you a
cab I am curious to know though in my
future am I still going to be drugged
down by the same negativity that I have
been uh in the past well that's up to
you isn't it well uh it's if it's your
if it's the other half of your life what
are you going to do I mean One Moment
One Moment One Moment what I do get up
and leave him I don't want to do that
one moment
you in any
relationship are always being of service
to the other individual by allowing them
to see reflected from you what they need
to see to learn to grow in the ways they
want to learn and in any
relationship you are being served by the
other individual to see reflected in
them the things you need to learn about
yourself to grow in the way you prefer
to be remember this that's good I like
that thank you remember
thank you remember
this being of service to other
individuals is actually more easily and
more quickly and more thoroughly
accomplished when you are being the
fullest being you prefer to be because
if you are not being fully
you then they're not in a relationship
with you anyway okay then I can take
that job I won't then allow yourself to
understand understand the following
fundamental it is the simplest thing in
creation to understand okay whatever it
is in life that really does generate
what excites you the most that is the
signal of who you are oh good act on it
with Integrity every other circumstance in
Integrity every other circumstance in
your life will automatically fall into
place as a detail under the thing that
represent presents your strongest
intention and everything that needs to
work itself out and everything that
needs to be in the life you are living
will be there in the way it needs to be
oh that's fantastic it is a very simple
mechanism and it always always always
works then I'm excited about this and
I'm going to do it there's one other
little thing yes animals seem to like me
I've always been curious why well you
radiate a very jovial frequency oh
really oh
yeah and also you have spent many lives
in direct communion with nature in that
way oh and they sense that you have been
a Healer many times in that sense and
they sense that oh that's what and they
sense the warmth of your heart and are
drawn to it and I'm always able to see a
deer when we go to our Mountain place I
always get to see a deer they're just
beautiful animals and I always get to
see them oh thank you and remember they
always get to see you
I hope so thank you so much well thank
you dear
one at this time you may
all I say continue
good evening bash and to you good
evening um I occasionally hear and a
number of people hear a relatively high
pitched tone very steady and Pitch uh
what is it it can be a few things one
thing it can be for many of you is a
sensitivity to the electrical activity
within your own body from time to time
when it achieves a certain resonating
reinforcing standing wave it can trans
translate in certain ways along your
nerve patterns to create the idea of a
sound in your ear another idea is that
sometimes many of you will be sensitive
to what is called the prime frequency
the background frequency of creation
itself especially now that many more of
you becoming more sensitive to
electromagnetic waves and you are
expanding your senses along that line
and are becoming more sensitive to the
very centered vibration your signature
vibration the vibration that represents
who and what you are as a Consciousness
sometimes that is what you are hearing
in its sense it
represents a
level a tone an
orientation that allows you to
understand you are aligning in many ways
and that you are expanding your senses
in many ways it gives you a line of
sight so to speak a clearness of
Direction so to speak it is as a needle
that lets you know when you are to some
degree hitting a mark
and passing through a particular
vibratory gate a vibratory doorway that
means you are now going on to another
level you follow me yes does that mean
that at times when I hear it more
frequently it means that I am more in
alignment or there it also can mean you
are processing more yes okay the tone in
a
sense is
actually your recognition in auditory
terms in vibrational terms of of what is
the Blended tone that represents what
used to be the difference between the
old and the new
u in other words the old U the idea of
the old U has a certain vibration the
idea of the new you has a certain
vibration when you finally allow there
to
be a blending those vibrations reinforce
each other in such a way as to create a
central tone that allows you to
recognize it as the blending of one
dimension with another a crossover tone
you follow me yes does that assist you
yes does it make a difference I mean
sometimes it's in my right ear sometimes
in the left does that mean sometimes it
can be representative of the direction
you are approaching the blending from
whether through classically speaking an
intuitive side or an analytical side it
can be representative of that sometimes
it is simply an echo vibration in a
sense doesn't necessarily have a direct
connection to exactly how you approached
it it can be representative of also many
other different things but generally
speaking it can represent the direction
from which you approached this
particular blending through this
particular processing okay thank you well thank
processing okay thank you well thank
you
sharing good evening Melle and to you
good evening in a session you had told
me that I had a Lifetime on your planet
I and I was wondering if it was past
present present or future in your
terminology it would be future thank you
it is however contemporary as far as I
am
concerned thank you um and I I also um
and One Moment One Moment not finished
yet okay bye it is also a life that
comes and goes and is not in your terms
firmly fixed in our world it is a great
traveler and spends a lot of time in
sirious energy as well in Arcturus
energy as well in pleadian energy as
well and in various other civilizations
as well it is a great Explorer thank you
well thank you and
I I also want to know why um you uh you
gave me the nickname mermaid and
Starfish because it has to do
with adanan connections that you also
have in your past that was your
recognition back then in those lives of
the connection that you are talking
about now from this point of view the
Stellar connection
starfish and the idea of mermaid being
the serious connection the amphibious
connection through the dolphin energy
especially in Atlantean times thank you
well thank you thank you sharting
good evening Bashar Andrew you good
evening Bashar I teach uh lectures on um
food and nutrition how exciting yes it
is and uh I was interested in your
reflection on food as it relates to
color and vibration and in turn how it
relates to the body oh my oh
yes well if I still ate I might attend
one of your
lectures however in our society at this
time we absorb the energy of light
directly that can give you your first
clue food in that sense the solid
sustenance you still create upon your
planet for food to be the symbol of
sustaining yourself through
materiality is in of itself like any
physical object simply a representation
of different vibrational States and to
some degree the color will
represent the balance point of the food
so to speak speak now in general
therefore those things that you call
Green in coloration in general in
general for there are always exceptions
and always specific differences in many
different ways but in general the green
Foods represent in and of themselves
obviously enough the strongest and most
balanced connection to your natural
energy state that which is represented
as an extension of the Earth itself
that is why the idea of vegetable
sustenance will allow you to experience
yourself on a vibrational level that is
light in nature and very strongly
connected to Nature and clear seeing you
follow me so far perfect there will be
variations to some degree on this theme
especially in what you call the yellow
white range for recognize that many of
the things you call Staples in your
Society are almost always yellow white
the idea of what you call Rice the idea
of what you call corn in that sense
these things these ideas in general will
represent connections into specific
dimensionalities of Consciousness
especially the emotional body itself the
emotional body is solidly affixed within
that vibration of the yellowish white as
far as the food substance is Con concern
and it is also connected to what you
would call very spiritual
aspects and that is why much of those
foods are in your terms revered or
ritualized many times because it
represents the spirit idea of the
essence of your Consciousness as a
physical being the substances that are
white whitish yellow in nature are not
very far removed from their Natural
Energy State at all
they are very simplistic in structure
generally speaking you follow me yes now
in no way shape or form are we saying
that you must force yourself to be more
spiritual by forcing yourself to ingest
something that your body perhaps will
not derive enough sustenance from and
only those things but the idea generally
is that as you elevate your vibrational
level you will usually find yourself
losing the urge for something of denser
sustenance eventually as a society you will
eventually as a society you will
primarily subsist upon the idea mostly
of vegetable formats with a little bit
of fruit
format and basically almost nothing
else in time you will subsist directly
on energy as we do
now you follow me yes I do um a question
about the green Foods yes um green
relating also to the heart chakra
vibration uh to the green foods and the
fact that we're moving into a heart
vibration um or do they correlate is but
is more than just the idea of the heart
which still carries the vibration also
of a Rosy idea to some degree more
associated with many different forms of
the fruit rather than the vegetable but
they are polarities to some degree of
each other and not meaning it in the
sense that they are actually opposites
but they are complimentary in certain
ways that is what is symbolized by what
you call the crystal your pink and green
turmaline the transition and the
junction of the heart and also the
crystallized idea of the etheric
Consciousness the nature Consciousness
that you are now crystallizing by the
emerald vibration it is the emerald
vibration of your Earth itself that
gives rise to the power represented
through the green food substances the
clarity of focus in that sense yes it
has to do with the heart but the green
itself is not a direct representation of
the hard energy as such except in a
different way on a different level
altogether dimensionally speaking which
is something we will not go into at this
time you follow me yes thank you does
this assist you yes very much well thank
you very
much shooting hi bash hi thank you very
much for um allowing us to communicate
with you oh well thank you very much for
allowing us to communicate with all of
you I know we enjoy it imens
good so do I oh thank you um I feel as
though I'm kind of repeating myself this
is the third time I've been up here to
you but it is always the first uh-huh um
uh-huh yeah yeah
um okay but yes what what I feel as
though I need some more specific answers
on what is you on what really excites me
on doing what really excites me the most
yes um the last time I spoke with you
um the last time I spoke with you
um we
discussed not having to um make a living
in the ways that didn't excite me
anymore yes so consequently what
happened is um the next few days I got a
whole bunch of jobs that didn't really
excite me no right and and um I've
really had uh a lot of problems with my
friend problems yeah well I I look at
them as problems why why not look at
them as
experiences because I don't like them oh
I don't like not being able to pay my
rent and my bills I'm not used to it oh
you're not used to it no oh all right um
I was on workman's compensation for
couple of years 2 and a half years and
after an accident and I was able to
pretty much get inside of myself and and
grow to know myself more I had a lot of
time yes and then I guess I chose for
that experience to not be there anymore
because I gave a whole bunch of the
money away all right and to where now I
have to work and the same as everyone
else has to but I've been working in
ways that I don't prefer to
okay what do you want to
do well what I really want to do is be
of service to people and help them to
understand um more of the reality and
the truth of themselves well in what way
um I wish to be a channel oh what in
what way remember channeling is doing
anything you really love to do when it
comes right down to it the thing that I
really enjoy to do right now is open
myself up psychically
and yes yes yes yes yes it's been a
really slow process all right all right
never mind that never mind what it's
been what is it going to be
now well I I just want it to speed up
and all right all right how will you do
it
how will you design your expression of
channeling in what way do you wish to do
it um I wish to work with people on like
a psychological psychic yes yes on a
oneon-one and in group yes all right and also
and in group yes all right and also
through
writing through writing well all right
up to this point and especially at this
point I'm having so much worry about
money in survival and paying my rent to
the point that this month I don't know
if I'm going to have even a place to
live at the end of this month all right
um exciting isn't it yeah it's exciting
and it's terrifying at the same time you
know I'm I feel like I'm a nervous wreck
and I feel like I can't concentrate on
what I really want to do because I'm so
worried about the money and I see oh
maybe it's not an issue of concentration
maybe it's an issue of allowance
what do you
mean what I mean
is do you really
trust that what excites you the most
will support
you I guess I don't because it hasn't
manifested but you haven't really done
it
yet have you no I haven't because I
don't know where to begin I all right I
don't how do you see what kind of a
picture do you have in your imagination
when you see yourself doing the thing
you say you want to do
describe it to
me are you interacting directly
physically are you touching people are
you writing are you sitting in a chair
are you lying down are you flying around
what are you
doing um different things depending on the
um different things depending on the
person on the are you in any particular
kind of a place are you out in a meadow
are you under the ocean where are
you I see my myself more in a room with
candles
and yes music
and may I ask you a question yes thank
you are there any
places of this nature that you are aware
of that you could work out of yes have
you discussed with them the opportunity
of doing
so yes and
I just um
yes I guess I'm afraid because I just
don't know how to begin or how to start
and I all right but we have just discuss
the idea of a start once again are there
places like this that are set up to
allow you to do these kind of things
that you could be working
through where there is a constant flow
of individuals coming in seeking out
just the type of Services you wish to
provide and could you not be one of the
individuals in one of these places
providing those
services and have you talk to such
places and discuss with them the idea of
allowing you to work out of those places
to be of service to those individuals
who come in seeking that help yes or no
yes I've touched on the idea all right
touched on it yes have you been really
convincing to them that that's something
you really want to do
no why not if you say that's what really
excites you then why do you not come
across to them as if that really is
true um is that what you really want to
do do you really want to be of service
in that way I want to be of service in
that way do you want to be of service in that
way do you want to be of service in that
way or is there some other way I don't
know if there's some other way that is
is that the one that you are aware of
right now that seems the most exciting
that's the one that seems to be most
exciting I thought I thought at one time
that the way that this was going to
transpire is that
I yes I have played with the idea of
being an actress I was trained to or
played with the idea of being an actress
yeah because I'm it's it doesn't excite
me as it doesn't excite me to the point
that I I will pay the price that many
individuals will W whoa whoa
whoa pay what price the games and the
prices that people see that other people
that other people play in this town so
you are telling me that your definition
of being an actress means you cannot
Envision it happening any other way that
you have to play those games that you
must buy into those definitions and that
you cannot imagine it could happen any
other way for you is that what you're
saying well I I've gone in and out of
the acting business for 10 years and yes
all I would get is people hitting on me
and wanting something in return for yes
and I just wasn't interested I'm not
interested in those kind of games all
right so I just figured that are you
interested in being an
actress yeah I'm interested in being an
actress but I'm not prepared to go
through going to parties and all the
social and all that crap all
right I'm why do you have
to why can you be not an actress without
all of
that because um yes here comes another
definition now this is only a
definition because what it it
just because that's the way you've been
taught it has to be yeah that's the way
I've been taught it has to be and all
right We R I I like to spend a lot of
time in meditation and being quiet I
don't like parties I like then don't go
why go I don't all right then and so so
what's happening is I'm becoming not an
actress anymore because you don't go to
parties because I don't go to parties
and because I would never go to bed with
the directors and yes but if your
definition if your ingrained definition
of an actress
is simply that you have to do those
things in order to be an actress then
you're always going to attract
circumstances that only give you that
particular route to travel if you
redefine the idea that you can be an
actress without those things then you
will start discovering other
routes you will not discover any other
route to walk through until you change
the definition of what you think you
must be as an
actress if you simply buy into the fact
that that's the only type of offerings
you will get in being an actress then
that's the only type of offerings you
will get start changing your definition
of what you think you need to go through
or what you think you have to go through
in order to be an
actress be the actress you want to be
include all the definitions of anything
that has to do with being that actress
in the way you want those definitions to
be do not buy into the idea that in
order to be an actress you have to go
through this doorway or deal with that
individual there are many individuals
within what you call that business on
your planet that do function within the
idea you call Integrity I haven't found
any that's because you're not the
vibration that believes they
exist because you have been brought up
to think that these other type of
individuals are the only type you will
find it is your strongest fear and that
means it's your strongest belief your
strongest fear is your strongest belief
don't forget and if that's all you can
believe you'll run into that's all
you'll see the other ones will be
invisible to you because you're not
operating on their
wavelength they can't find you you can't
find them because you're not the same
frequency because you fear that the
individuals that do not represent your
wavelength will be easier to find but
understand if they are easier to find
they are on your wavelength because of
the fear itself that they will be the
only individuals you will find so if
that's all you're finding and and you
don't prefer it change your definition
of what you think you ought to be change
the frequency of the definition of what
it is to be an
actress and then you will discover and
attract the individuals who operate on
the same level all it is is your
definition that's all it
is understand mhm that's all it
is it's that easy it's that simple but
until you believe it you will get the
same thing now
thing now
there are also now that you have shared
this idea there are also individuals
present this night of your time who
while they may not be able to directly
assist you can give you some suggestions
mhm and so they can simply interact with
you when this interaction is over for
the evening just having put out what you
desire having taken the time to express
the willingness of what your integrity
is having stood on your own two feet as
you have just done and stated your
preference publicly is one way to
radiate the frequency that will allow
all others on the same level to come up
to you and interact with you on that
level understand yeah I understand it
will make a difference if you believe it
will MH if you believe it won't it
won't that I promise
you understand do can I ask you a question
understand do can I ask you a question
brief um do you perceive that this is
the pathway
that I originally saw
saw my
life acting is a very strong one of them
yes and understand this your pathway
your purpose is simply being as fully as
you can be anything you want to be that
it excites you to be the things you do
in your life the projects the goals are
not the purposes of your life they are
the methodologies you are choosing to
express the purpose of your life which
is simply live the life to the fullest
that's the purpose of all of your lives
how you go about it they are not the
purposes they are the
methods MH understand so the method is
up to you anything you do that is the
most exciting thing you can think of to
do will be your method for fulfilling
the purpose of this life because
remember even though you are a
reincarnational being you have never
been this you before you will never be
this you again the you you are now only
has one life to live live it to the
fullest by being who you prefer to be be
that vibration and that is what will be
vibration and that is what will be
reflected in your life but how you get
there is up to you if the idea of being
an actress is the most exciting
way be the actress you want to be on all
the levels of that definition
remember that acting is
channeling because when
you act the part of another
personality if you are really doing it
the way it was intended to be done you
literally are another person while
you're that part and I do not mean
figuratively MH you may think you look
the same but you are another person
because a person is not who are what you
are it is an artificial construct and an
artificial projection of your
Consciousness and you can be any person
you want to be regardless of whether you
maintain a continuity of outward
appearance or not and yet many of you do
realize that when an actor or an actress
is really the part they do even look
different acting is
channeling any form of creative
expression in that sense is the positive
definition of channeling MH incorporate
these definitions into one stand on your
own two feet State what you prefer and
to put it very colloquially in your own
terminology don't take any
Guff I won't I refuse to I'd rather that
doesn't mean that you cannot expose
yourself to certain environments and
allow you to meet the people that it is
necessary for you to meet in those
environments if sometime perceive that a
particular environment doesn't contain
the vibration at all that is the
vibration you are then don't go but
recognize that you will attract yourself
to whatever environments that you need
to to meet who you need to meet that is
on the same level and if there are other
individuals in that environment that
aren't you will not interact with them
mhm understand yeah I understand they
simply will not be attracted in that
sense and even if they are the light you
shine will determine whether they
maintain the capability of involving you
in a dialogue or not for the second they
see if they are not acting with
Integrity the light that is in your eyes
they will not be able to stand in its
Radiance and they will make some excuse
and go away yeah yeah relax give forth
who you are shine be that person thank
you thank you
sharing hello B and good evening to you
U there so many things I want to know
now I'm not sure which I want to ask but
you know them all okay remember that a
question is an answer removed from
yourself okay on New Year's Day uh
coming back from Las Vegas we're at
Palmdale and I and a friend and uh her
little girl saw four flying saucers yes
and uh
it seemed that I communicated with them
yes I asked them what they were doing
there and they said they were changing
the molecular structure of the people so
they could stand the new age vibration
yes that is called identification okay
um I just wondered if you have any
comment on that or well simply that from
time to time assessments will be made
identifications will be taken and the
idea simply is that a frequency will be
sent and it will be observed how closely
it is
matched to see whether or not
individuals in your Society are allowing
themselves to be more equal and whatever
there are open doors that you are
willing to allow the energy to come into
energy will be sent to Aid and assist
you in those adjustments but it will not
be done for you it will be sent to you
and if you have allowed there to be open
doors you will take that energy whether
consciously or unconsciously and make
the adjustments that are necessary to
Aid and assist in the acceleration so
that you become more acclimatized to the
changes that are going on throughout the
electromagnetic field of your
planet that is a quite common practice
and quite common occurrence all over
your
Globe does that satisfy you yes it does
thank you well thank you very
much
Shing good evening and to you good
evening thank you in the expression blessed
expression blessed
are and we hear the different
descriptions of people who are blessed
does that
reflect the choice of a
the choice of a
person choosing what is most exciting
for himself yes in a sense [Music]
yes in a sense although on the
fundamental level the phrase blessed are
refers to the fact that you are all
blessed in a sense that you are all made
out of living
light my but the idea yes of recognizing
a particular frequency of a particular
individual and saying blessed are it is
a recognition that that individual is
completely within alignment to the
vibration of Harmony which means in that
sense they are doing the thing that
excites them the most to do yes help me
please to understand that
yes how a person who would be doing
how a person who would be doing
something that seems very negative like
Sorrowing blessed are The Sorrowing yes
how is
that well thank you I will tell you good
now the idea as we have discussed many
times of what you call Sorrowing is
simply the negative polarity of release
laughter is the positive side Sorrowing
can have a positive effect if it is used
as a centering as a release as a
positive processing that is The
Sorrowing that is referred to it is not
the idea that it is preferable to choose the
idea that it is preferable to choose the
negativity but the idea is that if
individuals know they are strong enough
to have done so if they simply do not
know there is any other way to do it and
they have still chosen the idea that the
only way they have to Center themselves
is through the idea of The
Sorrowing then they are still learning
in a positive way they are still getting
to the point they want to get to even if
they do it through the idea of the
suffering in that sense no one has to
suffer but if someone has as their
strongest intention the idea of a
positive notion and yet they simply do
not believe it can be done through any
other way other than The Sorrowing well
their strongest intention still means
that their Sorrowing is being put to
positive use understand great does that help it
use understand great does that help it
does thank you well thank
you at this
timing we would
suggest that you all become
comfortable what shall be done in this
interaction will be the idea of the
projection of your imagination
Consciousness into one of what would be
called our mothercraft our city
ships for frame of
reference its ancient name would
translate in your language as the solar
wind it is approximately one mile in
your terms of
length and contains several tens of
thousands of
beings Now understand that while your idea of
Now understand that while your idea of
physicality may seem seem seem seem to
be focused upon your
Earth the projection of your imagination
Consciousness does not mean that what
you are about to experience is quote
unquote just your imagination in the
invalidation sense what you are
experiencing is real because you're your
imagination is real and indicative of
real dimensions of reality even though
not all of them that you imagine May
directly physically apply to your planet
but they are no less real and your
experience will be no less real and it
will create changes within you that will
manifest in your lives in ways that
benefits the life you are living on your
terminology therefore three deep and loving full
therefore three deep and loving full
breaths your eyes may be open they may
be closed that is up to
you but allow yourself to feel the
centeredness of your being and
float in that space that allows you to
know there have been times in your life
when you have connected to all the
different levels allow this to be such a
time and whether your analytical mind
seems to tell you it is not happening or
not know that it is
and now as you continue to breathe
softly lovingly warmly cooly and gently
and strongly with
conviction and
certainty picture in your mind's eye or
with your physical
eye the room you are
in picture all of yourselves together
pict picture yourselves as individuals
picture yourselves at the same time as a
collective as one
individual with many
faces imagine now that all of you no
matter what physical configuration you
are in to each other are now
surrounded by a thin translucent blue
white crystallin energy
shell this will will be the ship that
elevates you up to the
mothercraft let it solidify around you
if it remains ethereal in nature so be
it whatever your imagination dictates
the image to be shall be the image that
works best for
you invalidate none of it your
imagination knows what it is
doing feel the energy within this
crystallin bubble no matter what its shape or
bubble no matter what its shape or
SI feel the raw thrumming power the
pulsing beat as this ship aligns with the
beat as this ship aligns with the
primary fundamental vibration of space
and time itself as it becomes the very
idea of the vibration of light and space
and time of existence itself it is
powering up rising in pitch and as it
does so the room that you may imagine
yourself seeing through the hall begins
to dissolve into a gray Mist a limbo
state of all that is and
nothingness and as you float
together imagine the pitch of your craft
to change Higher and Higher and yet at
the same time a deep thrumming
Foundation increases in strength and you
rise and rise and Rise until you look
down and you see
space and the stars and your earth below
shining and bright in the light of your
son and as you rise and rise and Rise
you look up and you see the long
cylindrical shape of the city ship of the solar wind
shape of the city ship of the solar wind
as it hangs over your world between your
Earth and your moon
and you approach and it grows in your
field of vision and you are all
breathing as one and you feel the
excitement and the anticipation of
meeting old friends and new
friends as we open our hearts and our
arms and our minds to greet you and
welcome you aboard you blend and merge
and pass through the hull
itself and you find you are surrounded
by a bright white
space in this space and out of this
space faces May emerge and may sink back
into the whiteness eyes may open and
close and disappear figures may come out
and solidify or they may in that sense
pass into ethereal
Mists and as you recognize that you are
aboard you sense the beating of the
hearts of all the beings on The Craft
and you feel the heartbeat of your own
heart matching that
frequency and as you match that
vibration beat after beat after beat
after beat the shell of your ship
dissolves and you find yourself floating
in that brilliant
whiteness and you merge into the energy
and various beings take you by the hand
or take you by the heart
and smile and we welcome
smile and we welcome
you and now
allow your
imagination to explore any portion of
the ship you desire you will pass
through any Hull any bulkhead any floor
any level
level
see what you are simply curious to
see we will give you simply a moment on
your own or together or with
friends on the ship to
explore and
remember that you are all connected to
each other and you all feel the
experiences of each other as you
discover the images on the
ship remember that your imagination May
create what you
see in your pictorial Mind's Eye to look
very familiar to you it may choose
symbols that you are used to to
represent what you are seeing do not
think you are not on the ship if you see
something that does not appear that it
should be on the ship you are seeing it
but with the eyes of interpretation that
is all right the essence will sink into
you and now to your heart's Delight
simply explore
understand that you are absorbing all
that you need to
absorb that which you feel you do not
have time to explore
now will be continued in your dream
realities you are always
welcome now that you feel the
vibration familiarize yourself with it
you can always
return and for now
feel the connective link the connective
thread the connective chord that all of
you have to each other the agreement and
the bond of your Brotherhood and your
bond of your Brotherhood and your
Sisterhood of your being hood of Earth
and collect yourselves back together in
the spot in which you
arrived and as you
breathe and feel the difference of the
energy gather the shell of your craft
around you once again its sparkling blue
white crystallin brilliance
and receive the gift of our love and
allow yourself to sink back through the
hull out into
space and watch as the solar wind
recedes and look down and behold the
beauty of the gem of your
planet its beautiful blue and white
Brilliance and feel the love
feel the love for the ship that is your
world and embrace
it and love
it and
live and as you settle back down onto
the surface of your world and allow the
surroundings of your room to resolidify
around the outside of your crystallin
craft and allow the crystallin craft to
dissolve into the structure of the
room and to dissolve into the very
center of your
being
understand you have been aboard that
ship you will interpret it in the coming
days in whatever way shape or form you
need to but the experience is
real you will take from it what you need
we give to you really the
energy of our love and our
being and we thank you for
coexisting within the dream we have
co-created to
share as you take three deep
breaths allow yourself to feel the
connection with the Earth deep into its
core and your connection to the Heavens
to the
farthest star you are beings of celestial
star you are beings of celestial
light you are
unlimited you are
everywhere all that
all that
is is
all of us
together space and time
are your
definitions live within the center of
your being live within the now within
the moment in love and light and all
space and time and
distance shall be
compressed into
nothingness feel the vibration that is
the excitement of the being that you
are you are now not the same beings that
you were at the beginning of this
interaction W
up and now live
how'd it go great [Applause]
[Applause]
excellent thank you all very much for
being here tonight some still up on the
ship I think for e for