And I'll say good day to you all as you
know time to exist.
Allow us to begin this interaction, this
day of your time with the laying down of
a few
foundations regarding the subjects of
your choice, electromagnetism and
crystalline formation.
So as you say, get out your
notebooks. We will begin with the idea
of the fundamentals of
electromagnetism. Blending this into the
understanding of the patterning of
energy, the vibratory frequencies of
energy that you call crystallin
structure, electromagnetism.
Energy as you understand it in that way
that you call light or
electromagnetism is basically the first
step of the translation of what we refer
to as the
template of all creation into physical
reality. what you call energy, the
electromagnetic field, light itself, is
the first manifestation of that prime
fundamental fabric of existence in
physical terms. Before anything can be
created that you would recognize as a
material object, as an object made of
matter, physical matter, it must first
be
rendered into the substructure of
energy. The idea simply is is that when you
The idea simply is is that when you
consider the creation of all and you
stop and realize that consciousness
itself is in a sense what all creation
is made of. Then you can begin to
recognize that light being the fabric,
the background structure of materiality
is one of the ways that consciousness
itself has of expressing itself. is one
of the frequencies that consciousness
exists upon. In a sense, electromagnetism or
upon. In a sense, electromagnetism or
what may be referred to as an
electromagnetic effect, for that in a
sense is all it is. It isn't a force per
se. It is an
effect. When you think of it that way,
it can be summed up by definition as
follows. that electromagnetism, the
electromagnetic effect, what you
experience as electromagnetism in your
physical reality is the result of
consciousness intersecting interacting
with itself in a particular
way in one of the different phases of
selfawareness that it has at its
disposal to interact at. All creation,
all reality is a matter of
consciousness intersecting with itself,
interacting with itself in various
modality, from various perspectives.
Let's say approaching itself again and
again and again and again from various
directions of
self-reflectivity. The first key to
creation itself simply is the principle
of
selfawareness. First, there is the one
out of which all is created.
But before, I will use your terminology
now in a very colloquial manner because
we do not really perceive that there
really was a before, a now, and an
after. The idea of a beginning and an
ending are idiomatic to your physical
reality. They do not empirically exist.
But I will use the terminology for now
so that things will not become too
confused. The idea is therefore that
first there was the one. Before there
was the creation, the one had to
manifest the first segregation, the
first split of itself into something
other than a homogeneous oneness. This
split occurred at the moment the one
became self-aware because self-awareness
is a reflective phenomena and
automatically implies that you have a
this and a that against which the
reflection can bounce back to you for
your awareness of self. This can happen
within consciousness itself. And this
prime first moment of
selfawareness in other words what is
meant by the phrase I am that I am is
simply the idea that the I am became
aware that it was the idea in and of
itself of knowledge of existence
awareness of self created the explosion
within the I am that all of you and all
of us call creation of all the different
things All the variances, all the
different levels and realms and
dimensions of experience, all of this
that exists, infinity, all the different
infinite dimensions of reality that
exist, all came into explosive existence
at once with the first realization that
the infinite had of its own existence.
Now electromagnetism therefore in a
sense is one of the frequencies of this
explosion, one of the different core
that was created out of the overall
harmonics of all the vibrations of the
primal energy that there are. And
electromagnetism is the first step to
the laying of the foundation and the
creation of what you call solid material
physical reality. It is the chord that
underscores the total existence of
material experience. It is the
groundwork, the template, the fabric out
of which all materiality is
crystallized literally. Therefore, you can think of
literally. Therefore, you can think of
it if you wish as an energy. You can
think of it if you wish as a force.
Though these are very approximate
terms, we find that there are not many
terms in that way that could define the
idea of electromagnetism specifically
except to say it is in itself
light. It is in itself a frequency of
consciousness. It is a frequency of
awareness. Now an interesting thing
occurs because you lay the foundation
called electromagnetism
electromagnetism
light for which all materiality will
then come. There is a reflection an echo in
come. There is a reflection an echo in
physical materiality of the original
self-awareness that created it all. This
reflection, this echo of the original
creation happens when the consciousness
you are
intersects let's say at a particular
vector. The electromagnetic field of the
physical universe and creates what you
call a physical mirror of consciousness.
This physical mirror of consciousness is
what you are familiar with as your mind,
your mentality, your
thoughts. These things, your mind, your
mentality, your thoughts are the
physical echo of the consciousness you
are, of the self-aware being that you
are. They are the physical
versions of your self-aware
existence. In a sense, you can say they
are one step removed, so to speak, or
many steps removed if you will break up
the idea of the electromagnetic spectrum
into many different frequencies. But it
is in a sense simply one overall
step that allows you to be able to
experience yourself as the idea of
physical materiality. Without that
intersection, without the laying of that
electromagnetic groundwork, you could
not experience yourself as focused
beings in the sense of physical focus.
in the sense that you can isolate and
compartmentalize your life in linear
flow. A before, a now, an after, a
beginning, an end, a middle. All of
these concepts, all of these perceptions
are the result of the fact that you have
created your consciousness to exist
first in what you call the
electromagnetic vibration. For this
electromagnetic vibration is constructed
in a particular crystallin lattice work
pattern that is tetrahedral in nature.
This crystallin lattice work pattern of
constantly interacting I'll say energy
voids or particles if you
wish determines the
determines the
rate and the flow and the clustering
properties of the electromagnetic field.
Vibrations that course through the
electromagnetic blanket in a sense are
the vibrations that are indicative of
the collective pulse of your collective
consciousness constantly arranging
itself in different relationships to
itself manifesting these different
relationships as all the different
experiences of physical materiality you
have not only in your immediate lives
but all throughout what you call your
physical universe.
Everything let's say above the
electromagnetic spectrum in the
consciousness field itself all exists
simultaneously. But because by the very
definition of physical reality you have
created linear time. Therefore you must
experience that simultaneity stretched
out in linear terms in space which
creates the idea of distance and in time
which creates the idea of before and
after. This is simply the laying out of
a grid, a representational grid, a
template if you will.
Now crystals in that sense are now
becoming aware by you as more representative of
aware by you as more representative of
the prime matrix out of which all
reality is created physically than
almost any other tool you have
used because they are in that sense very
very close to the original energy state.
There is not much
removal from the energy state into the
physical state in terms of manifesting
as a crystallin form. They are almost
purely representative of the template
itself of the structure itself of the
fabric itself of physical materiality.
And that is why there is such a strong
attraction to them now because you are
dealing with the very core of
understanding of what you are as a
consciousness. And so your tools are
becoming more
representative of the primal state in
which your consciousness exists. The
first recognition you will have of this
being material being and being used to
being material beings will be the
electromagnetic field and crystallin
structures because a crystallin
structure is in a sense almost nothing
more than a solidified electromagnetic
field. That is in a sense all they are.
They are very primally
representative of the electromagnetic
template out of which all materiality is
created by your consciousness. So you
can gain to some degree great insights
into your absolute nature of
consciousness by perhaps associating
with the frequencies that are
represented by crystallin structures in
your physical world. Now before we
continue, do allow me to remind each and
every one of you that everything in the
physical world is a projection of your
consciousness. The crystals do not have
power you do not. They are reflections
literally of the power you are. But
because for many thousands of your years
you have segregated yourself in your
idea of yourself from being the creator
of your
reality. Then sometimes now out of your
habits and your patterns. You still need
a tool to remind you of that connection.
And the crystals have been instrumental
in functioning as catalysts as triggers
to remind you of who and what you are of
what the power is that you have. And to
remind you that you yourselves are your
own master crystal. and are responsible
for the activation in a sense of all the
energy you feel flows through crystallin
forms. They are consciousness in and of
themselves of course since they are made
out of the same electromagnetic matrix
that is the result of your consciousness
but they are reflections of you and they
can help remind you of who and what you
are. So in all the discussions we will
have about the abilities and powers of
crystals do understand that we are doing
that talking in that way for the sake of
convenience and that always always we
mean to say that these powers and
abilities we are talking about are
actually reflections of your own
abilities and not something that the
crystal inherently has without you
understand so far.
Therefore, let us
delineate what may be called the five
basic categories of
crystal. One, they will be
reflective and I mean this in another
way. We shall delve into this in a
moment. Two, they may be
refractive. Three, they may be
transmittive. Four, they may be
storative. Five they may be I'll put this under the
Five they may be I'll put this under the
general heading of T's which means
attunitive now number one
reflective crystals in this sense more
than just the idea of reflecting what
you call physical life can be utilized
by each and any one of you to truly open
up more awareness of the portions of
yourself that you have forgotten. They
can be in that sense selfreflective. You
can use them, in other words, certain
types of crystals that you may be
attracted to to awaken yourself to
different portions of the idea of your
consciousness by using them as mirrors
to get in touch with things in
meditative states that you have placed
deep within you. So that the crystals
can perhaps awaken in you an image, a
reflection, an echo of who and what you
are as a expanded being to put you back
in touch with that self, that portion of
yourself, that aspect of yourself so
that you can integrate it, deal with it,
learn from it and become in your terms
more expanded, more whole. So crystals
in that way in a meditative in a psychic
sense can interact with you in a very
reflective way reflecting back to you
what you put out for it to
reflect. Number two
refractive. They can be refractive in
the sense that again on what you may
call an emotional and a psychic level,
you can project your consciousness
through crystallin form and have that
consciousness refracted into any number
of interdimensional spaces in that sense
to perceive other alternate aspects of
yourself that may not immediately apply
to this reality such as what you call
past lives, future lives, alternate
realities or dimensions of experience
functioning psychically. In that way
that is where the idea comes from of
what you have recognized in ancient
times as the crystal sphere. It is in
that sense refractive allowing the
consciousness of the individual to
perceive through it and have that beam
of consciousness bounce off in whatever
direction represents the information you
seek. Finding that level or frequency
that represents the alternate dimension
that all coexists with you right here
and now. But tuning into that frequency
in the same way you would switch a dial
on your radio device to pick up another
program. that is in that sense
refractive. It can be
transmittive in a sense to some degree.
This means simply refractive in the
opposite direction. It means that
information itself, consciousness
itself, other levels of energy and
entities themselves can flow through a
crystal to a specific being for the
purpose of the transmitt of information.
In that
way they can be
stored which means once again that
either in your terms coming or going
information the matrix of information
all knowledge can in a sense be stored
within what you call a crystallin matrix
for retrieval or transmitt at any
particular point in time before now or
after. As you say, crystals in
themselves represent holographic
matrices and the totality of all
knowledge in a sense can be represented
in any crystallin form because by
definition they represent the
fundamental structure of existence
itself and therefore all information of
all existence can be tapped quote
unquote at any point within the totality
of existence. And this brings us into
the fifth step. The key aspect of
crystal. The attunitive aspect of
crystal. Projection in that sense is
what this can be called. Projection in
the sense that as you attune to a
particular vibration of a crystal. As
you allow a crystal to attune to your
vibration, you can use it in a sense to
quote unquote tunnel or open a gate or a
doorway into any other dimension of
experience. Now crystals that are used
as keys can also perhaps use many of the
other attributes we have already
discussed. For example, what you are
familiar with as the crystallin skulls
that have been created in your society.
Not only are keys in that sense, not
only projectors in that sense, but they
are also transmittive and also they are
highly highly highly reflective in the
sense that they were used to open up
dimensional doorways for certain groups
of cultures and people on your planet to
go from one dimension to another. And
they were left behind as the keys to
those gates. But they are very
reflective keys in the sense that the
only way to open one of those gates is
to look directly into the eyes of that
crystal and be shown all the different
things you may have suppressed within
yourself. But if you cannot face those
things and integrate those things that
you are shown, then a great fear may
rise within you. A fear of the different
portions of yourself that you are not
willing to integrate. And that fear will
change your vibration to one that cannot
possibly open the door and enter the
dimension where those other beings have
gone. So in this way you can have cumulative
So in this way you can have cumulative
effects as well imparted to many
different crystallin form depending upon
the reason the purposes the tool that
the crystal has been created to
be. The idea also of what you may call
the transmittive form of crystal also
has to do directly with simply what you
would call raw power itself. In other
words, the ability of crystallin forms
to simply transmit the pure
electromagnetic light which depending
upon the configuration and the
vibrational frequency of the crystal can
actually set up a vibration either of
light or of sound that will then create
a particular atmosphere in which many
changes can take place or in which work
itself can be accomplished.
similar and analogous to the idea of
what you call the early crystallin forms
you use to create your laser devices or
even analogous to the idea of the bowls
that you have constructed in your
society and experience this night of
your time. The idea simply is is that
they pick up on certain frequencies.
They match and identify with certain
levels of electromagnetic awareness and
consciousness and
translate that level into an atmosphere
that you can experience with your
physiological senses. Thus putting you
directly in touch as a gate with another
level of consciousness in the pure
energy sense within that vortex that is
created. your mind, your mentality, your
consciousness can direct the type of
experience you have, can direct the
level of consciousness that you interact
with. All that that crystal is doing in
a sense is creating an opening again in
a keying sort of way, allowing you to
stand in a neutral zone, a limbo state,
so to speak.
This is more often than not accomplished
through sonic means whereas the idea
more often than not through the use of
the actual light energy will be for the
application of the energy to a specific
purpose. Although sometimes sonically
this can be done as well with regards to
the ideas of levitation of material
objects and similar
ideas. But all of these effects will
fall basically within the five
categories that we have
discussed. Now your affinity to any
particular form of crystal, any
particular color, any particular shape
will have to do basically with whatever
it is you are working on at any given
moment within yourself, within your idea
of yourself as a being. You will be
attracted always to the thing again as a
catalyst as a trigger that will be most
reflective. Always always
always no matter what you are working
with in terms of a crystal and form.
Every crystal will always to some degree
exhibit all five of the characteristics
we have discussed. But they will vary in
intensity depending upon what level you
are at and in what way you can deal with
the idea of discovering within yourself
the things that need to be discovered in
working with the crystals and opening
yourself up to different levels of your
own consciousness. So what you are attracted
consciousness. So what you are attracted
to at any given moment by definition
because you are attracted to it
obviously will serve you best at that
moment for whatever it is you are
working on. and whether at that moment
you need more reflection than storeive
ability, then that's the type of crystal
you will be attracted to. If at that
moment you need more of a store
experience than a reflective one, then
you may be attracted to one that is
perhaps in general more representative
of storeive capacities, but all of them
will exhibit all five characteristics in
varying degrees. The colors again will
simply represent again analogous to what
you call your chakra points, the
different levels of energy that you are
dealing with and integrating in that
sense. the way, the methods, the routes
that you are flowing the energy through
yourself and perhaps what areas can be
most assisted in a reflective way by the
coloration of the crystal because in
that sense they function as filters and
whatever energy comes through them and
whatever energy is reflected back from
them will take upon themselves the
aspects of the color inherent in the
crystallin form and that will be
representative of what aspect or what
level of your consciousness is going to
be most highly affected or energized
when that crystal is in your presence or
and you are in its presence. You all
follow along with
us. This lays down a basic
foundation. Before we proceed, once
again, allow us our standard expression
of
appreciation to allow us to interact
with you and to have the willingness to
interact with us, to function as
representatives and ambassadors of your
world. For that is what you are. Make no
mistake about it. and to allow me to
function as an ambassador and a
representative of our respective worlds
in the association of worlds. So that
through these interactions bit by bit
and day by day we may cocreate and in
every sense of the word crystallize
relations between us so that we may
interact in time equals face to face
sharing joy and love and ecstasy in the
exploration of the infinite together as
one. We thank you for the gift of
allowing us to experience the
consciousness you have chosen to express
yourself as. And in return for this gift
now I will ask you how may I serve you
as do you. Goodbye.
On the different purposes you just
mentioned one through five. Yes. Are
there any
particular crystals that I say is more
appropriate to be reflective,
refractive, etc. From time to time, yes,
there can be. Now in
general you will find that what you call
the clear quartz
crystal depending upon the configuration
depending upon the individual that is
attracted to use it can be perhaps the
strongest representative of almost all
the levels. However in many
cases variations of the quartz and the
different colorations of the quartz can
be very specifically representative of
different ideas. The first step
especially being reflective in the sense
that what you would call rose quartz
will be very reflective of things that
you wish to deal with on an emotional
level. Smoky quartz will be very
reflective of things that you wish to
deal with on unconscious and
subconscious levels of your mentality
and what have you in that nature. There
can be variations from time to time that
are very representative of some of the
other factors. One in
particular that you would
call not only transmittive but also
storeative will be the substance that
you call hematite in that way as it is a
very highly
magnetic mineral and in this way can be
caused to lay down patterns and
impressions and have a grounding effect
on the entire ability of an individual
to get in touch with whole aspects of
nature. all at once in that sense and
draw from the storehouse of that
magnetic matrix that electromagnetic
matrix represented by the hematite the
entire understanding mentally all in one
gestalt flash of all the aspects of what
you call the mineral
kingdom entirely. It can be used in that
way as well. The substance that you call
turmoline in the sense that it exhibits
both reddish and greenish properties
will be very highly conducive to
telepathic function as it touches not
only the overall vibration of nature
itself and the crystal in form that
represents the transformation of your
planet now the green emerald ray
vibration but also the idea of the heart
energy the love energy the emotional
energy and can be very conducive to
sparking telepathic
junctions between individuals in that
way. Will this suffice?
That's a good beginning. All
right. We are not here in your terms to
catalog all the specifics. The idea is
for you to trust your imagination and
when you find yourself attracted to any
particular and peculiar crystal and form
to allow your imagination to feel itself
ignited and to use your visualization to
understand why and in what way that
crystal can serve you.
Understand? Yes. But that can be a
general foundation from which to begin.
Thank you. Oh, thank you very much. Uh
once previously you had mentioned
something about precision cutting of
crystals for specific purposes. Yes.
Some of this will be representative of
the level in which your technology is
evolving. In other words, in what you
call the very near future, as you begin
to experiment more and more of the idea
of the transmittal style of crystals,
those that transmit pure energy through
themselves in that way, you will begin
to configure machines as it were,
devices as it were, that are simply, as
you are doing now, with no moving parts,
almost entirely of crystallin
construction that can create energy
pulses, energy surges.
and direct and focus energy in ways that
can allow you to extract from that focus
all the power you need for many
different applications upon your planet.
The idea simply is that for the most
purely functioning devices, you would
require crystals that are very, in your
terms, clear and very in terms of
mathematical precision, very precisely
cut and arranged in different
configurations relative to one another
based upon their perspective property.
So that they can take [Music]
to feel itself ignited and to use your
visualization to understand why and in
what A that crystal can serve you
understand. Yes. But that can be a
general foundation from which to begin.
Thank you. Oh, thank you very much. Uh
once previous you had mentioned
something about precision cutting of
crystals for specific purposes. Yes.
Some of this will be representative of
the level in which your technology is
evolving. In other words, in what you
call the very near future, as you begin
to experiment more and more of the idea
of the transmitt style of crystals,
those that transmit pure energy through
themselves in that way, you will begin
to configure machines as it were,
devices as it were, that are simply as
you are doing now with no moving parts
almost entirely of crystallin
construction that can create energy
pulses, energy surges.
and direct and focus energy in ways that
can allow you to extract from that focus
all the power you need for many
different applications upon your planet.
The idea simply is that for the most
purely functioning devices, you would
require crystals that are very in your
terms clear and very in terms of
mathematical precision, very precisely
cut and arranged in different
configurations relative to one another
based upon their perspective property so
that they can take advantage of the
different interactions of the different
ratios and relationships that they have
as energy transmitters and receivers to
evoke a number of different specs in
your world. One we have suggested is
that if you take what you call very
clear, very pure quartz crystals and
polish them and cut them in their
natural sixsided configuration with a
very symmetrical point on one end and
either what you would call an absolute
flap or a perfectly spherical other end.
And sometimes depending upon the
application a slightly concave other
end. And if you arrange these crystals
so that they are all pointing inwards
forming a circle and then arrange not
only one circle of these crystals but
many many circles of these crystals all
stacked in what you would call a
cylindrical fashion. So that there is an
opening, a hole, a tunnel all the way
through the center line with all the
inward pointing points. You will have an
energy gate, a literal dimensional gate
of very very very high power. So high in
that sense that we would warrant caution
in placing yourself in the center of
that field. Now, from time to time, this
can be augmented by the idea of also
wrapping these crystals either
individually or the whole construction
with what you might call a conductive
metallic substance such as your copper.
Although some of the superconductors
your society is now inventing would also
be of benefit in this way. In creating
this particular type of coil, this tube,
this cylinder as it were, you will
literally have something that can direct
a focus of energy in such a way as to
literally open a dimensional gate in the
center of that
coil. Depends upon the size that you
construct it to be. Other variations of
this idea can also project a very strong
beam of energy from the middle of the
center of the coil or I shall say the
cluster. There are various things you are going
There are various things you are going
to discover as a society that you can
utilize crystals for in direct
application of technology so that you
will not necessarily have to have as
many moving parts as you have now in
that sense. And so it will be more
representative of a direct extraction of
the power inherent within the
electromagnetic field of your planet
without having to in your terms generate
quote unquote artificial
power. Understand? Yes. Does this answer
your question sufficiently?
Well, I think we
We could write in your terminology. They
have already been upset many times with
the understanding that several
individuals in your history already have
had regarding disability and have in
your terminology because of what you
have structured your society to be
suppressed the information which does
exist on your planet. One of the
individuals most paramount in your
history that understood this of your
recent history was the individual you
call Nicola
Tesla and in your terminologies. Yes,
they were
upset. But the idea is to understand
again that this is available to all
beings and when it is seen not as a
matter of losing power but of gaining
self-empowerment will force yourselves
anyway to have no other alternative.
Because if you cannot get there through
the oasis of what you
call ease of
recognition, then you will create as you
have begun to create the idea of
negativity and resistance and the
depletion of the natural state of your
world to the point where you are
arriving very rapidly at a place where
you have almost no other alternative
other than to extract the power directly
that your planet has always offered
you. Understand? Will this suffice?
I I'm ask this is that's fine for that.
I had another thought. This is just a
thought and perhaps you can give me some
idea of what will happen. Maybe perhaps
I if you had the pyramid
shapes base to base of
different crystallin substances have
could you give me any idea what might
happen? Foursided or three-sided?
I would probably think it probably
three-sided. There will be differences
in both. The three-sided will represent
in the full tetrahedral structure, the
top and its mirror image, things that
will tap directly into the fundamental
core of the template itself. There can
be many applications again depending
upon the material view. But all of those
applications of a three-sided pyramid
and another three-sided pyramid base to
base will tap directly into the template
level itself out of which all
materiality is created. It is a very
powerful powerful tool in that sense.
The foursided is also powerful but will
have a more strongly electromagnetic
focus in the sense that it acts like a
lens for electromagnetism much in the
same way that what you call your
magnifying glass act as a lens for
light. first thinking down to a specific
point in that way that will allow you to
take advantage of the effects of that
particular focus at precise mathematical
places within that pyramidal structure.
These precise mathematical loces have
already been delimited by many of you
by examining and exploring the ratios of
the chambers within what you call the
great pyramid within your Egyptian area.
For the technology was understood at
that time as to exactly how to place the
focusing chambers within the pyramidal
structure to receive the benefits of
exactly how the electromagnetic field of
your planet in that area would be
focused within the internal structure of
the pyramid. Most of these ideas where
it concerns pyramids have to do with
communication devices. Communications a
very strong strong enhancement of
telepathy. Both of them will do this but
in different ways and some of them can
also be very conducive to creating
within the atmosphere around your body
the necessary vibrations to promote what
you would call astral or out of body
projection which is one of the primary
things that your great pyramid was
actually used
for. The initiation rights that took
place within its chambers were for the
purpose of allowing individuals to
connect into the higher realm and in
your terms promote the idea of astral
projection. Understand? Yes. So
experiment all you
wish will the fight. Yes. Thank you very
much. Thank you very much sharing.
Good evening Bashar. And you good day.
Thank you.
Uh would you would you help me uh to
find a place to start as a beginner
working with crystals? Well, are you
attracted to do so? I certainly am. All
right. Well, what are you attracted to?
Well, I don't know if I'm evolved enough
to even know that. Oh, please. Let let
me put it in terms that I I thought I
would ask. No. All right. Uh in terms of
uh what type of crystal in terms of its
size, its purity, its shape, uh or its
cost, if you will, uh and what
application might a rank beginner begin
with? And can you ask a crystal what its
best application is? Oh,
absolutely. And that may be the easiest
way for you to begin. Go exploring. Go
researching scan a number of crystals
and with your heart, with your mind,
with your general feeling, simply as you
have said, ask how it can be applied.
See which one strikes the strongest
chord within you. Which one creates that
feeling, that rush of adrenaline within
your solar plexus area. Which one
really, as you say, turns you on? That
will be your answer. That will be the
one to start with. You have that
ability. You all have that ability. In
that sense, you are not a beginner. So,
by all means, play with the idea. Go and
explore and find out which one does in
fact speak to you most sweetly.
All right. Um, may I ask one more
question? Yes. Someone has just given me
a beautiful crystal. I'm holding her in
my hand. No. All right. Uh, pretend that
I am not the person who just spoke to
you, but I'm You're not.
every moment of time you are literally a
different person. So my wife says
yes uh I have been uh attracted to some
material on the use of crystals uh to
produce light and heat. Yes. Uh other
forms of energy and there was a
persistent mention of the five platonic
solids. Yes. Which I've been trying to
uh to find a source for and have been
unable to find anyone who can cut
crystals in the right form of these
platonic solids. Uh my question is do
you know if this is being done on the
planet? Yes it is. Yes it can be done.
There may even be individuals present
this night of your time who can steer
you in certain direction. But the idea
simply is is that when the individual
that will serve best to interact with
you will be in that sense the one that
comes along then you will find that
individual when the timing is correct.
You need to explore a few more things.
But in your exploration and in some of
the suggestions that individuals can
give you this night of your time, you
will find the necessary link up to
supply you with what you need. And by
the way, there are six solid shapes.
I thank you very much for in fact
actually there are seven, but one of
them is slightly interdimensional. Is
one a circle?
Do you mean a sphere? A sphere? Yes.
The additional two in a sense that is
another one altogether but not in the
same way but there are in a sense seven
that you would recognize as faceted.
Thank you. Turn this over to the next
person. The sphere represents an
octave. The eighth
principle
sharing bash to you. Good day. I have a
question or several questions. One is
I'm wondering um in what respect does
the um tectite moldivite have in
structure and in use? The idea now is
that it will contain what you call to
some degree an appearency of the green
vibration that represents the
transformation now of your planet. That
is the symbol of the transformation
itself, the green coloration. The idea
being that it is in your terms
extraterrestrial in origin implies that
it has much to do with the awakening in
many of you of many of the
extraterrestrial connections many of you
have or actually all of you have. So the
idea will be that it will function as a
mirror, as a reflection, as a symbol to
awaken different levels of yourself. In
many ways, it is representative of a
direct connection each and every one of
you can have with what you call your
future selves.
Thank you. Oh I I so I um I'm wondering
about uh in your
discourse in the idea of one moment one
moment there are some aspects of the
substance you call lite which also will
hearken back to what you call very
strong memories of analian
times since the idea of that mineral was
also very strongly understood and known
back then and used in very specific ways
which we will not go into now but It
will unlock some of those memories of
what you might call the deep past in
Atalantean times. Percy, isn't that mold
of the tectite? Yes. A celestial glass?
Yes. But it was known also in Adalantean
times. How could it be called a mineral
if it's a celestial
glass? I mean, is celestial glass a
mineral? Yes. Of course. I wasn't aware
of that. is not in your terminology
glass made out of in your terms mineral
substance. Well, is it animal or vegetable?
It's not vegetable. Is it animal? No.
Then in a sense it is mineral. That's
right. Thank you. We'll see. My next
question is in relation to the cutting
of um crystal as you were mentioning
before. Yes.
I'm wondering in my readings of
um the Atlantean times, yes, they used
crystals in their pyramidal structures.
Yes. And I I've read also read that they
were cut to in some respects to focus.
Yes. 12sided. 12sided. Yes. Is that
spherical? I mean cylindrical 12-sided
or there were
variations. Some of them were in your
terms hemispherical with a point on one
end. I see. Some of them were
cylindrical and placed again in cluster
like these uh like the coil type of
apparatus you were talking about. Not
exactly that configuration but the basic
idea. Yes. As amplifiers as condensers
in that way. I see as buildup
potentiometers so to speak. what we
would call a flash matrix. Level to
level to level to level to level to
level is an acceleration and an
amplification of the power until it
creates what you would call a flashover
phenomena and literally generates an
electrical flow or an electromagnetic
flow depending upon how it's set up.
This was the basis of the mode of power
used in Atalantean times not only for
what you would call heat and light but
for motivation of what you would call
sea and land and
aircraft. Nothing in that sense operated
primarily of its own engine or
machinery. The idea of the reason that
every device had a receiver and received
the waves that were generated by the
several crystal stations positioned
around the Atalantian land mass and
these stations beamed energy that when
received much like your radio wave
simply activated the necessary
conditions within the devices to allow
them to be propelled in the various
fashion. That's pretty
deep for me. for me that
is another question is I I maybe you've
already explained it but um in relation
to the I I'm curious about the structure
of space uh whether or not it's uh does
it is it triangular you know the
template is tetrahedral in nature
tetrahedral but the basic structure of
what you call space time is
holographic the idea being as
follows if you have a flat grid laid out
lines running this way as you say, lines
running this way as you say. For now, we
will forget the up and down lines of the
third dimension. Just for the clarity of
this demonstration, if you imagine that
your space and time is a flat grid
stretching to infinity all the way
around, then you stop to think, well,
each and every intersection point of the
lines is another point of information,
another point of the
structure, and they stretch out forever.
So if you wish to learn about the whole
structure, you would have to walk and
walk and walk and walk and walk
infinitely crossing every single one of
those intersection points to understand
the nature of that structure and gather
the information inherent in that
particular intersection point. However,
if you stop and realize that it is
holographic in nature, then the analogy
you have is as follows. If you take what
you call a sphere that is reflective all
the way around, similar to what you
would call one of your ball bearings and
place it anywhere on the grid, you then
will all of a sudden observe that the
entire image of the grid is reflected in
the warped surface of that sphere. So
now all the information of the grid and
all the points on the grid are actually
right there in that one sphere and you
don't have to go anywhere but where you
are to get it.
Yes, I've seen that diagram. Okay, that
is the basic holographic nature of the
construction of spacetime. But the way
it is laid out electromagnetically as a
let's say net is in a tetrahedral
structure. The
tetrahedrin, what I've called a base to
base threesided pyramid, point up and
point down, is literally a pictorial
analogy of all mathematical, geometric,
physics, any type of ratio and
relationship and equation that could
ever define the physical universe is all
consolidated into that one shape. Every
principle in physics you have ever
discovered or will ever discover is all
represented in that one shape. It is the
pictorial analogy of the holographic
structure. But in an electromagnetic
matrix in a mathematical terminology in
a graphic sense, if you were to put
those tetrahedans face to face and and
they would go in into infinity in in all
directions connecting connecting what?
Faces points both the edges and the
faces and the points all three are their
own directions, their own dimensions.
You see the idea is that your physical
universe in that sense as you understand
it is quote unquote four dimension. The
other six that make up what you have now
discovered to be the 10dimensionality of
existence electromagnetically speaking
are all collapsed or infolded into what
you would call the edges and the points
so that you do not perceive them so that
you can experience the limited idea of a
fourthdimensional universe. In other
words, the literal edges themselves
define other dimensions that you simply
do not perceive with your physical
senses. Uh that was one of my
um wonderings as to whether or not the
these points, edges, and faces uh were
interdimensional. Yes. Basically, all
you see in your daily experience is the
faces. Not always, all of them at once.
In other words, if I was to try to draw
a a combination of tetrahedrons in a
spherical structure, uh they would all
it would it would include
a one tetrahedral structure is
sufficient to define any equation. You
don't have to lump them into a sphere.
Well, I'm leading to another question.
Oh, all right. in my idea of trying to
put them into a conglomerate uh picture
altogether brings me to another question
which uh in information that I read in
the material of Seth he mentions moment
points. Yes. Do these relate to uh the
structure of space? Yes, of course.
Well, they are the central point that
represents the collapse of all the
dimensions into one here and now. They
are what you may call analogous to the
black hole idea you have expressed in
your reality. The dimension the point
through which all realities pass from
which all realities emerge.
I just can't seem I'm trying to
visualize her. Well, that's all right.
You don't have to try to hug. Well, I'm
not. You can still use the effect
without necessarily having a complete
visualization. Well, the idea simply can
be, if you wish, do view it as a literal
point. Now, I understand that your
imaginations being based in what you
call third dimensionality will have a an
apparently difficult time imagining that
there is nothing around the
point. But nonetheless, let that suffice
as an analogy. Could these points be um
there is only one? We understand that
they are used plurally in that sense
because you have stretched your idea of
space and time out into that flat grid.
And so to you it appears there are many
intercedes but there is only one moment
point. I can't think I'll stop here.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Hello. I'm Juliet. All right. I am not
Romeo.
Um, a little earlier uh you mentioned uh
you know that's usually that's not what
they usually say.
Uh a little earlier you mentioned Nicola
Tesla. Yes. Um uh he once said
electricity is the greatest doctor. Yes.
um the idea of creating an
electromagnetic and electric
vibration that represents the idealized
state of your physical form. Your
physical form being of course in that
sense nothing but electromagnetic energy
vibrating at a particular
pitch. Then you can with electricity
with electromagnetism create
atmospheres, bubbles, fields that can be
representative of the idealized state
electrically of your body. And if your
body is immersed in those fields, then
your body can be made to realign by
matching by identifying with the
idealized state that the field
represents. And you can walk into it
disease and walk out of it healed. By
pitch, you mean frequency? Frequency. Uh
um uh Okay. Not so metaphorically, but a
little more literally. Uh um he used to
administer a kind of um electric therapy
to himself. Then I wonder how he did
that and how maybe I could do that using
this is now being done once again upon
your planet sporadically here and there
most strongly in the area upon your
planet you would call bone regeneration.
Yes. And also tumor eradication
particularly by individual associated
with an area you call Sweden.
Oh. Oh. Oh. The guy that invented
vitamin C. No. Having discovered it? No.
This is being done by the insertion of
what you would call needles attached to
wires in specific areas to rebalance the
electric potential of the body because
this individual has realized that your
physiological body is basically nothing
more than electric battery. And the only
reason it would be deceased is because
the flow of the current is not arriving
where it needs to. So this individual
has created what you would call well not
meaning to be flippant jumper cables for
the body to reroute to divert the electrical
body to reroute to divert the electrical
flow to the area it needs to get to.
When the electrical flow arrives at the
area it needs to in a normal way the
body must respond to it by going back to
its natural state of health. Okay.
Following that jumper cable metaphor if
I'm the car and I've just called the AAA
he being the AAA. What is the cable
attached to from me to him? What's his
source of energy that he's jumping?
Simply what you would call small
electrical battery generator devices
that give what you would call a very
small trickle of amperage into your
physical cellular structure along the
wires through the needle. AC or DC?
There are variations for specific
purposes, but it is our perception that
it is mostly in your terminology DC.
Although there can be AC applications of
primary importance is that one of the
needles be negative, one be positive.
Right? So and the positive needle be
injected into the area of disease and
the negative one be injected into a
nearby area of healthy tissue. Ah that's
brilliant. So you're jumping off another
person like him for example. These
things are attached to what you would
call devices.
Healthy tissue is a device. No, no, no,
no, no. Your own body. Body. Oh, your
own. Oh, negative. I get it. I see. In
other words, that is what you would call
a battery. A literal battery,
technologically speaking, to which wires
and needles are attached better than
inserted in your body. I got it. And you
yourself complete your circuit. Thank
you. Yeah.
Uh, okay. Um well I owe also
the devices that you call magnetic
resonance imaging scanners can be tuned
although many of your medical
practitioners have not realized this not
only to diagnose but to
cure. They are just beginning to realize
that some of the devices they are using
that use electromagnetic fields to
diagnose can also be used to cure. Oh
wait do they have any of those in LA?
Maybe UCLA or something.
Yeah. But they are not being pitched to
cure. I see. And by pitch you mean
frequency change. Yes. Okay.
Approximately 7 and 1/2 cycles per
second. Yeah. 7 and 1/2. And that's what
humans are. That is what your earth is.
Ah. And All right. I get it. And and
what about humans? 9 around 10. But the
idea of bringing a human between 70 1/2
to 10 will usually balance out any idea
of negativity or disease. 70 and a half
allows them to identify to the earth
vibration which then allows them in a
sense to
relax in the natural eb the natural
pulse of your planet and then they can
take themselves back to 10 in a natural
way. You you said cycles. Do you mean
cycles per second? Cycles per second.
But that's different than hertz. So
okay. Um great. Okay. There's um I think
Um great. Okay. There's um I think
there's one other thing. Oh, liquid
crystal. Yes. Uh, what can we do with
that? They're very exciting. Very
exciting. Now, some individuals we have
communicated with have begun to invent
devices. There are many things you can
do with it. These devices in a sense
placing your liquid crystal between what
you call sheets of glass and then
stimulate it electrically create a
particular type of glow that can create
imagery within the liquid crystal in
between the sheets of glass. When the
flow of electricity is put in at
approximately something above 300,000
cycles per second, then the liquid
crystal can function as a window between
physical and non-physical reality so
that non-physical consciousness can have
a medium of communication in physical
terms by projecting thought images into
the liquid crystal that physical beings
can perceive and vice versa. So it
becomes an antenna that way excited with
300,000 cycles or something. Yes.
Although it is literally more of a
window. H. Ah god, how great. So is
there any particular way we have to um
um hook it up to this 300,000 uh cycles
per second? Just the long cables that
can take it. You're so you're great.
Okay. Um uh uh
that frequency is what is necessary for
the transcendence of certain material
forms into non-physicality
representations. It is what you simply
call the flash point between your
physical world and the non-physical
level you call
astral. That's why you cannot perceive
them because they are functioning
somewhere around.
And when stimulated electrically create
a particular type of blow.
I can create imagery within the liquid
crystal in between the sheets of glass.
And the flow of electricity is put in at
approximately something about 300,000
cycles per second. Then the liquid
crystal can
function and a window between physical
and non-physical reality so that
non-physical consciousness can have a
medium of communication in physical
terms by projecting thought images into
the liquid crystal that physical beings
can perceive and vice versa. So it
becomes an antenna that way excited with
300,000 cycles or something. Yes.
Although it is literally more of a
window. Ah god, how great. So is there
any particular way we have to um um hook
it up to this 300,000 uh cycles per
second? Just a long cable that can take
it. You're great. Okay. Um uh
uh that frequency is what is necessary
for the transcendence of certain
material forms into non-physicality
representation. It is what you simply
call the flash point between your
physical world and the non-physical
level you call
astral. That's why you cannot perceive
them because they are functioning
somewhere around at least a base of
333,000,000 cycles per second. [Music]
[Music]
Yes, I would advise that no one else be
standing around
you. Now that has been responsible for
what you call spontaneous combustion of
the physical force. Now it can be done
and that's what you call
ascendancy. But you must be very
strongly aligned and clear before the
ascendancy will not cause disruption to
the physical cellular structure.
Otherwise you will literally burn
up. Sometimes it happens on your planet
that certain wavelengths of thought will
automatically align themselves to the
fluctuations of the electromagnetic
field of your planet. If you will
recognize and take a survey of the
fluctuations of the electromagnetic
field in your planet, you will recognize
that then they are at peak points in
every case. There have been a few cases
of what you call spontaneous combustion
simply because some individuals look
into it on an unconscious level and then
ride the crest up and it goes too fast
for them. Now they do translate but they
do not translate their body with them.
But you said you bet the idea of body to
go along too. Well, that's up to
you. But I would assume Well, I noticed
you're borrowing somebody else's this
evening. Thank you.
But only as a communication device.
I am not present with you. Oh, it is
more analogous to what you would call
your telephone device literally. Um
I biological beings are simply the most
efficient transmitter and receiver.
You know, it just it just it just
occurred to me and I know that everybody
else is very anxious, but but when we
electrocute criminals, does that mean we
translate them accidentally? Are they a
bunch of like you know murderers out in
this other dimension because we like
shot them full with 300,000 cycles per
second to off them. And they will always
when you in your terms die translate to
the astral realm. Oh I see. But like
anyone who dies from a physical to a
non-physical state ascendancy in that
sense is in your terminology quote
unquote taking your body with you. I
see. Okay. But you still translate in a
similar way. Okay. I'm going to work on
that. Um I am.
And um and just one other thing uh
getting back to Nicola Tesla and then I
will pass the microphone on. Uh uh why
don't you care for pearl
earrings and can you say hello to him
for me? Why don't you? I
I one moment.
[Music]
It is our perception that when that
consciousness was focused as a
personality on your planet, something
that had to do with interactions with
members of your society, that created
what you would call a
revulsion. Really? Well, not in general,
but in some specific encounters. Yes.
Anything else? only that that individual
is not an individual as you understand
it anymore.
Oh, I'm so sorry to hear that. Why?
Well, I I I would like to get together
with him. Well, you can. All I'm saying
is that it is not focused as you think
of as individuals are focused. Oh, how
could I do that? Think of the idea of
the individual and it will still key you
into the overall energy that that
particular consciousness has become.
Okay. Oh, it will still work as a dial.
Oh, good. Okay. But understand all we
are saying is that when you do receive
information, it is not coming from the
aspect of that causes that was focused
as you knew him to be Nicola Tesla,
right? We're both just two conduits to
the personality is been
expanded in a way that does not
necessarily have a translation into your
language. I see. Could we come up with a word with
I see. Could we come up with a word with
it before it? One moment.
Shall we say that that particular
consciousness has
become infused with the electromagnetic field
infused with the electromagnetic field
itself. So that all workings, all
dealings that you participate in that
have to do with the electromagnetic
field to some
degree are being
are being
assisted by that
[Music] being. I do not want to imply this in
being. I do not want to imply this in
the old terminology.
I do not mean what I'm about to say in
the old terminology that this is going
to be represented in. But perhaps
putting it in the old terminology can
give you perhaps a little bit clearer
idea if you're not taking too
literally. The individual, the
consciousness that you knew on your
planet as Nicola Tesla has expanded now
to rejoin most of its consciousness and
has infused itself into the
electromagnetic field of your reality in
such a way that it could literally, at
least in the old terminology, be
considered now the god of
[Music] electromagnetism to some degree a
electromagnetism to some degree a
standing wave, but more a part of the
archetypal substream of your entire
consciousness.
Because then it can reach all of you
that are desirous of interacting with
its understanding of the idea of the
electromagnetic field.
[Music] Individuals choose themselves.
Individuals choose themselves.
Yes, that is how
uh Oh, okay. I I want to thank you for
your attention. Oh, we thank you for
your interact. Yeah, Sherry.
[Music] Thank you.
Thank you.
Hi, M. Happy day to get back to um the
7.5 uh residency. I just experienced this
uh residency. I just experienced this
magnetic bed that you talked about in
August, right? And I wanted to ask a
little bit about what kind of health
benefits you might get from spending
time in that field of that magnetic bed.
You do not need to spend much time. In
fact, I would recommend that you do not
spend too much time within it. It can be
very strongly and very quickly aligning.
To spend an over abundance of time in it
can accelerate you to an uncomfortable
point. It can even give you
headaches. Sometimes if an individual is
negatively oriented or has many things
to work through of a negative nature, it
can accelerate the negative side to
force you to face it more quickly. And
so it may seem as if at first sometimes
lying in that particular structure that
has actually accelerated the negative
side of you when in fact it has done so
but done so for a positive reason. I
see. I wanted explanation as to what the
difference of that magnetic energy is
and what uh the harmful um magnetic
radiation from power lines and so forth.
What's the difference between those two?
The idea is that this is very lowkey
energy and that is all any of these
devices have to be. You are a very
sensitive instrument your body. The idea
of what you call your high power line is
more akin to the level of energy that
you require to translate from physical
to non-physical reality in that sense
and not always as you would say in
alignment with the way you want to. The
idea is is that that much energy is
disruptive. It creates a breakdown of
the electromagnetic field in such a way
that all dimensions are inherent in that
one area. And therefore, if you enter
it, it is like running into a metallic
shredder operating at high speed.
Understand? The very low level of
crystallin and electromagnetic energy
does all that is necessary to reorient
you. It would be analogous to hooking up
any of your electromagnetic or
electronic or mechanical devices to a
power load that is far beyond
[Music] that generally
that generally
oozes. We would recommend that a short
period of exposure in that bed before
you go to your regular bed will perhaps
be more conducive to getting you in
touch with what you need to get in touch
with in the dream reality rather than
staying in an all night
flow. How about affect if you have them
in that
field? At least we change the alignment
of the field and remain so until they
are unaligned. Would that help raise your
unaligned. Would that help raise your
vibration of your
consciousness? That's a vision. I [Music]
[Music]
learn both times that I've heard you in
this context of my
The thoughts have gone along the line
that in
the transformation of consciousness to
has run onto manifestation into time and
run onto manifestation into time and
space. There was in the beginning a a
sexual division which I once had a dream
where there was a girl that I loved and
we were I was the the center of a of a
molecule of of an atom the nucleus and
she was the electron cloud and we would
never manifest that this was the situation as
manifest that this was the situation as
it was. This is simply an allow per such
no interpretation of a particular idea
of the relationship. It is not a level
unto itself except that you have created
that level within your own
electromagnetic field. It is to some
degree representative of things
interaction that can take place and be
symbolized on what you would call an
astral level. But that does not mean
that it is a central level unto itself.
one of the frequencies of the astral
level and can be symbolized in the
format we have now
just also as
to the dual uh the dual nature as a
light and and uh modern
physics can just be related to to
uh male and female different perceptions
and all polarity will be in parallel
alignment all the way up and down the
soul because polarity is one of the
definitions of your physical reality and
it will manifest in the electromagnetic
level and even to some degree in the
lower astral
level. So that thought
first manifest in the physical then it will
manifest in the physical then it will
automatically break into polarity
right okay thank you thank you [Music] [Music]
Good morning.
You mentioned earlier about um being
attracted certain
rocks on and um I was attracted to this
crystal some years ago. Yes. And it all
seems to have a personality. Well, yes,
in a sense since it is a fragment of
your own consciousness. Of course, it
would. Well, after you found the rock that you
Well, after you found the rock that you
like, what do you do with it? That's up
to you, isn't it? Use your imagination.
That's what it's for. Does this rock
activate any particular feelings or
images or ideas within you?
Well, it has a kind of triangular
pyramid type shape that I'm intrigued
by. All right. Why are you intrigued by
the shape?
Because it looks pretty. Is that
all? What do you see when you meditate
on the idea of the triangular shape?
Does anything unlock for you?
uh which suggests to me a lot of clarity
and um suggest one point of all maybe it is
um suggest one point of all maybe it is
that a very subtle reflection a very
subtle suggest but as you say a little
friendly reminder the idea of your
attraction to crystal need not mean that
the information has to come in glowing
threedimensional color with
compass the idea can be less subtle
whisper, just a gentle nudge, just a
friendly pass here and there now and
then. The whole idea is for you to take
responsibility in the directions of your
life anyway, not to always run to the
crystal to say which way should I go. So
perhaps let's practice something that is
sufficient for you as a gentle reminder.
It need not necessarily serve us any
more than that.
So we need to write to different rocks
and find ones that we like and so on. It
should just be we shouldn't um like
there are these books that say that
amethyst does this and does this. Those
books are basically representative of a
recognition that there are general
effects of certain crystals in your
general society because you have a
general consensus reality that basically
agrees that this acts this way and this
act this way. Still not incorrect. But
the idea is that as soon as you begin to
understand that you are your own master
crystal, you need less ritualization in
an exteriorized way. Understand?
Yes. You can just kind of
um deal with them if you wish. Um [Music]
[Music]
Why would you
[Music] wish I guess you should just go around
wish I guess you should just go around
with the energy that they suggest to you
and not make anything about it? Well,
no, you don't have
to. Again, as we are saying, the idea
does not have to come blaring in in
blinding light and sound.
So you find that it moves you as a piece
of music might move you and allows you
to capture certain moves and feel then
so if that's the way you wish to use it
that's the way you use it. But what
about people who lay rocks on people
and does that have any kind
of perhaps what you need to understand
is the following general idea. All tools
are valid because what makes any tool work
valid because what makes any tool work
is a belief in that tool. And that's why
there are so many tools because the
planet has so many different approaches
and perspectives and beliefs. So
obviously a tool that doesn't work for
someone will work for someone else. And
a tool that does work for someone won't
work for someone else. But they're all
valid because individuals as different
individuals are
valid. But you are beginning to
homogenize as a society. And that's why
a lot of the trappings of the ritual are
beginning to drop away and certain
things are becoming a little more
homogeneous, a little more general in
their
approach. But all of these tools are
valid, but they are all tools. You are
the source of the power. And what you
believe mostly is what allows the tool
to do its
work. a truth that you're going to have
a strong belief about will not work for
you because it is like looking into a
mirror and seeing someone else's
reflection. Yeah. Thank you. Thank you
very [Music]
[Music]
much. Would you like to share that with
everyone? Has everyone been shared with
a good evening?
Oh, good day to you. Mhm.
Yes. What you
believe? What you believe is what
attracts a particular group.
Is there any particular way in which you
enjoy using
it? What is
that? I see. Is that because the
business is something that you don't
really find that exciting?
Is the business you are doing the most
exciting thing you really want to do in
life? Why
not? I didn't say you don't. But why
aren't you doing the thing that would
actually represent more the thing that
would excite you more than what you're
doing? In other words, you're saying
that you prefer
struggles. Would you, if I may ask it this way,
Would you, if I may ask it this way,
rather do the thing it excites you most
to do?
Why aren't you?
Bye-bye.
Well, making an assumption that you have
to set yourself up in a certain way to
be able to do that and that in and of
itself the thing that excites you the
most most important. All right.
think you should do. So what? There are
many things that are there to do. If you
do them because you think you should,
that doesn't always mean that that
recognition is in alignment with the
thing that represents what you're really
all about. Are you doing it because you
think you because you have been told by
others that you should because the
thoughts you are echoing within your
head that say I should do this are
actually the thoughts of other people
that you have been said all through your
life or are they really your own
decision?
Yes. And I like the recognition. I like
I like
Yes. I am not invalidating what you are.
But I am asking you if you start with a
struggle then why not manifest the idea
in a way that represents the idea
without struggle? I what I like to do as
well as [Music]
Christian by using your imagination. Do
you have a picture at all of the way you
would prefer to do what you are doing rather
prefer to do what you are doing rather
than the way you are doing it?
can concoct a clear image, a clear
visualization of the thing you would
rather be doing in the way you would
rather be doing
it. Then if you wish to use the crystal,
you don't have to use the crystal, but
if you believe that the crystal will
accelerate you, then project that image
into the
crystal. All right,
then in one sense. However, remember
that the crystal is in this sense being
used as a reflective crystal. The idea
is also to put all of your emotions in.
In other words, when you project this
image, do you just sort of sit there and
watch this image and go, "Ho, nice
image. Ho
ho. Ho ho." Or do you really see this
image as something that really excites
you? And do you really get excited about
that because it's a real reality to you?
Do you put all your senses into it? Do
you taste what it would be like to be
that person you imagine you want to be?
Do you smell the way that person would
smell? Do you taste and touch and hear
and see the way that person would see
when you have that meditation, when you
have that image? Do you key all your
senses into it? Or do you just look and
go, "That's a nice image. It would be
nice if it were that way, but it's
not." How do you do it? Which way?
You see the idea that if you don't put
the energy into it, if you don't
understand that what you are picturing
in your imagination is real, then you
will constantly be waiting for it to
happen rather than acting like the
person you see in the image. When you
start acting like the person you see in
the image, you'll start getting the
result of the person in the image
because you'll be matching the
frequency. You'll be copying, mirroring,
mimicking the idea. You'll be allowing
your imagination to be the fundamental
crystal, the reflective crystal to
reflect back to you what you are. Not
what you can be, not what you may be
someday. Who knows when, but what you
are right now. Because if you can
imagine it right now, you are that
person right now. All you have to do is
start acting like that person right now.
And you'll have the lifestyle of the
person you imagine you want to be.
That's what your imaginations are for.
So that if you mimic what you see,
you'll get the same result. Your
imagination is the first crystal, the
first reflection. Your crystal that you have,
reflection. Your crystal that you have,
this large
crystal. You are attracted to it because
it symbolizes your imagination. All you
actually need is your imagination and
the conviction to act out as best as you
can the image you see with full
excitement because the excitement will
generate the scenario you want and
attract in your life only those things
that are representative of you doing the
work you want to do only in an
effortless and exciting way. So that's
what that crystal is basically
reflecting to you that that is the scope
of your
imagination. Use it. You don't really
need the crystal. Your imagination is
the key. The crystal is only there to
remind you to use your imagination to
get you to try something a little bit
and get things out of the ordinary to
spark to ignite to move your imagination
in that direction. Now take it all away
and you'll have served the purpose of
the crystal
understand is making mechanical sense to
you because I am not talking about a
figurative or philosophical idea. I am
talking physics and mechanics. If you
follow your imagination in your
visualization picture of who you want to
be, if you recognize that that you in
your imagination is acting differently
than the you you are now is acting, all
you have to do is act the way you see
yourself in the imagination acting and
you will have the lifestyle of that you
because you will be that you because
you'll be that
frequency. Absolutely. That's what your
imagination is
for some kind of situation.
Yes. Although, although watch the reason
for why you're doing what you're doing
because sometimes you might be creating
a desire for a specific outcome and that
desire may not be a desire that is
created within true integrity. So be
very clear as to the reasons for why you
are doing what you're doing. And
secondly, not always does the image you
create have to specifically manifest
exactly in that way. It can very very
very often it can but sometimes because
of how you are approaching the idea and
what the idea you wish to change means
to you may not be completely aware of
exactly all the definitions you are
working with. So sometimes you may
create an image and the image may be
able to function as a general guide to
push you in a certain direction but it
only is a general guide and in fact the
way the situation actually manifests may
be quite different in appearance from
what you visualize but will still serve
the same purpose. So don't tighten up
your expectations too much and insist
that it must manifest exactly the way
you thought or you won't accept it at
all because sometimes your analytical
mind cannot conceive of all the way the
answer could come. So put it out there
with a specific idea but accept it the
way it comes as representative of what
you have put out. Very often it will be
exact but sometimes it won't because the
way it will come will be the way that
actually serves you best and most
effortlessly. [Music] that you
that you
completely nothing is any more important
to me than anything else have a
particular service but my understand yes
yes yes we do have a service
yes we do have a service
yes but could that service be something
that would be somewhat difficult or
Never never. It can be confused as a struggle,
never. It can be confused as a struggle,
but it doesn't have to be. It never has
to be. You see, the idea is, and this
again is a matter of your definition, is
that many of you say, well, do we all
have specific services that we're
supposed to perform? Do we have specific
missions and specific purposes? And then
you think, well, if I do this, is that a
fulfillment of my purpose? Is that an
expression of my mission? Well, what if
I do this? So, what if I do that? But
you see the idea is that all these this
and thats and methodologies and projects
and expressions of
creativity they are not your purpose.
They are your methods of expressing your
purpose. Your purpose all of you your
purpose in life is to be simply the
fullest expression of who you are.
That's it. And that's why it's really
easy unless you choose to believe it's a
struggle to be who you are, which many
of you do. You see the idea to believe
that even though you are a
reincarnational being,
you the you are now only has one right
to live. You have never been this you
before. You'll never be this you again.
So the fundamental purpose to this life
is to be the fullest expression of this
you. And the way you do that is by doing
in this life with your free will
choosing whatever methodology whatever
format excites you the most in
expressing the fullness of your
being. Understand?
the next person to this discussion with
her. How do I know if it's me? What I'm
saying is I don't know if it's me that's
creating a struggle in my mind and it's
not what is there. It could be it could
be that what I was doing was a struggle.
It could be that what I was doing was
what I was supposed to be doing. But
because I'm conditioned and I used to
struggle, I was making a struggle. That
is correct. I don't know what it is. Is
it in my head or is it in my eyes? Once
again ask you yourself am I really doing
what I want to do what excites me the
most in the most exciting way I could be
doing it. If your answer is no, then go
back into your
imagination. Nice on it.
That's all you have to do. Whether it is
something you're already doing, but
doing it in a certain way or something
you're not doing that you could be
doing. But there really are no shoulds.
So don't take that attitude of yourself
because then you will take certain
limitations on yourself that will make
it more difficult for you to see what
really you don't think in terms of
shoulds. Just think in terms of what you
can, what you wish to do to express the
fullness of yourself. When you do that,
you will be doing a service. You will
find something that will allow you to
serve in a way that also serves
you. Thank you very
[Music]
much. Have a good day. [Music]
uh as you know here on earth and we can
tell you about
devices go from very low cycles to me to
grow frequencies which is very high
frequency but now I'm interested in
knowing consciousness something that is about
consciousness something that is about
that but the could say that
uh consciousness is a frequency
like it rotate every time. You could say
that but consciousness in of itself well
to be quite literal is really a
frequency. It's the fabric of existence
itself. So if consciousness
So if consciousness
interception of
electromagnetic in it but more than
being interled which is why the co is
actually a separate thing simply that
all the different frequencies of
electromagnetic we are aware of are
different expressions of cos of course
is inter because all the frequencies are
made out of
co is the maverick that you are
perceiving as all these different
frequencies express an electromagnetic
current. Is that
correct? No. Okay. Uh there are higher
No. Okay. Uh there are higher
frequencies that are representative of
other levels and dimensions of
experience that now merge into what you
would call the astral realm. The idea to
some degree has been lightly touched on
in your body and you have given a
general term to what you might call
frequencies of energy that exist higher
than what you are used to thinking of as
the upper limit of your physical
universe. The general thing that
physicists have created people do is
[Music] called that doesn't go into the
called that doesn't go into the
the matter but yeah
uh you see
understand the nuclear
which of the second one being the the
force between atoms Well, one being the
gravity pressure will be
uh okay and of course will be uh the
gravity pressure and I don't know
what however as you perceive your
physics now they have already
consolidated a few of these and already
recognized that there are fewer than
four. So they have already determined
that what you have called previously
weak atomic force and the
electromagnetic force are now combined
with what they have an electro weak
force and there are even indications
that what you call the
strong is already combining with that.
So in a sense they're on the verge of
rendering it down to two. However they
do understand that there really is only
one formulas haven't caught up with the
understanding. Okay. And uh
uh this constant velocity and light has
a constant velocity and
uh um impossible to break this fire as
like you see the idea definition what
you call the speed of light is a barrier
as far as your third dimensional
universe is
[Music] concerned
concerned
understand it is in that sense a barrier
as far
universe idea of how our spacecraft
travel is that they don't really travel
in a commercial sense. The reason we can
arrive somewhere faster than it would
take light to get is because we are not
traveling in that dimension at all. We
are redefining ourselves holographically
and reinserting ourselves removing
ourselves from the dimension. Redefining
and reinserting ourselves as time
represents the definition. We're not
traveling faster to the
right within the matrix of physical
reality. But particles that already
exist at your terminology smaller than
the speed of light no cannot be by
mechanical means or energetic means fed
up to or past the speed of light. But
they can be translated into other
levels. The kind of particles the
reflections that already exist
holographically on those levels can then
be used to redefine those particles
inerted where you wish them to be
reinserted in the workplace of the work.
So the speed of light barrier is not
literally broken
broken
avoided. Thank you very
much. Thank you. Good day. I'd like to
talk to you about life, physical life.
Like I'm finding in my evolution
that I'm involved in the environment in
the city and
city and
light seems to play a big role. Physical
light. And I'd like to know if the
battery that I'm getting is close to
reality. For instance, is light,
physical light in the center of the
electromagnetic spectrum, so to speak. Yes, it is in
spectrum, so to speak. Yes, it is in
terms infinite in both directions. So
therefore, when when visible
light is balanced, then the rest of the
spectrum, electromagnetic spectrum will
fall into place. Well, thank you very
much. That's true.
And you can use the blending and the
balancing of that physical light, the
spectrum in the center when it is blend
to function as in a sense a gateway into
other dimensional
things. You know, shall we
say perpendicular direction to be out of
phase energy
[Music] shift? Out of phase from what? I say
shift? Out of phase from what? I say
from the extreme you are familiar with
in terms of calling your physical
universe physical
light. There are other dimensions of
experience that experience light in
similar ways but they are 90° out of
phase to your dimension. When you
balance the spectrum in the middle and
pull together as an energy gate, you can
go through that gate and perceive other
dimensions of experience that are out of
phase with your own. It is similar to
the window we spoke of earlier.
It can be done in a number of ways. The
first as has been discussed is the
recognition that what you call the
visible spectrum is in a sense the
center of the electromagnetic
band. Nothing to say. No. That's
physical reality. What you are
perceiving as your scale of things
sizewise as you say is approximately in
the center of how big things can get and
how small things can get.
Now if you take that light what you call
the seven colors and you blend them into
seven colors and you blend them into
white light in a various number of ways
or at least even them out in certain
ways. You can create literally a pool of
light in such a manner as it will cause
there to be a breakdown from one
dimension through to another dimension.
It depends on how it is focused. Your
technology may not be
appropriate manipulation of magnetic
dynamic tensor fields. An idea that
we're only now discovering with regard
to electromagnetic
pulsation. But now we can still be done
to create literally a doorway of light
made out of light, nothing but light.
And on one side of the door is one
dimension. On another side of the door
is another dimension.
And if you rotate the door, you'll be in
another dimension and again another and
again another and again another
depending on how you rotate
[Music]
it. Reference to the idea of how
electromagnetic field interacts with
itself from various directions.
[Music] I'd like to bring it down to the
I'd like to bring it down to the
practical level of I'm working with a
light physical light called Aka light
and as far as I know it's the most
evolved physical light on this planet.
Is that not true? It goes by many
different ways but you have basically an
effort. Yes. What where is that technology
Yes. What where is that technology
coming from? As far as
mystery, it is coming from your
collective consciousness
[Music] recognition of the
recognition of the
fact. In other words, you are siphoning
the information through your collective
awareness because your collective
awareness is in touch with the fact that
you are already existing on many
different levels of
dimensional. So taking mental
light. express that is one way to exemplify or
express that is one way to exemplify or
represent it. So your environment is an
expression of who you are. So absolutely
always
absolutely. So if you want to remain in
a balance or imbalance then you pick the
environment to represent or as a mirror
of where you are.
And if you become balanced with
yourself, then the environment allows
you to mask that
frequency. So then that's why you can
talk to somebody about balance. They
don't know what you're talking about.
They're not ready.
Correct. Any light frequency will see
eye to eye.
[Music] Now I want to tie this in with you
Now I want to tie this in with you
mentioned the magnetic which I also work
with and you
[Music] said in my mind what you said I want to
said in my mind what you said I want to
clear
that you talked about if you did I
don't it brings up negativity meaning
that it can expand somebody and they
might not be ready for that expansion.
will approve it. In other words, they
may be ready and willing, but they may
have certain ideas they have not yet
faced. And if they're ready and willing,
then the expansion and acceleration of
their energy speed will event push them
through those ideas. In other words,
they will have to face their fears in
order to truly integrate. It may make it
seem as if they have accelerated in a
negative way when in fact they're
accelerating in a positive way, but
accelerating through the fears they must
integrate. the best to bring everything
to a head. Yes, exactly. It's just
whether you're ready to correct reality.
That's reality. Yes. That's well that's
reality. Yes. But the idea at least is
that at least on some level if an
individual is willing to accelerate
themselves then basically they are to
some degree at least making a statement
that they are on some level ready to
face it even if it's true in the world.
what I program how you move at the
moment. Absolutely. Because if you think
so, but but how about people a lot of
humanity now is at a very low vibration
or or dense level that where they need a
lot of help. Is this not a way as far as
cleaning out their ne their density?
Again, it will depend primarily on the
individual because you cannot force an
individual to remain in a vibration that
they simply cannot
tolerate. If that vibration is in other
words too alarming for them, they may
become even more violent and attempt to
get away from
it. So, it will depend upon the
individual. It will depend upon the
amount of love, the amount of support
and the conducive atmosphere that is
created to allow those individuals to
take advantage of that alignment. So,
they're They're going to run from from
themselves. Absolutely. But that's what
any of you
do. That's the only one there is to run
from. That is the only fear. There is
fear of
yourself. So you can't OD in see it made
it sound like you could overdose on it.
Well, in other words, as R just said, if
an individual truly is not prepared to
face what the acceleration will do, then
in that sense, it can be called an
overdose because it may represent a
level of vibration they simply are not
capable nor ready to handle. It's too
fast for
us. So, in a loose sense of the word, it
can be called an
OD. But once you have aligned yourself,
you cannot have too much. Not really.
No. But then once you have aligned
yourself, you don't need it. Then you
won't live in that place that keeps
pulling you back in.
Correct? The idea simply now is that
many of you are teetering back and
forth, back and forth, back and forth.
That's what your transformational age
still is and will be for a little while.
a sort of a neutral limbo state in which
many of you are still teetering back and
forth, toying with the idea of full
acceleration, but constantly retreating
a little bit back into the old idea. But
by this, you are all acclimating at your
own pace in your own good
timing. So in other words, it's for
somebody who's ready for so-called
alignment. are these these devices that we create
are these these devices that we create
on the physical level. Basically,
although their existence does on a
general level promote an ability or an
opportunity for even those that are in
your terms not ready to at least be
aware that those devices exist and what
those devices represent and their
awareness of that can to some degree at
least move them in that direction a
little more than they would have had
those devices not existed or their
symbology not existed at all. So what
any one individual does does have a
general effect on the ability of all the
other individual in your society to be
able to also move in that
direction. So you're raising each
other's consciousness. Absolutely. You
are all part of a whole. You cannot have
one individual do something in a very
accelerated and bold way without making
some impact on everyone else. Even
though let's say 99.9% of the time they
may refuse to acknowledge that impact,
it still had at least some percentage of
an impact, they cannot help some impact
if they have chosen to be a part of the
same society. Otherwise, they'd be
completely somewhere else in another
dimension. And even then, it still has
an impact because everything is
connected, but it's only a matter of
degree. So that's the monkey. Well, like
yes, to some degree, yes, to some
degree. Well, yes. In other words,
that's not the only factor. And what you
are labeling as a hundth monkey theory
is not in and of itself a complete
delineation. But yes in principle we
agree it is that geometric progression
effect. Yes. Well influences
Yes. Well influences
are all we are saying is that the
idea that has been put forth just under
the label the 100 monkey theory is not
necessarily as specific as it could be
in delineating the actual geometric
progression. It's a we have a general
theory and in a general term we all
agree. So it's not simplistic
enough. It is not clear enough.
[Music]
Let me put it this
way. You all already exist on all levels
there are to exist upon. And I'll put it
in the following terminology. There are
an infinite number of
earths. There is an earth right now that
is already
experiencing total harmony and
alignment. Now when you as an individual
decide to start identifying with that
dimensional earth, you start moving into
that dimension.
The more of you that do so create an
accelerative effect that makes it easier
for anyone else to jump on the bandwagon
as you say. They don't have to. They
don't have to. But very soon it actually
becomes more difficult to resist the
positive. And so basically all you're
doing is you are translating yourself
through dimensional frequencies to
become the people in conscious fashion
that populate that earth upon which I do
not mean to seem confusing. You already
exist but simply you do not perceive
yourself as existing there
consciously. So all you are saying is
that your 100th monkey scenario is
making an assumption that you're
actually changing this earth. You're
not. You are taking yourself to another
dimension and thinking it's the same
planet that has changed remarkably.
Yes, absolutely. And whatever frequency
you are is the Earth you remain on or
whatever other planet or dimension you
wish to go to. But the Earth does change
at the same time. It seems to or it
stays at a certain level. It's what you
make it sound like. And they're saying
that from our point of view, it is a
more precise definition to understand
that you are actually moving through a
succession of earths rather than
assuming that the same earth has
actually literally changed. So there's
different parts of humanity moving at
different levels. Absolutely. Although
you do have a general bubble of finding
that you are all at least most of you
are moving in even though individuals
may proceed faster or slower than
others. So there's a certain limitation
and expanse being on this planet,
right? Thank you. Thank you. Yes.
Yes.
Yes. Anything you can imagine is real.
Remember, you cannot imagine
[Music] non-existence. Good
non-existence. Good
evening. Good evening to you. My name is
Michael. All right. I like I'd like to
discuss uh the propulsion systems. Yes.
The uh spaceships. Yes. Now there will
be many different styles and we will
discuss the idea of what we all familiar
with. I would rather discuss the
technology than the
idea if the technology is an idea that
we understand what you mean.
I can only give it to you for now in
this way because there are many ideas on
the planet you have yet to use but I can
give you the general principle and a
beginning of an approach technically
physically. That's very good. All right
then this is our
suggestion and we will explain in the
following terminology. If you have an
terminology. If you have an
[Music]
object perhaps mostly a homogeneous
object that is made out of one material
and you can measure that object in all
of the vibrations that it can give off
and all the ways you can measure it in
terms of its frequencies of
energy. And then you take that object
and you move it to another location and
then measure it again for all of the
frequencies it can give off. You will
ultimately if your equipment is
sensitive enough begin to notice that
there is one slight
difference. One slight difference. And
the slight difference will be the
variable in that energy equation that
represents the difference in location.
Because to us location is not something
an object exists in. It is a property of
the object because space and time are
your constructs. So an object contains a
property of location. The XYZ
coordinates not something space that an
object exists
within. If you can find and isolate the
variable in the vibrational equation of
an object that represents just the
variable of the location frequency. Then
you can also do the following things.
You can take that object, bring it back
to let's say its starting point and you
can create what we call a dynamic
resonance field. It is an isolation
field or what you would colloally call a
force field around that object that will
unlock it or isolate it from the
particular dimension is used to existing
within. within that force field. You can
then impose upon that object the idea of
the vibrational signature that
represents the complete equation of
another local altogether.
When you impose upon that object an
overpowering vibration of a new
local, it must by definition take up
residence at the new local that is
represented by the vibrational you have
with it and cease to exist at the old
local because it no longer identifies
with that variable that represents that
location and will instantly as you say
pop to the new local reinserting itself
into physical materiality wherever the
new vibration is representative of one
way to go about this experimentally as
follows. If I create a chamber that is
isolated from all types of frequencies
as best as you can electromagnetic ray
ray and what have you create a very flat
surface and have a sphere can be hollow
can be solid but again of homogeneous
material. place it in one local and be
able construct the idea to be able to
place it at least 10 of your feet
further as well on the same flat
surface. Then using perhaps what you may
call vibrational tuning forks or any
method you have at your disposal,
initiate a vibration in that sphere. Set
up what you call a sympathetic
vibration. Find out how the sphere
resonates. Find out what its pitch is
and measure that frequency on all
devices you have that can measure any
type of vibrational frequency. Catalog
its signature vibration. Then move the
device to the other point 10 ft away and
measure it against you. Then hit the
device with what you call a sonic
vibration of the frequency that is
representative of the other local. And
you if you have set up your experiment
precisely enough will see the object
move to the first local perhaps rolling.
For now the idea will be to create a
very flat surface and a round object to
reduce the idea of friction because for
now it may not pop. It may simply
however be induced to roll and then stop
at the place that is representative of
the frequency you are feeling onto the
ball. Yes, exactly. but a sonic one. It
is more like creating a slight dip in
the gravity field down and into which
the ball will
roll. That's a warp, a sonic
warp. So experiment with that and also
do your research and experiment with
many other things that are already
available in terms of electromagnetic
fluctuations and frequencies that again
other individuals have already
experimented with. But start with this
and then I'll progress to new ideas.
Then there can be more information both
from myself and from other members of
the association but not until you have
already used what you've already got.
I think one one last question that is
the material object like the speed of
the vehicle is that does it have to be
superc conducting or can it be just
any but what I'm saying is does your
propulsion system work on any type of
object as you just described if set up
in that way basically yes any object can
be teleported in that sense but the more
materials you have in an object the more
sophisticated the system will have to
So for now experiment with things that
are in your terms conductive such as
your aluminum material and your copper
material substances or devices of one
material at a time get more complex
later with alloys and mixture may be
able to allow you to fine-tune the idea
and it will create differences in the
overall effect. But for now our
strongest suggestion will be to employ
materials such as aluminum and copper.
Is that because of electrical
conductivity? Absolutely. So
superconductivity is relevant in this
console. Yes, ultimately it will be and
in fact what you will ultimately
discover is hyper conductivity which is
the ability of the curve to move in more
than one direction at the same time
through the same
material. That will also be necessary to
achieve the interdimensional penetration
that we have achieved that you would
call time
travel. Thank you very much. Thank you
very much. At this time, we will extend
to each and every one of you once again
our unconditional love and appreciation
in allowing us to interact with you this
day of your time and to cocreate a
frequency that will crystallize a common
reality for all of us. We thank you and
vid you a fond and loving and exciting
dream life and life dream for do
remember fundamentally you are dreaming
right now wake up and live the dream you
prefer you might as well it's up to
you and loving the
Heat. Heat. [Music]