All right. Say, how are you all this
evening of your time? As you create time
to exist,
allow us to begin this interaction, this
evening of your time with a
reminder that in two of your week's
time, in honor of your
Halloween, we will share with you our
version of a ghost story.
Next week of your time we have already
told you that we will tell you another
story. It will be entitled the
sound. Tonight of your time in this
interaction we will discuss nothing at
all. That is tonight's title nothing at
all. This to some degree will also be a
little bit of a story. Not exactly in a
story format, but we will be creating
with you a little bit of fun, a little
bit of philosophy in this way, playing
with a point of view. This is not
necessarily meant in your terminology to
be deadly serious.
The idea simply is is that we would like
to discuss a notion that many of you
have explored for quite some time that
really any being in any civilization
gives some thought to now and then and
that is not even so much the how but the
why of everything.
Why do things
exist? Why? Why is there something as
opposed to simply nothing at
all? All right, let us play with this
concept. Now, we will be putting this on
extremely simplified terms, but that is
so we can play with it more easily. it
can be rendered into a type of storybook
level as you say on your planet so that
we may enjoy the understanding through
simplicity. So allow us to begin by
pointing out that there is at least from
our point of view a very good reason why
there is something and not simply
nothing. Usually when you talk about the idea of
Usually when you talk about the idea of
existence and non-existence, what you
think of as nothingness and
somethingness, you tend to forget that
there is actually a third category, a
larger category in which both of these
concepts belong. It is called everything.
First, there is
everything. Within everything, there is
nothing and something. Nothing isn't
everything. Neither is
something together. You have to have
them both to have everything.
So
fundamentally, even though you may
perceive that everything quote unquote
began with
nothing, in order to complete the
concept, to fulfill the concept of
everything which is broader than
nothing, nothing couldn't remain stable.
It had to give birth to something in
order to complete the concept of
everything. Understand so far?
Now we have discussed the idea even as
your own physicists understand that
space and time are your creations, your
illusions, real while you're in it, but
your creations and illusions
nonetheless. And time and space are what
you call discontinuous.
That is another way of
saying that one moment does not actually
smoothly merge into the next. It is
analogous to what you call your frames
of film. One moment, then a gap, then
another moment, then a gap, then another
moment, then a gap. But these moments
happen so rapidly, flicker on and off,
so swiftly that you do not necessarily
on your physiological dimensional level
perceive the gaps in between. Much in
the same way that unless your film runs
too slowly, you do not perceive the
blackness in between the frames, but
perceive it as a smooth continuity of
fluid motion. Physical reality to some degree
motion. Physical reality to some degree
is structured like that. On, off, on,
off, on, off, on, off. With each on
moment being
discreet and whole and different,
however slightly, from the moment before
and the moment to
come. It is entirely its own definition
in that moment. That is why as we have
discussed with many of you, whatever it
is at any given moment you choose to
define your reality as is what you will
perceive and experience your life to be
because you simply continue a particular
definition creating it in whatever way
you want to moment to moment to moment.
What you did in the past can seem
connected but it doesn't have to be. any
sense of continuity is simply because
you choose to believe in the concept of
continuity. But this idea allows us now
to express that everything in containing
nothing and something because it has to
because it must in order to be
everything. allows you to see that how
your physical reality operates is by
nothing and something taking consecutive
turns at playing their part. One moment
there is something then nothing then
something then nothing then something
then nothing. So swiftly you do not
really notice the nothings in between
except as a general a general all
pervasive spacess in which you believe or perceive
spacess in which you believe or perceive
the something is happening. As we have
pointed out, much of what you think of
naturally or normally as empty space
actually contains the majority of
existence. But it is simply not on your
wavelength. You only perceive a very
thin slice at any given moment of the
frequency that has to do with the
somethings you are creating that you are
focused on. The nothings give you an
opportunity to shift gears as you say to
go into neutral so that you can create a
difference from one moment to the next.
If things were not discontinuous in that
way, change would not be able to occur
in the way that it does. You would have
no neutral gear in which to change your
direction. Any attempt at change would
be almost overpoweringly impossible
because you would have to overcome the
entire inertia of the infinite universe
itself in order to affect a change in
any one area if it really all was
absolutely continuous and locked in from
one moment to the next. Now, a
paradox. There really is. All right. All
right. This is going to sound perhaps a
little funny, but we're here to have fun
after all. There really only is one
moment. Just one one
eternal now moment.
It manifests itself simultaneously in
many different ways,
multi-dimensionally, multiaceted,
multiaceted,
multi-expressive. But every moment you
perceive as a different moment is the
same one
moment in one of the ways it has of
manifesting itself. You simply perceive
it as a before or after moment because
of the definition you have given to your
reality of linear time. Before, now
after they all exist now. It is all one
moment. Yes. right right
now, right
here. The idea
therefore is to allow yourself to
recognize that working in tandem with
nothing which gives birth to something
which gives validity to the nothingness.
You need both and always will have both
in order to fulfill the concept of
everything and anything you could
possibly create yourself to be.
We thank you for allowing us to play
around a little bit with these
concepts to perceive that these
endeavors, these
perceptions can be things that uplift
and enlighten you and do not necessarily
have to be taken so seriously even
though they are representative concepts
of the fundamentals of existence itself.
You exist. You always have. You always will
exist. You always have. You always will
because you exist now. Because there is
only one now. Manifesting in all the
ways that it can. Therefore, if you
exist in this now, you will exist in
every one of them. And you always have.
You are being made in the image of the
are being made in the image of the
infinite creator just as infinite and
just as
eternal connected to
everything all that
is. We thank you at this timing for
allowing us to interact with you. We
thank you for choosing to interact with
us and for choosing to function as
ambassadors of your
civilization. That is what you are right
now. Make no mistake about
that. We thank you for allowing me to
function as an ambassador of our
respective civilizations in the
association of worlds.
In return for the gift of allowing us to
interact with you, I will ask you now.
How may I serve you?
Hi, good day to you. Um, I was wondering
on different occasions I've had the
impression that you see us or you sense
sense as um I sense you as an
intertwined series of overlapping
holographic connections to everything
else and everyone else. I identify you
as an individual by recognizing all the
relationships you are to every other
individual and level of consciousness.
Understand? To me, you are perceived
much in the same way we perceive our own
civilization. You are, as anyone is,
living light, a pattern of energy, a frequency,
light, a pattern of energy, a frequency,
a signature vibration that we
sense. If I were to make a shift in my
frequency and in a sense appear
physiologically upon your planet, then
with my eyes, I could see you. in much
the same way that you see. But for now,
because of the telepathic contact in the
way it is happening, I sense you much in
the same way that as you may sit and
enjoy what you call one of your musical
concerts, you sense the energy. You
sense the consciousness behind the
writing of the
music. I sense you in that
way. Understand?
It makes it easier for me
to appreciate how I sense you. Thank
you. Oh, thank you very much. Does that
serve you? Yes, it does. Uh, a number of
people also asked me to ask if you had
anything that just just noticed a
particular specific energy the last
couple of days and asked if you would
comment on that.
The idea to some degree has to do with,
let's say, taking care of
business, a cleaning up of many
acts, a placing things in certain order
because you are approaching that time
now, especially in this your
transformational, shall we say,
convergence year of coming down to what
you call the
wire of allowing yourselves now to sense
the energy as you approach what you call
your all hollow's eve area. As we have
pointed out this Halloween and your
November 1st and November 2nd are the
traditional days of recognition for the
destruction the day before, the day of
and the day after of your
Adalantis. And now this idea is growing
within many of you again to be aware of
the energies you are choosing your
reality to be. So that you are not
choosing destruction this time but the
idea of expansion in loving Wayne. You
are accelerating now to what you call
year of conviction. Your year of 88 as
you call it. You are all after your
small physiological earthquake finding
many things released and unlocked within
your consciousness. You have shaken many
things loose and are now examining them
as you pick them up and reinserting them
into your consciousness in the way you
now prefer to reinsert them. No longer
the old patterns hold. Everything is
coming unstuck within you. That is the
acceleration, the looseness and the
likeness and the rapidity that many of
you may be
feeling. Understand? Yes. Does that
serve you? Yes, very much. Well, thank
you very much. Thank you. And thank you
all for choosing to live on the edge sharing.
Yes. Good evening. And to you. Good day.
I have a question. Oh, all right.
Regarding the permanent magnet, could
you explain in your terms
um the function of the permanent magnet
regarding shape, material, frequency and
is it also possible to create a
perpetual motor from the per permanent
magnet? The idea is that electromagnetic
energy can flow through any crystallized
form in certain ways. not exactly what
many of you think the idea of quote
unquote perpetual motion to be exactly.
It does not defy any of what you would
call your physiological laws. But it is
quite possible to create what you might
call a device andor an engine that will
draw from the electromagnetic field
itself all the energy required can
amplify it and step it up so that it
pulls from other dimensions of reality
energy that may make it seem as if the
energy is coming from nowhere. But it is
not defying any laws. It is serving and
functioning as a channel as a conduit
through which energy from higher states
of existence electromagnetically
speaking can flow down or funnel through
creating a higher pressure than you
might normally get in your own dimension
of reality. Thus making it seem as if
you are creating more energy out of less
energy. But that is not the case. Yes,
it is possible with certain arrangements
and certain rotational masses and
certain ratios and relationships of
electromagnetic wavelength and frequency
especially the one that represents the
pulse the natural electromagnetic pulse
of your planet approximately 7 and 1/2
cycles per second. You can play around
with this much as many individuals in
your society have played around with
this and simply remember that all things
are the product of vibrational states.
All physical objects, magnets included,
of any type, are simply energy in a
certain crystallized pattern. Play with
the idea of the vibratory frequencies
that all things represent. Define them
by their vibratory frequencies. Relate
them to each other in that way and you
will discover a whole new set of
harmonics that can be used to reinforce
and or cancel out any other
gravitational or electromagnetic effect
you are aware of.
Does the material have a direct
relationship to the frequency? Yes, it
can. Yes, because by definition a
different material must be a different
frequency from another material. That's
how you know there is a different
material. It's a different frequency of
the same one energy. The field that's
being uh channeled or pumped in the
magnet, is this what you would term the
ether? What you call the ether is to some
What you call the ether is to some
degree your
dimensions version or
manifestation of one step removed from
the prime energy. It is the first
foundational energy material substance
out of which all further materiality is
crystallized or congealed.
It is not the prime energy itself, not
the prime template, but it is the next
step away from it towards physicality.
Okay. Thank you. I have one other
question. Today I read that the the um
president of the United States may
release to the public
uh his communications with
extraterrestrials uh shortly this year. It is becoming
uh shortly this year. It is becoming
more well known that your public now
desires to equalize that communication
and have that information released. All
the things that individuals on your
planet have been doing to equalize
yourselves with your government and to
open up channels of communication is
responsible now for many changes of
heart and changes of mind that are
taking place within your governmental
structure. We thank you all for this
because your government knows much that
they can share with you. Okay. Thank you
very much. Thank you all.
Sharing. Hello, Bishar. And to you, good day. I'm
Hello, Bishar. And to you, good day. I'm
here to greet you and to send my love.
Well, thank you. Our unconditional love
to you as well. Love you. I'd like to
ask you a few questions about your
planet and your life and your
civilization. We will keep it brief.
Okay. you last uh week you were talking
to someone about whether it was useful
for him to know about his reincarnations
and you said not particularly yet it
appears that you know not only about
your reincarnations but all of ours and
just about everything. So I'd like to
know how not everything. No. What where
do you only what I need to know at the
moment to be of service? Mhm. How did it
develop for you and the people in your
planet? And why did it develop? Because
we learned to live in the moment and
learn to trust that whatever it is we
did need to know, we would know when we
needed to know it. If that involves some
notion of past life, we would know it
when we needed it. The idea we were
simply expressing to that individual you
are speaking of is not that it is not a
valid way of understanding the self. It
is simply that we have observed that
many individuals on your planet place
let us say an
overemphasis on the idea of needing to
know the idea of past lives in order to
believe you have control over the
present. All we are saying is that your
present life contains all the
information it needs to be lived as it
is. And anything you really need to know
that might connect into a past or future
life, you will funnel into your present
knowledge in whatever way you need to to
reinforce what it is you are at the
present. I understand. Now, when you say
that you only have knowledge when it's
needed to serve, does that mean in your
everyday life you don't remember
Atlantis or the different things that
you have knowledge of from former
civilizations? I do not always need to.
No. At any given moment, I will know what I
At any given moment, I will know what I
need to know. Understand that everything
I discuss with all of you in these
interactions, I know absolutely nothing
of or very little of prior to the
interaction itself. In other words, I
have already outlined to you that next
week of your time, we will be discussing
a story which I have entitled the sound.
I have no idea what that story will be.
When it comes time for that interaction,
I will know the entire story and will
relate it to you. Well, are you
channeling from an extraterrestrial in
another planet? In a sense, you are.
Yes. For we are all connected on all
levels. In the development of your planet, did
In the development of your planet, did
you have the assistance of
extraterrestrials that came as you're
coming now in some form to some degree?
Similarly, yes. But our history in and
of itself is slightly different from
yours in the sense that even though we
may have had similar ideas to many of
you, we did not forget quite as much our
connections to everything. And so we
were able to rely very early on upon our
understanding that we had access to all
the information we needed.
Understand? Yes, I do. Um, can you tell
us a little bit?
Okay. Well, I basically want to know
just a little bit about your everyday
life and your All right. What we are
doing with you now is a part of at least
my everyday life and the everyday life
of many individuals upon my world. It is
a world not too unlike your world. It is
a little bit smaller. Gravity a little
bit less. We do not have the fluctuation
of seasons that you do. We have no moon.
Quite temperate, quite green, quite
lush, quite enjoyable. At any given
moment, the majority of our population
exists in what you would call spacecraft
exploring. There are no major structures
upon our planet, no cities as you would
recognize it. The idea is that at any
given moment, all our individuals are
interacting spontaneously creating
whatever it is they wish to do that they
find most exciting. There is art, there
is music, there is exploration, there is
discovery, there is learning, there is
growth, there is many of the things you
have just
different. Understand? Yes. Does that
assist you? Yes. Thank you. Thank you
very much, Sher.
Hello, Bashar. And to you, good day. Um,
speak up. Speak up so that all may
share. Let me move this up. All right.
Better. Um, I have to admit that every
time I come up here to talk to you, I
get this rush of adrenaline. Oh, all
right. I always I love it and I hate it
at the same time. Love it and hate it.
Yeah. All right.
Um, the question that I want to ask you,
I know I've heard it's kind of been
answered before. Um, never in the same
way twice. No. Okay.
Um, you say
that you should not should the Okay. I
don't know how to do that. What? Do what
excites you the most. Do what excites
you the most. Okay. And um with
integrity. Okay. With conviction, with
trust. Okay.
Um, one of the dilemmas I've been
putting myself through in the past few
months, um, has been specifically
because I haven't been doing the thing
that excited me the most. Why not?
Because um somewhere in my little fuzzy
brain, I get the this idea that I I
I cannot make a living at Well, maybe
you should get a
[Laughter] haircut. Shave the fuzz off your
haircut. Shave the fuzz off your
brain.
Remember, if you are aware of a belief,
you say you have a belief that says you
do not believe you can make a living at
doing what excites you the most. If you
are aware you have that belief, then if
you continue to buy into it, it's your
choice. Once you are aware you have a
habit, you don't have it anymore.
So if you
believe that you cannot make a living
that way and if you recognize you
actually have that belief then it's your
choice to perpetuate it or your
assumption that it has to perpetuate on
its own. But it doesn't have a mind of
its own. It's only you continuing to buy
into the idea that you can't make a
living doing what excites you that
allows you to continue to experience the
idea that you can't make a living doing
what excites you. only your definition
that that you are buying into that
perpetuates the experience you are
having. Now
remember when we talk about the idea of
trusting yourself, we are not discussing
something that is difficult to do. Many
of you we find recoil at the idea of
having to learn to trust yourself. Oh,
how difficult that must be, you say.
But you have always trusted yourselves
infinitely. It's just a matter of
whether you trust negatively or
positively more. You have always created
your reality with trust. Absolute
unshakable trust. Infinite
trust. Just depends on your definition
of what you put into the trust
machine. Because what you put into it is
what you get out of it. And it doesn't
have a mind of its own. and it can't
change what you put into it to something
different on the other end. So if you
find that you are in as you say a
dilemma then the dilemma is only product
of your definitions in life. If you are
aware that you prefer a different
lifestyle. If you are aware that you
prefer a different belief if you are
aware you prefer a different definition
then invent it, define it. Write it out.
What is the definition you prefer to
believe in? And understand that new
definition has just as much validity and
just as much ability to become
manifested as any of the other
definitions you had which you no longer
prefer. Just because you had an old
definition doesn't mean it has any more
staying power than any new definition
you prefer from this point forward.
So, you mean I can just change it
overnight? And overnight? You can change
it right now?
Right now? I know. I've been looking at
that for the past couple of weeks cuz I
spoke to you a couple of weeks ago and
um I just very simple tool. We will
share it once again. Your imagination is
the key. Do you have a picture of how
you would rather be? Yes. Can you see
it? Yes. Can you feel it? Yes. Can you
taste it, hear it, smell it, touch it?
Can you allow your senses to be
completely involved in that image of the
individual you would prefer to be? Yeah,
I can. But
okay. And no, but no. And every time,
let me finish. Okay. Sorry. Thank you.
I'm impatient. Why? I don't know. It's
because you don't trust what's going on
in your life right now. You are waiting
for something better to come along.
Nothing better ever will. Many things
that are different and perhaps more
expanded will, but it will not be
qualitatively better than what's going
on right now because what's going on
right now is the most important thing in
your life always. That's why it's
happening. Otherwise, something else
would be happening.
Therefore, when you see that image of
the you you prefer to be, if there is
any circumstance or situation going on
in your life that you, the you believe
yourself to be now doesn't know how to
handle, give that situation to the you
in your imagination you prefer to be and
watch how that you handles it. See that
you handle it with all the appropriate
attitudes and styles and
panach that you would prefer to have.
Watch that you in your imagination
successfully handle that situation. Then
copy it, mimic it, mirror that you, and
you'll get the same result. That's what
your imagination is for, to be the
blueprint to follow it, to mimic it in
the way you prefer to be. And then you
will be that person and have the same
results. It's that simple. So, do I
still um continue to make a living in
the old way in order to pay the rent and
the bills? No. Because the creditor is
coming after me. And understand again
what we have discussed about abundance.
There is more than one way to allow
abundance into your life. By doing the
thing that really excites you the most.
You will allow whatever type of
abundance you need to come into your
life to support you in whatever way is
representative of what you really need
to continue to do the thing it excites
you the most to do. You may not need
some of the things you think you do. And
there may be other things you might
receive that you have at this point no
awareness you could
receive. Circumstances can always change
and fluctuate.
Allow yourself to start acting with
conviction in that direction and every
detail if you act upon the opportunities
that come to you with conviction will
take care of itself. Remember this all
of you details are always subordinate to
your strongest intention. Your intention
is not subordinate to the details in
life. Details fall into place to
reinforce your strongest intention.
Always, automatically, effortlessly,
abundantly, flawlessly, always. There
are no
exceptions. Not even you. Okay?
Understand? Yeah, I understand.
Relax. First of all, trust that where
you are is where you need to be.
Impatience is created because you think
you need patience because you are not
living the life in the moment.
Recapture, rekindle the childlike
curiosity, fascination, and ecstasy with
everything that happens in your life
because everything that happens is there
for a reason. Believe that. Act like you
believe it, and you will be overjoyed
every moment of your life. You won't
care what's coming next because you know
it will only be more ecstasy.
So, I've been feeling sick and miserable
for a reason. Yes, because you do not
believe sufficiently in your own
ecstasy. You are resisting it, fighting
it, and that creates friction and
disease. Okay. Understand? Yeah, I understand.
Okay. Understand? Yeah, I understand.
Pleasant dreams to you. Thank you. Good
night. And to
you, Sharing. Good evening, Bashar. And
to you, good day. Uh, last week you
talked about consensus consciousness.
Yes. Consensus reality, right? uh one
aspect of that that I wondered if you
would discuss is we have decided
uh we've created a hunger in the
consciousness in this reality and to
satisfy that hunger we eat other
consciousness uh in what way we eat plants we eat
uh in what way we eat plants we eat
animals and what have you wondered why
we created this concept where we go out
and eat each other because of the idea
of how you have segregated yourselves to
begin with Not realizing that the power
already exists within you, you then must
rely on the external reality you have
created to sustain you. The more you
center yourself as we have done in that
way, the more you will rely directly on
the energy you are. Even as we do now,
we do not
eat. Your society in time will
eventually blend and balance within its
own energy to understand that you are
always completely sustained by your very
existence and will not have to rely upon
seemingly externalized manifestations of
that for support.
Okay. Thank you. Thank you very much.
Shutting.
Good evening. And to you, good day.
This is the first time I've ever heard
you speak. Well, this is the first time
I've ever heard you speak.
So, we are even. Good.
I want to know if you and where you
live, if if you people ever feel the
disease that you refer to that we feel.
No, thank you.
our civilization in times past. Yes, we
used to we used to have notions similar
to your own of
disease. Shall I share one with you?
Yes, please. It would translate most
appropriately into your language as
caves. Caves meaning in that sense
caverns, holes. We used to have a
disease where the surface of the skin
would become brittle and the underlying
muscular tissue would be eaten away and
would create caverns in the skin that
when the skin broke there would be
literally holes in the body and the body
would be eaten away in that
fashion. That was one disease. But we
have blended and balanced the idea of
our civilization and all the polarities
within it sufficiently so that we now
know we no longer need those particular
types of circumstances in order to force
ourselves to face anything we need to
look at. We are now so willing to
discover anything about ourselves that
we can always do it through ecstasy
rather than the idea of
discomfort. Understand? Yes. Your
civilization is approaching this as
well. In time, you will no longer need
the tool of disease. You do not really
need it right now, but many of you still
believe you do because of the way you
have been taught for thousands of your
years. But you're getting over
that. Understand? Yes. How how quickly
will we get over that?
It is our perception in general terms,
although of course it will be different
for individuals, but the general
consensus reality that we perceive upon
your planet will within what you call
the next 50 to 100 of your years no
longer experience disease at all.
Thank you very much. Thank you. I had
nothing to do with
it. It is your choices that make the
difference. Shing. Good day. And to you, good day.
Shing. Good day. And to you, good day.
Um my question I want to ask is um the
embodiment of the Christ consciousness.
Embodiment of the Christ consciousness.
Um in the Native Americans, some of them
they have a a legend that kind of talks
of a a a being of light that came on.
Okay. Um but the way they described him it
Um but the way they described him it
sounds like Christ that there was a
white ship that came on the water and
instead taken a little boat he walked
every civilization and every culture
will see interpreted it in the symbology
they understand best the expression of
the overall embodiment of the spirit of
any particular world different societies
will see it in different ways okay so
what I want to ask is
um then there wasn't like one Christ
there was like a lot of there may have
been one manifestation that you call
Jesus but no in a sense fundamentally
there are obviously billions of
manifestations of the Christ of the
Christ consciousness of the world's
spirit because all of you are a part of
it what's the population of your planet
that's how many embodiment there
are understand
Okay.
What you call the Christ consciousness
is the collectivity of all the
consciousness physical and non-physical
on your planet. It knows itself as a
singular individual, as a singular
entity. But it also knows itself as the
combination of all consciousness on your
world. And there have been many
manifestations that have reflected the
knowledge of that to you. Jesus was one,
woka another, Buddha was one, Mary was
one. The female polarity of the Christ
consciousness giving birth to its male
half. Okay, there have been many. So what's
Okay, there have been many. So what's
the significance of the timing that it
came like around 2,000 years? The
significance of the timing is simply
that that was the time represented by
your mass consciousness, your consensus
reality, when the initiation of a
certain momentum would do the most good.
Understand? When a spark would cause a
certain type of ignition,
when you needed to see that reflection
most, was it
was it
then did it just come from us or did it
come from like another planet? Would it
was it directly from another? It cannot
be as colloquially and as precisely
placed as that. It is interconnected
with all forms of consciousness. In that
sense, you could say it comes from other
planets. But it is also all of you. It
is your world spirit. It comes from you.
But it is connected to everything to all
that is. Understand? You cannot simply say
is. Understand? You cannot simply say
where does it come from? To its own
understanding. It does not really have
any particular
origin. Understand? Mhm. It is all
things in that way. All ways that it can
manifest are all of its origins and they
are all true and all real. That's what
it means to be a multi-dimensional
creator. It doesn't come from any one
place. It comes from everywhere and in a
sense nowhere.
Okay. Okay. Well, then like in the
Native American studies, it was um it
came at a time that right after a lot of
years of of they called like dark father
figures worshiped like um so was that
any particular manifestation of one
polarity will usually then tip the scale
to experience another polarity so that
it can be blended and balanced so that
everyone is always given an opportunity
to see both sides of the issue. and
choose which vibration is most
representative of the way they prefer to
be. Okay. Because my my qu my other
question had to do with
um when did the matriarch system end and
and why and why the the patriarch and
now are we going back to a matriarch?
You are going back to a blending. Uhhuh.
Neither one nor the other. The blending
of the male and the female within each
and every one of you. You have
experienced both polarities. Now you're
going to blend them. That's the whole
idea of your transformational age. The
blending of all of it. As we have said,
the so-called second coming is the
realization and the awakening of all of
you of the Christ consciousness that
each and every one of you
is all of you understand. Yeah. Well,
thank you very much. You're welcome.
Sharing.
Hello, Bishar. And good day to you.
Uh I would like your help in
understanding a certain phenomenon I've
been observing. Can you all hear this
individual? All
All
right. Um there have been people I've
seen lately who after achieving a very
high state of consciousness kind of
getting into emptiness and uh
nothingness emptiness and nothingness.
Um some will think into a very deep
depression. Yes. And some will go in the
opposite direction, become angry,
violent, almost maniacal. Yes, it has to
do once again with definitions. That's
all definitions.
Remember once again depression is
meditation judged. That's
judged. That's
all. Many things that you call anger,
jealousy, violence are judgments,
invalidations because of old definitions
that individuals no matter how much they
may accelerate may still choose to buy
into simply because for some reason they
do not necessarily know there is any
other way to be. Old definitions can
allow them to take any level of energy
and turn it into any idea positive or
negative. It may also be the assumption
on many of your parts that when you
become spiritually enlightened, you will
no longer be aware of negativity. Not so
just the opposite. You will be more
aware of negativity. You will be more
aware of the fact it
exists. You don't have to choose it. You
don't have to manifest it. But because
some of you think you shouldn't be aware
of it anymore and all of a sudden find
yourself becoming more aware of it, you
may cause a reaction, a negative
reaction within you because of your
primary belief about it. Understand?
Yes, I do. How can someone on the
outside help? Or what does one do if a
person seems to be at the point of being
physically destructive to themselves or
someone else? Fundamental. Fundamental.
Fundamental. Remind them you are the
creator of your reality. What beliefs
and definitions would you have to have
in order to create the reality you're
experiencing? Bring it back home to
them. Okay. Sometimes they don't seem to
to know that there's a problem going on.
They're kind of lost. Then all you can
do to be of assistance to anyone is
first of all not judge that they
actually are truly lost because in that
sense to some degree you are making a
decision for them which you cannot do.
You are trying to be responsible for
their actions which you cannot be. Be
whatever example you wish to be of the
unconditional, remember that word,
unconditional love you choose to be. And
then you can best serve them by being a
living example of something they might
be able to choose for themselves as well
if they want to, if they need to, which
they don't have to. Would you ever
recommend uh bringing them for medical
help? It will depend upon the belief system of
It will depend upon the belief system of
the individual. It will depend upon what
you might perceive might be
representative of something that they
really believe will work for them.
Maybe, maybe not. Okay? It again will
depend upon their belief system.
Now, you can share with them points of
view in a non accusatory way, but again,
whether they take your advice or not is
up to
them. And the idea is not to necessarily
approach them as if you believe they are
lost. Because everyone is eternal. Everyone is
Because everyone is eternal. Everyone is
infinite. And in that sense, no matter
what it is they do ultimately decide to
do at any given moment, as you say, not
that we are condoning negativity, but
still whatever they are doing as you say
is a drop in the
bucket as far as the infinite that you
are. Understand? Yes, I do. So see them
for their strength first of all and you
will radiate trust, faith and belief in
their ability to change when they need
to change.
Get them to change. Yes. Because all you
do then is reinforce the level they're
already on. Mhm. Understand? Yes, I do.
Does that serve you? Yes, it does. Thank
you. Well, thank you very much.
shedding. Hello, Bashar. Good day to you. Thank
Hello, Bashar. Good day to you. Thank
you for saying that you didn't know what
your story was going to be about next
week because it helped me to have faith
that I would know how to verbalize my
question cuz I I still not sure. Well,
you're doing marvelously so. It has to
do with
um a period that I'm going through right
now that I can at best describe as
watering. Watering.
I How does your garden grow?
I don't know yet. I don't know yet. All
right. Have you planted some seeds? Yes.
Well, watering is a natural act. Uh-huh.
To allow them to grow. Do you provide
them with enough light?
Yes. All right. I'm working on it. I'm
doing at it. I'm doing it. Oh. All
right. Yes, you are. Do not be too hard
on yourself, you know. Yeah. Enjoy your
gardening. All of you, many of you are
going for your own version of what we
have called the limbo state. Yeah. But
it's because now you are floating free
in the middle of a vast array of
opportunities. You are in neutral. So
you can now pick and choose which
realities you prefer to crystallize into
the one you will experience from this
point forward as your basic
reality. That's what the watering is all
about. You are seeing what comes up so
you can choose what you really want in
your garden. Understand? Absolutely. Is
this helping you? Yes. Because it seems
like in the process if I try to if I if
I try to think of why I'm crying or why
um I can I can pick any emotion that I
want to to justify it. Yes. But the fact
is that there doesn't seem to really be
one. Not really. It's just a process.
Yes. Okay. Crying in that sense like
laughter is a centering. It is a
releasing. Crying is a centering from a
negative point of view. Laughing is a
centering from a positive point of view.
They both get you there.
Understand? It doesn't always seem
negative. Sometimes it feels full of
love and comfort. When you understand
that it is a releasing, then it does not
have to be perceived as negative because
no situation has built-in meaning. No
situation is inherently one way or
another. So you can see any circumstance
any way you want to. That's the whole
idea. You are now all exploring the very
idea of neutrality itself. Of the fact
that everything is fundamentally blank,
empty, devoid of meaning until you
decide what meaning it has. The meaning
you decide to assign to any given
situation is the act of creation of
manifestation itself.
Understand? Yes. It seems that one of
the toughest parts of walking in this
direction is that you have to deal with
other people's reaction to say the
watering because they think it means
something else. Well, that's all right.
It gives you an opportunity to really
come to terms with the definition you
prefer your reality to be. Sometimes one
of the ways you do that is by hearing
all the other definitions other people
have to offer so you can decide what
definitions you're not.
Okay. Understand? Yes. Well, thank you
very much. Remember that nothing in your
life affects you and affects you in that
sense until you choose to be affected.
Yes. Thank you. Understand? Yes. Well,
thank you very much. Thank you, Bashar.
We know you all have a very tasty
garden.  Good day, Bashar. And to you,
Good day, Bashar. And to you,
good day. I um was here last week for
the first time and I really enjoy you.
Oh well, thank you. We enjoy all of you
and just like this week we are here for
the first time as well. Every time is a
completely new time. I had a lot of
March 15ths this last week. Oh, very
accelerative of you.
Um, I wanted to ask you, uh, one of the
images that, uh, that I've gotten, uh,
intuitively is the
centaur, and I don't know a lot about
it, and I wondered if you could could
enlighten me with anything that you might uh, have
me with anything that you might uh, have
about the centaur.
I think you'll have all the astrologers
in the audience
buzzing to some degree.
The idea primarily as we would perceive
that energy it can be viewed in many
different ways. One is to recognize the
connective power you have from humanity
to nature. What you call the animal of
the horse in that sense represents a new
mode of things in your past symbology.
It is in a sense a more expanded version
of the animal you call the dog which is
the symbol of service in that way. In
this sense it is that strength of nature
which carries you far which carries
humanity. The blending and the merging
of humanity and nature that allows you
to walk and run free of spirit with full
potential and energy running and
flowing. Understand? Yes. When you say
free of spirit, you mean free in spirit,
not free from. No, not free from. Let us
say free as. Yes. All right. Thank you.
Oh, thank you very much.
Shooting.
Hi. Um hi. Hi. Hi.
[Laughter] Um, for the past 2 years, my friend has
Um, for the past 2 years, my friend has
been beaten by her mother, child abuse.
No. All right. And yesterday, she had
called me and was very upset with her
mother. All right.
And I told
her that finally someday she's going to
need to call somebody and ask if it was
child abuse or not because lots of us at
school heard lots of stories about you
know her mother hitting her or mother
doing this to her or anything like that.
So I called first and I was talking to
them asking what would happen stuff like
that and then I called her and then she
called. All right, speak up. speak up so
that all may hear. And she called and
they told her it was child abuse and she
was very upset and she wanted to run
away and she wanted to kill her mother.
No. All right. And I told her that
wouldn't be a good idea because it would
only add to the negativity. Yeah. So, I
was wondering why her mother and my friend
wondering why her mother and my friend
chose this for themselves and a dream I
had that's been going on about a shark.
All right. And I want to know if that
had anything to do with it. Yes, it
does. Individuals in that sense who seek
to physicalize their agony upon
others are simply in a state of
believing that they are
powerless. Sometimes individuals will be
born into their lie that are strong
enough on one level to allow them to
work through this energy which they
believe is devouring them from within.
Individuals that lash out in that way
are expressing a belief they have been
brought up with themselves and perhaps
expressing experiences they have had as
children themselves in understanding
that they are powerless in believing
that they are powerless. They will
resent anytime they perceive strong
power in someone else. your friend is
very powerful. Knew in a sense by being
born to this person that they actually
contain the strength necessary to help
this person to help the mother to turn
the person back into themselves and
allow them to begin to understand how
powerful they are as well by reflecting
it back to them. Now we are not saying
that your friend has to necessarily
remain in that particular relationship
for sometimes a physiological detachment
can be one way of showing the person who
is lashing out what the consequences of
their acts are.
But since it was chosen between the both
of them, all we can say at this time is
that if your friend is willing to find
that power within themselves and express
it radiantly as absolute strength and
unconditional love for the
mother. Any individual who feels
themselves to be powerless will not be
able to stand up to a light that
brightly. They will not be able to
interact with someone that blindingly
bright. If that individual can allow
themselves to focus on their own
power to radiate that unconditional love
to reflect to the mother that she does
not have to believe she is helpless,
powerless, does not have to lash out at
others she perceives to be powerful
because she does not believe herself to
be powerful because she is jealous of
that power because she doesn't believe
she contains the power she sees in
others. if she can remind the mother,
you are just as powerful as anyone else
you perceive in life. In fact, because
you can perceive that power in other
people, it means you have to contain it
as well or you couldn't perceive it.
Radiate that trust, that belief
unconditionally, unswervingly.
It will allow the mother to be more or
less overwhelmed in that way with love.
Wave after wave after wave of
love can change and transform almost
anyone. Now, it can also be perhaps
Now, it can also be perhaps
suggested, as some of you may already
have suggested within your mentality,
that there might be individuals who can
perhaps assist aside from your friend,
the mother, in getting back in touch
with her own power. So, she does not
have to lash out at those she feels
contains more than she does.
So she does not have to deny to others
what she felt she was denied in her own
life. The dream interactions between the
both of them and between you and them
can be very assistive in this
way. You can as you have already
utilized the same symbol of the shark.
Tell your friend not to use the shark in
that sense in a negative way as a
symbol, but to in the dream reality see
the animal devouring all the negativity
itself and cleaning up the energy sea in
which they both
swim. Understand? Mhm. Clean up the old
tissue, the dead
tissue, and let the ocean be pure. Let
the waters between them be clear. She
can use the symbol that way. It is a
present you can give to your
friends. Understand? Yes. And you can do
it as well to add your
assistance. Does that serve you? Yes.
Well, thank you very much. Thank you.
Pleasant dream. Thank you, Sharing.
Hi, Bashar. Good day to you. I've
thought about you often. Oh my.
It wasn't bad.
[Music] All right.
All right.
I have created a pregnancy. Oh.
And I know that I h that we create
things for growth and for change and
that I wouldn't have created this if I
didn't have the ability to deal with it.
Have you allowed yourself to be in touch
with the consciousness?
[Music] Um that's a very interesting question.
Um that's a very interesting question.
Well, thank you very
much. Actually, I think the answer to
that is no. All right. Why not?
I've been seeking um outside yourself.
All sorts of opinions. Why not? The one
of the one closest to you, your own and
that of what you would call the child
because it's not a child yet. Well,
actually, I have spoken to this soul
who's co-created this with myself and
the father. What have you gotten?
I'm not clear yet, but I see the growth
and a lot of the um insight that this
has already brought to me. All right. Do
understand that not everything in that
terminology must come to physiological
fruition in order for you to learn what
you need to learn out of it. You know,
well, I've been thinking about that
because I know we discussed that at at
great length at another point. And I've
been thinking about this issue of of
prolife. Yes. This issue of I think
abortion is a very valid choice. All
right. The idea, however, is simply that when
The idea, however, is simply that when
the timing is appropriate, nothing will
stop it. When it isn't, nothing will
allow it to happen. Why not simply trust
that if whatever is happening to you is
happening that it is representative of
your overall timing and whatever needs
to work out will work out appropriately
one way or another. Why not trust it?
And on one level I do trust on one
level. Yeah. There is only one level to
you. You don't have to segregate yourself
You don't have to segregate yourself
into many levels. Well, what I what I
respond to is the outside pressure that
there is a limit, a time limit, a this
or that. All of these. Why? Well, why do
you choose to buy into those
definitions? They don't have to exist
for you.
What time limit? Well, it seems to me
that a time limit in terms of making a
decision and a choice about bringing
this soul to fruition or not No
No
matter what you may believe those time
limits to
be, if for some reason it serves you to
not have the child, then whatever needs
to happen will happen before such a
so-called time limit is reached.
Relax. Your nervousness is preventing
you from seeing clearly that everything
is still working out in perfect timing.
You don't have to concentrate on the
time. The timing is flawless.
Learn what you need to learn while you
have the opportunity.
I was listening to the to one of the
women who was up here before me speak
about uh the watering and the
opportunities and the choices in the
gardens and this other woman speaking
about uh the high and the depression.
And I just recently came out of a period
which was extremely high. It was expanded. It
was extremely high. It was expanded. It
was every moment full. And there were
enormous successes and creations that
came out of that time period. And in the
timing of this, I'm I feel as if I have
been in a depression or um a meditation
or as you say a meditation, which I much
prefer. All right.
um in these last few weeks and the
timing of it after this extremely high
creative time for me. Yes. Yes. Well,
you did some creating, didn't you? Well,
yes, I certainly did.
[Music]
Yes. Yes. It seems that it seems Yes.
Seems what, Bashar? My trust has has
been enormous and I I love the trust
that I have in It always is. I your
trust is always the same level. Always.
It's the definitions that make it seem
different.
So your uh suggestion to me is to simply
allow myself to exist in that trust and
however this situation is meant to
resolve itself, it will. Well, not that
you can't be in touch with what's going
on, but the idea simply is is that if
you really do understand that all the
events that do manifest in your life are
the product of your agreement and your
own timing, and you choose to prefer to
believe that they all fit into the
person you know you chose to be, then
why doubt what is happening? Why assume
that what is happening has nothing to do
with the original agreement and decision
you made for the life you chose to be? I
don't think that. Well, then I I do I do
believe that obviously I chose this
because it's here. Yes. And I do
recognize that. Then what are you
worried about?
It seems to have to do with some kind of
power in self. The power of self. Yes.
to make a decision and to create as you
say the kind of reality I would wish to
live. Yes. And in but you see what
you're doing is assuming that this
circumstance isn't representative of
that desire. You don't always analytically
desire. You don't always analytically
consciously know all the ways what you
desire could
manifest. Let it come to you in the way
it comes.
You do not necessarily recognize all the
doors through which it could come. You
cannot necessarily predict the manner of
its appearance. In knowing you have put
the main desire out, then assume that
what happens following the putting out
of that desire is the way the
manifestation needs to be represented to
show you the true path of least
resistance. It may be a completely
unexpected method, but if you understand
that it is the result of your desire,
then you will go with it and examine why
it happened that way. Even though you
may not necessarily have to analytically
always know all the specific reasons,
just know it must be a part an
expression of the unfoldment of your
original desire, even though it comes in
a format you didn't expect.
You cannot always analytically know all
the ways in which it could
manifest. Let yourself be
surprised. Do you want your life to be
boring? My life has been anything but boring.
My life has been anything but boring.
All
right. Let yourself be surprised by the
way you choose to do the things you want
to do because the way it happens is the
way that will allow you to learn what
you need to learn for the next thing
coming along.
understand? Yes, I do. Thank you. One moment. Yes. Stand [Applause]
[Applause]
there. Breathe slowly and turn slowly
around three times. One breath per
turn. Feel energy rising from your feet all
Feel energy rising from your feet all
the way through you out your head in a
ringlet all the way up into infinity all
the way back down through your body down
to the center of your planet up and down
three times as you turn. See it as a hot
white ring of golden light up and down.
Up and down.
That ring represents the connectiveness
and the communication you have with all
levels of
consciousness. As you breathe, you are
breathing with the universe as one. You
know what you're doing. Everyone you
have made an agreement with knows what
they're doing. Trust
yourself and relax.
Thank you very
much. At this timing, you may all take a
short break. We will resume contact in
approximately 10 to 15 of your minutes. [Applause]
How's it going? Great.
Your attention for your attention for
just a moment, please. Uh, here's the
next names. Uh, Mary Jesco, Eileene,
Molly, Don Stewart. Continue.
Hi, Bashar. Good day to you.
Um I have an interesting observation
that I've made uh regarding uh present
and a past relationship I've had. All
right. Douche. Okay. Uh this past Well,
it's the past relationship is a present
relationship as well, right? But it is
not in the same capacity, right? Uh it
is uh my friend Paul from Wisconsin. We
involved in one at in one at one time in
a relationship uh of a romantic value as
we define it here. Uh uh it didn't work
out and and we parted from that.
However, we're uh we're good friends
now. And there's a worked out as it
needed to to represent what you needed
to learn. Yes. Yes, it did.
Um the interesting connection I've seen
one of the
uh there there's a powerful draw or
connection with Paul at this time and
the person I've attracted into my life
now uh has a strikingly uh large
quantity of similarities uh to should
that be so surprising?
Uh well, I was hoping that well no I
wasn't hoping but uh I was thinking that
perhaps I had what I had learned from
the relationship uh from Paul would not
need to be learned all over again. It
doesn't assume it is the same thing.
Okay. It it feels quite similar. All you
are doing is feeling a vibration that
represents a particular frequency that
you may still be on that represents
different ideas you are going to
explore. It is a vibration that also is
to some degree representative of the
overall family vibration you all are to
each other. It is simply a vibration of
recognition. Okay. uh this present relationship
Okay. uh this present relationship
although there's a strong connective
connect connectiveness as well. Yes,
there's also a a great degree of
struggle involved in it um to some
degree. Now we are not saying this is
the only reason we are only telling you
what we perceive as one of the variables
within the energy equation. Both of
these individuals you are discussing
have recently in other lives been what
you call to some degree not necessarily
literally biologically but in the
capacity of what you call your children
to some degree you are simply
recognizing a certain type of education
now going on between you the similarity
to some degree has to do with the fact
that they both do have similar issues to
resolve within themselves. Uhhuh.
Understand? Yes. I would agree with
that. Therefore, you are simply being
available to reflect to each in turn
similar ideas so that you can again grow
in the way you need to be of service in
the way you need to allow them to grow
in the way they need to and be of
service to you in the way they require
to. Okay. Understand? Right. Right.
Well, it it seems to I I do understand
what you're saying. Uh it seems to me at
this time that the uh the issues that
were uh uh of that created a struggle in
the relationship that Paul and I had in
the past are very similar to the ones in
the present. I I felt that I I really uh
had a grasp and understanding uh on
those issues at that time. No. All
right. I seem to be drawing the same
thing back. But again, understand you
may simply be getting another member of
your family that has many of the same
things to work out. Now that you have
gone through it once, you know, it's
different and you can be of more
accelerative assistance to the other
individual by not reacting the same way
you used to. Okay. Understand? Yes, I
do. Uh uh you have made an agreement to
reflect certain things. doesn't mean you
cannot attract other ideas as well. But
you have made an agreement to reflect
certain things to that individual. Okay?
Do not assume that you are missing
something. Uh-huh. Do not assume that
you are in that sense truly struggling.
It is only your definitions once again
which can allow it to seem so.
Uhhuh. Okay. uh in relation to one of
one of the similarities uh in regards to
the same question between the both of
them are there's a tendency of uh manic
depressiveness okay uh but it is not a
tendency it is a choice okay they both
choose to manifest that yes and uh Paul
uh has been one who has been diagnosed
by our society as having manic
depression and um it is another
variation in this pace of some of the
tantrums they used to throw.
Okay. Okay. Well, he's presently on uh
on medication of this sort. There will
always be a quote unquote
physiological reason for everything that
occurs in your consciousness first, but
it does occur in your consciousness
first. We will usually give you quote
unquote the consciousness reasons, what
you might colloquially call the
metaphysical reasons, but you are always
going to manifest some
physiochemical mechanical reason to give
yourself a physical reinforcement or
symbol of the idea you decided to play
out one way or another. But these things
are not literally the causitive factors.
They are the reactive factors to an idea
which was begun in your
consciousness. This goes for any event.
Okay. How does one in Paul's case uh
who's presently feeling dependent on
this medication, however, has made a
choice to attempt to wean himself off of
uh the medication he's taking for manic
depression. Uh it is one way for now of
that individual to come to terms with
the whole idea of the interaction that
you have already had the whole process
of being weaned from the parent of
learning a
true independence.
Uhhuh. Understand? Yeah, I understand
what you're saying. It's very relevant.
Yeah. Um yes, could you give some
practical uh uh measures of assistance
uh that I could refer back to him at
this timing simply once again that the
power is within and that the choices
come from the definitions you have
bought into most strongly. So the
clearer his definitions are about what
he believes to be true about life will
allow him to get in touch with why he is
creating what he is creating. But his
process and his pace are his own.
Okay. There cannot be much more than
that we can share at this moment. Okay.
Since he is in mid-process. Okay. Thank
you. Thank you very much. And thank you
for the creation of your family reunion.
Sharing. Hello Bashar. And to you good
day.
Um I need to be closer. Okay.
I have no idea what I want to ask you.
Congratulations. Maybe it doesn't have
to be a question. Would you like to turn
it into a statement?
Okay. Um, I love having you here and
hearing what you have to say and what
you share with us. All right. Do you
understand that all we are saying is
only a reflection of what you already
know? Yeah, I do. And I then love that
about yourself as well. All of you.
Love the fact that I have the ability to
understand. Yes. The unity.
Yes. Love the ability to understand. You
know all the things we are talking about
already. Okay. Love it in us. Love it in
Okay. Love it in us. Love it in
yourself. Love it in all that is.
Okay. Um All right. Now I have a
question. All right.
If I have I I know I have a great power
but I don't. You all have the same
power. But I I and I tend to not use it.
Oh, you always use it. Always. Remember,
you cannot help but use it. Uhhuh. You
are always using 100% of your power. As
we have said, even if you use 90% of it
to make it seem as if you're only using
10%, you still use 100%.
You are always using it. It's just a
matter of
defining where you flow the power into
what types of manifestations, whether
you create the illusion that you hide
some of it from yourself or not. But
that's all definitions. You're always
using 100% of your power. Always. So if
my perception is that I'm only using 10%
of my power, then get in touch with the
definitions of why you would believe you
are only using 10%. And it will put you
in touch with the remaining
90. Find out where you are flowing
it because you are flowing it. It is
simply a matter of your focus, of your
attitude, of your
definitions. Understand? Not quite. It
has to do with what I'm conscious of,
what energy of my own I'm conscious of
of using to some degree. Yes. Although
this does not necessarily mean you have
to be quote unquote analytically aware
of everywhere it's going. Yeah,
you can be conscious of it in the way it
plays out in your physical life. You can
see by all the interactions you have,
all the synchronicity that occurs in
your life. Oh, there's my power. Oh,
there it is. Oh, there it is. You are
creating in a sense, in a real sense,
the room you are in all the individuals
within it.
Your version of them is what you are
creating. Look at what you're doing with
your power. You can see it all around
you, can't you? Yeah. Well, there it is.
Okay. Thank you. Well, does that assist
you? Very much. Well, thank you very
much. Would you do me a favor? Yes. Give
yourself a hand.
Thank you.
Sharing. Bashar and to you. Good day. My
question involves um the uh close
encounters from the Zeta Reticuli group.
Yes. And one of the things that um was
described was a glowing white sphere and
I wanted to know if you could describe
the purpose of that sphere and also I've
been very drawn to use it in my own
meditations and found it to be very
powerful. Oh yes, go right ahead by all
means. Let your imagination be your
guide in that sense. The glowing white
sphere to some degree is representative
of the
intersection of one consciousness with
your dimension of experience. Their
consciousness with your dimension of
experience expressed in energy terms. It
can fluctuate and vary from time to
time. Sometimes you may perceive it as
the idea in that sense of a ship or a
field which surrounds a ship. But the
idea is that it is mostly the result of
the intersection of their energy with
your energy fields.
Um it was described to be used um to
almost put a hypnotic yes spell. It is
the interaction of consciousness to
consciousness. It is the interface.
So in my own uh discoveries I've been
using uh the tetrahedrin because I would
uh I've been drawn to try and create it
myself eventually. I'll try create it. I
will create it myself eventually. Can
you give me any guidelines in using it
as a truly materializing it as a tool?
It is again a tool a crystallin form
that represents the basic fundamental
unit of physical reality. The
tetrahedral structure is the simplest
unit of physical reality you can have
and that represents therefore the gate
between the physical and the
non-physical universe in your terms. So
I can you would describe that as the
most direct way I could use to truly
actually materialize light myself if you
wish. Yeah. Many of you are becoming
more sensitive to the idea of the
intersection of consciousness in your
electromagnetic field anyway. You are
beginning to see colors and lights you
formerly couldn't see. You are living
light itself.
So the idea is that you can allow your
focus to shift to be able to perceive
more and more the direct interaction of
consciousness with the electromagnetic
field itself and you can perceive that
as light. Yes. All right. Thank you very
much. Remember also that when you see it
in your imagination that is real just as
real and that will allow you to blend it
into the physical reality as well. When
there is not as much of a distinction in
your definitions between imagination and
physical reality, you will understand
that what you see in your imagination is
just as solid as what exists in physical
reality and that physical reality is
just as dreamlike as your imagination.
So in it, so in the in blending the
barriers between my imagination and yes,
this reality, the act of blending is in
creating definitions that do not allow
there to exist barriers between those
things that allow them to be one for
everything is the same one thing.
That's very helpful. Well, thank you
very much.
Thank you for lighting up our lives.
sharing. Good evening. And to you, goodbye. Good.
Good evening. And to you, goodbye. Good.
I want to go over something and see if
you can fill in any holes where there
may be a holes. This all right. We're
talking about create from our beliefs or
definitions. Yes. And then that is the
blueprint, right? And then you activate
it with your emotions, your strongest
emotions. And then you pattern it with
your thoughts.
And then we come into the part of
judgment in which we use um polarities.
Yes. Expectations. Yes. Now this is not
necessarily a natural thing. It doesn't
have to happen. But this is what some of
your society has created as their quote
unquote habit pattern. That's not an
automatic thing to have invalidation.
This is what has been happening. Yes.
Okay. And my question is, is this the e
the uh judgment that creates time and
aging? Yes. Because the more you segregate and
Yes. Because the more you segregate and
separate things, the more pieces you
create things to be, the more space and
time there has to be for them, all these
pieces to exist within. The more you
live in the now, in an integrated,
unified whole now, single idea, the less
space and time there needs to be to fit
everything in your
life because there aren't as many
divisions. Understand?
Yes, I do. Emma, on that, if you make a
judgment of a let's say we have a a
moment, let's separate a moment. A
moment. We have a moment. Yes. And then
we have judgment. Okay. in the
invalidational sense is usually the way
we mean it. We do not simply mean
discernment or observation.
I know you mean judgment at that point.
Then we create additional time and
space. Yes. At that point. Yes. And so
we have a tendency also to u diffuse
ourselves. Yes. Because as your phrase says if you
Yes. Because as your phrase says if you
judge you become the vibration of
judgment itself. That is what your
phrase means. Judge not lest you be
judged. It's not a
command. It's a mechanical
principle. It means that if you judge,
if you invalidate, you become the
vibration of invalidation itself. So as
you render things into segregation, you
become dispersed. Yes. It doesn't mean
you're being judged from outside. It
means you render yourself more into the
vibration of separation, space, and
time. Okay. So you've separated yourself into
Okay. So you've separated yourself into
these different moments. Yes. or and
then you have to recollect yourself and
that takes time. Aha, that was
how do you recollect yourself? By living
more in the moment,
by not creating as much time, by not
invalidating, by trust, by faith, by
love, by light, by excitement. So just
by living in the moment, you will re so
to speak recollect yourself. Yes. And
reenter. Yes.
That's it. It's that simple.
Go for it.
You mean I've been doing it the hard way
if you insist. Yeah. Okay. Thank you
very much. Thank you very much. Shing.
Blessings. Bashar. And to you. Good to
be here in person with you. Although I
thought about you many times when I was
in Europe this time. Oh. All right. But
I'm not literally in person with you.
No, I know you're not in. But we are
with you in spirit. But and I'm very
happy about that. Enjoy. Um, interesting
experiencing been going on here. Before I left for
been going on here. Before I left for
Europe, yes, I went to talk with one of
the channels and before he went into
trance, he announced to me that whole
golden light was coming into my solar
plexus and there was this tall Indian
named White B that wished to give me
something. All right, fine. I thanked
him for that. Yes, that was it. Uh,
another channel later on down the
stream. Instead of speaking to the
entity that I had presupposed I was
going to speak with, here come a white
bow. Yes. To get in the whole background
of our relationship. Yes. Told me that
when I was in Italy that I would have um
I should go to a chapel. Yes. And walk
up to the altar and see what I had left
there. No. God knows when. Of course, he
wasn't going to tell me where this
chapel was. And you know how many
chapels there are in the in the country
of Italy? Two or three.
hundred or thousand. All right. Yeah.
Okay. So, I went about my business
enjoying the harmonic conversion,
enjoying the clear air and the mountains
and the green pastures. Oh, thank you.
And I found myself Yes. in the
catacombs. Yes. And um this tingling
comes up the back of my spine all over
the body. Nice. And I now have lived
these experiences enough to know that
when that happens, I pay more attention
to that than what anybody is saying.
Thank you.
And I seem to have been in the altar of
a St. Sebastian. All right. Didn't know
a thing about him, but I didn't hear
anything from the tour guide. So when I
came home, I dug my face into the
Encyclopedia Britannica and read up on
St. Sebastian. Yes. Now, now I wanted to
tell you how much I appreciate your
encouragement to us for trusting
ourselves. Well, thank you. Because I
now know that when I get that expression
of feeling in the body that something
else is going on besides just the
superficial buy and sell over here.
Well, do tell.
I find that my whole metabolism is
changing. Yes. Yes. I'm uh I don't know
if it's the body temperature or not. I
wonder if you could elucidate a bit on
that because I think some of it may be
reflected in body temperature but your
entire metabolism is crystallizing in a
different way. Yes. How's your
breathing? Uh much deeper than it ever
was before. Thank you. Okay. Yes. Um the
uh light colors that I get in meditation
are much more sharply focused and much
more vital and intense. Okay. Now comes
the cranium here. Yes.
is I I'm hearing vibrations. Oh my. Oh
my. Yes.
Do you allow it to be music to your
ears? Uh I allow it in in a friendly
manner and say this is what it is. Thank
you. Okay. I also find myself to be
counseling people in some sort of a
psychological way which is a new thing
to me. No.
In this particular life existence. All
right. Okay. So, mirror mirror, I just wanted
Okay. So, mirror mirror, I just wanted
to acknowledge you and thank you for
sharing your power and your strength
with us to help us realize our own power
and our own our unconditional
appreciation at allowing us to reflect
back to you your inner life. And I'm not
even going to ask you to tell me what
I'm going to do next because it really
doesn't matter because whatever I do
next is going to be right where I should
be and what I should be doing. Well,
thank you. I wouldn't want to unwrap
your presents anyway.
Thank you again. Thank you. One moment.
One moment. One
moment. Let's just say
yes. As some of you have already
understood a different meaning to your
word that from the old lives you have
lived to the life you are living now
communion will take on a different
meaning. Mhm. Thank you. So be it. Thank
you. Shing.
Hello Bashar. And to you good day.
I ran into an article in this secret of
SAF that this paragraph really intrigues
me. I'd like to try it on you. It seems
to have to do with the kacina energy. A
similar said the sun and its
significance. All right. Apparently, the
energies of humankind and the energies
of the physical environmental natures
around human beings coexist in a
partnership. The human being creates his
own world while the sun and stars create
the specific magnetic blueprint of the
physical universe. Somewhere in between
the two creations lies the coexistence
and the harmony as energies are moved
from one system to the next. Yes. In a
complete harmonizing focus following the
sun's blueprint, the energies of the
genetic blueprint of each individual as
well as his
mind spirit dreams, wishes, whims, and
intentions are programmed against the
energies of the sun in a sense. Okay.
the uh in the quasi planar realities,
the structure realities that give rise,
that give shape, that give form to all
that you consider to be the different
universes and dimensions of experience.
In
between all those different universes
are universes unto themselves. The quasi
plane our realities the abode of the
kacina energy. The messengers, the
energy. The messengers, the
manifesttors, the deliverers of the
magnetism that delivers in that sense a
face of a blueprint an expression in
archetypal energy reflections in the
substream of consciousness.
Okay. [Laughter]
[Laughter]
I get that it's uh the question is this
the theory of this is kind of like the
sun giveth and the sun taketh away and
it seems to fit in on earth we have a
life expectancy of so long well that is
changing and on us a sunny it's a lot
longer yes they're saying it's like the
sun we need the sun for our birth and
growth and then after a certain period
of time it starts decaying the the uh
glands and stuff in the body on a
sequential basis all right but again
That physical mechanism is only a
reflection of a belief system of a
definitional system within you. As soon
as you begin to uplift and accelerate
your vibratory level to more match the
vibration of certain parts or aspects of
what you call your central star, then
there will not be the friction between
your lower vibration and the higher
vibration of the star. The friction will
not wear you away. As soon as you match
that frequency, it will vitalize you and
sustain you directly for longer periods
of time. Okay, that seems to be the crux
of the thing is like this is a
technology that seems like it can clean
up your gen your genetic patterns and
everything. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. But
instead of going all this, if all you
have to do is change your belief system,
then this is going a long way around
just to Well, that is the way you have
done it. You don't have to do it that
way. Any machine or technology you
create is only an expression of
consciousness anyway. It's up to you. Whatever works
anyway. It's up to you. Whatever works
best for you, whatever works as a
process, as a tool. Different
individuals will have different choices,
preferences. Okay, this one excites me right now, so
Okay, this one excites me right now, so
I'm going to look into it some more.
Thank you. All right, thank you.
shedding.
Hi Bashar. And to you. Well, I wanted to
Good day. Good day. Um, you are doing
some rewiring.
I I am. Um, rewiring in your brain
structure. Is that why my head is
killing me? Yes. It is also because you
are preparing yourself to enter a new
field of
endeavors. You are allowing yourself to
begin to reel eyes.
that you have the capacity to really
affect physical change with your points
of view and you are going to be slipping
into your version of the mainstream to
allow yourself in those expressions of
conviction in a loving way to assist the
change that needs to happen upon your
planet. You are rewiring yourself in
that sense. And for now, because you are
to some degree, well, I'll say kicking
yourself upstairs right now because of the old
upstairs right now because of the old
ideas, it may hurt for a while because
you are undertaking to some degree your
own operation without as much anesthetic
as you used to need.
You are rewiring yourself.
Literally when you say um to manifest a physical
when you say um to manifest a physical
change, you mean in what my desires are
for myself or Yes. And also in service
to the entire planet.
Okay. Becoming involved as you say
physically in many different ideas going
on on your planet. H Bashar. Yes. I want
then along with that cuz you're always
that's right on. Um I want to share
something I'm excited about. Okay. Oh,
by all means. And you beat me to it, but
so I'll share it with you. Why? Um well,
I'm getting ready to um travel again,
right? And I'm really really excited
about it because I've learned so much
from the last time that I was going to
travel. You are stepping up. Yeah,
definitely. A new cycle. Yeah, I'm so
excited, man. Yes. And the thing is, I
don't even know where I'm going, but
it's like I don't know where I'm going.
And but you'll find out when you get
there, right? And it's okay. I don't
know where I'm going, but it's kind of
like I already know that I'll meet the
people that anyways I'm so excited about
it. Well, thank you. Thank you also for
choosing to be so bold. Thank you for
choosing to be so centered and thank you
for choosing to be a living example of
how others can allow themselves to
center their own being to create the
changes that then will represent what
you call heaven on earth. I know it's
happening. I'm so happy. Bashar, can I
ask a question? Well, along with the
sharing, it's kind of more like sharing
an idea. No. All right. Um because this
one still kind of confuses me. But you
know what's so neat about all my
confusions now? It's like I'm working
them out. So it's okay. But okay, now
there's this thing, right? Okay. Yes.
This thing. Yes. This thing. Hang on.
I'm getting to it. I'm so slow tonight.
My head's killing me. Okay. So there's
this uh I've talked to you about
abundance and creating what you want all
the time. That's all I talk about,
right? So there's this thing people call
visualization. Yes. So I went to this
like you know dumb weekend thing with
and it was like you know in order for
you to have what you want in your life
you need to define what it is right. And
so the whole time I was getting sick and
nauseous going, well, the thing is if I
felt and if I knew in my being that I'm
always doing the most perfect thing and
my life is exciting and I visualize the
major intent of my life, then why do I
need to worry about the things that I
want in my life? Like for instance, can
I give an example? Okay, by all means.
Okay, so I tried it, right? And I wanted
to go on this kayaking trip that me and
you spoke about last time. So I
visualized myself like in the white
water and doing the rolls and all these
exciting things. And see the whole thing
is it never happened. Yes. And so then I
So the whole thing You mean physically,
right? Physically it never happened. So
what I That doesn't mean it didn't
happen, right? Okay. Well, here's the
thing. It's like a multi-dimensional
question because Yeah. Okay. Okay. So
the lady was saying you must it's so
important in your life to say
specifically to create in the now the
thing that you want in the future. So on
one hand, if you're creating in the now,
why even have to do it in the future
because you're living it in your dreams,
right? That can happen that way. Okay.
And then the other thing I realized is
why even limit it to the kayaking
experience because look what happened
anyways. I ended up not going and that
was perfect, too. So can you tell me?
Well, the thing is if you really think
about it, people are, you know, we're
like visualizing what we want. So I sit
in my car driving going, I want so and
so. And then I think, well, why even say
that? Why don't I just say I am having a
most ecstatic wonderful experience and
however it manifests will excite me.
Yes. Why not? Is that is that okay? You
know like
see the thing is I told this to this
lady right I said let me offer you my
philosophy here right? So I told her
this and she says well then you'll never
know where you're going because you're
not defining what you want. And I said
well I have just in a more general way.
I've just Right. Okay. So a very wise
man a very wise man named Bashar said
abundance the definition of abundance is
having what you need when you need it.
That's what you said. Okay. Now I want
to know yes I have what I need when I
need it but I want surplus. Can you I
Okay. Well, the reason is
the only idea to use your example that
needs to be factored into the equation
is to simply once again get up and act
on the things you want to do. I am all
right then. Okay. Because you know,
okay, you know, if you really
know to use again your example, you
could have simply gotten up and gone
kayaking.
Whoa. Wait a minute. No, no. I'm not
just going to go, "Oh, yeah, you're
right." No, wait a minute here. See, the
thing is when I say I mean, I've been
talking about this for years now. Okay.
The thing is I want I want to get
something, right? So, it costs me money.
I don't have the money. So, I go, "Okay,
yeah, but I have what I need when I need
it. But I want to have what I want when
I want it." Yes. But the idea we are
sharing with you is that you don't
necessarily always need the money to get
it. That's what we're saying. Well, this
was Well, okay, that's fine, but what
about when I want the 20 bucks to go buy
dinner or something? I mean, my god, I'm
like, I'm broke, right? And it's like,
okay, I'm doing what I want. I'm very
Why do you not explore all the possible
ways you could get dinner without the 20
bucks? Because I've done that for years.
I'm I want the 20 bucks now. Why? Cuz I
want I want I cuz it's easier just to
say, "Okay, instead of going, oh, you
know, hey, can I have dinner at your
house or whatever?" Right? One moment.
One moment. Here's where your
definitions start getting refined. First
of all, look at the fact that you are
considering those other ways to be less
than the idea of having the money. Yes,
you are approaching it as if it is a
poor way to be. I'm poor. Yes, you're
not poor. I know, but I think of myself
as poor when you have to borrow $10 for
gas. It's like I know I'm bold because
I'm going on my trip right now and I
say, "Okay, it'll all come together."
But I would love. And if for some reason
you were to drive into a place and all
of a sudden win a lifetime supply of
gasoline, wouldn't you feel rich?
Yes, I would. Well, then all I'm saying
is that you don't necessarily have to
get it in the way you think you must. We
are not saying that the money cannot be
there. But the idea simply is is that if
you define other ways as being poor,
then you don't really give yourself an
opportunity to experience those other
ways in the way you could be
experiencing them abundantly. Your only
definition of any other way other than
the money is that it is poor. Not rich.
No, not always. No, not always. But
obviously a vast majority of the time.
Well, it would be nice to whip it out of
my own wallet, you know? I mean, that'd
be
fun. I mean, I would prefer that. I'm
getting honest here. I would prefer
that. But examine why you would prefer
it. Because it gives you freedom. Why
doesn't the other? Because you depend on
other sources for it. Not true. Are you
saying you don't depend on other sources
for money?
Not if you're doing what you love to do
and you're just creating your what you
know then you will get whatever type of
abundance you need to get what you need.
So can we redefine abundance then as
something like maybe not just getting
what you need when you need it but
um well you end up participating getting
what you want when you want it.
Well, yeah. I'd like that. Yes, you can
define it that way. All we are saying is
that sometimes if you are paying very
close attention, the only reason you do
not manifest it in the way you want it
is because of the invalidation you are
placing on some of the other ways you
could have gotten it.
Okay. So, a starting point would be then
to take off the judgment of the way it's
coming in. Yes. And that would make it
all equal, whether it's the money or the
whatever. Yes. Yes. And that would free
it up. So then you don't have to say,
"I'm going to have $5,000 by March 1st."
No, you can say if I have a situation,
and one of the ways the situation could
be alleviated is to have $5,000 by March
1st. I will allow that to be one of the
ways, but I will also allow the
situation to be alleviated by any other
form of abundance that might come along
more quickly. Right? Because that would
just put money on one on the level of
details. And if your intention was to
have the incredible experience you want,
the money would just be one of the
details and oh the money is a detail.
Now if you choose to create the money to
be an end all be all in itself if you
focus on the idea that you must have the
money. You can create a reality where
all you get is the money. No, I've never
had that. All right. However, I don't
have that problem. If that is really not
your focus, if that's really not your
focus, then you will have the money when
you really need it. But you will have
other forms of abundance as well. Many
times when individuals really become
insistent that it is the money they
really want, they also do not sometimes
at the same time cocreate an opportunity
to use the money. They just have the
money. Recognize there have been situations in
Recognize there have been situations in
your civilization when many people have
had a lot of your money and died popper
because they acted like one because they
simply were focused on the idea of
having the money and not using the flow
of abundance. Well, it just when you say
when you need it, it's like I would
rather have it not when I need it but
when I just want it. So need it is like
well you'll have it when you need it. I
always have it when I need it. Yes. But
what other time do you have to have it?
When you don't need it.
Why would you want something in your
life when you don't need it? If you want
to move around as much as you do.
Wouldn't it weigh you down? You know
what I'm saying? You always do this to
me. You know what I'm saying? I do know
what you are saying. Sure, I could sit
home for the day if I didn't have gas,
but it would sure be nice to have the
money or whatever. I'm just using that
as an example. If you want, you know,
whatever you need a new tire on your
car, it' be nice to be able to afford it
if you needed it, want it. Yes. Yes. But
that's not the only way to manifest it.
So, just be open to all the ways then.
Yes. Okay. Why be insistent on having to
acquire the tire in a certain way if
that really doesn't represent the path
of least
resistance? This is happening for a very
specific reason. And one of the specific
reasons is as follows. It's teaching you
how to approach other individuals in a
bold and equal way. It's teaching you
how in that sense to know that you are
able to exchange equal for equal even if
you don't have money. Oh, that's true.
That's already happening. Yes, I see
that already. That's great. Thank you.
Well, thank you very much. Thank you so
much. I have such a great time on my
trip. Thank you so much.
One moment for any and all that are
willing to
participate in this little game we will
now create. If you feel like it, and no
one will judge anyone for any action
they take. If you feel like it, you may
take out one of your dollar bills and
throw it at this
person. It is up to
you. a gift if you wish to give [Laughter] [Laughter]
[Music] it. Remember, remember [Applause]
[Applause]
remember one of the greatest
gifts you can give is to allow others to
give. Thank you. So
this Thank you. At this timing we will
thank you all for enjoying yourselves so
very much and for being free in your
collective abundance. We extend our unconditional
abundance. We extend our unconditional
energy and love to you all and bid you
all a fond and loving good day.
How did it go?
[Applause]
I just want I [Music]
[Music]
just want money.
I just want
What is it?
[Laughter] Figure that one off. What did you do? It
Figure that one off. What did you do? It
wasn't there. It was Bashar.
Uh, okay. Things are getting out of
hand. I just want to say everything that
stayed in the air is
hers. Everything that hit the ground is
mine.
That was fun. We'll do it every week. Same rules.
Thank you all for coming. Those of you
who would like a copy of tonight's money
tape in around the corner, we'll be here
next Thursday. Remember, next Thursday
is going to be the sound's already
entitled it. And the following is going
to be a ghost story. He's already
entitled is going to be two stories from
his sector.
Thank you for coming. See you next
Thursday. [Music] Don't
Don't
forget she was having a