you exist.
We will begin this interaction this
evening of your time with the
understanding that the transformation of
consciousness that you are undergoing
upon your planet this time involves the
very simple concept of learning to be in
love with the entire world in which you
exist. Learning to be in love with the
entirety of the multiverse with the
entirety of creation. Love is the
primary vibration out of which
everything has been created by the
infinite creator. In that way, love is
the infinite creator. It is the very
substance, the very fabric that you
experience as your manifestable
reality. Love, you have talked about it
for quite some time upon your life. You
have recognized its existence for quite
some time in your civilization.
But many of you have not realized that
what you are actually talking about,
what you are actually discussing is the
very essence of creation itself. The
very fabric out of which everything is
created. All of your experiences, all of
physical reality, all the nonphysical
realities, any experience, any
conception, any imagination pulls from
the fiber of love itself. the energy
that is required for the concept for the
idea to blossom into a type of reality
that can be experienced by your form of
consciousness whatever form you have
created your consciousness to be. So in
the idea of learning how to create the
realities you wish to create, learning
how to create the realities you desire
to create upon your planet in the way
you wish them to be. It is all the
process if you will of learning how to
be in love, how to identify with that
vibratory fundamental basic out of which
you create everything anyway. You are
all natural creators. You are all
automatic creators. We are not
discussing that you must learn something
new that you do not already do. We are
simply here to assist you in realizing
that you create your reality anyway. And
that if you simply are willing to shift
the focus of how you create that
reality, then you will be able to
perceive and experience the type of
reality you say you prefer. Is all of
this translating so far into your
language appropriately? Do you
understand? Yes. In this way, therefore,
with each and every individual and
collective interaction this evening of
your time, do allow yourself to
recognize that the whole idea and the
whole process of understanding, the
whole process of learning is not the
idea of truly learning something new,
but the process of remembering more and
more of what you already are. for
created in the image of the infinite
creator you were and that means you are
an infinite creator. Therefore, when you
allow yourself to truly work with and
not against the fabric of love out of
which all reality is created, when you
blend with that flow, then you will be
able to sculpt your reality out of that
love into any form that represents your
true heart's desire. We at this time
before we interact in sharing will
extend to you our appreciation and
deepest gratitude in allowing us to
interact with you in this way. For
through this interaction, we as a
civilization get to experience all the
loving ways that each and every one of
you have uniquely decided to create the
realities that you are. For each and
every one of you is made of love. And
therefore, in a fundamental sense,
everything you do is an act of love. We
simply accept the invitation from you to
reflect back to you your memory that you
can live consciously in the manner that
lets you know you are a creation of love
and light. We find you. You may, if you
light. We find you. You may, if you
wish, proceed with your interaction.
What what do you physically look like?
In your terminology, you would describe
us as an average 5 ft of your height.
Slender in form, humanoid as you would
call it. Though in our perspective,
perhaps you would be humanoid to us if
we consider ourselves to be that human
form. In this way, we are white whitish
gray skin coloration, very wide upturned
eyes as you would call it, very large
pupil that would make our eyes seem
almost entirely black. Although they are
actually grayish white in color, we
would most closely approximate what you
would call your Eurasian racial blend if
you wish some sort of comparison that
you are familiar with. Though we are
more slender in that way, but that will
suffice. Are you familiar with the movie
that's playing right now? Star Trek 4.
It is within the memory of the channel.
Yes. What's your impression of that? It
is an indication that your consciousness
collectively is beginning to recognize
that on your very own world you have had
for some time another alien species what
you call the zitasian whale and dolphin.
This is in that sense an accurate
representation in so far as it points
out that the whale dolphin life form on
your planet is intelligent and in
communication with extraterrestrial
consciousness and has been for quite
some time. Specifically, however, the
consciousness that you would call the
star Sirius in your language, that is
one of the primary civilizations that
has been in telepathic communication
with the whales and dolphins of your
world. Also, that which you call
Arcturus. Is there a lot of life
throughout the universe? It is the rule
rather than the exception. You will find
that life will blossom in whatever form
it is capable of blossoming wherever the
conditions in any form on any level will
allow it. And this is basically
throughout creation of course in one
sense everything is alive. Since
everything is created from consciousness
everything in that sense is innocent
alive. Why do you channel through the
why not come down in person?
We have made an agreement with this
individual prior to this light to assist
you in this way. Coming down in person,
as you say, is not impossible and will
be able to occur more often in your very
near future within the next decade as
you count time, no longer than 30 of
your years maximum. But the reason for
why we do not invoke mass landings at
this time is because this is your world
and you are choosing to rearrange and
operate your world according to your own
whims and desires. We cannot interfere
with that idea and until you decide to
function as a unified planet that is
willing to function in concert with
other unified planets. We cannot force
this point of view upon you. Do
recognize your governments are very well
aware of our existence. But because you
have created your society in layers that
can hide information from other layers
then many of your members do not know of
our existence although many of the
mainstream members as you call them in
your society within your governments do.
The idea is not to force ourselves upon
you. The idea is to simply let you know
when you are willing to know that we
exist and we are waiting to expand and
share with you many different ideas. Now
physiologically and psychologically
there is also a reason for the amount of
time the interaction between your
civilization and our civilization is
taking. Your civilization operates at a
different frequency in a sense than
ours. Everything is made of different
frequencies of energy of the primal
energy of creation. Not in any way,
shape or form do we mean this in a
derogatory sense but because of what you
have created your society to be. you
operate on a very low slow frequency.
Societies that function as whole unified
worlds operate on a very accelerated and
high frequency. When those two
frequencies are brought together, the
higher energy would have a tendency to
overwhelm the lower energy and force the
lower energy to speed up much in the
same way that a faster turning gear will
impart more energy to a slower turning
gear. And even though the faster gear
will slow down to some degree, the
slower gear will speed up more greatly
by comparison in forcing the lower
energy to become faster. It will bring
to the surface many of the things within
your embodied unconsciousness that you
may not be willing or ready to face.
Forcing upon many members of your
society a psychotic shock for something
they are not ready to handle within
themselves. So we will maintain our
distance until you are willing and ready
to create equality within your own
selves, equality with each other. And
that to us will be the signal that you
will be capable of consciously
functioning on an equal level with other
whole civilizations. Thank you. Thank
you.
Sh. Not all at once.
For sure. Hi. Hi. How do you feel about
being on television tonight? Any
opportunity that you have co-created
with us to allow other individuals to
recognize that they can create the
reality they desire will be most enjoyed
by us. We thank you.
Great. Do you wish to share something
else? Um, well, I'd like to share with you
Um, well, I'd like to share with you
that I'm going to go u be with the
dolphins next October in Monkey Maya,
Australia. Have a wonderful party.
Thanks. It's the first time I've ever
planned a trip to one moment. We will
thank you as well for your participation
and interaction within what you call
your technological media. [Applause]
Have a wonderful and exciting time
within your monkeya area. You will find
that you will begin to be able to truly
share a common dream with them. Your
life will become very much more dream
like. You will recognize that your
physical reality is literally a
dream. Sharing
[Music] Guys, have you any suggestions as to the
Guys, have you any suggestions as to the
individual's ability to accelerate their
own evolution which will eventually I'm
sure accelerate the collective
consciousness but any specific direction
as to how to accelerate our own gears?
Absolutely. Each and every individual
need only follow one simple point. Do
what excites you the most in your life
with complete integrity. That's it. You
will then by following what excites you
the most be truest and in synchronous
harmony and in synchronous accord with
the path you chose to be as the
individual you chose to be in this
physical light. So when you follow what
moves you, what allows you to experience
that knowingness within you, that truth
that is true for you, you will then be
glowing and shining most brightly as the
facet of the multi-dimensional crystal
you chose to be. And that is how you
will have the greatest impact on the
total crystal by fully being the facet
you are. By being truest to yourself, by
doing in your life what excites you the
most, knowing and trusting beyond a
shadow of a doubt that you will be
supported 100% by the universe in your
choosing to do so. You follow me? I do.
I have one question. All right.
I have personally experienced moments
where there's a dichotomy or a split in
in my excitement. That is one of the
definitions of your world or has been
the experience of dichotomy or polarity.
Please continue. And the frustration to
me is that it it takes me away from that
moment of clarity and I'm aware that the
dichotomy is an illusion and still I I
step to one side and look at it and the
other side and look at it and I feel I'm
being pulled by the own my own inner
struggle. Are you saying any suggestions
as to how to become very one-pointed
about these? One moment. One moment.
Understand that it may not need to take
a linear form. You are learning to
become a generalist. And so in this way
you may find that the way to perhaps
perceive your path to be the clearest
along a particular line may be to do
many different ideas or approach it from
many different points of view. The idea
of course being that change is the only
constant and therefore the most stable
factor in creation. Now, are you saying
that from time to time you may find that
there are more than one thing that
excites you equally?
No, I don't think that that's exactly In
what format are you expressing your
dichotomy? Can you share an example? It
seems to be an internal dialogue between
what I find exciting and what I find
fulfilling. I don't know. I don't know
exactly how to describe it because it's
a subconscious internal dialogue. All
right. One moment. One moment. One
moment. You got it. You say what I find
exciting, what I find fulfilling. Why
are those two different things? I don't
know. Are they? Well, apparently in some
instances in my life, they they are. All
right. Let me ask you a question if I
may. May I? Sure. Thank you. Define
exciting.
It seems to be stimulating and activates
a lot of energy. All right. May I ask
you another question?
Yes. No. M. Yes. Thank you. Define
fulfilling.
Some experience that leaves me with a
sense of peace. A sense of peace. A
sense of
quiet. I don't know how to describe it.
It just leaves me with one moment. One
moment. So, are you saying that
something that stimulates you and
something that leaves you with a sense
of peace? That's two different things.
It can be in my in my experience. All
right. Would you prefer that what
excited you also fulfilled you and what
fulfilled you also excited you? Yes, I
would. Why?
Because it feels better that way. All
right. How do you know it feels better
that way? Because of the times when
those two energies line up. Yes. When
they're in alignment, I feel in
alignment and there's no there's no uh
static. All right. Are you saying that
when you are fulfilled at the times you
experience the idea of quiet peace that
you think that at those times you should
be jumping up and down? No. No, not at
all. There's some psychic static that
takes place in in the questioning of
will this will this thing that appears
to excite me eventually it's a it's a
mental head trick. Finish the sentence.
Will this thing that appears to excite
me to excite me eventually cause me more
um distraction or will it bring me to
fulfillment or peace in quiet? Then once
again allow us to give you the
definition of excitement. Mhm.
Excitement definition excitement is the physical
definition excitement is the physical
Now are you paying attention? I am. All
right. the physical
translation of the vibratory
energy that
represents the path you chose to be in
this life. So on that
definition, anytime you follow what
truly excites you the most, until you
decide that it doesn't, until you
invalidate, until you judge that it
doesn't and create the illusion that it
seems not to. Anytime you follow what
excites you the most, it will always
lead you and can only lead you in
directions that will also be fulfillment
of the path you chose to be because
excitement and fulfillment are the same
idea. You are choosing to separate them
in your definition and thus you are
creating the dichotomy simply because
you assume that excitement and
fulfillment are two separate things and
that one may not lead to the other or
that they are parallel paths. It is one
in the same
energy. Excitement is your indicator.
excitement or simple knowingness which
is also fulfillment in a sense. That
sense of peace that is your indicator
when something in your life is the thing
that will work for you most
effortlessly, most easily, most quickly
because excitement is the physical
translation of the vibrational equation
of the vibrational frequency that
represents the path you chose to be in
this life. It will always lead to
fulfillment if you let it. You follow
me? I do. Does that assist you at all?
It does. The the I think the the the
turning point for me is that there are
certain scripts I've accepted from the
sociological program, right? That give
me the illusion that I'm excited or give
me the illusion that I'm fulfilled. And
it's determining what's truth from my
own center as opposed to what's been
superimposed by the sociological. All
right. But that does not have to be in
and of itself an unpleasant experience
to determine for you what is true. That
in of itself can be a very exciting
script. You follow? So the more
different ways you allow your path of
discovering what excites you to be in
and of itself exciting, the more
excitement you will have. If you
continue to say, well, the discovery of
what excites me is not exciting, then
you yourself are spending energy in ways
that you say you don't want to. Allow
the discovery of what excites you to be
a part of the excitement and you will
find yourself more excited all the time
because you will then be able to use the
methodologies of how you discovered what
excites you the most to also assist
yourself in the future and assist other
individuals when they come to you and
say how did you discover what excited
you the most? How can I discover what
excites me the most? And you can say let
the path to discover what excite you the
most excite you as much as anything. And
then you will attract in an obvious way
the things that excite you the most. And
the whole process, the whole exploration
will be exciting. Allow yourself to live
with that childlike fascination, the
childlike curiosity, rather than the
idea of the
discriminating, judgmental, invalidating
consciousness that says, well, the
process in quote unquote getting there.
Everyone knows that the process has to
hurt. Everyone knows that the process
itself can't be exciting. Everyone knows
sociologically speaking that you can
only be happy when you finally somewhere
way out there down the road. Oh, who
knows 10, 20, 30, a thousand years. When
you finally get there, then that's
exciting. Everyone knows the process.
Like medicine is supposed to be bitter.
Who says? No one says. That's your
beliefs. That's your rules. You make
them up. You can change them. So if you
allow the process itself to be just as
exciting, then is when you will
paradoxically allow yourself the highest
degree of acceleration in your life
because what you are doing is allowing
where you are to be a valid part of the
path you chose to be rather than
something that is an interruption in
that path or a rough spot on that path.
You recognize that everything in your
life is in your life for a reason and
that you can use it with that attitude.
And if you do, then using what is in
your life with a positive attitude will
allow all the things you desire in life
to reach you and approach your present
much more rapidly. You follow? Yes.
Thank you very much for being willing to
share of that unique perspective that
you are. We thank you sharing for sure.
Nice. Are you familiar with a channeling
that's come into two books? One is
called Right of Will. The other one is
um original cause. Are you familiar with
that energy at all?
Define. Well, it's it's written as if
it's in the first person
God that God is speaking and is
channeling through this
woman and it's second book original
cause is speaking about the beginning of
creation as if God is speaking in first
person describing how creation came
about and how things got kind of say
screwed up in the beginning. You will of
course find as we perceive this
particular energy that what you are
quote unquote reading to some
degree will be an interpretation in your
symbolic terms. Some ideas may be quote
unquote on some levels literal.
But many of the ideas, while they are
not in essence incorrect, are translated
into symbology and terms that make sense
in your language and so may not be
directly representative of quote unquote
an actual description of an event, but
in essence they describe the event. You
follow me? Yes. And now it was described
that way in the book. I mean that's
before it started
said just said that
Um is this are you familiar with this
concept of how
um how this book went or should I try
and describe a little bit to you? You
don't have to try. You can simply
describe it. Okay. Um I spoke about in
the beginning that God became aware of
himself. Yes. Self-awareness, self-
knowingness, the first primal
separation, the first creation. Yes. And
then he became aware of another presence
inside himself. was looking to see if
there's anything else out there or in
there. Discovered something else in
there which was
feeling. And it when he put his
attention on this feeling, sometimes it
felt good, sometimes it felt bad. When
it felt bad, he decided I don't want
this. Toss it out of himself. No. Okay.
Understand all that is what you refer to
colloquially as God, infinite creation.
is everything that is is all that is and
all that is knows there is nothing
outside. There is nowhere to get rid of
anything too. All that is acknowledges
and accepts all portions of itself as
all that is or it would not function as
all that is. It recognizes the idea of
itself as polarity.
In this way, therefore, it is simply an
opportunity for any fragment of all that
is to express itself through either
polarity gate either in positive
integrated ways or negative segregated
ways. But in that way, all that is did
not attempt to get rid of any portion of
itself because there was nowhere to put
it. All that is is literally all that
is. You follow me? Yes. Now again the story
You follow me? Yes. Now again the story
is being put I do not mean this in a
derogatory fashion in a very story book
format for certain levels of
consciousness on your planet to be able
to as you say get the point in terms
they are already familiar with because
your society thinks that there can be an
outside thinks that there can be a
truly objective ive universe rather than
a completely subjective one thinks that
there truly is right, wrong, good and
evil rather than simply the idea of
positive and negative expression. Right,
wrong, good and evil only being
subjective value judgments and not
necessarily an indication of whether
positive or negative energy is being
used. So it is being put in a format that
So it is being put in a format that
certain individuals will be able to
understand but it is let us say again
not meaning to be derogatory and not
meaning to be judgmental extremely
simplified in concept following. Yes. Um
what is your concept of God or or is
there this original cause? When I
started off this dialogue, I said God
became aware of himself and you said
yes. In a sense, although it always was
and always will be and is now, in a
sense, there really is no beginning and
really no ending. When we talk of
original causes, we are again also quote
unquote forced to use terminology that
is your thirddimensional terminology,
the terminology that makes the most
sense to your analytical consciousness.
But there really is nothing that began
per se. Time space are your concepts.
They are your
illusions. In a sense, within the
framework of space-time illusion, you
can say there are beginnings and
endings. But from the point of view of
all that is, it always was and always
will be. There are transformations that
are ongoing within it constantly. But
all of those transformations from its
point of view all occur
simultaneously. You following? Yes. And
do you accept that like all that is
always has been is you accept that as an
intellectual understanding or as a an
experiential reality? As an experiential
knowingness. Okay. So you're just
trusting in yourself. Absolutely. A
knowingness that feels right. It's like
that makes sense to you. You can look at
it from what you call a pragmatic point
of view and this we can share with you
in your language. Do you exist? Yes or
no? Yes. Thank
you. Recognize. Therefore, if you exist
now, you always will and you always
have. You see, your assumption that you
may cease to exist or that there was a
time when you didn't comes from a belief
in your society that existence can
become nonexistent. But it
nonexistent. But it
can't. Non-existence and existence are
already both quote unquote real.
Non-existence is already full of
everything that will never exist.
Existence is already full of all the
things that will always
exist. One does not become the other.
They are the polarities of creation
itself. They do not shift into each
other. Therefore, if you exist now, you
always have and you always will. Perhaps
not in a specific format that you find
your consciousness to be embodied in
now. Although again everything being
simultaneous in a sense your body the
body you are now has always
existed from some points of view you can
say it existed in
potential but still to other points of
view that is the same thing as saying it
always exists because different levels
of reality no matter how rarified they
are physically are just as solid so to
speak and just as real to non-physical
consciousness as your physical reality
is as solid to you as a physical ical
being. Now time again and space are your
illusions. Allow me to ask you a
question. You exist in the
present. Understand you always will. You
do not in the sense experientially exist
in the past. You do not experientially
exist in what you call the future. You
only ever experience your existence in
the present as what you call now. You
follow me? Yes. You always will.
You always will. It will always ever
forever be now to you. It will never be
any other time but now. Therefore, what
you call the past and what you call the
future are actually being created in the
present from the present. It is not
truly linear. That is your
illusion. Therefore, you will always
exist in the now. It will always be now.
And now is eternal forever. If you are
aware of yourself now, you always will
be because it will always be now. And
never will it be any other
time. Now whether this makes some sense
or not in your language that is the way
that we can translate the concept best
into your terminology. Has it assisted
you at all? Yes. And could you do this
further say how could I as an individual
or a group of people helped us stay in
now? There is really no other time you
can be in but we understand that
sometimes. Yes, it seems that way. You
can allow yourself to remain in now the
most once again by acknowledging that
everything that occurs in your life
occurs for a reason. And allow yourself
to recognize that nothing in your life
no matter what you change it into will
actually be better in a sense in a judgmental
be better in a sense in a judgmental
sense than what you are doing now. It
will be different. It can be more
expanded. It can be grander in many
ways, but in a qualitative sense, it
will not be better. It will simply be
different. Allow yourself to recognize
that many of you do not live in the now
because you are seeking to achieve
perfection. You will never achieve
perfection because you're already
perfect. Now at any given moment you are
the perfect manifestation of what you
are being in that moment. What you will
be in the next moment will be a
different manifestation of perfection.
Not a better one, a different one. But
everything you do will be a perfect
manifestation of the thing you are
doing. Even if it is perfect
misery, it is still a perfect
manifestation of misery. Now, if you
don't prefer that, then you can change
that. But the way to change it most
quickly and most easily is if you find
that your life at any given moment is
the way you don't prefer it to be to
acknowledge that because you create your
reality, you
chose to have your life be that way. You
are in control of your life all the
time. Even when you create the illusion
that you are out of control, you're
controlling it. And if you feel out of
control, you must have had a good reason
to believe that you can be. Perhaps if
only to discover what it is like to feel
like you're out of control and then
decide, I don't prefer to feel this way.
I now that I know I chose to create a
feeling of being out of control. I know
I can choose to know I am in control and
therefore everything changes. Now I will
do what I prefer to do which is what I
was doing then by choosing to feel like
I was out of control but then I didn't
know it because the definition of being
out of control is simply creating a
momentary ability to forget that you are
in control all the time. You are that
much of a creator. You are so powerful
of a creator. You have the ability to
forget you are the creator. But at any
moment you can remember that you created
forgetfulness. And then you will
remember that your life can be whatever
you choose it to be. You follow? Yes, I
do. Thank you very much for remembering
who you are. Yay. Yes, I'd like to know
what the next step is in planetary
communication via television or
consciousness networking for particular
motion picture products. What do you see
the next few years hold for the
enlightenment of the masses and mass
media such again as television or uh
film? It will depend upon the subject
matter you wish to deliver but much of
it as it already has been can be
utilized to deliver many messages that
you do in fact again create your own
reality in this way. At the same time,
you will find that what you call your
media can also get to the point where
ideas themselves can be shared from
individual to individual or from group
to group without what you would call the
telepathically created
technological symbol that you call your
television equipment or radio equipment
and you can use the telepathic medium
itself. Now you will find that there can be many
Now you will find that there can be many
let us say intermediate devices that
will operate through electromagnetic
etherromagnetic and electronic
frequencies that will also be able to
tap into what you call the non-physical
dimensions particularly what you would
call the lower astral. You will be able
to invent devices through which beings
that have been physical and are no
longer physical can communicate with
beings that are still physical. You
follow me? Yes, I do. This is up and
coming as you say and will broaden your
understanding of what communication and
interaction is all about and the fact
that once something exists it never does
not exist and that you have the ability
to retrieve quote unquote anything by
tuning your frequency to the appropriate
band. You will begin to learn through
your technology that you can actually
focus on and locate any point in space
and time anywhere in the universe and
have it right there in front of you on
your screen. When you begin to use the
universe as the holographic matrix that
it is, you will be able to call out the
coordinates of any time and space and
present them to you on your
screen. You follow? Yes, sir. We
perceive this to be also up and coming
in your technology. But again, it is up
to you. Perhaps in a sense, the most
important question because you are
living in your world that uses these
devices is what do you see as the next
step? What do you wish to do with that
medium? And when you find what it is, do
it. Then you will have made the
difference and you will have co-created
the change. Then you will know.
Follow your excitement.
Sure, the medicine very much. Thank you.
Thank you very much. Yes. Hello. Hello.
I'm delighted to meet you. You are so
familiar to me and I've never seen you
in the physical.
Not many people. Yes. Nor have I seen
Daryl in the physical. So, uh, and
you're very familiar since. So are all
of you. What is familiar about us is a
certain portion of yourself that you
have forgotten up to that.
which you have allowed us to simply
remind you or reflect back to you. But
in a many ways, we are also familiar on
many different levels because many of
you in your own dream realities actually
visit many other civilizations all the
time. You are very busy when you are all
asleep. You are not dormant in the
least. As a matter of fact, many of you
are highly active, maybe more active
than you are in physical light. Yes, you
have identified with us with our
vibrational pattern because in many ways
some literal and some allegorical. Our
civilization actually does symbolize
your own future self. So you are
familiar with that vibratory frequency.
You are simply finding it as a lure and
an attractant into more and more of what
you know you are all becoming. We thank
you for allowing us to shine that back
to you. Oh, all right. Uh, I have a
question. Um, I have been working as an
instrument of the awakening here in
Hawaii, of course. And, um, for some I
have a question on why actually, but why
am I able to channel an
extraterrestrial? It started about six
maybe eight weeks ago and I'm one of
three people that I know and I don't see
us as doing what u Daryl's doing. It
does not have to be that way. Yeah.
What's the purpose? First of all, do
recognize that our job is being done
most correctly when you do not need us
anymore. Therefore, you will find that
this methodology is not the way that it
is paramount for the channeling to
occur. You have made your own
association because many of you have
many lives in other civilizations as
well. And you may be forming
reconnections to portions of your own
family that are willing to assist you
just far enough to get you in touch with
a portion of yourself that can then do
the work. Yes. You follow me? That's the
primary reason. They are acting as
guides for you. Okay? Not that you have
to manifest it in this way, but that you
be willing to let yourself be inspired
by what you feel to manifest what you
want in your physical reality in your
own way. That is the whole idea why we
are interacting with all of you anyway
to get you to realize you all have the
ability to channel your higher self and
that all of you also have connections to
many other levels of consciousness and
many other civilizations. None of you in
a sense are original to this planet you
call. So many of you will simply reform
the familial connections you have had
from many different lives and many
different time tracks and allow that now
that this is the transformational life
to all come together in whatever format
you needed to come together to be of
service in the assistance of the
transformation. That's why yes it feels
like family. It's a nice word familial.
Yay. Yes. Feels like that. Okay. Uh
could you give me a couple?
I do not have any with me.
Names of
them. Sir, there are many individuals
that you are surrounded with that can
supply you with much information now
that you have made it known that this is
what you request. You will find that
what you call your literature revolved
around the entity known as Seth will be
very beneficial in many ways. Okay. If
you are not already familiar with that.
Oh, I'm familiar with Seth. I thought
maybe for training myself a bit further.
We perceive that there are a few but not
many. Again, perhaps simply the
experiences of different channels, if
they have recorded them, can be of
benefit. But recognize this. If you have
made such an agreement, you will always
attract yourself to whatever training
you need and always rely upon your own
imagination. That is what your
imagination is for. It is the tool that
is most accurately tuned to the
vibratory awareness of your being. And
therefore, if you need if you believe
you need a ritual, if you believe you
need a methodology, if you believe you
need a technique or an exercise, ask
your higher self through your
imagination, what will work best for me?
And then don't invalidate what you get,
no matter how silly it may seem. Trust
the vibratory awareness of your gateway
imagination through to your higher
consciousness and allow yourself to
recognize that you always have the
ability to get your own answers in that
way. One way that might assist you would
be to open up that gate and open up that
communication in a very relaxed and
meditative state. Perhaps being immersed
in almost body temperature water would
be of great assistance. Evol. Okay.
Thank you very much. Thank you. Yes. Um
first I want you know a quick question.
Do you eat do you eat where you're from?
Not so much the physical food anymore.
No more direct energy absorption as many
of you are also beginning to lean
towards but not quite yet.
The other thing is um well if we're
reaching I feel it like sublimally in
terms of reach another civilization
and what I'm wondering is wouldn't it be
fun to really get into a spaceship and
go to another civilization. Yes.
And so I was wondering what you see as
we have said our interactions with you
from our point of view will occur within
the next decade to 30 of your years.
Also, much sooner than that, you will
begin to discover that there are groups
on your own world that are already
experimenting with similar technologies.
You have had the technology on your
planet to visit other worlds for quite
some time. But because of the type of
governmental system you have created,
much of the information has been
suppressed. Now, much of this
information is coming to the surface
with everything else that you are now
bringing to the surface to get it all
out of the open. And you will find that
within the next three of your years and
primarily within this your present year,
primarily within the spring and
summertime of this year, there will be
much revelation of information that you
have had this technology all along. And
different groups upon your planet will
begin to utilize this information to
create your own version of spacecraft.
And then you see the whole idea is is
that you will be able to meet us
halfway. Yeah. following. Yeah. Look into the
Yeah. following. Yeah. Look into the
work of the individual you knew as
Nicola Tetla. That individual knew how to
Tetla. That individual knew how to
create those devices in
principle. Also, you will find coming
out of many different areas around your
planet this information. Simply as you
say, keep your eyes and your ears open.
For sure. I know other people talk too.
Why are we all locking our doors all the
time? You are opening them now. This is
the end of the cycle of limitation.
Wherein you have kept the doors locked.
You are now beginning to realize that
you yourselves have the keys to unlock
them. Whereas before you did not know
you had the key, you did not even know
there was a door. Now you
know you follow. Yeah. The idea of all
the limitation you have ever
experienced, however, has also served a
purpose. For now you are masters of
limitation. You have done it
all in such a highly concentrated state
that you are now the experts on
limitation. Any other planet wants to
know what's it
like. Now that you have done it all, you
have now found the door out of that
particular room and are entering another
room where you do not need to play that
game any longer for now it has served
you. You follow me. Thank you. Bashar,
thank you very much. We love you as
well. you then you could you tell us or expand
you then you could you tell us or expand
on the idea of the difference between
out of
literal experience as it is in simply
recognizing that your body is a part of
your consciousness not that your
consciousness exists in your
body. Right? So out of body is more of
an expansive point of view where you
recognize that the body is in
consciousness and you simply blow up
like a balloon to include the body but
also contain perspectives that are quote
unquote beyond the definition of the
body. It is viewing through another
portion or as a greater portion of the
self. Look at it as if you were a
sphere. on that sphere is a dot. Now
that dot can move all over the skin of
the sphere and it can also move within
the sphere to any point. Right? That dot
represents at any given moment where you
are focused, where you are looking and
what determines your reality.
Therefore, the idea is that if you have
the outline of a little body on the
surface of that sphere, when the dot is
on the surface and in that outline, you
are focused as a physical consciousness.
When it then moves perhaps backwards
into the sphere, you then perceive
yourself to be quote unquote out of
body, but all you are in is a different
portion pool of the energy that is the
sphere of reality and experience that
you are. Mhm. It is not that you have
actually left the body anywhere. You
have simply refocused yourself to a
different portion of the total idea of
which the body is only one part.
Therefore, remote viewing and lucid
dreaming and all of these experiences of
different plains of awareness are all
simply viewing yourself through
different locations within the overall
energy sphere that you are. You
following? Yes. Thank you. Thank you.
One moment. you then you okay first of
all if this information about
advanced space flight is that known at
the governmental level some do
understand that many of your governments
actually have in what you call their
possession some extraterrestrial crafts
yes have they been able to derive uh
enough theory and technology from these
craft in order to make their own some
but not fluidly for they are missing
have on several understandings that
consciousness is a part of the equation
in understanding the
technology and in this way also some of
the materials are a little bit as you
say beyond their capability to penetrate
but they have applied some of this
technology to some degree now and then
and in a sense even before they had
possession were working on some of these
understandings they do understand some
of the basic principles but again as
long as they choose to utilize them for
the idea of selfmpowerment gain in that
way. Selfishly, you will find that some
of the principles will not work because
they are only based on an integrated
point of view. Are these technologies
being used in our space programs at the
moment? It makes me angry that the
Challenger would blow up in mid-flight
and not have the benefit of any advanced
technology that was available. All
right. But do understand that that event
and then the fulcrum point of your
country's interaction with Libya and
then the polarity event of what you
would call the disaster in Soviet Union
Chernobyl are three parts of the same
overall event to begin to bring what is
within to the surface. Those three
events are the fulcrum points between
third and fourth density in your
particular world format that allow you
to realize that the only reason that
those so-called disasters happen is
because you think that what is within
you if it comes out will destroy you in
that way because you create yourself to
have many cracks, many leaks in the
surface idea that you are rather than
looking at yourself in an integrated
way. Again, we recognize the idea you
are expressing, but there is no real
reason to be angry at them in that
sense, for you're only being angry at a
portion of yourself because you are your
governments. You have created your world
to be the way it is. Each and every
individual, the idea is to glean from
those events what you can glean out of
them in a positive way. Do understand it
is no accident as there are no accidents
that in what you call your shuttle
event, there was a
teacher. She has taught her lesson. If
you are willing to receive it, you will
recognize as you are recognizing that
there are other ways, simpler methods.
And this is one of the things that your
government is also beginning to learn.
But because of what you have created
your government to be, they may act like
they are getting at a little more slowly
than what you call the mainstream of
society. The more you interact with
them, not in an accusatory manner, not
in an angry manner, but in a loving
manner, in a sharing manner, in an
unconditionally loving manner. And
express to them that you believe in
peace that you know there are other ways
that are simpler. There are other ways
that are more indicative of using the
reality that exists rather than
attempting to ram your way through
walls. Then perhaps they will begin to
shift their programs toward the type of
programs that will allow them to share
the information with you rather than
thinking that by doing so they will lose
their power. You see they are only quote
unquote afraid of losing their power in
that way over you. What they do not
understand is that by sharing with you
they will gain their own selfmpowerment
and everything will equal out and that
the government can do what a government
needs to do and that is serve you not
rule you. But all of these events are
bringing all of these ideas out in the
open and forcing them to face the
different portions of themselves that
are not working fluidly. So in this way,
if you are going to feel something, you
can feel anger if you wish. We would
suggest that you redirect your energy
not into the idea of anything
prolonged, not into the idea of
judgment, not into the idea of hate, not
into the idea of frustration or guilt or
accusation. But allow the anger to serve
you naturally. Anger is only for the
purpose of allowing you when you see
something go on in life to align with
what you know is true for you and what
you know can be possible. Then there is
no need for the judgment and no need for
the negative feelings from that point
forward. Now the situation has aligned
you. Now you know how you can serve by
suggesting alternatives to your
government and allow them to hear the
words of all of you saying we believe in
peace. Let's do it this way. Shall we
together?
Oh thank you.
[Music] Thank you. If you believe in
Thank you. If you believe in
peace, then you do not have to hate
war. You
follow. You do not get peace by hating
war. You only get peace by
loving. Hate only reinforces the things
you say you do not prefer because that's
what you're focusing
on. Be peace. Live peace. Breathe peace.
Share peace.
Love. Unconditional love will transform your
Unconditional love will transform your
entire world in the twinkling of an eye.
Unconditional love for all.
Yes. No m.
Yes, you are. Don't forget that.
Thank you.
Yes, Bashar. Um, along the theme of
unconditional love, I'd like to share
and invite your reflection on something
that happened last night with the
channel, Daryl and his fiance and
myself. We went to a hotel in the White
area where there were dolphins.
And it was well, there were several
interesting and synchronous things that
happened. Uh, first of all, it was night
and so we were able to go out to the
pool. There were very few people around
except a young girl sitting on the stone
bridge with her feet uh in the water and
I talked to her and I found out the
names of the dolphins. She knew them.
She'd been there several times. Nice.
And then one of the dolphins, two of
them were cruising the pool and the
other one, Eva, was coming up and and
listening to us and being with us. And
then at one point, she began to play
with this leaf in the water and toss it
over and have me get it and throw it to
her. Thanks. And then she went down and
took it to Daryl and to um Erica.
Thanks. And while this was going on, I mean, we
And while this was going on, I mean, we
were so ecstatically delighted at her
willingness to play with us. Good. Uh,
and I was also intrigued because I found
out that there were was one male and two
female dolphins. And I thought that we
had come as a little triad,
ambassadors, representing the humans. Uh, and we were
representing the humans. Uh, and we were
also one male and two females, which was
fun. What I would like uh to know from you is
What I would like uh to know from you is
how much of the interaction of energy
between Sirius
uh represented by
Chap and yourself representing SSI and
Darl representing Earth that triad was
how much of that energy was this
particular dolphin aware of
say 30%.
The idea of the environment in which
those beings are kept has to some degree
altered their ability to perceive
certain ideas as they are in a sense
numbed to certain energies because of
the environment you follow. Yes. But the
energy was present. It was sensed and an
awakening also occurred not only in you
but also in the dolphins.
That's lovely.
Thank you for your interaction and your
willingness to begin and open up
communication and allow yourself to act
as ambassadors as well in the other
direction. Thank you. It was totally delightful.
Thank you. It was totally delightful.
Sure.
Thanks. One
One
moment. It is once again time for what
to call a public service
announce. Do realize each and every one
of you that you have chosen to be in
this gathering for your own reasons. And
no matter what any individual may have
to share, there is always some way that
you can apply the idea to yourself. Even
though there may be relative different
degrees of significance to you, there
are no boring situations in life, only
bored minds. Allow yourself to recognize
that it is no accident that you are
hearing what you are hearing from any
individual and that if you allow your
childlike fascination and curiosity to
come to the surface, everything everyone
says and everything anyone does will be
able to be applicable to you, if only to
give you an appreciation of the
infinitely wondrous
orchestration with which all of these
interactions are taking place. Because
there is not one single factor that is
an accident in this orchestration. Not
the colors of the clothes you are
wearing that each other is seeing. Not
what your names are, not how you are
sitting, not how you are breathing, not
what you are saying. None of it is an
accident. It is all there so that you
can support each other in the total
interaction that we are together. So
that each and every one of you will be
able to get out of it what you wish.
Thank you.
that announcement just felt great. Thank
you. Uh along the lines of a
communication, a group of us in our
human dolphin journey that we've been
doing, we went out into deep sea the
other day. Nice. And got into like
limitless blue green water. Good. And I
became fascinated with diving down into
the light reflections that seemed just
to forever. Okay. And as we were
returning to the boat, we spent some
time just going down a little bit in the
water. Very much killed by your
excitement and our procreation. So,
thank you. And you can also use that to
allow yourself to remember at any given
time that just as you were able to hear
the whale through the medium of the
water, you are all connected in an
energy sea as well of electromagnetic
ethermagnetic energy. That is what your
consciousness uses to create your mass
consciousness, your mass mentality in
physical terms. It is through that
energy. see that you are all whether you
know it or not constantly communicating
telepathically with each other. When you
allow yourself to float in a peaceful
state in the energy sea in which you are
all immersed, you will be able to hear
not only each other but every single
consciousness within creator in whatever
way you desire to tune your
consciousness. That is what you will
receive. In much the
receive in much the same way you have
created what you call your television
and radio. Recognize all of the frequencies.
radio. Recognize all of the frequencies.
All of the programs are there at the
same time. Immersing the device in an energy
time. Immersing the device in an energy
sea of radiation.
You get the one you tune into at any
given moment, but they are all there all
the time. Swim in that sea and extend your
time. Swim in that sea and extend your
antenna in whatever direction, space or
time. And do you all wish to take a
short break? Sounds good. Enjoy and we
will resume shortly. They have
They have
more cheese. Yeah.
All right. Sh.
You then you
I have um some questions about marriage.
Oh, right.
Is all right. Simply allow me to remind
you once again that confusion is
co-fusion. Fusion with more of yourself.
It is a limbo state that allows you to
view many more probabilities than the
mind that you usually function as
previously conceived were possible for
you. So in confusion you unlock from
previously held concepts and allow
yourself to examine new concepts. It is
only a limbo state for a while because
you have not yet chosen to relock into
any particular concept. But confusion is
a very flowing, active, creative,
energetic state in many ways. And so you
can come from that point of view, come
from that place of harmony and allow
yourself to recognize you will say
precisely what you need to say.
Okay. Um, I I entered a
marriage on the belief system that that
could be a path to me, right, to much
higher levels of consciousness. And
obviously in many ways it was because
whatever it is you are considering now
obviously resulted from what you chose
to do then. And so if you're willing to
let anything in your life serve you as a
learning process, you can recognize you
are now functioning in a different plane
of awareness because of the situation
you chose to create and attract into
your life. This is true. Um, and I'm not
now experiencing
um a lot of daily things which I would
prefer not to experience. I would prefer
to experience more peace. All right.
Ease. All right. Then all you need to do
in order to create that in your life is
be true to yourself and not be
responsible for other individuals, which
you cannot be anyway. You're only
responsible to other individuals, not
for them, to them. You are responsible
to other individuals by being the
fullest representation of the
individual. You know you are by
functioning within your integrity and
knowing that as long as you are not
consciously and maliciously doing
something to hurt someone else, then
what you do according to what you know
to be true for you is what you need to
do in life. And that doing it is what
will allow you to create harmony and
happiness and ecstasy in your life.
Regardless of what any other individuals
in your society may wish you to believe
will happen within what they choose to
experience in their life based upon what
you choose to do. You follow?
Um yes. Um well
well there seems to be an insinuation in
your statement about what I could
do
best. What excites you the
most? What would you prefer to do to
create happiness in your life?
Can you allow yourself to come up with
something without putting what you
accept as society's restrictions on the
statement? What would make you happy?
What do you wish to do?
Keep it simple. Yeah. I my my I I've
always felt that what would make me the
happiest would be to live on the beach
here and not have to work. All right.
Recognize first of all that if you are
willing to do at any given moment what
excites you the most, it will always
then open you up to attract into your
life whatever will also support you in
life and be just as
exciting. If you are quote unquote
working at something you do not enjoy,
then you are not being true to yourself
and you simply may be creating or buying
into the belief that if you are willing
to do what excites you the most that it
won't support you. But it can. Or if the
immediate thing you do that excites you
the most isn't what will support you, it
will attract into your life what both
excites and supports
you. Life does work that way. Nothing is
too good to be true. Nothing.
You follow me? Could you repeat that one
last sentence? Nothing is too good to be
true over the one before. Oh, thank you.
Recognize that when you act upon your
excitement, you are following in
synchronous harmony the vibration of the
path you chose to lead at any given
moment. Therefore, if you follow what
excites you the most at that moment that
you have the capability of acting on,
you will then link up that situation
with whatever other situation needs to
come into your life to allow the
excitement to continue to generate the
momentum that represents your life, your
path, what you chose to be. Excitement
is what lets you know what is most true
for you. It's your beacon of awareness
to know when you are consciously in
synchronous harmony with the path you
chose to lead and therefore what you can
do in life that is most effortless and
also able to support you
automatically without struggle without
strife and without trying to make a
living. Life and the universe support
you. You deserve to be alive. If you are
alive right now, the universe will
always support you by supplying you
automatically with whatever
opportunities represent your ability to
continue to be who you are if you are
willing to act that
way. The universe always supports you
100% in whatever idea you believe
yourself to be most.
Now if you believe well I have to
struggle in order to make a living and I
believe that nothing that does not
contain struggle will work for me. Then
the universe will support you in that
idea 100%. It will say well if that's
the way you want it here are the
situations that will reinforce the
belief in your life that you have that
nothing will work for you easily and
that you have to struggle in order to
live. Here's all the situations that
represent the belief you have. These
situations are given to you by the
universe automatically to show you what
your beliefs are. Not to prove that you
are stuck in anything. Not to prove that
you have failed at anything, but to show
you beyond a shadow of a doubt. Look,
the reality you get is because that's
what you believe to be true. If you
don't prefer it, change the belief. When
you change the belief I do deserve to
create a reality of effortlessness and
ease and I will be supported, then
that's the reality you will get. The
universe will support you 100% in that
direction. It will say just as
magnanimously and just as equally, well,
if that's what you want, here it is.
Because now that's what you believe. And
as you believe, that's what you
experience in physical reality.
All you need to do is be willing to
recognize that 100% trust in the
direction you prefer will create the
reality you desire to experience. Do
recognize. We are not suggesting that
you do something you are not already
doing. You are already using 100% of
your trust, but you are using 100% of
your trust in a direction you don't
prefer. So place the 100% trust in a
direction you do prefer and then that's
the reality you'll get. It's simple
mechanics and simple
physics. You follow me? Yeah, I follow
you. But but okay, evidently I believe
that in order to get my sustenance, I
have to struggle. All right, but that
was then. What about now? You're a
different person now. So yeah. Okay. So,
I heard your tapes and I heard you last
time from listening to it all and I
understand and I can say I believe that
um my life can be easy and that oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
listen listen listen I believe my life
can be easy
when I believe my life
is
easy you follow me and see the
difference I I believe my life can be
easy when I don't
know someday. Who knows? I believe my
life is easy
now. Now you are on the threshold of your
Now you are on the threshold of your
believability. You are exploring that
threshold. What are you truly willing to
believe is possible for you? Listen to
the language in which you put it. It
will indicate where your threshold of
believability is. As soon as the threshold of
is. As soon as the threshold of
believability is squarely within you in
the present, then you will experience
the life you desire. As long as the
threshold of your believability is still
out here somewhere in the future, no
matter how close it is to you, if it's
not in you, you won't experience
it. So, you are now exploring where your
threshold of believability is. Let's
do ah we're getting to that.
Let's do a little interaction that will
assist you in recognizing where the
threshold of your believability is. All
right. Yeah. Thank you very much.
Now, first of all, begin and each and
every one of you can do this at the same
time. First of all, begin by creating
for yourself in any way, shape or form
that is comfortable for you. Does not
have to be very complicated, just
anything at all that represents the
so-called idealized way you would prefer
to live. Have a picture of yourself
doing something you would enjoy doing
and being supported in that
lifyle. Not having a shadow of a doubt
that you are supported. Truly feeling
that that's the way you live. That is
the way you live and everything is just
fine. Have that picture in your mind of
that idealized state and then I will ask
you a series of questions. All right. Do
you have that picture or that feeling?
All right.
Now be very honest with yourself and for
now for you with me in these answers. Do
you think now really honestly think that
within oh say 10 of your years that will
be enough time for you to be able to
create that way of life. Will that be
enough time? Yes. All right. 5 years.
Yes. 3 years. Yes. Two. One year. Yes.
Can you live that way tomorrow? Yes.
Absolutely. Then you will be. Are you
being honest?
I know that I can be in that picture and
be comfortable with it tomorrow. All
right. That's not what I'm asking you. I
am asking you if you truly believe that
that's the way you will be living
tomorrow. Yes or no? Thank you. Do you
truly believe that that's the way you
will be living in 3 years?
Do you truly believe that that's the way
you will be living in 10 years?
Yes. Do you truly believe that is beyond
a shadow of a doubt the way you will be
living in 20 years?
No. Why not?
Because I have a picture.
So, so I think that those conditions are
even available
understand it as the idealized essence
of the way you feel about living. We are
not asking you to have a picture that is
absolutely structurally rigidized. We
are talking about the lif style in
essence in the way you feel. In other
words, do you believe that you will be
living the way you want to be living the
way you prefer to be living no matter
how that is in 10 years? Yes. Do you
believe you will be living that way in a
month? No. Do you believe you can be living in
No. Do you believe you can be living in
the way you prefer to be living, no
matter how that is, in one
year? Do you believe you can do it in 3
years? I believe I can if I if I I believe I
I believe I can if I if I I believe I
could do it in. All right. Are you sure?
Can you really feel it? A year. All my
attention on just doing that. Yeah. All
right. Why would you do
otherwise? Why would you have to put
your attention on anything you do not
want to do?
I guess because I think
that I have to take care of a lot of
other interim things. But understand
when you are doing what truly represents
the vibration of your reality, all the
details take care of themselves. Not
that you will not be doing anything. It
is simply that when you live the
essential way, when you live in
synchronous harmony with the path you
chose to be, everything is already on
that path in the format it needs to be
and will fall into place as it needs to
fall to let you continue being the
person you chose to be. So you will
simply automatically and effortlessly
and coincidentally attract into your
life all the tools necessary to allow
the details to be taken care
of. It is all one package. You see the
difficulty you are having is thinking
that your life is a series of separated
ideas rather than one homogeneous event
in which everything that truly needs to
be done to allow you to be the person
you need to be will be taken care of
automatically. The things that don't get
done if you are truly being who you know
you need to be don't need to be done to
allow you to be that
person. You follow me. Okay. But I think
what I'm getting which is what what I
need to get is that it's more a matter
of
feeling a state that I want to feel
perhaps for you it is yes then taking it
out of analysis then an acquiring or an
attaining some outward form. Oh yes yes
yes. The outward form is only a
reflection of the inner knowing. When
you create and generate the vibration of
the inner knowing, this is the way I am,
then your outer reality shows that to
you. You don't get the outer reality
first before you create the inner
belief. You always only get in physical
reality what you already believe to be
the most likely reality you'll
get. And only when you choose to truly
believe with your whole heart and soul,
this really is what I'm all about. This
really is the way I prefer to be. When
you generate that feeling and that
desire and that energy within you, then
your outer reality has absolutely no
choice but to reflect that inner
feeling, that inner
knowingness. Yes. And it is that simple.
Letting yourself know that that
vibration of truth for you is your
vibratory frequency, the vibratory
frequency that represents the being you
chose to be. You will then tune yourself
to that station. When you tune yourself
to that station and let your dial remain
on that station, only the things that
are pertinent to that station can be
received by you. And you can't receive
anything other than what the station is
you are tuned into. But you must decide
to tune to that frequency first.
Otherwise, you're listening to a program
you don't
enjoy. Change the dial and the program
will change along with it.
All right. May I ask for the question? You
right. May I ask for the question? You
don't have to ask. If you could ask um
something else that has come up for me
in my life is uh some months ago I got
uh guidance let's say to move from the
islands because of the earth changes
coming our understanding and this goes for all
our understanding and this goes for all
such so-called prediction is as
follows changes there will be and there
may be isolated events in which
individuals ual may choose to believe
they need to experience the
transformation in catastrophic or
disastrous ways.
However, no one needs to experience the
transformation in a negative way. If
individuals are willing to wake up
within themselves now and recognize they
deserve happiness without having to go
through trials by fire in order to
believe they deserve happiness, then
they won't have to place themselves in a
scenario where they are shaken away.
Allow yourself to simply recognize that
any such
information is only an
opportunity, not an absolute dictim,
only an opportunity to be aware of the
energy within you and what reality you
choose to believe is more true for you.
When you simply recognize that you do
not need to experience that type of a
tool, then you will find that even if
you were to remain in a local that did
experience it, you wouldn't. And that if
enough individuals in your local will
understand they do not need to
experience it that way, the entire local
will not. You follow
not. You follow
me? Yes. No.
Uh yeah. Uh not quite. The idea is to
simply be in touch with the fact that
the so-called future is always fluid.
There are many probable realities. And
when someone says or you perceive, well,
this is going to happen then and it's
going to be very catastrophic, it is
simply one perception of one bandwidth
frequency, one probable reality. Now
that you are aware that there is energy
behind that probable future, if you
don't prefer it, you don't have to stay
on that frequency. It doesn't
necessarily mean that you have to move.
If you simply find that you are in any
local wherein the majority of
consciousness insists on experiencing
the transformation in negative ways, in
catastrophic ways, in destructive ways,
and you simply know you don't need to.
Then whether you even try to or not, you
will simply attract into your life
automatically an opportunity that will
remove you from that local without you
even trying.
without you even planning
to you
follow. So if you find yourself
following what is most exciting for you
and you simply find yourself not
attracting a situation into your life to
remove you from the local you are in. If
you do find that the local you're in is
the most exciting local you would like
to be in in general, then take it as a
sign that you will be able to remain in
that local and that nothing will
interrupt the path you chose to leave.
before and if I find that that person
excites me, then go to where you find it
to be more exciting. But recognize that
that doesn't necessarily mean that you
are taking yourself out of a place that
will experience destruction. You are
simply following the flow of your own
path and going to where you are most
excited to be to surround yourself with
the environment that is then conducive
of the idea you are being. That is it.
None of your planet has to experience
the change in catastrophic ways. None of
it has
to. Depends on your willingness to wake
up. Now, you follow. Yes. Um, one more
Now, you follow. Yes. Um, one more
question. All right. I'm planning a
40-day retreat of silence and partial
fasting. Have a wonderful time. 40 days
is the typical cycle for the complete
transformation of a personality from one
phase into another. 40 years in your
terms for an entire culture. 7787 will
represent the 40th year from 7747 in
your counting. Between that time, a
whole date, a whole culture has
transformed into another culture on your
planet. And you will recognize that from
7747, that was the beginning date that
your culture or at least parts of it
became aware beyond a shadow of a doubt
that you coexisted with other
civilizations in the universe. 7787 will
represent the end of the cycle wherein
the majority of your world will be
aware, at least as a possibility, that
other civilizations exist and will
become more and more aware that portions
of your government also know that other
civilizations exist. 40 years for the
change of a personality of an entire
civilization. 40 days for the change
completely of a personality of an
individual. Enjoy. Is there anything in
particular that I could be doing? Yes.
That you have during those 40 days? Be
yourself completely. Follow your trust,
instinct and intuition. Learn to trust
that the universe supports
you. Thank you. You have created that
particular unique manifestation of your
own self exploration. We thank you for
choosing to be so
sharing.
You um well I have a sharing and a
couple of Oh, right. Uh the first one is
it occurred to me that uh the star
system could also be pronounced play at
the oh how synous of your language
also a similar tonality we've been you
know we've been working with that
circle you've talked you share with us
before and one of the things that came
up for that for me
was I was on a a ship with four beings
and a a very liquid surface on a floor
surface. They were working with a set of
cubes kind of bouncing up and down,
guys. Which I took to mean some level of
preparation, guys. Uh can you tell me
did they appear to be very short or of
your own type? More of my own type. Oh,
uh I was wondering if you had any more
information about that particular. It is
simply your willingness to identify with
them as them and balance yourself along
their frequency to become more familiar
with them so that you can interact more
and more with them. I was curious what
they were doing with those cubes or
balancing those cubes. What that was
about. In a sense, it is the direct
infusion of your particular vibratory
pattern into what you would call their
computer network.
a device that can read your energy,
freeze it, if you will, into the matrix
it represents, and then in that cube
form be completely plugged in as what
you would call one of the cells of the
brain that makes up their
computer. So that they will then with
all the individuals they do this with on
your planet have a combined building
block style
representational artificial model
consciousness of the collective
consciousness of your entire planet. You
follow? Yes. you. One other thing
guys, these ships that were recently
cited of uh Air Alaska, Japan Airlines
about a month ago or so, guys, you
mentioned that uh it was a collection of
civilization, an association of sorts.
Guys, what you to use an analogy? Now we
do not mean that this is literal in our
terms but to use the closest analogy on
your planet it would be as if it were
what you would call a United Nations
ship did not come from any one
particular civilization evolved. Yes.
You you have in the past shared with us
different stories not only among the
dolphins but among your people. Is there
a particular story or legend that they
are carrying on their journey that they
are deliver it to us. We will deliver
this with the assistance of the blending
of another consciousness at another
time, but not yet now. All right. All
right. But you are perceiving that that
is yet to come. That was a part of what
you took with you in that
identification. You follow me? Yes. But
the timing has not quite unfolded, but
it will. That'll just allow my
excitement to all right.
Thank you very much for all right you
guys for sure one moment you want
for sure you have talked about signature
vibration guys do they have physical
representation for each individual and
if they do how can you source that you
have access to your own signature
vibration it is simply that cord that
moves you the most the one that is also
So perhaps in a sense easiest when you
are at your absolute most relaxed and
centered, easiest for you to quote
unquote sing or
hum. That will be representative of the
overall tonal vibration of your physical
body, your physical consciousness, your
physical awareness and also it will be
an indicative link to the other levels
of your consciousness in non-physical
reality. Everyone
is is recognized no matter how many
times their personality shifts or no
matter how many overlays they place upon
it. Everyone is recognized by what we
refer to as the signature vibration. It
is simply the frequency that makes you
different from everyone else. So you're
saying this is something that is more
heard than seen. It can be simply felt.
But you will find that generally
speaking the closest you may get to it
in physical terms is yes through your
auditory sense because then it will be
the tonal pattern that allows every
single cell in your body to say ah yes I
recognize that as my idealized zero rest
state tonality that is who we are that
is who I am. You follow the level zone
that represents whatever chord moves you
the most. Is it possible to assist
someone in discovering that in
themselves? Go right ahead and
begin. What do you think is yours? Are
you in a state of idealized
relaxing? All right. Then when you are,
simply hum to yourself. Sing to
yourself. When you hit it, it will allow
your entire body, not only your physical
body, but your emotional body from right
here to vibrate. You'll feel it. You'll
tingle all over. You'll
know. One sign physically that you may
get is that colors may look a little
brighter when you hit the tone. Mhm. All
right. All right. One other question. Yes.
All right. One other question. Yes.
Sometimes when I'm sometimes when I do
things or talk to people or just do my
excitement, Yes. I see uh purple
geometric flashes. Yeah. You are tapping
through the crown chakra into the very
basics of the astral and causal plane
which many times are interpreted by your
physical
You are tapping through the crown chakra
into the very basics of the astral and
causal plains which many times are
interpreted by your physical
consciousness as abstract geometric
forms because it represents the
so-called building blocks of physical
reality. You are creating a physical
You are creating a physical
interpretation of the geometric matrix
of the vibratory pattern of the
fundamental energy that creates physical
reality. [Music]
[Music]
My new mark. Enjoy the show.
The shark. This morning I was reading an
article called the anatomy of ecstasy.
In which some scientists were explaining
what's going on when we're in this state
of cosmic consciousness. Yes. And what I
gathered from that is that when both
hemispheres of the brain are firing
simultaneously, we will be in that state
of unity of being. Yes. And also you
will allow yourself to let us say let
both hemispheres fire
simultaneously when you realize that you
actually do function as one brain and
stop thinking of yourself as a split
being into two hemispheres.
So what suggestions do you have for me
in terms of I just gave you one.
Stop thinking of yourself as a split
being split into two hemispheres. Begin
to recognize that there is always
communication going on in the total
brain at once. If you wish therefore in
your imagination visualize that you are the
imagination visualize that you are the
total consciousness that you are is at
the very center of your brain. And at
the same time at the same time in your
visualization in your imagination in the
dimension of your imagination imagine
this. Every Every
thing,
everyone, every
situation, every object, every attitude,
every experience that you tend to think of as
experience that you tend to think of as
representations of the externalized
reality, they are all
you. All
you. So imagine your consciousness is at
one of the same time at the very center
of your brain straddling if you wish the
two hemispheres touching both hemispheres if
hemispheres touching both hemispheres if
you wish to tend to think of it that way
and at the same
time see yourself as all that you
experience. See all that you experience
as yourself. Then you will create a
stronger link and a bridge between the
inner reality and the outer reality. And
you will recognize that the outer
reality is the inner reality and that
the nomenclature in and out is all
arbitrary. You are a single
consciousness. You are a single
event. You follow me? Yes. You will
blend cause and effect into one event
and will live in now here and now. All
of it functioning pulsing as one idea,
one event. Sleep on it. Thank you. Thank you
event. Sleep on it. Thank you. Thank you
very much. Sure. There will be but a few
moments remaining for this interaction.
Proceed. Yes. Uh speaking of sleep, some
of us have been very excited about the
idea of lucid dreaming. We were talking
about it earlier. Uh would you explore a
little bit of that? How we can e more
easily put ourselves into that state and
what is it about realizing that you're
dreaming that become so excited that you
break your connection and come back to
your body?
Many times when you create a certain
type of excitement that you do not have
the experience of feeling any other way
other than the way you have felt it in
your body, you will not think that you
can experience it in a non-physical
sense. So when you create within you a
vibration that you're only used to
feeling in physical ways, you will snap
yourself back to an environment that you
think is necessary to experience it. It
is simply habit. That is all. You can
get over it in this way. Allow yourself
to simply recognize that you are living
a dream right now as we have discussed
many times. And you can allow the
physical dream to begin to blend with
the non-physical dream so that you
always know that you are at one at the
same time dreaming and also wide awake.
Allow yourself to know more and more
that you are in control of the events in
your physical reality. And it will leak
into your dream reality to allow you to
know you are in control of the events
there. And that you have the ability at
any given moment to determine what you
will allow in your dream reality as an
experience and what you will not. So
that you will be able to determine your
control over the dream reality which
will in turn reinforce your ability to
know you have ultimate control over the
physical dream as well. You follow me?
Know you are dreaming right now.
begin to create as you are doing the
reality you prefer that will leak over
into the dream reality. The dream
reality will leak over into the physical
reality and once again you will remove
the idea you will dissolve the idea that
the dream reality and the physical
reality are two separate reality. It is
all one reality.
All one reality. Yes, I've been
experiencing that more and more. You are
lucidly dreaming now.
I got that. Thank you. Thank you very
much at
all right.
What part of I am you and what part of
you are you? All 100% in both
directions. But how you may specifically mean that
But how you may specifically mean that
can be taken in the following way. You
are a multi-dimensional being. I am a
multi-dimensional being. There are
intersections wherein we overlap. Those
intersections are determined by what it
is you choose to experience yourself to
be in this life. You say I will set up
this scenario so that I can experience
my personality. I experience my
consciousness in this way. If that
scenario will overlap with other
scenarios, then when I meet those
standing wave patterns, when I meet
those intersections, they will reinforce
themselves to add to the momentum of the
path I chose to lead. You have common
threads in you, common to us. We have
threads in us that are common to you.
When those threads cross and when your
consciousness in moving along your
thread and our consciousness in moving
along our thread come together face to
face, then we simply share that part of
the total equation that we both
separately are.
Thank you very much each and every one
of you at this time. Allow us to extend
to you our appreciation and our
unconditional love and gratitude in
allowing us to experience the unique
manifestation of consciousness that each
and every one of you individually and
collectively are. We thank you for this
gift for it allows us to see all the
different ways that all that is has of
expressing itself within the vibrant and
vital creation that it is. You are just
as vibrant. You are just as vital. Give
yourself the benefit of the doubt. If
you choose to doubt at all, allow
yourself to know that you are the light.
You have the ability together and
individually to represent the shining of
the light of infinite creation through
the vow through the prism that you chose
to be. And when you let that inner light
shine, it will dispel all shadows of a
doubt in your life. The path that you
are will be transparent, crystal clear.
You have only to decide now consciously
that you will begin to live as you
prefer to live. That you will begin to
live as the being you know is true for
you. There is no one way.
There are an infinite number of ways to
express yourself and your connection and
your relation to all that is to infinite
creation. Once again, if there were only
one way, there would only be one person.
Look around. You are all the different ways.
around. You are all the different ways.
We with you all beings within creation
are all the different
ways infinite creation has of expressing
itself within the creation it is. You
are co-creators.
co-creators.
Create the way you prefer to create. For
create you always will whether it be
positive or
negative. So create the way you prefer
to create. And once again allow us to
remind you all you need to do in
whatever way that works for
you is to wake up and dream.
Each and every one of you is as powerful
as you need to be to create anything you
desire in life without having to hurt
anyone else or yourselves in order to
create it. That's how powerful you are.
Wake up to that dream. The reality that
you are pleasant dream [Music]