[Music]
We will begin this evening of your time
with a little bit of a difference in our
interaction. You may entitle this
evening's take turning on the light.
In this way, we will upon commencement,
upon the resume of this interaction,
after your break this evening of your
time, we will commence with a particular
technique and a particular
exercise that will require that each and
every one of you remain in the seat you
have chosen for this evening rather than
standing as you are standing now.
Therefore, we will simply begin this
evening of your time with the idea of
sharing as the technique and the
exercise that we will take you through
after your break time will be
specifically and extremely intense in a
very specialized way and will require
that each and every one of you are in as
relaxed and comfortable a state as you
can be. This technique will take each
and every one of you through the
understanding of how to
directly allow negative imagery within
you to be transformed into positive
effects instantaneously through a very
specific visualization.
We will discuss this more after your
break and at this moment we will
commence with the idea of sharing
unto you.
I just want to share with you my thanks
for all the sharing that you've done
with us and all the reflections that
you've allowed us to connect with from
you. We extend our appreciation to you
as well for allowing us to reflect to
each and every one of you the idea of
your own self-empowerment and the idea
of your own centered life.
Thank you. I think that many of us and I
know for myself have come to the point
in our lives where our lives are truly
becoming dreams. We are living our
dreams. Hey, and I'd like to share
something um that happened to me
recently and probably a lot of other
people here by all means a dream that we
shared together that was a dream and
also reality and that was an evening
when I found myself in a large
auditorium and I looked around and there
were thousands and thousands of people
there. There wasn't an empty seat in the
entire place and we had all come
specifically to that place to that
location from wherever we lived from
where we were were to experience the
gift of channeling by two gentlemen on
the stage uh Jack Pel and Kevin Ryerson.
Hi. And to me looking around the
auditorium, it was magic because I
realized that we indeed are beginning to
live our dreams, to live in fourth
density. And the amount of energy and
agreement and delight in that connection
was marvelous. It is the lever that will
move your entire planet, the entire
universe. Yes, I know. And it's so exciting to me.
Yes, I know. And it's so exciting to me.
Another thing that's uh been exciting me
tremendously recently as you know uh is
the idea of more and more connections
with the water humans, the dolphins and
whales that's going on around the
planet. And this may or may not be the correct
And this may or may not be the correct
timing to ask for another communication
with the the dolphins calling themselves
the dreamers. Could you say something about
dreamers. Could you say something about
that after the exercise after your
break? Wonderful. Thank you very much.
Well, thank you. Sure.
Bashar, this seems to be a night of
thank you. Um, in the four months, some
odd four months that I've been coming to
hear you, my life is changing so
rapidly. Last Friday, I got fired. All
right. Very rapid change indeed. Yes. And uh
Very rapid change indeed. Yes. And uh
and I've been offered two or three jobs
since then at $200 or $300 more a month.
So I see it's it's falling into line. I
love Yes, it always does when you trust
that it always will. And I and your your
help with uh teaching us how to look at
the positive side of it without being
airy very positive thinking has been
largely responsible.
Fine. I think
okay I have one question. uh on a on a
more personal level for myself. I've
just finished reading communion and um I
was uh it was it had quite a an impact
on me that I still haven't sorted out
and I my question
is I have trouble remembering my dreams.
Is there some way that I can facilitate
this in to remember my dreams better?
Some of the techniques we will share
with you this evening will open up many
gates within you. Primary among them
will also be the dream gates. Great.
Okay. But again, rely upon your own
imagination. Rely upon your own ability
to choose consciously to remember your
dreams and allow yourself to recognize
that your higher consciousness will also
listen to the choices you make as a
physical being. You follow me? I do.
Thank you. Thank you. Sharing.
Hello, Bashar. Hello. I have a question
for a friend of mine. All right. She is
the friend here. So, you can ask the
question of the friend. No. No. I'm I'm
going to ask a question of fine to find
you. All right. Um, we enjoy having fun
with you. Good. I enjoy it, too. Um,
she's ill. All right. and she has um
something going on in her right
ovaries that she's been having trouble
with off and on for about three
years. And she has asked you about it
before. She said when she very first uh
came to hear you about two years ago,
she asked you a question about it. You
gave her a meditation cue, which she has
done from time to time. Um, but the
situation continues and it seems like
her body is just kind of hate to say it, but
body is just kind of hate to say it, but
it's starting to fall apart in a way.
She's got troubles with her stomach.
She's got a super high yeast count in
her body. She's exhausted to the point
that she can hardly work.
And hasha had in this way any of what
you call your typical
diagnostic assistance.
She has not gone to a medical doctor.
Why not?
I think she's afraid. All right. Then
that may be the indication that that
would be the thing that would allow her
to face the components within herself
that she needs to face. If there is fear
in that in that way, then there is
something there that needs to be faced.
needs to be
integrated. The idea of whether or not
you participate in what to call your
typical colloquial medicinal practices
usually will be determined as to whether
or not you simply know that that is for
you or not for you. But if you find that
you have a fear regarding that idea,
then that is an indication there is
something that lies along that path that
you need to integrate. So that
individual, it would be our suggestion,
could at least give themselves the
opportunity to discuss these ideas with
those medical personnel for that may
actually be what will be of best
assistance right now. At least the
discussion with those individuals she
fears to face because then she will at
least be facing certain fears about
herself. You follow me? Yes. That may
bring up enough understanding to assist
in alleviating some of the so-called
problem, but it will at least steer her
in a direction that will place within
her the responsibility for facing her
feelings. You follow me? Yes.
The idea above and beyond anything, even
though we recognize in your society many
individuals desire to remove themselves
from certain practices, certain habitual
practices upon your planet, there is no
need to
force that type of spirituality upon
yourself. The idea is to be true to what
belief systems are strongest within.
That is what will allow you to
integrate, to know that you no longer
need certain belief systems that you say
you desire to no longer need.
You follow me? Yes. Does that assist?
Yes, it does. Thank you very much. Thank
you. Bye.
Sh. Hello. Hello. Um, I
Hello. Hello. Um, I
recently had gotten in contact with um
some old thoughts about some crystals.
Can you speak a little? And I have one
with me right now. And it appears to me
to be black because when I hold it to a
strong light, it it's so opaque. I can't
even like a purple tinge to it. All
right. I was wondering um what it is and
how I can use it. How does your
imagination tell you to use it? Uh to
get in contact with fears, basically.
All right. Have you done so? With some.
Yes. And and they're not fears anymore.
Well then, well then there's nothing
else you can add to this.
The idea of the black coloration can be
symbolic of that which draw that which
is absorptive in that way. It can allow
you in a meditation to go into the very
center of your being and absorb and draw
and attract all information that you
need on any level for any reason
whatsoever. You can use it as a basic
fundamental symbol of an inward flowing
gate, the center of your being in that
sense. You follow me? Yes. You can use
it that way if you wish.
There are many ways you can use it. It
will depend upon the affinity your
imagination has and the willingness you
have to allow your imagination free
reign in determining in which ways it
seems to work best for you. Okay? You
would not have attracted that idea if it
would not work for you on some level.
You would have attracted something else.
So simply trust your imagination since
you have already indicated that doing so
has brought you rewards. Do you follow
me? Yes. Continue to trust it in that
way. There are many other specific ideas
we could annotate for you with this
idea, but you are doing just fine. It is
allowing you to create the balance
necessary within your life. It is
allowing you to also
exercise your
imagination. You follow me? Yes. And
that exercise in the imagination is what will
exercise in the imagination is what will
balance you out. You follow me? Uh-huh.
Does that assist you? Yes, it does. One
moment. Do you like blue flowers? Yes, I do.
Do you like blue flowers? Yes, I do.
Then you can use that as a symbol as
well. You can carry one with you as you
walk into the
stone. If you
wish, you can walk through a field of
them in your imagination. If you wish,
and each and every one of them may have,
well, to put it in your terminology,
secrets to share with
you. Listen to them. They are the waves
of mentality that carry
information. You follow me?
Yes. Thank you. Um I have one more
question. Hey, just recently um I
channeled an energy called Darca and I
was wondering if there's anything you
could tell me um about that energy or
how I may um get a stronger bond. Thank
you. To some degree it is an archetypal
format. From our perspective, from a
relative point of view, there seems to
be a linear connection back through what
you would call ancient India. At least
in the Himalayan region to some extent.
There may be a gate, a very strong
doorway there for you in that way. If
you follow that path, you may find
yourself wandering in and among those
mountains at some point in your life.
One moment. You may find some of those
moment. You may find some of those
flowers in that area as well. To some
degree, a field of that color, of that
color blue, in that way to some degree
represents a familiar land to
you. Some of it is extremely ancient.
You are retracing your steps in many
ways and walking backwards through that
doorway, going back through that
absorbed doorway.
You will collect yourself together at an
origin point so to speak. So you can
explode in a new direction in a new
universe. The crystal, the dark crystal
for you in that sense is a doorway, a
gateway in that sense. You are going
back through the zero point and you will
reexlode in a new direction in white
light. You follow me on the other side
of that door. But there are many ancient
streams that you are retracing at this
point. Enjoy. Thank you very much. Thank
you. Shannon. Shannon.
Hello.
Hello. Would you share with us some of
your knowledge about astrology covering
such um topics as how it originated in
our planet, how it works? I know it's a
belief system, but uh what are the
energetics involved? And um could you
comment about the planet Vulcan? Is it
physical, non-physical, a real or a
myth? And what role will astrology play
in our in the future of society that we
are creating? It's a good thing we do
not wear watches.
Astrology as you call it, yes, in a
sense is a belief system, but it does
represent at least an instinctive
awareness of mathematical vibratory
relationships, wavelength relationships
that, to put it very simply and
succinctly, represent the overall
general agreements of your entire
society. the timings of the events and
the interactions synchronistically of
those events, the signature vibrations
of all the individuals involved in the
contract and the fulfillment of some of
the ideas, the general themes being
played out in each individual life and
the overall lives and contracts and
agreements you have formed with each
other. You can glean energy patterns
from the idea. You can make correlations
in that way knowing that when you are a
non-physical being and choose to project
yourself into physical materiality, you
will take on a solidification of
whatever vibratory patterns in that
universe happen to be going on at that
time. And so there are reflective
symbols that represent each and every
one of those particular let us say lay
lines of the universe through your
particular coordinates. And in being
born physically at a certain time, you
will in a sense freeze those lay lines
into your physical form and they can be
read. They can be scrolled out in that
way. It is to some degree a mathematical
relationship. But much of it is
dependent upon the instincts and
intuitiveness of the individual doing
the reading, doing the calling out. For
like everything, it is still
holographic. And the information
extracted will depend upon the point of
view of the individual doing the reading
and the place in time the place in
timing that the individual that the
reading is being done for is at at that
particular moment. Now this idea the
basic understanding the perspective that
you recognize today as astrology was
begun in what you call atalantis. It has
been let us say rendered into a
different form since its original
inception. And much of the information
and much of the understanding has in
your terms been let us say misplaced
rather than lost entirely or
misinterpreted in many different ways or
let us say simply interpreted along the
modalities of the
time. But generally your instincts can
serve you and you can glean what you
need to glean out of any particular
vibrational relationship pattern and you
can be highly accurate in that way.
Now the idea of a Vulcan as you say well
we perceive that in your
society there is a very
small planettoid mass orbiting your sun
on the inner orbits that some of your
scientists have in your terms called
Vulcan. But the idea is that your solar system
But the idea is that your solar system
does contain two planets that are not in
your physical dimensional vibratory
plane. Neither of them are specifically
the idea you would call Vulcan. But
there are two planets in that vibratory
plane that you do not perceive
physically. They are a part as far as we
are concerned of your solar system.
There is another physiological planet
that you have not discovered yet but it
is not inward. It is farther out. You
follow me?
Yes. Astrology.
Most of these ideas will become
coales simplified down to their basic
fundamental formats of recognition which
is again the understanding that all
things are vibration and that your
consciousness is vibration. that your physical reality
is vibration. that your physical reality
is the product of certain
interreationships of vibrations within
the consciousness that you are. It will
all be understood as synchronicity, all
be understood as one and the same thing
interacting in many different ways. It
can be rendered down into very
simplified mathematical formula if you
wish. But the mathematical formula will
not necessarily take the configurations
you are used to using now. There may be
new symbols that are created, conceptual
symbols that may be in and of themselves
representing more whole relationship
type concepts rather than simply
discrete numerical values. Astrology may
in what you call a 100, 200, 300 years
of your time be rendered into more
precise understanding of energy
relationships and the vibratory
schematics that generate any particular
physiological universe. In other words,
when you learn the scale, the fabric of
those vibratory cords within the
hologram, astrology will be more of an
applied idea in a physiological state.
You will know what strings in a sense to
pull to generate spontaneous creations
of physiological environments and
universes. You will set up the
parameters in that way. It will not
simply be a received information. You
will vibrate in accord to the
understanding of the particular
relationships energy and you will be
able to play it like a musical
instrument and generate conditions
throughout the physiological universe to
reflect the idea of your mentality. You
follow me? Yes. Thank you very much.
Thank you, Karen. Hello. Hello. Um, I'd like
you, Karen. Hello. Hello. Um, I'd like
to know the origin of my fear at night.
Well, it is always from within you.
In what way do you feel? How does it
feel? What type of fear? Can you define
and describe it? Um, I'm fearful
of my thoughts. I'm fearful of seeing
something. When I was a child, I saw an
entity. Yes. And it scared me for years.
All right. And can you tell me what that
was? To some degree, in your terms, it was a
To some degree, in your terms, it was a
manifestation of what you would call.
Now, this is both spiritual and
extraterrestrial consciousness. Do understand it is quite
consciousness. Do understand it is quite
normal, quite natural for children who
have not yet unlearned that they are not
supposed to see those things to see
those things. quite natural because
everyone has the ability to see energy
in various form projections of
consciousness into one reality or
another. This is a quite natural
phenomena. In a sense, you are being
paid a visit. It was not unfriendly. But
the fear you feel was simply the fears
that came up of the belief systems that
you had already by that time bought into
within your society. Seeing something
that does not seem to fit, seeing
something that you have been taught does
not fit usually causes you to re-examine
in a flash the idea of all that you have
been taught and it is very for your
civilization unsettling and that causes
fear. You feel like you have no stable
foundation. You feel like that one
particular event, that one particular
interaction removes the stabilizing
foundation of your life and your ego
consciousness panics. That is the fear
you are feeling. But recognize it is
quite a natural event and in this way it
actually increased your stability in
many ways. For change and fluctuation
and interaction are the grand constants
of universal creation and your ability
to perceive more widely than more
limitedly is what actually will
stabilize you. You follow me so far?
Yes. So the idea is to recognize that
there was nothing inherently fearful
about that interaction. Simply what was
brought up within you were many of the
beliefs you had bought into at that
time. You were buying into them very
rapidly. You were locking into them very
solidly. And so you had arranged with
that friend by a prior agreement. Well,
let me put it colloially. Say friend,
I'm going to go into this physical life.
If at any time you find that I am going
to limit myself a little bit too much,
well do step in and chalk me out of it,
won't you?
You follow me. They were only doing as
you had agreed. They were allowing you
to always know that there was that
little bit of uncertainty, that little
bit of unexpectedness that would not
allow you to lock too strongly into a
particular reality that you did not
necessarily want to limit yourself
within to that extent. you following.
Mhm. Now, they are still with you in
many ways, you will find yourself easily
able to communicate in your dream
realities above and beyond. first of all
with them. If you are willing to
recognize that it was by agreement, by a
friendly arrangement, and that they
performed a service, a service you asked
them to perform in that way to ensure
that you would not become too rigidized
into this particular reality. So that
there would be this gate that you would
need to explore at this time. So that
you would leave something open for
yourself. So that you would know that
once you stepped through that gate, the
whole world would be new and fascinating
again as it was when you were a child.
You follow me? Mhm. So you may now
within your sleep time simply open up to
the understanding that everything has
occurred by your agreement and call upon
your friend again and you may begin
dream dialogues that will allow you to
acclimate and feel more at home with
that being and then they may be able to
share many stories with you.
Where is my friend from?
Not now. Let them tell you. Okay. All
right. Thank you. Well, thank you very
much. And pleasantry.
Hello, Bashar. Hello. Yeah, this is a
personal uh question. Reference to um
last three years I've been pursuing an
acting career. Pursuing it. Okay. Are
you tired
yet? sometimes. Yes. Uh all right. Okay.
Are you an actor? Yes, I am. Well, thank
you. And
uh in the effort to try to make a a
living at it, I've encountered many
stumbling blocks. Y and I was wondering
if you have any advice in this uh that
you might be able to offer. Yes. Treat
them as opportunities to refine your
craft, not as interruptions in it. How's
that? Good. Act through the so-called
Good. Act through the so-called
stumbling
blocks and you will gain a wealth of
information. You will discover a wealth
of facets about yourself that you will
be able to then channel in your acting
career. But recognize the idea of
acting. What you call true acting is
channeling. You are actually being those
different personality fragments. You are
being those
persona. You have given yourself the
different scenarios you seem to come
across to develop certain ideas. Now we
do not mean that you have to suffer. No,
no, no.
You are simply looking at it as
suffering. You will discover as soon as
you change your attitude and your
perspective that these same
circumstances will contain a wealth of
excitement and a wealth of
interesting escapades. You will also find that they
escapades. You will also find that they
are there for a reason. And when you
stop treating them as interruptions in
your life and start treating them as a
part of the path you are, you will find
that they will actually lead you more
often than you think they can into
scenarios that you have been trying to
get to. But because you are saying that
these things have no business being in
your life, you do not allow them to be
the conveyors that they actually are to
take you where it is you actually want
to go. Because you will get where you're
going more often than not by unexpected
means. Not always the way you think is
the way you should get there. Well, this
is what it says in the
book. This is the way everyone knows you
have to get there. ABC. There it is. If
I cannot get from A to B, I cannot be an
actor. But there are many ways to
arrange the ABCs. And when you arrange
them in different ways, that's when you
create language. You create different
words, new meaning. Allow them to order
themselves in whatever way they need to
to speak the language that is your
language. That is what will get you
there. You do not have to go by the book
to follow it. Mhm. Does this assist you
so far? Yes, it does. Any other aspect
you need to investigate? Uh yeah. On
expecting. Yeah.
Expectancy is different from
expectation. That's what I was going to
ask. All right. Expectancy is the
knowingness of your deservability.
The allowance and the willingness to
feel the momentum and the desire and the
excitement within you and you know this
is what I am all about. I am an actor.
This is what moves me. This is what I
desire to do.
Expectation very often is the laying
down of certain parameters through which
you are taught to think must be the path
you take to fulfilling your
expectancy. But that is not always the
case. You follow me? Yes.
Unexpected. The
unexpected spontaneity. Does not an
actor after all wish for spontaneity in
the acting? Then let life itself teach
you the act and the art of spontaneity.
You follow? Yes. You will then simply
fall into the park.
That would be nice. That is what the
stumbling block can be for. And and
And and
and listen to yourself. That would be
nice. Would be
someday. It is right
now that spontaneous. Everything you are
doing is a spontaneous action in one
way, shape or form.
You can make it seem
stilted by the viewpoint you have of
it, but allow yourself to know that
everything you do
experience does add to your repertoire.
All right? Be
right? Be
yourself first and
foremost. Then you can be any other you
you can
imagine. When you are willing to have
that degree of spontaneity about
yourselves, others will recognize that
and will desire you to express your
craft for their
work. For they will wish that degree of
spontaneous realism and life that will
come from you follow. Yes. Oh, thank you
very much. Thank you.
Break a leg.
Shann evening and to you. Good day. Two
areas of dialogue. Number one. Number
one, there is a man holdings have
anything to do with the
idea and do I do you feel or see any uh
do I have any practical working
relationship?
A we do not perceive that area as what
you would call in the immediate future
beachfront
property. There are
centers of energy that you may wish to
avail yourself of to tap into. There are
many many lucrative as you say in your
society ideas, ideas,
communities,
centers, expressions of art, expressions
of
life, new understandings of technology
that will arise in that area. It will be
a center in a different
way. Not that any other area of your
world has to be eliminated for it to be
so. It is in a sense a beach head in many
It is in a sense a beach head in many
ways mostly of energy and new
ideas and new expressive form. And in
that way you may find yourself becoming
involved simply because you may be
attracted to that area and wish to
partake of some of that land for that
usage for the expression of the
different ways in which energy can be
expressed and projects can be created in
that area. It is very fruitful that area
for the creation of many interactive
energy endeavors
mainly ranch land and desert now. Yes.
You see an accelerated future for it in
which which will take place in his
lifetime and yours. Yes.
and yours. Yes.
The practical potential working
relationship is not between our
companies but my going down there and
availing myself of that energy. Or is it
both? There may be some interaction, but
you may
find that you may wish to create things
that are more tangential to the things
that they are interested in. You may
have some common interests that will
allow you each to do what you need to do
and you may trade along certain lines.
The interaction as we perceive it now
will mostly come from you simply
occupying a similar area and using the
energy in your own way. It will simply
be noticed by those that use the energy
in other ways. You follow me? Yeah, I
do. Uh it was described to me briefly in
a psychic session that he was uh in
another lifetime a father to some
degree. Yes, in a sense has been a
mentor and a grandfather as well.
Second question is in watching the show
that's on this week America wondered
would would like very much to hear your
feelings about it. Also, it occurred to
me as I was watching since I'm thinking
about something else that may happen in
this country which is based some form of
accelerated economic depression that in
fact the writer director was in a
metaphorical way really writing about
that as well to some degree but again
the idea does not have to be a
depression. What you are simply
recognizing is that your economic
structure is shifting, is changing. And
yes, in your terms, the old one may need
to break down. But that breakdown does
not in any way, shape or form mean it
must be in a depletive manner. It can be
replaced. It can be regrown in a
different way. It can be transformed.
You follow it? Yeah, I do. I don't see
depression as a pjorative word. I didn't
mean it that way. All right. But there
will be do you feel a major shifting in
the economy? Oh yes.
Values in America reflect that in a
certain unconscious consciousness. The
values of your entire earth reflect it
because you are now becoming global and
so you need a global economy in a sense
although it will not be economics as you
have known it.
And that may be one of the answers to
the global economy. Yes. begin by basing
your economics on each other, not on a
symbol.
You understand? Yes. Well, yes. About
50% of that. If you could move through
that and and talk about the global level
as well.
You yourself are what your services.
That is all there is to it.
Direct interaction between
interaction between
individuals with the removal of the
limitations you call
borders will facilitate an interactive
global I it is simply the
reortionment of the resources that you
have and the reshifting of your
priorities for there is no lack upon
your world at all. There is no
overpopulation upon your world at all.
There is simply a particular
dispersement of
individuals and resources in such a way
as to make it seem as if there is a
lack. You follow me? Mhm. So the sharing
of responsibilities in any path. Okay.
And the reliance upon the resources of
all rather than the hoarding of or the
fearing of others in terms of being able
to deplete your own resources.
Democracy of ideas.
The republic of ideas in a sense.
But we understand what you mean.
That does.
Hi Vash. Hi. About 10 years ago, my
father died and having two heart attacks, two
died and having two heart attacks, two
heart
transplants, and it very uh had a great
impact on myself and his younger
children. shed some light on the agreements that
shed some light on the agreements that
we had in the participation of his
passing and the effect it had on their
lives. This
individual has also been a mother to you
all many times has nurtured and cared
for you all many
times. In this way, this individual has
always enjoyed in many of the lifetimes
the larger gathering of the family, the
larger creation of family members. In
that way, the
way, the
idea simply in this way is that the
heart energy that was being
utilized to some degree was being
blocked by belief
systems. Belief systems that allow the
individual to buy
to buy
into the perspective that to care for
and nurture to some degree meant sacrifice
nurture to some degree meant sacrifice
to follow. Makes sense.
Now this individual as we perceive the
energy of this individual has been
reincarnated for approximately what you
would call seven of your
years. All of us. Yes. Is there anyone
that I
know? Yes, it
is. Use my
imagination. This may
fluctuate. This may in your frame of
reference not be
considered accurate. Is there a male youth of
accurate. Is there a male youth of
approximately that age that is what you
would call brownish blonde?
that you are aware of.
I can hear the individual is somewhere
near in your sphere of
availability, somewhere near in your
sphere within one or two levels of
acquaintance. Possibly, possibly as we perceive the
Possibly, possibly as we perceive the
vibration and again this may bear
translation difficulty into your
language, into your vibration.
with the
Roman that he would
call the child may
appear will
carry some of that energy.
This is at this point difficult to
perceive
clearly but it is a very joyful child.
Yes. So the child will be as
well this time
free from the
constriction but there may be something
about the
heart that still allows there to be a
recognition of this identity. There may
be palpitations in the
heart of this child that can aid the
child and assist the child later in life
or right now in many ways act as a
sensor device sensitive to
electromagnetic energy. We will
We will
see. But we sense the child's energy
very strongly at least from our
perspective. And it seems in your terms
physical solid and to
you
close it passing had a profound
effect on me as I was standing in line
of course but uh very much so
emotional and psychological
disorientation on other children and it just saw after
on other children and it just saw after
not for a long
long
she still I
still need to
know is that always this individual love
unconditionally. Still, if they are
willing to receive the gift of that love
and use that love, use that
love to know that life is for living,
for enjoying. If they are willing to express
enjoying. If they are willing to express
the joy of that individual through
themselves, then they will be allowing
that energy to exist still in their
lives and they will be expressing his
energy in the way that the gift was
meant to be
received. Sadness in that way, while it
may serve other purposes for them, is
not the expression of the gift of his
love. directly involve. Yes. I I in fact call
directly involve. Yes. I I in fact call
upon him and feel his love all the time.
Yes. I'm not sure that they they can if
they wish.
If you
wish the exercise that we will share
with you this evening of your time, you
may share with them and again it may
open doorways within them that will
allow for dream communication with the
oversoul of all of you. Let us say a
family clan meeting within the
soul to understand that that portion of
that individual on that level is still
very much alive even though there is
reincarnational aspect still going
on and that once you gather together and
reaffirm the
familial familiarity then you can get on your
familiarity then you can get on your
life knowing I'm lost. No way.
Thank you very much. Thank you,
chatting.
Good evening, Michelle. Oh. Oh, one
moment. It might also
be Richard or Ricky. Yes.
Yes.
Um I have three questions this evening.
Um one represents seven other people
here this evening. Oh, right. Um last
night at 5:30 I lost my mother and our
dear beloved grandmother. And they would
all like to know where she is and who
she's with if possible.
There are what you would call right now
beings that are presenting themselves in
what you would call angelic
form to soften the
transformation. You follow me?
Always an individual in making the
crossing as you say is always in loving
hands. Always
Always
always they are
nurtured. They are assisted along bit by
bit until they can awaken
from what might have been the
shock of the crossing. A shock that is
only created because of the belief
systems that you may wish to take with
you. Bit by
bit they will drop those belief systems
like you would take off a heavy
cloak and another cloak and another and
another until you yourself are all the
garment you need until you are shining
light. They are on that road right
now. They are peeling away the outer
petals of the
flower to arrive at the kernel at the
seed to where they will discover that
they are made of shining
light. They are being shown shining
light by these beings that are assisting
them. There are
aspects within those beings that they
will recognize as old
friends. And to some degree they are,
old friend. There are aspects they will
friend. There are aspects they will
recognize from other lives, not knowing
at first that they recognize them from
other lives. Simply that they recognize
them and that they are
familiar. And oh my goodness, there you
are. Where have you
been all this time?
They will be eased into the
understanding. They will be eased into
the understanding that they can love you
still and that any love you feel for
them will be felt and it will assist
them in accelerating to understand their
own creator. So send them love and you
will be playing your part from this end
even as those beings are playing their
part from that end to assist them to
awaken to the new state of life in which
they now exist. Again, no one is
lost. Everyone is exactly where they
need to
be. There is no real
separation. And again in your dream reality
reality
within three of your months at the
outside there will be a flood of love
and communication from them once they
arrive at a certain awareness
level. And in that communication may
come many of the
ideas that they do know you love them,
that they wish you to know they love
you, and that the best way to express
your love for them is to live your life
to the fullest.
You follow it? Yes, I do. Um, the second
question is concerning automatic
writings that I that I was given to do
I would have a question concerning my
grandmother. Um it's not that funny
but between all of us. She loved
chocolate. Would she be able to have
what she
in a sense? Yes. For again do understand
that when you first as you say cross
over from physical to non-physical
states, you recognize very quickly
relatively so that you are a thought
form in a world of thought form. Now you
know you create your
reality. The idea is still the same
there only more quickly. The second you
conceive of any idea that is what you
will experience and it will seem to you
as solid as physical reality seems. You
follow me? What she may come to realize very
me? What she may come to realize very
quickly that the main difference will be
is that she can eat all the chocolate
she wants and she won't get ill.
And that may allow them to begin to
wonder what is going
on. You follow
me? Whatever beliefs you carry with you
are what you most immediately
experience in the astral realm because
you are a thought form in a world of
thought form. And as you think so you
perceive seemingly solidly. But the
minute you change your thought, that is
what you perceive. That is how you
create your physical reality as well.
But because it comes with the notion of
time, then here it takes
time. There there is no time. So as soon
as you think it, that's what you
perceive. And in a
sense, because of the lack of
limitation, the experience of the eating
of that idea
chocolate may be far more exhilarating
of an experience there than it ever was
in physical
reality because it will be being
tasted with the entire
soul. You follow me?
Does that assist you?
Um, may I ask the other question? Yes.
Um, I was given automatic writing over
the past 20 years to finish a novel and
screenplay. All right. It's very
political. Um, I was told I could be stopped by
Um, I was told I could be stopped by
who? By the FBI.
Um, how so? And who told you? Maybe the
FBI in
Um, what I want to know is I did my part
in writing it. I had never written
anything before. All right. And I want
to know why it isn't out. If if America
needs to hear this,
why is is it not out? And perhaps simply
because of the fear that you may be
buying into or that other individuals
may be buying into that it can be
stopped. It is only the fear that it can be
It is only the fear that it can be
stopped that stops it. Well, they're
afraid afraid of it. But am I
responsible for pushing it and the
publishing of it? If I did the writing,
do I have to do that, too? You do not
necessarily have to. Of course, you do
not have to do anything. But the idea is
that if you are motivated to want to see
it expressed in a certain way, then
simply it is not a matter of working at
it. It is not a matter of struggling to
get it out. It is simply a matter of
still being excited about the whole
event, the whole idea. In other words,
do not peacemeal it into, well, here's
the writing. Well, here's the
publishing. Well, here's this. Here's
that. Allow it to be one event that
partakes of a single momentum. A single
momentum. Carry the same excitement for
all phases. Let all phases be
representative of one idea. Then if
there is anything you can do about the
rest of it, you will simply
automatically attract whatever
individuals are necessary into your life
who may be able to facilitate the rest
of it better than you can. You follow
it? Yes. Yes, I do. Does that assist?
Yes, it does. And thank you very much.
Remember an idea whose time has come
cannot be stopped no matter what. Follow
it. I see. Thank you. Uh, one more. This
is a question for a friend of mine who's
here tonight. She has a menangioma
behind the eye. They want to operate and
they don't guarantee that she will not
be blind. It's attached to the retina
and to the brain. and we want to know
she believes in holistic and spiritual
medicine and we are trying to stop her
from being having surgery since there's
no guarantee. Uh do you have any
feelings on? We can suggest that you can
do a combination of the
two. If there are belief systems within
this individual, even a small belief that
individual, even a small belief that
they perhaps should avail themselves of
the surgery, they can at the same time use
surgery, they can at the same time use
the meditative and holistic as you say
approach to again wrap the entire event
in an aligning energy that will
precisely guide all the individuals in
that event in such a way that it will in
your terms be successful. uccessful. You
follow me? Yes, I do. Yes, I do. Thank
you. Thank you.
Chatting.
Hello, Bashar. Hello. I was wondering if
you could please beam me up in your UFO
ship in the physical.
Not at this timing. Okay. And then I
wanted to ask you uh regarding my
physical problems, where could I go? Who
could I seek out? What kind of um
healings can I seek out for my bodily
problems? What are you defining as your
so-called problems? You mean tell you
what's wrong with me? What are the
circumstances? Yes. Well, it doctors
have botched me up and I find that every
time I try to go to a doctor to get
help, they botch me up even more. And
then I tried to go to the holistic
doctors and they also bodgeged me up. I
see. So I don't know who to go to
anymore. How about you?
Well, I told since you created the
situations with them since you created
the so-called misalignments in that way,
why not uncreate them? Well, I tried
going to myself and it just helps to a
certain degree. It doesn't help totally.
All right. In what way do you imagine would
right. In what way do you imagine would
be necessary for you to be completely
aligned then?
Well, I don't know what you mean. All
right. In what way do you believe you
are out of alignment?
Well, my body is is has a potentially
life-threatening situation on it right
now. If I don't such as well if I don't
get help I know I'll end up in a
hospital or you know I'll pass away
eventually. I hate to say that. It
sounds so negative. Not necessarily. But
recognize again when you say well I know
that it will wind up this way. That is
your prescription for yourself that you
are writing right now.
doctor, you are assuming a particular
outcome just because of a certain
circumstance you
have. That circumstance does not
necessarily have to have that outcome.
So there is really no reason for you to
say, "Well, I know it will wind up this
way." If you choose to believe that
that's the way you'll wind up, that is
what will create that scenario. Your
beliefs are what govern your physical
reality totally,
utterly. It was your beliefs that
attracted you to the particular
practitioners that allowed you to feel
more and more
misaligned. Your beliefs about them,
your beliefs about yourself were not
aligned. And so any interaction you had
only increased and accelerated the
misalignment. When you allow yourself to begin to
When you allow yourself to begin to
align your beliefs about yourself with
yourself and your beliefs about physical
reality with yourself, then you will
know you can at any time write the
prescription that
will allow you to function as that which
can center yourself since you are that
which imbalanced yourself to begin with.
Now define the idea you
assume is a
lifethreatening scenario. Well, I have
what's called a degenerative disease
where it's destroying my body and
causing me to rapidly age. Does it have
a name? Well, I was diagnosed by an MD
and a dentist with this particular
thing. And I see the handwriting on the
wall. What wall? What handwriting? And
whose is it?
Well, it would well for instance, even
my own dreams gave me warnings of this.
Yes. But again, understand your dreams
in that way, your higher self is simply
speaking to you about the state of mind
you are in. And it simply told you that
if your state of mind does not change,
this is the physical
result. You follow me? Uh-huh. That is
what warnings are all about. Warnings
are not sentences that are passed upon
you. They are opportunities to discover
the state of mind you are in and
understand completely what that state of
mind will result in. So when you say
well I know this will lead to that that
is the state of mind that created that
to begin with that will of course then
lead to other things. Well, originally
when the first doctor botched me up,
which is was the main cause and the One
moment. One
moment. In what way did they botch you
up? Well, they caused an infection in my
bone. All right. Why, in your terms,
were you seeing them to begin with?
Well, because one referred me to
another. I guess he got a kickback.
Why were you going to a doctor to begin
with? Well, I shouldn't have, but at
that time I thought they were gods. And
why were you there? For what reason were
you there? Well, that's what I'm saying.
I had no right to be there, but one told
me to go to the other one. You are not
answering the question. Why were you
seeing one at all? Did you think you had
an illness at that point? Well, no.
There was nothing wrong with me then.
Why were you seeing a doctor?
because another doctor referred me to
him. Why did you go to the first doctor?
Well, because everybody has to have a
checkup. That was all I went to was for
a checkup. All
right. Thank you for answering the
question. That is all we were asking you
is what brought you to the first doctor
to begin with. Well, it's for a checkup.
Thank you.
Now, recognize again that there are many
different belief systems and cycles
within your society.
The reason you are there to begin with
and what you are told to begin with is
always going to be reflective of the
beliefs you have within you to begin
with. So
you leading yourself from doctor to
doctor and continuing on a cycle of what
you call
degradation is indicative of the way
your mental processes were working
before you even went to the first doctor
for the
checkup. What were you taught about the
idea of needing a checkup?
Well, I I don't know what I was taught.
I I don't know what I was taught.
How did you feel when you went in for
that first
checkup before you went in? Well, I I
remember how I felt and I and I guess
that was the cause of it. I I I was I
remember how I felt emotionally. Yes.
How did you feel? I I was grieving. I
was in great sorrow and grieving. In
fact, and and that that kind of thing.
Why? Well, it was such a trivial little
Well, it was such a trivial little
thing. That's why I don't even as I look
back, I don't even know why I was so
sad. It was such a trivial thing as I
look back. But then at the time, it was
a big thing to me. What was it? Well, a
boyfriend was mean to me. All
right. All right.
But understand when you are in those
types of states
emotionally you create symptoms in your
body that the doctors may have thought
indicated something else.
Also understand that the treatment that
the doctors had upon you, the effect
that their treatment had upon you is a
continuation of what you were attracting
into your life emotionally at that time.
allowing people in that
way to enact out upon you their lack of
integrity. You were surmising that you
were under someone's care
emotionally and they hurt you or you
allowed yourself to be hurt. You chose
to believe in being hurt by that
individual. You created the appropriate
emotional state to go along with it. And
you continued that idea going from
supposedly authority figure to authority
figure who continually reinforced the
original state you created with your
boyfriend. I see what you're saying. So
you have continued the momentum only as
a reaction, a reaction to reaction to
reaction to reaction. But but but let me
ask you this.
Well, I don't I you know, I don't mean
to prolong it, but this this oral
surgeon who caused the inspection of my
bone, I feel that he was getting back at
me from another lifetime, getting
revenge back at me from another
lifetime. What about whether or not that
is the case, the point of the matter is
is nothing
nothing can happen to
you that does not belong or fit in what
you will allow in your belief system.
Whether that individual was someone
partaking in revenge or not has nothing
at all to do with the fact that you
created for
yourself a state of vibratory awareness
that would allow you to attract an
individual who may or may not do that to
you. You are responsible for this
regardless of their part in it. They may
have their responsibility, but you are
responsible for any effect that occurs
in your being. Well, that's true. But
but how do I get out of that? I I I'm
getting to that point. Okay.
First and foremost, take responsibility
for having created what you have
now. Because no one can do anything to
you that is not in synchronous accord
with your vibratory awareness with what
you will allow to happen with what you
will create for
yourself. You understand? Yes, I do. All
right. Start treating yourself with
respect. Start learning to love yourself
Start learning to love yourself
unconditionally
regardless of what anyone else thinks of
you. That is the prescription you need.
You need to start to know yourself, to
truly believe in yourself, to truly love
yourself regardless of whether anyone
else ever shows you love because the
universe loves you. All creation loves
you. You
exist. And the only reason you would
exist is if infinite creation loved you
unconditionally to have created you to
begin with.
Start treating yourself with the same
respect, with the same unconditional
love, and you will heal yourself because
you will go back to your natural center
and you will not rely upon others for
your validation, for your
validation, for your
validity. As you relied upon the idea of
your boyfriend, as you relied upon the
idea of those doctors, as you rely upon
any other individual to validate you,
you invalidate more and more and more of
yourself and you eat away at
yourself. You tear yourself
down because you are looking for others
to validate you. You do not believe you
have the power it takes to validate
yourself. Any emotional reaction you
have to any scenario as you described it
from your boyfriend in that way does not
come out of the
blue. That type of emotional reaction is
not always what will be a reaction to
someone who chooses to be mean to you.
It does not have to be that
reaction. Usually that type of sorrow,
that type of hurt only comes when you
even a little bit buy into the idea that
what they are saying to you might
possibly have any validity in your
life. That you would have to buy into
the idea that hurtful things that
someone might say to you might possibly
have anything at all to do with the
person you actually are. rather than
saying, "Who are you talking
about? Your hurtfulness toward me has
nothing to do with the love I know I
deserve. So I choose to know that your
statements may be a reflection of what
you believe is true in your reality, but
I know it's not true in mine. And so I
will not have those emotional reactions
of negativity because your emotional
reactions are always secondary to your
beliefs. If you are experiencing
negative emotionality, it is because you
have negative
beliefs. There is no way you can
experience a negative emotionality
without already believing a negative
belief. All emotions are reactions to
belief. The belief is there first. The
emotion many times when it comes out
shows you you have that belief. But the
emotion is never there first.
Never. So if you find yourself in a
negative emotional state, it is because
you are already in a negative belief
state about
yourself. The prescription you need from
yourself is to love yourself every
moment. You deserve it. You are worthy of
You deserve it. You are worthy of
it. You are worthy of
life. You are strength. You are
infinite. You are
unlimited. You are as powerful as you
need to be to create anything you desire
without having to hurt anyone else or
yourself in order to create
it. Write that down.
to yourself from yourself as your
prescription from yourself. The doctor
self that you are to the patient self
that you are. Sign
it. Take it to the pharmacy of
life. Fill that prescription out. One
supply unlimited of unconditional love.
Please get behind the counter. Yes,
ma'am. Right
away. Here it is. An unlimited
[Music] lifetimes supply of unconditional
love. All right.
You can completely regenerate
yourself. And if you love yourself and
are willing to believe you deserve that
love, then you will allow, not
make, not force, not
push, allow yourself back into your
natural state of health. Because the
only way you have disease is by holding
yourself out of balance because of what
you believe about
yourself. When you allow yourself back
to your natural state, you are in
harmony. You are aligned. You are in
love with life, with creation, with
yourself. And no matter what anyone else
And no matter what anyone else
says, if it does not
fit within your prescription for
understanding who you are and what is
true for
you, do not swallow that
pill. For only when you swallow the
judgments of others do you then need an
antidote.
You follow me.
This night of your time rebalancing and
also for you in particular for you. The
exercise we will do this evening of your
time will have a profound impact for it
is designed
specifically generally for many
different ideas. It can be applied but
also specifically for what any of you
might believe to be physical
limitation. Finally, at this timing, you
may all enjoy a short break and then
when we resume, please all Thank you. be
seated.
Oh, now are you all having a good time?
Well, you're really going to have a good
time now. We are going to procreate something
now. We are going to procreate something
for you to sink your teeth
into. Literally.
Now before we begin this meditation,
allow us to preface the
idea with
it. What we are about to
describe that you will be
visualized or meditating
upon will
contain many of what you might
call graphic. And sometimes in your terms
graphic. And sometimes in your terms
violence
pets. This is not to shock you in the
negative sense. This is not to upset you
in that sense but a very distinct reason
for the particular imagery we will evoke
from you.
This will go towards the
understanding of taking this
imagery, letting this imagery represent
any negative imagery you may have and
learning how to turn it
around. Allow it to work for you in a
positive way. But first, we must begin with some
way. But first, we must begin with some
of that negative imagery.
But it will
be though
graphic quite primal and
imaginative so that you can allow
yourself without
fear to become as we say caught up in
the image. Allow it to be for a moment
more thrilling than truly fearful. It
will not be prolonged.
If you find any facet of it in your
terms repugment, recognize simply that it is
repugment, recognize simply that it is
for the purposes of allowing yourself to
know how to
transform this idea from negative energy
into positive energy, how to turn on the
light within you.
There are specific
reasons for the particular imagery.
Again, as we have
said, all of this will play a very
specific part in the portions of your
consciousness that this will key into
and
unlock. Let yourself flow with it at
whatever level and at whatever rate you
are most comfortable.
And if you find yourself at any given
moment having certain reactions or
thoughts regarding the imagery we will
describe and
define, at least allow yourself for the
time of the
meditation. Do not stop yourself from
proceeding. Do not analyze, do not blame
yourself for locking on to a certain
idea in a certain way, for having a
certain reaction. Do not spend the
energy in more negative
self-inccrimination. Simply go with the
flow and you will see how one will lead
to another.
It will be relatively
brief. And with this
technique, you will be able to
apply this
idea to any negative
scenario and any negative physical
manifestation of any source within
you. And you will feel a
difference. You will feel the likeness
of breath and the coolness of breath
that will allow you to know that there
were ideas that you had chosen to hold
on to and that you have now released and
transformed them. And
And
so let us
begin. Three deep breaths. Relax. Close
your
eyes. Allow your imagination for a
moment to
breathe. Simply float and enjoy. Become in
Simply float and enjoy. Become in
whatever way, shape or form you need to
comfortable in that
sense. Allow yourself to know that even
a modicum of comfort will
suffice. You do not have to be as
physiologically comfortable as you have
ever been in your
life. Just relax.
Now it can be a specific idea going on
in your life right now and for the
purpose of this exercise it can be just
a general
idea. Either will
work. Either will allow this to be
ingrained within you to the point where
you will be able to use it when and
where a specific circumstance may arise.
So do not think well I do not have a
specific circumstance therefore this may
not work for me. Go with the
flow. It will key into what it needs to
key into. Imagine therefore
into. Imagine therefore
now any particular specific or general
idea of
negativity that has occurred is
occurring or that you fear will occur or
focus on the idea of fear itself as the
negative circumstance if you have no
other specific idea in mind. This will
work very powerfully for the idea of
sphere itself transforming
it. Allow yourself now in your
imagination to embody that negative
idea in some animalistic
form. we would suggest. So this is up to
you. Any form that you feel exhibits a
natural aggression in your
terms. Any form that you typically
identify or can
identify with a negative expression if
you wish. We can supply some suggestion. It
wish. We can supply some suggestion. It
can be the idea you call of the darker
color. For now use the notion of black.
It will do as a
symbol. You can express it in terms of
what you might call a
panther. Something you feel in your
terms the power that can be used
dangerously. It can be a dragon. It can
be a dog. It can be a cat. It can be a
rat. It can be anything that you feel
has the sharp teeth necessary to
aggravate, disturb, and deceive you. to
gnaw, to nag, to obsess, and to pull the
life's blood from you, to drain you, to
inflict and
infect. Embody this idea into some
animal form. See it now. Just see it. It is not
form. See it now. Just see it. It is not
going anywhere, neither towards you nor
away. But just see it in as vicious and
negative a form as you can imagine. Just
observe it. Just
it. Just
observe and see in its actions all of
the things of the past that you have
felt were negative. All the ideas, all
the fears, all the beliefs, all the
circumstances that you may have bought
into as negative
ideas, anything that is physical, any
disease, any
imbalance, anything that may in your
life be going on now or have gone on in
the past, anything you fear may come up in
past, anything you fear may come up in
your future, embody that now into this
being, into this beast as you go. and
just observe.
observe.
Now, and this is most
important, we are going to
utilize the flash point alignment in
very brief mode that you call anger.
Now, as you observe this animal, as you
observe all that it has meant for
you, as you now become
tired of this expression, as you now
know beyond a shadow of a doubt that as
you see all of these aspects that you
know are the expression of the
negativities you have
created, Feel the natural anger. You are
enraged with this being
now. Feel yourself now to become your
version of this. Become a mirror image
of this and feel the intense anger
towards this energy in that way. Feel
the burning sensation. Feel the idea of
the energy emanating, radiating, pouring
from you in that way. Allow it to break
you into a sweat if it does. And at this
moment, use the anger. Become a version
of this animal. But three, 10, 100, a
thousand times larger, a thousand times
more keen, more precise, more vicious at
this moment. And you right now, the
teeth that are yours. and bake the head
of that animal
off. Spit it
out. Watch the blood, the red,
deep blood
pour from the
animal. See it pour and see it carry all
of the internal doubt and nagging fear
out. While remaining the same
While remaining the same
size, allow the image you are now, the
dark reflection, to shatter like a
shell, and drop away from you, revealing
the same animal, but in a golden
metallic configuration, burning with bright white
configuration, burning with bright white
light, blinding white light. And as you
now look down upon that dark
animal, as the blood drains from
it into the stones, the crevices and
cracks from your
mouth, allow
now as you transform into a golden
metallic dragon, a birth, a shack of winding
dragon, a birth, a shack of winding
white heat to emanate from your mouth,
utterly consuming the carcass of the
beast and the
blood. See it ignite with spontaneous
combustion. See all of the different ideas ignite.
See all of the different ideas ignite.
And at this moment, at this moment
now, see any dark shape that exists,
that may exist, that you fear may exist
within every single cell of your body.
See each and every one of those dark
forms that you cannot penetrate. See
them ignite on fire. See them rise in that
ignite on fire. See them rise in that
fire. See them catch with that blinding
white hot fire of dragon
flame. And see them
all burn to
ash. See it all
smiling as
ash. Hear the smoke of the
embers whisk away in the new fresh sea.
See the ash
crumble and see it dissolve into what
was once the blood now turning into
crystallin sparkling streams of water
flowing over stones allowing green
growth to arise from the stones creating
a green and verdant valley. Water
rushing down streams of mountain pure
clear cool
water. See the foliage. See the trees.
See the clouds on a bright sunlit day of
your world. Feel the breeze washing
through as the last particle of the ash
washes into the
stream down the mountain across the
valley floor far
below creating green in its wake and
flowing out to sea to sink to the bottom
of the ocean and lay there as sediment.
to serve as a foundation for what
was for all things
past. So that all things present may
grow from that fertile soil of the ashes
of the past negative
light. And as you now inhale as the
golden shining vag of light white
blinding, feel the coolness of breath
still. Three
time. Feel the
revitalization, the new
moonlight, the clarity. of
light. Spread your
wings and leap into the sunless
air and become
one with the
sun. the
golden white light of all
white light of all
creation. You have
released, you have ascended within the
new self that you
are above and
beyond any
shadow of the dark.
Three breaths and slowly allow yourself
to return. This particular
This particular
utilization, this particular uses of
your anger and of your negativity is
always available to you to allow it to
transform into complete and utter
positive manifestation. Anytime you feel yourself
manifestation. Anytime you feel yourself
at a balance point, at a nexus point, at
a fulcrum
point, allow yourself to take yourself
through this gate.
and transform your
reality
will. We thank you for your
participation and willingness in the
sharing of this
unlocking. We thank you for allowing us
to hold your hand while you turn the
key that releases you through.
We thank you. Our unconditional love for
you all. How are you all here? Thank you. Sh.
I love when you say that.
I don't say it. Oh, yeah. Hurry. Thank
you. Um, I have a question for a friend
also, a friend in family. It's a woman
that I live with, and uh, she's asked me
to ask a question to her before, and
tomorrow's her birthday, so I thought
this would be a good time. All right.
Happy birthday. Her name is Mary. Happy
birthday, Mary.
She uh has uh she had two daughters and she
uh has uh she had two daughters and she
lost one of them
uh last year in November. Her name was
Angel. She was 17. And the daughter that
she has still she has five altogether.
But um one just the smallest one lives with
um one just the smallest one lives with
me and her. The other this is a very
strongly Plleadian family.
um her family. Hey, okay. Uh the
daughter that uh is in question, her
name is Kathy and she's 16 and since she
was 14, she's on what uh a lot of
teenagers do when they get to 14, I
guess. uh she kind of just like dropped
out and uh she she really uh I've tried
to tell her that she's going to have to
take responsibility for her life and
start from right where she is and take
one step at a time. But have you told
her what responsibility means rather
than allowing her to continue to assume
that responsibility needs to be continue
to be defined in the way that her world
has always defined it as a burden as a
blame? Well, I just tell her that she
has to decide what she wants to do, what
she it will make her happy, and uh Yes.
But are you saying it in a way that
makes it sound like a burden? I don't
think so.
Are you allowing her to know that the
expression of her responsibility is what
will free her?
Um maybe you could share something uh
for Mary about angel and her passing
once she
did. Angel can be used by the other
children as a mirror as a reflection.
They can communicate with that being
very easily if they are willing to expand in
easily if they are willing to expand in
love towards that being. When they think
of that being, there will be
communication and love will be
returned. And they can know that that is
the love they can have for themselves.
And it is that love that will free them
in that way. And allow them to be
responsible for everything they create
in life. For they chose this life even
as angel chose the death to be of
service in this way to function as a
guide. You follow me? Yeah. her next her
sister Kathy that I'm talking about. It
seems like seems to me that it would
have been like a shock for her to you
know maybe put her life together, but it
seems like it's not going that way at
all. It may seem that way now, but that
is basically a reaction once again.
There's simply many belief systems that
have taught the individual how to react
to certain circumstances rather than
allowing the individual to react
naturally to certain
circumstances. Again, the idea all stems
from having been
taught certain methodologies of action
rather than allowing the individual the
sense of natural responsibility, which
means freedom, rather than getting them to
freedom, rather than getting them to
think that they have to struggle and
work through something in order to have
the freedom they desire. Well, she seems
like since she was 14 that she has
chosen to do what she's wanted and it's
only gotten her into trouble. She did
have all the freedom she wanted. She
chose and she got it all. And now she's
I don't think she's happy. I know she's
not. But it's just like she has been
free and she knows that she doesn't have
to do anything anybody wants her to do.
And that's I think part of the reason
why she is she willing to do the things
that she truly wants to do.
I don't know. unless that's just party
and it's like she's doing that
good. Allow us to form a
suggestion. This individual is in the
middle of a very highly sensitive
psychic development
point. This individual if she thinks of
angels can be in communication with
angels. This individual can carry on
This individual can carry on
dialogue. This individual may have
already carried on some and not been
willing to reveal
it or may not have been allowed to
recognize it for what it was. We will
We will
suggest that a suggestion can be made
delicately to this individual to this
cathic that she can sit
down, calm herself, use
integrity and speak in her mind, in her
heart, in her soul to angel.
and sit and
sit and
listen. Just listen for a while. And if
she is willing to
listen for a
while, she will begin to know that there
are still
agreements, still extensions of the
agreement that can be carried out by
Kathy for
angels. And that calf can take upon
herself the position of responsibility
that will allow her also to feel
fulfilled in many ways she does not sort
of feel fulfilled now. You follow me?
Yes.
We would suggest that as a starting
point. The degree of willingness this
individual has to involve herself in this
has to involve herself in this
particular type of interaction may
determine what she will or will not be
able to do from this point forward in
many different areas. I understand
also to do this in an area that is a
natural setting might be of assistance
particularly one that may be near or
above the ocean.
You follow me?
Yes. And also if need
be, she can sit and look in a mirror and
see in herself that portion of angel
that is within her and that portion of
herself that is within
angel. These are our suggestions at this
time. There are also
others who can be at this time of
greater assistance for it is more their
place to do so in this dimension or
others both. Okay,
for now that is the assistance we can be
in setting up the stage but it is for
others to come in and place some of the
props. Okay,
fine. I'd like to ask a question for
myself. Uh in uh the vein of a a word or
phrase from my guide
in the vein. Oh, well, I'm in that
direction. It seems like a new little an
idea to explore. Well, go right ahead
and explore it.
Did what I
suggested for Kathy appeal to you at
all? Uh, not particular in regards to
Angel. What about the mural? I see.
I see.
What happens when you sit and look in a
mirror? I wonder who that is. I wonder.
All right. Then our suggestion is for
you to sit look in that mirror and ask
and then listen. You will get an
answer and that will allow you to know
you are in touch with your God.
Just listen. After you ask, just
listen. All right. Thank you. Thank you.
Let us know if you will
what happened. Okay. Thank you.
Hello, Bashar. Hello. Um, I have about
three questions. Number one, yes, they
relate. Uh, the first one is about
personal relationships.
that I've just released with a uh young
man and I want to know if this
relationship um has an agreement to continue in any
um has an agreement to continue in any
way. All relationships continue even if
they do not continue physically. Mhm.
Now there may be many things that this
individual needs to learn about their
own independence in a way and also
perhaps you let us say to some degree
degree
some lessening of mothering may be in
order. You follow me?
Are you sure? Oh yeah. All right.
You have literally
been mother and child a few times.
You follow me? Yeah. All right.
You have opted for this particular inter
relationship now because it is time for
that individual to
learn that he has two feet but to stand
upon them and to learn that he does not
need the relationship in a mothering way
so much needs to learn more of the idea
and understanding of
equality between the male and the
female. You follow me?
Are you sure? Oh, yeah. All
right. Then allow yourself to know that
quote unquote backing off a little bit
is in many ways actually moving closer
together to enact the agreement you have
had. You follow me?
Are you sure? Oh, yes. All
right. Let it persist you for now.
You are in step with the agreement you
have made.
You see it going on. You see there in a
sense. Not that that does not mean it
cannot include other individuals. And
our perception is that it may very
swiftly attract another individual
because there may be some aspects about
the idea of an interaction between you
and another individual that that other
individual needs to see.
Is that other individual in my life now?
No comment.
Okay. Simply allow yourself to
recognize that this individual also
needs to
recognize is that other
relationships can enhance all
relationships and do not have to be an
interruption in a relationship. You
follow me? Yeah.
Now what we can say is
that to some degree the other individual
that at this point we perceive may come
into the picture as you
say has been involved
before and may to the original
individual represent someone who stood
between you
before in a very different way, in a
more familial way, in a more fatherly
way. And there may be
resentment, but that is what this
individual needs to work
through. You follow me? Yes. All right.
Then simply trust that if you are doing
what you know to be true for you and you
are functioning within love and your own
integrity, you are not responsible for
the reactions and feelings of others in
that extent. You follow me? Yes. Are you
extent. You follow me? Yes. Are you
sure? Yes. All right. Do you wish to
continue? Yes.
Yes.
uh the relationship with this person
that I spoke of who I released this
relationship with this younger
person. Uh
uh do you see a career connection with
him at this time? We cannot say. That is a
at this time? We cannot say. That is a
pivotal involvement that will touch on
many different
ideas but it is all in the process of
being decided right now and that one we
have already discussed that aspect of
the interaction we have already
discussed the emotional level of that
interaction is
primary to everything else at this time.
Okay. I'd like to know.
Um, I'm at a cross crossroads in my life
right now about my career. How exciting.
Yeah. Is there something that excites you
Is there something that excites you
above and beyond anything else that you
desire to do in life? Yes. Are you doing
it? I'm working through it. I'm working on
I'm working through it. I'm working on
it. In what way? Well, right now I'm
deciding uh about steps to take towards
it. Steps? Yeah. I see. How many do you
think you will need? Perhaps
no idea. No idea. Then why begin to
count them?
Act upon whatever you can act upon that
excites you the most. And it will lead
to anything else that excites you the
most that you may at this point not be
able to act upon as you would like to.
But if you do act upon whatever
opportunities present themselves that do
excite you more than anything else you
can act upon. Acting upon those
situations will attract you to any other
situations or circumstances you need to
be attracted to to give you the
capability of acting upon the things
that do excite you most in life.
So you're saying follow the excitement
always. always because excitement is
what lets you know this situation is the
most effortlessly accomplishable
situation you could possibly do. That's
what excitement is for. Excitement is
the sign you always ask
for. That's what excitement is. This is
the thing that is most synchronously
harmonious with the path you chose to be
in this life. And excitement is a thread
that leads to all other
excitement. Whether the surface scenario
the excitement comes with seems to be
connected to anything else or not is not
the point. Spontaneity on that level
will always be the rule. But the
excitement is always the clue that lets
you know here it is the thing that is
the stepping stone on the path you are.
You follow me? Mhm. So at any given
moment act upon whatever scenario or
situation presents itself to you
effortlessly automatically that excites you the most
automatically that excites you the most
that you are capable of acting
upon and that will always lead you into
whatever circumstances will give you the
capability of acting upon anything else
that excites you that you may at that
given moment not have the capability of
acting upon.
In other words, go with the flow. Right.
Right. Yeah. Do not fight your own
ecstasy. Trust, trust, trust 100% that what
Trust, trust, trust 100% that what
excites you in life is what will support
you in life. Right. Right. Thank you.
Thank you. I think that's completely We
thank you. Thank you. Sharing.
Hi Basher. Hi. I have two questions.
Number one.
Number one is that I want to know what's
going to happen to my country. Which is
it? It's Persia or Iran. I see. And uh
as the very we are at a very difficult
situation, right? And you are in a very
highly volatile transition point. Yes.
Yes. And I want my family. They are
leaving and they are going to come here.
They're leaving everything they have
back there.
And I want to know the move they're
making uh is the right move or is not. There is
uh is the right move or is not. There is
no right and wrong. If they so desire,
if they feel that is in their best
interests, then for them it is correct.
That's the way they feel right now. Then
it is correct. But what's going to
happen with this mad man who killed so
many of our people?
Understand that this individual is only
acting as a collective reflection for
the belief systems, the combined belief
systems of negativity in that particular
civilization and in your whole
civilization at this time as other
individuals will do. These individuals
simply do not know that they are strong
enough not to have to reflect that
degree of negativity.
They in a sense have never learned the
idea of unconditional love being the
ultimate power in creation and they seek
only to dominate and doineer as the only
way they can understand their
relationship to
creation. So at this time that whole
area the energy of that area through
many lifetimes has built up this
volatility. this understanding, this particular
this understanding, this particular
point of view and allows certain
individuals to embody all the fears, all
the negativity, all the
negativity, all the
disconnections from
creation that that culture has felt.
Every culture at this time upon your
planet is going through their own
transformation in their own way. And
there will be for now in each culture
those individuals who have been brought
up to believe they are
weak. And in that way those weak
individuals will take upon themselves
what they perceive to be the idea of
power and strength which is to dominate
and harm other individuals. But that is
a sign of powerlessness. These
individuals are only in a sense
thrashing in their own self-created
nightmare and they are taking as many
individuals with them as they can
because they feel themselves to be dying
inside. You follow me?
Yes. Now your
Now your
culture is going to go through many
rapid changes within the next decade.
You will find also that by what you call
your year
1,997, there will be an utter complete
transformation of that entire area upon
your planet.
There will be a
spark and the spark will be
ignited and that spark that is
ignited will touch off what you might
call a an emotional chain reaction in
the people in that area over a wide
expanse. And from what you call your
year
1,997 through what you call your year
2000 and with ramifications proceeding
to
2011, that entire area will
undergo a change as it has never known
in what you call your recent history.
And that spark will be the
recognition that the barriers and the
definitions and the creed that have kept
everyone separate that is what you are actually
separate that is what you are actually
fighting against. Not truly an
individual. That individual has only
taken upon themselves to represent all
of the symbols that keep your people
separate. All of the ideas, all of the
beliefs, all of the creeds, all of the
old ways, all of the habits, the
rituals, all of the old idea of the
inequality of the races, of the
cast, the
level
society. And that
spark will unite and bind that entire area
area
ahead. There may be still much
escalation of violence. Many ideas may
be torn down
physiologically. But yet out of that it
is still a way. Violence though it is
though it does not have to be. It is
still a way to make room for a new
understanding. One way or another, that
society must free itself of the shackles
it has wrapped around
itself. And even in a sense, if it must
break down its entire social structure
to do so, it
will. Again, not that it has
to. But out of that deep deep
suffering, out of that will come a
momentous transformation in that area,
in that land.
This transformation that you're talking
about, we are not talking about becoming
a communist country.
No, we are talking about your entire
planet beginning to
recognize that all borders are
confining, that all labels and all
ideologies are simply different points
of view and that there are many things
in every culture that each culture can
blend and assimilate and benefit
from. It will not be any label you now
possess upon your
planet. It will simply be the
unification of your planet as a planet.
You follow me? Yes, I
do. Now, my number two question.
I
u I have lost my father about a year and
a half ago and I was not able to say
goodbye to him. He was in Iran and I was
here. I wasn't allowed to go
back. So I miss him
tremendously and I uh Do you mean that
in your terms he has physically
died or do you mean you simply have in
your terms physically lost track of his
whereabouts? I I think I lost the track of where he
I I think I lost the track of where he
is about and I would like to
know how how is he
doing and I just uh name his name is excuse
is excuse
me he's all
right you are releasing at this time
will center you with his energy. Okay.
His name is Masoot.
Do you need his last name too? Whole
vibration. Okay.
Morati.
Age in your toes? 60.
Our perception at this time is that he
is drinking
tea. In a sense, he is well, though he
is in your terms plagued by
pressure, plagued by doubt, plagued by
worry. Why?
Mostly because of some of the things you
have talked about. Mostly because of the
idea that he is beginning to sense deep
within his
heart that there are connections between
you no matter how far apart you are
physically. And that in a sense what he
wishes most deeply is that anyone that
he loves understands that and gets that
message which has now just been done.
There will be for this person in his
dreams a visitation and an
assurance that all is
well. That there are no limits to space
and time where the heart is
concerned and that you are just as
together as you have ever been.
The tea will warm him perhaps
unknowingly on many more levels than
just his physical
body. For it will now be sweetened with
your love.
How can I get my mother to be convinced
of that? Because she cries every day.
All right. How can I get her to be
convinced of that? tell her to drink the
same tea. And in her meditations, in the
tea. And in her meditations, in the
drinking of that tea, she can learn that
she can begin to see
him where he is when he is there and
that together they are communicating in their
together they are communicating in their
dreams all the
time. Call to each other. Let them call to
Call to each other. Let them call to
each other not out of the sorrow which
separates you but out of the joy, the
knowingness and the love that they
share. The love will provide an open
channel of communication. They will
They will
know. They will
hear. And they can be
drawn in some ways
together. Not necessarily always, not
necessarily physically for
now, but in some ways they can
know. One moment.
A symbol that may work
well will be a
bright painted blue
violet character M.
Focus on that
energy. It represents an ancient
connection and it can act as a beacon
drawing all of the energy back
together. A blue violet
M. Pay attention to your dreams tonight. Tell your
Tell your
mother to learn to know when she is
dreaming so that in the dream she may
then go and
visit and learn what she needs to learn
of his
whereabouts. All right. Okay. In a
way, this may be in your terms crudely
phrased in your language as a
translator.
But what can provide some energy and
some light, whether you may or may not
light, whether you may or may not
understand it
colloquially, is to know the following
phrase. The blade of
Sargon. Now reflect the light.
We thank you. Thank you. Pleasant
dreams. Thank you. Powerful
dreams. ancient dreams.
Hello Bashar. Hello. This time I'd like
to ask a question. It's kind of twofold.
Like to know the origins of the hermetic
order of the Golden Dawn. And personally
for me, how the yeast and charging
talisman would work.
what you may call the Golden Dawn to
some
degree had some of its
origination in Atlantean
times. Though the energy
itself or the way it is expressed upon
your planet is representative of energy
that also comes from off of your world
in many ways.
But the origins upon your world in that
sense at least can be represented to
some degree in Atlantean times. There
have been different versions of it
represented down through the ages as
well. Bits and pieces and remnants
surviving to be rebuilt again and again
and again at various ages and epics in
your history. Any of which may seem to be the
history. Any of which may seem to be the
origin but which is not. Talismanic
Talismanic
vibration is simply an equation in a
sense. It is a signature vibration for a
certain idea, a certain perspective, a
certain thought.
You can invoke these vibrations in any
way, shape or form from you with colors,
with sound, with
light with what you call inscriptions
which are in a sense equal formulas.
They are, let us say, miniature energy
gates, miniature vortexes,
vortices, each of which can be tailor
made to a specific type of frequency or
energy, for a specific purpose, for a
specific focus. They can in a
focus. They can in a
sense to some degree be considered as
looking glasses into different realms,
into different worlds, a different level
of your world.
through which you can allow information
to flow by focusing upon that particular
vibratory awareness by creating them in
whatever fashion your imagination says
represents that vibratory
awareness all of them are magical
because you are magical in that
sense of it yes does that assist yes
very much thank you very much and thank
you very much for that meditation made
me feel really good thank Thank you for
creating that feeling within yourself.
All right. Thanks.
Sharing.
Hello, Bashar. Hello. Hi. I'm asking
about a health problem. Um,
one moment. Notice how lenient I am
being with all of you tonight. special occasion.
Letting you flip the switch this time
yourselves. Turning on the lights as it were. Please
Turning on the lights as it were. Please
proceed. Yes. A health problem. Um,
uh, it's I've had a long-standing
problem and it's turned into a pain
problem that's gone into my muscles and
I was wondering if you could see any
treatment, specific
treatment or how to break the cycle in
your terms. Yes. Along the lines of what
you call your typical approach, have you
already had diagnosis? It's very vague.
All right. There there's no real
concrete I think it was started from a virus
that seemed to go into the muscles. How
is your diet?
Lousy. You may You may
require
some amino and protein
complexes to sheave your nerves.
Some of them may in a sense be under
pressure and have been
stripped. Some of this can be alleviated
sometimes through balancing of certain
crystallin forms. Sometimes what you
call fluorite, sometimes quartz in that way.
fluorite, sometimes quartz in that way.
In the natural state, you understand it
as clear or the blue violet
fluoride. Also, what you may call some
deep tissue massage or pressure point
massage may balance some of this idea
out. Some healing energy from the hands
of a healer may be of assistance in
balancing out as well. That also may
make you very disoriented and dizzy
unless you allow yourself also to
balance the idea of your diet
first. Now, in what way in your turn
would you prefer to eat?
Um, I like sugar.
Why?
seems to taste good and it seems to the
foods that are attached to it are kind
of uh
pretty pretty. All
right. Recognize many individuals and
again we are not saying this right or
wrong but simply we are reflecting the
idea you are exhibiting in this way.
recognize many individuals will partake
of more increase in the idea of the
substance you call sugar because they do
feel themselves in many ways to be
accelerating and since they do not know
what to do with it or what it is many
times they will mimic that idea with
physiological acceleration as well. You
follow me? Yes.
Now, can you
imagine how you would prefer to feel
physically? Put it another way, can you
remember what it's like to feel healthy?
No, that's the problem. All right. I
can't. It's been a long time and I can't
get back into that. All right. If you
say so.
Do you want to get back into that
feeling? Yes.
Are you sure?
Yes. I just feel like I don't know how.
All right. But you say you cannot remember
right. But you say you cannot remember
what it felt like. Right. It's hard for
me to All right. Then how do you know
that you want to get back into that
feeling?
If you don't know what it's like, how do
you know that's the feeling you want?
I would just prefer to be out of this
feeling. I know that. And into what
other feeling?
You see, many times the idea in and of
itself is simply a lack of willingness
to
believe that you can create the scenario
you prefer in terms of a model for
yourself. Now let's work it another
way. You may be thinking you have to
create that model in a specific format
and you may be able to create it in
another format in a representative
format. Let's put it this way. If and I'll use
Let's put it this way. If and I'll use
your word if for
now. If you were, as you understand the
term healthy, what would you be able to do
healthy, what would you be able to do
physically that you cannot do now? Uh
back to my work and back to your work.
Yeah. What work? I've acted.
Acted. All right. Is that something that
you prefer to do? Yes. I I feel like I
was given an ability to do it. That's a
gift. All right. So, you enjoy it.
It feels right. All right. Very good.
Very good. Do you know how to act now?
Yes. Can you act healthy?
That's been the hardest challenge. Why?
It's uh believing in it.
And I don't know how to change the
belief. I see. What is the belief that
you have? That I'm not. All right. Or
that I can't. All
right. You know you have that belief
then. Yes.
Will you state the belief in a sentence?
That I won't be able to get well. All
right. Will you state it another way? I am
Will you state it another way? I am
sick. I am sick. Do you believe that?
I'm real confused about it. All right,
that is all right for now. Take it a
step at a time as you say. Keep it
simple. Do you believe right now that
you are ill? Yes. All right, then say I
believe I am ill. I believe that I am
ill. Thank you. That was easy.
Now the next line of dialogue you are
crying out for here auditioning
for. Now all right I have just read you the
Now all right I have just read you the
line in the
script. I believe I am ill now. Will you
do me a favor? You are auditioning for
this part. Now would you please read
that line again with feeling? I believe
that I am ill. I don't believe
you. Come. Come now. You said that you
believe you have natural ability for
acting. Now let me hear some conviction
in this line. I believe that I am ill.
Well, come on, put some feeling into it. If
come on, put some feeling into it. If
you're going to believe in something,
you better believe in something.
Otherwise, why have that belief if
you're not going to get behind it?
I've I feel like I've been behind it for
a really long time and I've been behind
the suffering of it. One moment. Let me
call in the writer. There needs to be a
dialogue chain. I see this is out of
character now. That is not the
definition of the belief that needs to
be in this script. One moment, please.
I believe I am
tired of being
ill. I believe I am tired of being ill.
Will you say that with some feelings?
I believe that I am tired of being ill.
All right. felt a little more life in there. Let's
there. Let's
just put a period here after the word
tired. I believe that I am tired. I
believe that I am tired. Oh, that
sounded pretty
natural. One more time.
I believe that I am tired. Oh, very
good. You get the part.
You get to play a person who believes
that he is
tired. Now this person, let's do a
little character building here. Is it
fair to say that this person is tired
because she has been ill or are there
some other reasons as well?
I came up recently with the idea I've
been working with the pain problem and
it's very hard for me not to believe
otherwise when I'm in actual physical
pain. Oh, so that's the problem. I feel
method acting.
I see some actors will go to any length
to ensure that they really know the
part. are really living it, really feeling it.
are really living it, really feeling it.
If I'm going to understand
anguish, well, I want some pain. But I
really know I really know what it's
about. Yeah, I'm really feeling the
pain. Oh, I'm all
right. Let's close the script for a
moment.
In a sense, what is going on on a
general underlying
level is that you have simply been
brought up to believe that you do need
to
suffer in order to have an ingrained
understanding of things. You have been
taught to believe you need to
understand. Yes. And I'd like I believe
that and I would like to release that
because it's not fun. All right. All
right. Do you understand that it is not
Do you understand that it is not
necessary? Yes, I do. All right.
And I don't and I I understand it on one
level and I don't know how to release
it. All right. What level do you
understand it on? I understand it
intellectually and I What does that
mean? My the concept of it I and I feel
like I understand it in my spirit, but
my body doesn't get it.
your body. Why is your body different than
body. Why is your body different than
your spirit?
Uh, it's kind of feeling like a dead
weight. The idea
The idea
may feel that way, but that is not the
way in which I actually ask the
question. Why do you equate the idea that a body
Why do you equate the idea that a body
is not a feeling?
It's because it's something that I can
see as being real and concrete and I
can't really
see my spirit. Oh, you can't? Yes, you
can. Anytime you look in a mirror, you
are seeing your spirit.
You have been taught to believe that
your body and your spirit are separate
entities. They are
not. From a particular point of
view, that is
all. Your body is made of energy, is it
not? Yes. Matter is energy, is it not?
Yes. Well, if you were to tell me, well,
I can see matter, but I can't see
energy. Would that not be contradictory?
Correct. So, to say you can see your
body, but you cannot see spirit is also
just as contradictory. Yes. Your spirit
is right here. And you have
absolute commandment of your
spirit. Before we proceed, one more
reminder. You have also been taught to
believe that your consciousness exists
within your body. That your spirit
exists within your
body. Your body exists within your
consciousness.
You follow me? Yes. And you see the
difference? Yes. All
right. So, look in a
mirror. And know beyond a shadow of a
doubt that you are seeing your
spirit. That is your
spirit. It is your
spirit. Literally is your spirit.
Then how do I release this?
Pay attention. If you start to
attention. If you start to
understand that your body and your
spirit are one thing, then you will
start to understand that asking how do I
release it is not truly believing that
your body and your spirit are one
thing. If you are a
spirit and you have created the idea of
yourself to be a spirit that experiences
pain, allow yourself to
know that as you look at your reflection
in a mirror, as you are seeing directly,
literally your
spirit, start to see it. the way you
want to see
it. You have said, "All right, well,
there's my difficulty. I can't imagine
that." But we're giving you a head start
for there you are right there. There's
your spirit. There's a form. There's
something you can look at in the mirror.
We are simply letting you know that that
image is your
spirit. You have thought it was just
your body. Now you know it is both. So
now that you have something to look at,
now that you have something to start
with, look at the way it is. If the eyes
look tired, then you have a reference
point. Start to see the eyes as being
refreshed. See your carriage change. See
the color of you flush. See the vitality
come back in. Imagine it by using the
image in the
mirror. Then you have a head start on
your visualization capability. We are
not asking you then to imagine as you
say from scratch out of the
blue. Your body is your
spirit. Look in the mirror.
Relax yourself as best as you
can and literally breathe new life into
that image. You are the
image. You are the
creator. Breathe life into your
selfimage. The image you
prefer. Treat it as a
pattern. Change the pattern. redraw the
line to represent lines of
strength. If you see lines and you
recognize the lines as lines of
tiredness, you know the difference
between a line of tiredness and a line
of
strength. You know the difference and
you know you know the
difference even intellectually that's
all you need because now you have a
model. So your intellectual capacity is
all you need because you know the
difference intellectually between when
someone looks tired and looks refreshed. So
refreshed. So
use your artistic ability and redraw the
image in the mirror mentally,
visually and start to breathe as that
image.
Do it until you feel that image breathe
back. Let it be just as real. Because
everything is a mirror. You are nowhere
and everywhere. There is no true space
that you
occupy. That image might as well be the
real you because it
is. So as you see it
change and you can even literally make a
drawing if you wish that image is also
you and is an accurate reflection and is
your spirit. All the physical reality around
spirit. All the physical reality around
you is your
spirit. It is all you. Find the things
in nature that represent health to you.
And remember that that's your spirit
too. And you will
discover as you choose to
discover more and more and more things
around you that are
healthy. For the only reason in a way
you are perpetuating what you are
perpetuating is because you will not
allow all the health around you to be
you. You are continuing to assume that
it is literally outside of you. You are
seeing it all around you but it isn't in
you. But the only things you can see
around you are the things that come from
you. So focus on the things in nature that
So focus on the things in nature that
are the healthy lines that are the
strong representative spirit and know
that that is your spirit
too. Acknowledge it, embrace it, accept
it back within you and your nature will
revitalize.
One suggestion that we have shared with
many individuals which may be of
assistance to you as
well to assist you in this exercise is
to allow yourself to lie down in what
you call a bath of almost body
temperature water. For in doing so, as
you float there and meditate, very soon
you begin to lose track of where your
body ends and where the water begins.
And so you do not carry such a definite
end to your form and a definite
beginning to everything else. You allow
more flow and blending and do not
isolate yourself from nature from the
rest of your spirit which is all around.
For all pain, mental pain, emotional
pain, spiritual pain, and physical pain,
is only the result of the isolating of a
portion of yourself from the rest of all
that you
are. Your spirit is all alive and you
are firmly floating within
firmly floating within
it and you are
it. You follow me? Yes. Enjoy.
Thank you very much.
Happy reflection.
At this
time, allow us to extend once again to
each and every one of you our
unconditional love and our joy at your willingness to
love and our joy at your willingness to
take your
hand to
reach out and to place your finger firmly
out and to place your finger firmly
with
commandment upon the light switch of
your life and turn it on.
on.
Repeat with your exciting and loving
dream lie once again with your mind.
Wake up and
live your
dream for physical reality is only what
you dream it to be
anyway. We thank
you. Good night.
Is there a day march into action in
dream reality
tonight for all individuals
participating in destruction? Nurturing
of dreams and life which are all the
same reflections of each
other. Reality is a mirror of the dream.
Dream reality is a mirror of the
physical blend and share for it is the
same light that reflects in both
mirrors. We share and swim in your dreams this
We share and swim in your dreams this
night of your
time. We bathe. Good night.
How it go? Great. Laugh.