[Music]
How are you all this evening of your
time as you create time to exist?
Allow us to begin this interaction this
evening of your time with a further idea
on the notion of
abundance. We will entitle this
particular tape all of it.
tape all of it.
Now recognize that we have discussed
many different ideas and aspects and
points of view and approaches to
realizing your own abundance in life
which is natural a natural state of
being. You are naturally abundant. And
if you can allow yourself to perceive
that natural abundance then you can open
all the doorways through which abundance
can come to you in any form any way that
it is able to come. Not placing upon it
as we have talked about before any
particular expectation of how you think
it should come because then that may
actually limit its ability to come to
you in the quickest possible way.
You have discussed many times the idea
of the ownership of materiality of
material things of what you call
possessions upon your planet. And there
have been different schools of thought
throughout the various ages on your
world regarding the idea of whether or
not you quote unquote own anything.
Generally, it is surmised by those that
think of themselves as approaching it
holistically, naturally, that you do not
really own anything. And in a sense,
this is
true. But the idea also can be said in
exactly its polar opposite way and still
mean the same thing. You own everything.
Everything. All of it.
Everything in a sense that you own
doesn't mean that you own it in the
sense of having to hoard it. Many
individuals who think about the idea of
abundance sometimes out of the habits
you have created in your society tend to
think of abundance as an actual holding
on to something, a having, a
maintaining, an isolating, a locking up,
a locking away of wealth of many
different types. But recognize as we
have discussed individuals who truly
function as rich individuals to use your
term you can very often observe is not
so much that they have things but that
they use them. They flow things through
the persona that they are through the
lifestyle that they are through the
situation that they are. Individuals who
express high degrees of abundance and
wealth are usually individuals who get
things to flow, who are facilitators,
exchangers of energy. Shifting this for
that, replacing this, trading off,
allowing individuals to receive certain
ideas that they need in return for other
things that someone else needs. The
whole idea of even your monetary form of
abundance is still the idea of exchange
fundamentally first of all, not so much
the idea of hoarding onto it. For after
all, if you actually hoard onto it, all
you're actually holding on to
physiologically is paper and metal. The
idea of what money is all about is what
abundance symbolizes, the exchange of
things. Now, many individuals, as we
recognize upon your planet at this time,
are dealing with different aspects of
their old ideas of abundance and what
they may believe prevents them from
having what they determine should be the
abundance they desire. But this is
simply because this prevention or
so-called prevention of abundance is
usually because of the attitude, the
outlooks, the way you look at abundance,
not because you are intrinsically
lacking in the ability to be abundant,
which everyone is in full natural steed.
Now the idea if you are willing to look
at it this way of recognizing your own
natural abundance is that all of it
everything belongs in a sense to all of
you. All of you.
You will use a certain form of abundance
one time and when you are through with
it, someone else will use it in much the
same way that when you are through with
one of your dollar bills and you in a
sense spend it, then someone else gets
to use it. The whole idea is to create a
flow in that sense. So recognize that
you already own everything and that each
and every one of you have a natural
access to every single form and
representative symbol of abundance that
exists in your society.
The whole
idea is to loosen up with regard to how
you see yourself as to whether you
deserve that or not and as to whether
you can handle the flow or not. For
these are the two main ideas that many
of you have created that seem to prevent
you from utilizing in a conscious way
the abundance that is naturally yours.
If you know you own it all already, then
realize there is absolutely no reason,
at least as far as the universe is
concerned, why you cannot flow whatever
level of abundance through your life
that you are willing to believe you are
the level of. And all you need to do to
really activate that flow of what you
already own is to trust that if what you want to
own is to trust that if what you want to
do with it
represents your intention within
integrity, you will be given the
opportunity. That's all you need to
assess within your conscious
commandment, within your conscious
decision-making capability that what you
want to do is within the flow of
integrity and represents the ideas that
excite you. those things. If you allow
yourself to fully believe and trust that
you will be able to handle whatever
opportunities are presented to you, once
you allow it to be all right to be who
you are, then nothing will stop the flow
of natural abundance in whatever way,
shape, or form it needs to come to
you. So simply remember, you already own
everything. Literally, you already own
everything. You can use
anything. And all you need to do to
attract to you the opportunity to use
it is to simply make the decision that
what you want to do is absolutely within
the intention of integrity. Because
integrity creates a positive flow. And
if you are doing the thing that excites
you the most, it will create the
activation emotional mechanism to
attract into your life the opportunities
so that you can act upon those
opportunities and accelerate and
stimulate that flow. That's all you
really need to do. We understand that in
your world now because of what you have
created yourself to be and the habits
you are in for thousands of years.
Sometimes it seems to take time to get
to the point where you will allow
yourself to be aware that you are a
being of integrity. Many of you don't
believe that you are a being of
integrity. You are taught from when you
are very young that integrity in that
sense is not something easy to do, easy
to maintain, that it requires stamina,
that it requires effort to maintain. The
idea of integrity, as we have already
also discussed, many of you are talked
out of following what excites you from a
very early age on not being willing to
trust that life can be that ecstatic and
that simple. Allowing yourself to
finally give yourself permission to know
you are a being of integrity for no more
complicated reason than because you say
so. That will be enough. You have that
degree of power. When you decide you are
a being of positive integrity, your life
will be reflective in a positive way.
And the only thing you need to do to
determine that you are in fact a being
of positive integrity is to decide that
you are and act like it. That's it.
That's all it takes. It is that simple.
We will remind you once again, it is
that simple.
at this timing. Allow us once again in
joy and ecstasy to extend to each and
every one of you our deepest
appreciation in functioning as
ambassadors of your society and allowing
me to function as an ambassador of mine
to bring us and our respective
civilizations closer and closer and
closer into the same dream, the same
sharing, the same ecstasy, the same
creative joy. We thank you for the gift
of your consciousness and your sharing.
And we ask you now, how may we serve
you? Hello, Bashar. Unto you. Uh, well,
I first want to thank you for your
suggestion to break the glass um that
you gave me last week. Oh, smashing.
Smashing. Yes.
Well, thank you. I cheated a little bit,
though. Oh, all right. Yes. How so?
Well, I I thought that I might have to
go through a few quite a few glasses.
And I had this um tape recorder, an
answering tape machine at home that was
that had a minor um it needed a minor
repair, but I didn't like the machine
anymore. And I was for the past several
months, I didn't want to throw it away,
but I didn't want to keep it. I didn't
want to repair it. I was sort of on the
fence with it. And I decided to use that
as my first thing to break. Oh, fine
goo. So, I I took your advice when you
suggested that I listen for the
particular tonal sound and I took the
tape uh the tape machine and I dropped
it in the living room and thumped and
then I dropped it into the kitchen and I
dropped it on different angles and I
different heights
and Mhm. I dropped it on cement. I
dropped it everywhere I could and it
didn't really break. So, I So, I took a
hammer and I smashed
it. I had Oh, I really did have a lot of
fun. Oh, thank you. Yes. And you
accomplished two levels of things as
well in choosing that instrument. I
know. For you have not only used it as a
symbol of your breakthrough and the
letting go of some of the old
ideas, but you have also symbolized a
thing we have discussed with many of you
many times. the idea that you are now
the recording device and that you do not
necessarily have to rely upon the
external symbols any longer to keep
track of what you think you need to
remember in order to simply know that
you will know what you need to know when
you need to know it. Yes, I thought of
that while I was smashing away. Nice.
Yes. Um when I was done with that
though, I did feel like I still needed
to break a glass. All right. So, I broke
the glass and initially it hit the
ground and didn't break. And I said, "Oh
my god, it won't shatter." You know, and
then it just fell over its side and it
cracked. Um, but in addition to what you
just said about the the tape machine
itself, I felt that there was another
reason that that there was more
symbolism behind the tape machine. In
addition to that, do Yes. I felt that
for me it symbolized the the smashing or
the or the release of regret in that in
that I got the machine partly because I
was afraid of missing calls and I was
afraid of missing
opportunities and um and then when the
machine broke which I didn't like to
begin with I didn't want to throw it
away because I felt that well that would
be wasteful. it still functions and I
would might need it again and I might
regret throwing it away and so then I
kept it and then I kept regretted
keeping it because it was just taking up
space like I mean this was non-ending
and I felt that no matter what I did
with this machine it would be regret I
would have regret associated with it and
well no I mean that's what it symbolized
and so I felt that that
was that was the thing that I released
was my worry about being regretful
So, no guilts. No guilts. No regrets.
Oh, I had a ball. Oh, thank you. Thank
you very much for throwing out the old
tapes. Oh, thank you very much. And for
remembering that you are the creator of
your so-called destiny, and you cannot
miss a date with Destiny. That's true.
Thank you. You will keep all the
appointments you agreed to keep and you
will not miss a one. Oh, thank you.
Well, thank you very much for having
such a joyful time in your
self-discovery. Oh, great. May I ask you
a question now? Um, I was wondering if
you could just give me some
um so your viewpoint on gluttony.
Gluttony. Mhm. Well, generally speaking,
it usually represents the fear that you
will never get enough. That there isn't
enough to go around. It is one of the
ideas we have already talked about
within the framework of abundance. Mhm.
The idea that you have to hoard in order
to assume that you are abundant when in
fact you already own everything. There
will always be enough forever and
therefore you can simply go on about
your business not worrying because you
will be where you need to be and be
provided as you need to be provided for
when you need it. Mhm. So it is a fear
of lacking basically. Okay. Great. Thank
you very much. Thank you very much.
Sorry. Hello, Bashar. On to you. Um, this last
Hello, Bashar. On to you. Um, this last
week I got a really much clearer
understanding of the fact that there's
that my oversoul has created a play and
this play uh everything in it is the the
creation of the oversoul. And I'm the
main actress in this play. And this
whole play is done so that I'm not
supposed to know that everything in it
is all me. But it really is. Is this
this is all true, right? Okay. This is
the old idea. Now you are in an age
where you are beginning to be allowed by
yourself to be aware that you are
everything in it. Okay. You are now
allowed to remember that because of what
your transformational age is all about.
Okay. So then my higher self has then
created a dream in which I start out in
third density and I awaken and this is
the dream of my higher self. Yes. Any
sense? Okay. Can you explain in what
sense? I want to but don't exclude the
self that you consider yourself to be in
this physical reality because you are a
part of the higher self. You are not
really separate from it. You are the
higher self in physical
terms. So this is your decision as well.
It is your dream as well. Do not simply
relegate it to the so-called higher self
as if the higher self in that sense is
truly so much above you and separate
from who you are and that you are just a
puppet. No, you are the higher self and
you have made the decision. It is your
dream too. You follow. Okay. And so what
we are doing here is to be able to get
more and more ability to unfold the
dream in the way you prefer to
consciously. Consciously. Yes. The idea
is to be awake while you're dreaming
instead of asleep. Okay. Then what I'd
like to know is about judgment is I want
I'm getting the feeling sense of
invalidation in a way. I'm getting the
feeling that all these things that I've
been studying and reading and uh
learning about I should do this, I
should not do this. One thing is good.
One thing I eat is good, one thing's
not. Uh crystals are good or this or
that. It's all judgment. Is that true?
And it can also be seen to be
preference. Some individuals may put
judgment upon it. But it is all simply
representative of preference and all
representative of the fact that no one
tool is the only tool. There is no one
way. As we have said, if there were only
one way, there would only be one person.
Okay. Judgment is simply the
invalidation that different tools work
best for different people. Okay. So that
therefore if I decide that for me it's
not good say to eat meat. Yes. Then
that's what's right for me. Yes. And it
and there's no absolute on any of those
things. Right. No. Now there may
sometimes be general patterns that you
all have agreed to generally. And so
someone may say, well that's the average
agreement and therefore in all
likelihood you will probably conform to
it to some degree and so it can be
rendered into a statement that says this
is generally beneficial for everyone or
not. However, still it always comes down
to the individual and you can unlock
yourself generally speaking from the
overall general agreement to a very
large degree and can simply determine
what is correct for you as a specific
individual. Yes. Okay. Could you give us
some u examples of what what is generally
u examples of what what is generally
beneficial to our society to not
necessarily assume right now that if you
walk at 60 m an hour into a wall that
you will go through it.
That kind of idea. In other words, to
simply trust the instincts of whatever
reality you know you believe in most
strongly would be our strongest
suggestion. Okay. Thank you very much.
Thank you sharing.
Hello Bashar. Hello.
Um I have a lot of energy. In fact yes
you always get I my body temperature
raises several degrees at night. This is
a typical symptom now of the
transformational age because you are
allowing more and more energy through
you and yet it is still passing through
a body that in your subconscious mind
you think not necessarily always capable
of handling the increase in energy. So
when you think that your body is
constrictive to that energy and the
energy is still flowing through it, it
will create the friction that you are
translating in your body as fever. This
is a typical symptom for many of you for
now until your body is accelerated and
acclimates and matches and harmonizes
with the higher energy you are now
creating. Then some friction and some
fever may remain, but as soon as it
acclimates, you will balance out. You
follow me? Mhm.
Um, in speaking to several different
psychics lately, they have noticed
um that I tend to scatter my energy. All
right. And I recognize that and I was
wondering if you had some suggestions.
Are you doing in your life the thing
that excites you the most? Yes. What is
it? Writing. Writing. All right. Does
anything else excite you equally?
Uh, communication with my friends. Is
that the same thing? Yeah. All
right. Anything else? Oh, lots of
things. Most everything equally equally
equally as exciting as writing as
communicating. Drawing or is that the most exciting
Drawing or is that the most exciting
thing? No, it's it's part of of an
overall drawing people and ideas
together. All right. So, that is the one
idea. Yes. Yes. Yes. And that is the
exciting idea. And you will use whatever
tools you are creatively capable of
using. Is that what you're saying? Mhm.
All right. You will not necessarily
continue to function as a scattered
energy if you start changing the
definitions of what you are as an energy
and recognize that the whole idea. All
the things you are doing can be looked
at as a whole idea of pulling together,
gathering, allowing communication to
happen between different individuals in
different ways through different
methodologies, perhaps talking, perhaps
writing and so on and so forth. Give
yourself an opportunity to define what
the whole idea is and that will assist
you first of all in realizing that you
do not have to think of yourself as a
scattered being. For it is only your
assumption from your society that you
cannot necessarily do all of these
things at once that have created within
you the idea that your energy is
scattered and therefore that is what is
going to be perceived by anyone
sensitive to your energy because you
believe you're scattered. You follow me?
Yes. So allow yourself first of all to
understand whatever the one definition
that can wrap up all of the different
methodologies you are creating within
your life. Uh-huh. So is it the idea
simply of communication and you are
exploring many different forms of
communication? Yes. Does that idea allow
you to feel less scattered? Yes. Why?
Because it's cohesive. Oh, thank you
very much. Thank you. Does that work for
you? It does. Thank you very much for
allowing us to reflect to you the one
unified whole idea that you are. Thank
you, Misha. Surely
greetings Bashar and to you. Thank you.
One moment. Remember remember that
another individual in a similar
circumstance might have needed a
different reflection. You can adapt what
you are hearing with any particular
individual in the way that works best
for you. It will not be identical for
all individuals by definition.
Otherwise, again, you would all be the
same person. Continue. Thank you. I
understand that on your planet, the
males, for the most part, have no hair.
Correct. Have you ever considered going
into the business of making toup pays?
No. Okay. Well, you haven't got any money on
Okay. Well, you haven't got any money on
your planet anyway, so you don't have
anything with which to pay for it. Toup
pay. Fine. Thank you.
Back to the camera,
Bashar. Yay.
One of the things that I do in a waking
state, physical waking state, is I will
imagine myself moving out of my body, sometimes
myself moving out of my body, sometimes
above it, above the rooftops. Yes. Uh I
can move around. When I re-engage with
my body, I get a rush like a rush of
energy is occurring. Yes. And um in this
state I don't have a visual perception.
It's more of a a knowingness perception
where it's it's as though it's um dark
out and I can't see anything but I just
know that I am above the tops of the
roof and sometimes because once again
simply of the habit of being in physical
reality. It may take a little while for
you to get used to the idea of how to
open. Now this is a metaphor. How to
open your astral eyes, okay? To really
know you are seeing because understand
you are not seeing in the same way at
all because you do not have eyes as you
understand them in the astral state.
Right? Well, that um bears on a related
area of this question and that is that
while I'm doing this, I also have full
perception of what my body is
experiencing. I can still feel my body
lying or sitting, touching, tasting,
whatever it might be. You can form
relative degrees of disassociation from
your physiological reality. Well, what
I'm saying is I'm doing both at the same
time. I'm aware of being out and also in
not really in but out, but feeling
still. Yes. Is this technically astral
projection? It can be because once again
technically your body is inside your
consciousness and therefore is always
contained in any expansion of
consciousness. Let's look at it this way
physiologically as a mechanism. Think of
your consciousness for now as a sphere.
All right. Yeah. Think now when you are
physically focused that the sphere let
us say is simply in the shape of your
body. All right. Okay. Then when you go out of
All right. Okay. Then when you go out of
body, it is not that you are actually
exiting the body. It is that you are
expanding the sphere so that your
consciousness is now out here further
and further and further. You follow me?
I do understand that concept.
Consciousness therefore is actually
always 360° around your body which is at the
360° around your body which is at the
center so to speak or physical reality
in a sense because it is so dense
represents quote unquote the center of
your consciousness. You collapse and
condense inward to form highly solid
reality. You expand and go outward like
a bubble to go into the more ethereal
realms. This is why when you expand the
bubble of your consciousness, you can
travel here and there and here and there
with absolutely no time involved between
absolutely no time involved between
traveling because your consciousness is
everywhere 360°. And all you're doing when you go
360°. And all you're doing when you go
from this point on the bubble to this
point on the bubble is in a sense
closing your eye here and opening it
over here to see a different point of
view. So if you perhaps use this
mechanism in your imagination and
continue to expand the bubble and assume
that you and the consciousness always
moves with the skin of the bubble and
yet at the same time can always be aware
of what is contained within the bubble
then you can jockey as you say back and
forth back and forth or remain in the
skin or go into the physical reality or
expand the bubble as large as you wish
or as tightly as you wish. This is a
direct mechanical analogy of astral
projection. It is not simply just the
idea of a spirit leaving the body is in
an expansion of your entire
consciousness. So that your focal point
is now on the skin of the bubble moving
outward. You follow me? Yes, I was aware
of this concept. Yes. And when I said I
was leaving my body, I didn't mean to
imply that I thought my consciousness
was exiting my body. Oh, we did not mean
to imply that you were implying that. We
are simply giving you perhaps the idea
of a mechanism to explain the effect you
are feeling. Okay. And um when I asked
is this technically astral projection?
You said it can be. And how would it not
be? We simply mean that it is one way to
We simply mean that it is one way to
describe it. Okay. So technically, yes.
Technically, I'm astro projecting. Yes.
Uh-huh. It just depends upon the idea of where
It just depends upon the idea of where
you choose to focus the main stay of
your consciousness. Many individuals in
other words would assume that it is not
completely astral projection unless you
lost the realization of the focus of
your physical form. Yeah, it is still
astral projection but it may simply be
that your consciousness is not focused
simply in the skin of the bubble but
throughout the entire thing. Multiply
focused certainly. Well, I understand
that the whole phenomenon of perception
anyway is the selection of a viewpoint.
Yes. In a created space. Yes. So, astral
projection is simply once again one of
those viewpoints in the sense of being
completely disconnected from the body.
That is simply another point of view.
Okay. Well, you're saying that astral
projection technically would require
this disconnection or apparent
disconnection from the sensations of the
body or does it doesn't have to. But
because of the habit your society is in,
and I'm not saying that this is the way
it has to be with you, many individuals
will not allow themselves to believe
that it has actually been done unless
they are capable of forming that
apparent disassociation to know beyond a
shadow of a doubt that they actually can
shuttle their focus of consciousness
back and forth between the physical and
the non-physical. Okay. When you are
quote unquote physically dead, that is
when the disconnection apparently
happens naturally. Although again, when
you elevate to higher and higher levels,
you will once again reform the
connection that you are feeling now.
Okay? So in a sense, what you are doing
in order to still feel the connection is
you are expanding astrally to a much
broader realm than the immediate sphere
just around your planet. You are
actually passing through that so that
you can maintain an awareness of the
connection all the way through the
different levels. Uh-huh. You follow me?
Yes. How would one go
about learning to open the astral eye as
you said? Again, there can be many ways.
You can use simply the analogy of your
own physical eyes and while you are
expanded simply begin bit by bit to
remove your focus from the physical. One
thing that can assist many of you is to
assume that you can also turn around on
the skin of the sphere and look outward.
Certainly see what that does.
see what that does.
Okay, that is one way. Use your
imagination as always. Okay. And also
there are many suggestions within some
of the literature on astral projection
that individuals in your society have
already written about. Okay. Thank you
very much. Thank you. Sharing.
Hi Bashar. Run to you. I've been reading
the u some of the Seth material. Seth
speaks and there's a concept in here
that I would like your help on. All
right. Can you all hear?
Okay. The soul can be described for that
matter as a multi-dimensional infinite
act. Each minute probability being
brought somewhere into actuality and
existence. Each mental act opens up a
new dimension of actuality. In a matter
of speaking, your slightest thought
gives birth to worlds. Yes. Okay. Now,
in words that are a little easier, I'd
like some examples.
In words that that
All right. You understand that
everything exists on different levels of
relativity. In other words, to use your
pragmatic example on your own planet,
the idea, let us say, of
the difference between something in your
terms, that is
human or let us say an insect is that
the relative degrees between what you
assume to be the perspective of the
insect is that they would look upon the
human as encompassing a large portion of
their reality. You follow me? Mhm. And
then relative to that you say, well, the
entire planet compared to me is a large
portion of my
reality. Well, simply stated, then you
can extrapolate further extensions of
your consciousness to assume that there
is a planetary consciousness that
considers itself to be a singular being.
And to that being there are then
galaxies, universes that are a large
part of its reality and on and on and
on. But everything is connected.
Everything is the same one thing
manifesting in all the ways it possibly
can. So whatever form it takes, the
insect, the human, the world, the
galaxy, the universe, it is the same
thing expressing itself in a different
modality. And so it is the same thing
having the same thoughts. So every
thought it has changes everything
everywhere. You create whole worlds
literally because all of physical
reality is a product of the imagination.
so to speak of infinite creation which
everything is made out
of and every single concept that you
define as a separate concept contains
the whole of all
creation. Is this making it any clearer
at all?
Yeah. much in a very pragmatic sense.
Also, different dimensions of experience
have the same degree of relativity to
other dimensions that your insect may
have to you. And we are not saying that
we are denigrating the idea of the
insect. But simply
put, your thoughts literally literally
can be the driving energy behind what
some other beings in another dimension
may see as a gigantic natural
phenomena. Just as what you call stars,
even though they are a part of your
physiological reality, are also aspects
of whole other levels of consciousness
activity. And you see them in your universe as
And you see them in your universe as
stars. That is how they interpret in
physical dimensionality. But they have
consciousness too. But not consciousness
as you understand it in terms of human
consciousness. And they are parts of a
greater consciousness still whose
thoughts create your worlds, your
universe. Everything supports everything
else. You follow me? Mhm. Is this making
it clearer? Yes.
Thank you very much. Okay, one other
question. Right after I started reading
this, I started getting um a stiff neck
that would go into a headache. Yes.
Could you help me on the symbology of
that? Generally speaking, anytime you
find yourself opening up to grander and
vaster levels of siphoning energy
through you, many of you will react in
the channeling chakra area at the base
of the neck between the shoulder blades
and up the bottom of the base of the
skull because that is where you usually
first receive that type of energy. It is
connected to the condundalini energy in
your spine and it indicates that you are
now flowing energy in an area you are
simply not used to flowing it and the
pain is the result of portions of you
that are now waking up. In the same way
that when you know you have cut off your
blood supply for a long time and the
blood flows back, you feel your arm or
your leg waking up with that prickling
painful sensation until it reaclimates.
So many portions of all of you have been
asleep for so long that when you allow
the energy to flow back in, sometimes
it's painful because that portion of you
is now waking up again. You follow me?
Yes. As soon as you let it flow
smoothly, you will acclimate. There will
be no more pain.
So use the energy, use it to do what
excites you and that will accelerate the
flow and alleviate all pain because all
pain is simply the product of resistance
to a portion of yourself that you are
now rediscovering.
Thank you very much. Thank you very
much Shann.
Hi Bashar. Hi.
Um let's see. Uh I have a question
that's sort of twofold involves two
things. They're both what is the first
fold? The first fold is um I about six
months ago was dealing with um having
periods every two uh or let's say twice
a month. And you told me that uh my body
was pretty much changing over to
glandular system and that I would it
would speed up and then it would spread
out to a point to where I wouldn't have
periods anymore. was a high degree of
probability, not an absolute. Okay.
Well, that started to happen. It started
to uh they started to come like every
month and a half and every two months.
Now, I'm experiencing a period which has
been going on. This is the third week
now. Nice. That I've been bleeding. Yes.
Okay. Um I went to a herbologist and she
uh told me that I was dealing with sort
of the last vestigages of detoxifying.
Yes. and uh that that was a a hormonal
imbalance and so on and so forth. What I
would like from you is some input as to
um what's going on in me or what this is
a symbol of what this is. I mean I'm you
mean aside from detoxification? Yes.
Why am I manifesting this? You are going
back to ground as you say in your
society. You are forming reconnections
with the fertility power of your planet
earth. You are now reconnecting in many
ways to some ancient symbolism in your
society. And you are reathering ideas
you have found useful in some American
Indian cultures that you have lived in
many times. God, I've been thinking
about that. American my American Indian
past lives. Yes. Well, you see, you are
sensitive to the track you are on. All
you need to do is trust it. Mhm. You are
simply reforming and giving back to the
earth in a ritual format. You are in a
sense allowing there to be a
reconnection between the nurturing
aspect, the birthing aspect of your
entire planet and yourself. As soon as
you balance and blend that connection,
it will stop and you will then sustain
yourself from a flow of energy from the
earth itself and you will become in a
sense highly magnetic and start to
attract many many many different kinds
of scenarios that will allow you then to
use what might be colloquially called
that old shamanistic power. Okay, great.
Because that that brings the next point
which is that I very much feel like I'm
going through a second coming in a
sense. Um well you know that is what the
second coming is all about. Yeah. It is
not the embodiment of the Christ
consciousness in a single individual. It
is the awakening of the Christ
consciousness in all of you. Right.
Right. Well okay
u the what that leads into is um has to
do with uh what excites me most. Yay.
Okay. What excites me most is is uh
working as an actress. All right.
Um, for the last seven years I've been
dealing with coming extremely close to
um, getting work as an actress. All
right. And then not getting May I
interrupt you? Yes. Will you answer a
question for me? Sure. Without thinking
about it. Okay. The first thing that
pops into your mind, yes or no? All
right. Are you ready? I'm ready. Are you
an actress? Yes. Thank you. Are you
acting like one? Aha.
Are you doing the things an actress does
or are you doing the things a person who
is not quite sure she's an actress does?
I'm doing more of the first lately. More
of it. Yes. All right. Yes. But if there
is still doubt, that's enough to hold it
all back. Yes. No, I understand that
that's there's a lot of self-worth uh
issues here. Um, what's interesting
though for me is that on on a very deep
level, I have a lot of confidence and
security about my abilities. Deep level.
All right. Um,
what about out here? Yeah. Well, yeah,
that's the whole point. Um, and and
what's funny is that I I will get I've
gotten I've done very well with interior
decorating, with designing jewelry, with
doing a lot of things that are very
creatively oriented, right? But they
don't excite me more. All right. Than
acting. All right. And I feel like I'm
on the verge of something very big
again. Well, you are. All you have to do
is take the step over the verge
and start acting like an actress
fully 100% remember all you are is a
100% idea. Right. Okay. I guess my
confusion with that acting like an
actress is that um I have had a lot of
judgments about the film industry um
having had success having been with sort
of the upper echelon you know successful
people in the business and seeing how um
some phony some some a lot of them can
be and how no I don't and you don't have
to be afraid that you will I've had a
big fear of that you hit it on the bud
because that's what holds many of you
back again. Yeah, I want to be
successful, but I believe that
successful people are not worth being.
Right. Right. Well, I know that's not
true, but I've definitely dealt with
those fears. You are redefining your old
beliefs and you are working them out. As
soon as you redefine them all to your
satisfaction and start acting like the
new definitions you have given yourself,
you will have the life that is
reflective of the new person you are
being. Uh-huh. Just be clear about what
your definitions are and you will know
why what is happening in your life is
happening. Okay? It is as plain and
simple as that. If you do not believe
that you want to be the type of person
that is typically successful, then you
will prevent your own success. If you
can understand that you can be
successful in whatever way you prefer to
be, you will not stop yourself and what
anyone else does with success will not
affect you. Mhm. Uh what what do you
have to say to uh attracting projects
into my life where I can uh make a lot
of money and I will say this but that I
there are things I just can't possibly
do. That is not true. Otherwise you
wouldn't attract them. Yeah. But then
why one more one more listen carefully.
When you act at any point all of you on
anything that excites you the most that
you are capable of acting on, you will
always attract yourself into the
circumstances and situations to give you
the capabilities to act on anything else
that excites you that you may not be
immediately capable of acting upon.
Because all excitement is a thread that
leads you into all greater excitement.
So act upon what you are capable of
acting on that excites you the most. And
you will grant yourself the capabilities
by experience to be able to act upon
anything else that does excite you that
you have attracted. And once again, if
you've attracted it, being able to
attract it is a sign that you are in
essence capable of acting upon it. All
you have to do is start believing that
you're that capable and you will see
that they will come to fruition. Only
your disbelief that you're that capable
keeps it at bay. Understand? So, so
you're saying that I therefore I can
attract the things that I do want to do.
Absolutely. Why not? Everything else is
pointless. I know that intellectually
it's like okay, I know this. Do not make
the separation. I know it's not separate
too, but somehow
I still feel like there's a knowingness.
Remember, remember, remember what you
choose to feel is based on what you
choose to believe. All feelings are
reactions to beliefs. You never just
have a feeling for no reason. If you
feel a certain way, if you feel hesitant
about something, if you feel there's a
separation between your so-called
intellectuality and your so-called
emotionality, you are choosing to
believe there is a separation. And
that's what creates the scenario you
get. Right? So use the feeling to
determine what you believe. If you don't
prefer that definition, change the
belief. The feelings will automatically
change and so will the reality. Keep it
simple. Why? Okay, great. I just want to
ask one other little Thank you. Okay.
You have what you need. Understand all
of these separate questions are not
separate questions. Okay. Start learning
how to integrate what has always
appeared to be fragments that you think
have nothing to do with one another.
They are all one idea. Great. All right.
Okay. Thank you. Do not fear. Do not
fear. All right. Just act. Be trust.
Step over the verge. You will be
supported. It can happen no other way.
And there are no exceptions. Not even
you. Thank you. Thank God.
And to you, one moment, please remember
also all of you, allow yourselves to
open up, and information that you need
to continue to do what you want to do
will always come to you in whatever way
represents the path of least resistance.
If that is your dream state, then trust.
When you wake up in the morning, you
will have what you need, whether you
intellectually know it or not. The more
you act and the more you trust your
actions, the more you will see coming
out through the actions that you already
knew what to do. But you have to act
before you will discover that. Continue.
Thank you. Um, last Thursday night after
leaving here, I uh spent about 5 hours
trying to get to sleep and every single
inch of my skin was itching like crazy.
All right. Finally about What were you
itching to do? I Well, that's good. Um,
obviously it wasn't sleep. That's true.
That's true. I was wide awake. Yes. I
heard a little scuttlings on the ceiling
and kept having imagining uh people
peeking in the window. All right. And so
I thought that was very Is that what
made your skin crawl? I hope it didn't
have that reaction. Hope, hope, hope,
hope, hope. Yeah. Why not? Well, because
I don't want to react like that to what
I think might be. What is like that?
What meaning are you giving to the
phenomena? I'd rather have it be itching
to do something. All right. You can also
allow yourself to recognize that if you
were being assisted in being accelerated
and that you were in a sense releasing
things, it may have also been that. I'm
sure that's what it was. Let me tell you
what happened after. Go right ahead. At
4:00 in the morning, I finally fell
asleep. At 6:00 approximately, I um came
awake from a dream. This is the third
lucid dream in a month and a half. I And
I thought I elected to fly. I knew I was
dreaming. So, I wanted to fly and I
wanted to fly and I kept flying and
flying. Finally,
um I uh thought to myself, I want to be
on Bashar spaceship. There you go. And
so, almost instantly, I was amazed. I
was sort of standing there on the deck
of a spaceship, but all the people, they
look more like Plleadenss. They were
humanoid and they had long robes with
all sorts of different colors of red and
geometric shapes. We are not the only
ones on our ships. And the welcoming
committees will always be those that
will allow you to adjust most easily.
That's kind of the feeling I had. Yeah.
So I I said, "Well, I want to talk to
Bashar." And so all these other people
were about 7 feet tall and looking at me
sort of smiling as if to say, "Don't get
in the way." And they were very
friendly. And so a very small person
came out and he didn't have what you've
described as your looks, but he was very
friendly. And he took me to a uh place
of governmental, some kind of an
institution where there was a long line
and he said he was going in to get
something for me. And so he just zapped
the line away, went in, came out
giggling and uh then I went flying again
and as I was thinking of home, my
consciousness from the time I thought of
home until I went into my body and woke
up never broke. Nice. Never broke. It
was always the same consciousness. I
woke up just laughing and screaming
because I knew that I had been
consciously out of my body. Very good.
So, um, one of the things that happened
while I was flying, and this is my
question, is that I asked to fly over
Hawaii. Yes. And a voice said to me,
"No, you're going to fly over Easter
Island." Yes. And I wondered what the
significance of the Easter Island would
be. For now, it is a very strong
magnetic key that is pulling into place
the pieces of a puzzle that have been
apart for a long time. So what you are
witnessing in the idea of Easter Island
is the actual driving motor that is
creating the triangulation between
Hawaii, Shasta and Fuji because it is
the ancient connection to Lamoria.
Okay, thank you very much for sharing.
By the way, yes, your
interpretation of our energy was simply
in a format that represented a more
childlike state of our existence.
It was very childlike and playful. I
love it. Thank you. Thank you, Bashar.
Shedding. Hello, Bashar. Strawberry. How
are you? Perfect. Thank you.
Want to ask me any questions?
What are you doing here? I'm enjoying
being in your presence as always. Are
you enjoying being in your own? Of
course. Are you enjoying being in the
presence of all these wonderful people?
Oh, that's one of the the reasons I come
here. It's only I only pretend to come
to see you. It's all of these people.
Enough. Right.
That's about it. Any other question?
Just came up to share with you and see
if you had anything you wanted to ask me
if you maybe there's some areas that
you're having difficulty. How's the
strawberry patch coming?
It's it's coming along and it's it's
timing in the real world is not quite
quite here yet as you can perceive but
it is moving along. The designs are
occurring some of the designs. Yeah,
I've been designing well I designed this
incredible crystal palace for the thing
in which uh this triangular held the
strawberries and always pointed to
Cissan and people came and got, you
know, wonderful. It's all right to allow
it to be a simple strawberry path. Yeah,
I' I've come back to that. It's gotten
back to rotated through all of this
phenomenal creation and back to a little
strawberry. You may get it grown in a
little pot with one. All right. Good
strawberry. As you say, upon your
planet, first there is a mountain, then
there is no mountain, then there is.
Right. Thank you for coming back to basics.
Thank you for coming back to basics.
Yeah. Oh, it's my my pleasure. Thank
you. My pleasure. Uh any any other
questions you needed to I think that
about wraps them all up.
Okay. Thank you. Thank
you, Sherry.
Hi, Bashar. And to you.
Um, I wanted to uh share with you that I
went uh to Atlanta, Georgia last week to
visit my family and my everybody in my
family that I've ever met was there. And
um it was the first time in about 15
years that we'd all gotten
together. And um what I wanted to ask
you about was that when I left here to
go back there, guys. In the four days
that I spent there, I felt like there
was a big energy shift, like I was a
very different person when I was there
than I when I was here before I left.
Um, you are always different. Yes, I
understand that. Now, since I have come
back to California again, um, I feel
like I'm yet a different person and I
haven't quite figured out what that
person is yet. In other words, what does
that person want to do? Well, that's
part of my problem because part of your
what? Well, part of your what? I don't
feel uh the level of excitement and the
uh one moment. One moment, please. Yes.
Will you do me a favor? Yes. Thank you.
You don't have to, but will you? Yes.
Thank you. Repeat after me. Okay. That
is a part That is a part of my joy to
discover of my joy to discover rather
than that is a part of my problem. That
feels better. Thank you. Continue.
Well, part of my joy to discover. Yes.
Um, for the last four days since Sunday
when I came back here, the level of
excitement that I have been used to
feeling in the last year or so hasn't
been there. Ah, very good. What you have
changed now is a typical transformation
for many of you. You will create in your
life at intervals the idea of feeling
the excitement in a certain way. But if
you stop to really think about it, even
though it seems as if you're feeling it
within yourself, you're actually
actually feeling it around you. And the
idea of when it no longer seems to be
around you is when you actually now have
the opportunity to know you have met the
level of that vibration. So it no longer
seems to be there. You have simply
acclimated to it so easily that it
doesn't appear to be any different than
you. And that's your cue to use it in
whatever way, shape, or form you desire.
And as soon as you use it, you will then
accelerate to the next level, feel the
excitement building again, acclimate to
that, use it, build to the next level,
feel the excitement again, acclimate to
that, use it on and on and on forever.
Mhm. So the idea is not to feel that you
have lost the feeling of excitement but
that you have simply matched it and now
you can use what previously to this
point seemed to be more energy than you
were used to using. Okay, that sounds I
follow you however I however
I I don't know what I desire to use the
energy to do. All right. Why are
you doing whatever you are doing in your
life at this time? Because that's what I
was doing before I left. All right. Does
that excite you? Yes or no? Do you know
what you don't want to do? If you don't
know what you do want to do? No. I'm I'm
feeling like I I don't know what's going
on. You do not know what you do not want
to do.
Well, I guess let me put it this way. Is
there something you are doing that you
no longer prefer to do?
Yes or no?
Yes. Are you sure? No.
Why do you think it is so difficult to
be sure?
I guess because I'm afraid of letting go
of those things. What would happen if
you did?
What do you fear would happen if you
did? I um I'd become destitute on the
street. Oh, destitute. How dramatic.
Isn't it? Now, may I ask you a question?
Yes. If you really stop and picture it,
do you honestly, now you can say yes. I
don't care. Do you really honestly
believe you will be absolutely destitute
to the full extent of the meaning of
that word? Of course not. All right,
then. Then you don't have to be so
melodramatic about it.
You asked me what I what could happen.
Uh yes, but I am asking you what you
really believe will happen. Not just
what is possible for someone. What is
possible for you? I'm talking to you.
Maybe what I'm what I fear would happen
is that I would let go of everything and
nothing would come in to replace it and
I would just How is that possible? I
don't know. Do you know as you have
heard many times that nature does not
allow a vacuum to exist? Yes. Do you
understand what that means? Yes.
Then understand you cannot create a hole
without something filling it. It's not
possible. There cannot be non-existence
in your existence. If you
change things have to flow in the
direction you change them into. They
have to has no choice. No choice. You
are at the controls. The way you steer
is the way your whole reality will
follow. Has to be that way. So is what
you're saying that I don't have to have
something to replace it with before I
let go of something else. You already do
have something to replace it with. And
when you let go, you'll find out what it
is. The reason you don't know what you
want to do is because you're not willing
to let go of what you don't want to do.
enough to allow yourself to realize what
it is you already do somewhere within
you know you really want to do. Did you
understand that? Some of it when you
hold on to something you don't want to
do strongly enough, you may not make
even enough room for even the awareness
of what you want to do to come in. You
have to let go a little bit, at least
enough, at least to make at least enough
room for the awareness of what you want
to do to come in. You're not letting go
at all. Mhm. Let at least something go.
You're going to be in control. You can
regulate it. You have that much control.
Let it go at least a little bit and make
at least enough room for this little
teeny tiny awareness to come in and say,
"Look over here. This Well, all right. I
won't scare you. This might be something
you would be interested
in. I'm not saying you have to be
excited about it right now, but this
might be something you're interested
in." Allow enough room to at least be aware
Allow enough room to at least be aware
of what it is that does excite you
because you do know but you're not
allowing yourself to know that you know
it. You follow me? I follow you allust.
Let me tell you I can do no better than
this when you do that and when you trust
it and act on it. The only thing I can
tell you is that I absolutely guarantee
it will
work. But I can do no better than
that. That's up to you to find out. I
and no one else can prove it to you. But
you will prove it to yourself. The
second you decide that's what you want
to believe will happen. Remember
believing is seeing not the other way
around. So if you are not willing to believe it,
So if you are not willing to believe it,
you will not see it. But I guarantee it.
The second you are willing to believe
it, you will see it. And nothing can
stop it. Nothing can stop it. Absolutely
nothing can stop it. Nothing. We once
talked to a member of your
society affectionately called the
wizard and we gave an analogy perhaps
now this may or may not work for you but
it might work for some of you. We are
not saying that you have to literally
believe this is true in a mechanical
sense, but it might shake up your
perspective. Turn it around a little
bit. Rather than assuming that you have
to in a sense pull something into
existence, why not assume that anything
that you do not specifically deny
reality will come into
existence? So that then all you have to
think about are the things you don't
want and then everything else will
happen. You can do it that way if that
works better for
you. But understand every single
circumstance has an equal opportunity
and an equal energy to manifest in your
reality. So simply take it for granted
that all of the wonderful positive
things that represent the person you say
you would like to be will occur and the
only things that won't are the things
you don't
prefer. You follow me? Mhm. See if that
works for you. But trust
it. Allow yourself to be relaxed. Allow
yourself to center. Allow yourself to
meditate in a relaxed and joyful way.
And remember, if you are actually
enjoying the process of discovering,
then you are not being impatient,
waiting for something better to come
along. The more you enjoy where you're
at, the quicker you realize any other
probable reality you may also desire to
be. Wait, can you figure out once more?
The sooner you enjoy where you are in
the now, the more likely you make it
that you will attract other
opportunities for you to act upon. The
longer it takes for you to enjoy where
you are, the more you keep other
opportunities at bay because you have
not yet finished learning what you need
to learn from where you are.
That's so relax into where you are and
that will create the space to let more
things come in. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Sh.
Hi Bashara. Hi. Um you said that um
we'll always you know the abundance will
come and all that good stuff. Yeah. All
that good stuff. Yeah. That um
opportunities will will present
themselves. Opportunities present
themselves. Yeah.
When an opportunity when an opportunity
presents itself, yes, you don't act on
it. Yes. Have you lost it forever or No,
it will come in another form. Okay.
Always remember if you don't act on it,
then that's a part of your lesson. You
can then define why you didn't act on it
then, you can always use every
circumstance to the positive.
Always. Always. Always. Always. Okay.
And um I just have one small question
about my daughter. Oh. All right. Um
she's been having these she's a
real happy child and and pretty well
adjusted. Well adjusted.
Yeah. For the crazy life that she leads.
You got
it. And she's been having these
really Okay. Bad terminology. Um She's
going to be these um these dreams, these
bad dreams that are disturbing to her.
All right. Is there anything that I can
do? What are they? Well, about people
taking her away. Taking her away? What
is the age? Five.
Five. What kind of people? She she can't
tell me. Um it'll be most of the time
it's a man and most of the time it's
while she's at school and she's playing
with her And all of a sudden, somebody
comes and tells her to go with them. And
she says, "I can't go. You know, my
mommy won't like it." And and the person
keeps proddding her to do this. And when
she wakes up, she's very agitated. She's
shaking all over. And she's just real
fearful. And I'm wondering what's going
on or is there anything I can do or what
is there? May I ask you a question?
Sure. Just to clear something up.
What kind of adjustments have you made
in terms of sharing the idea of what
type of society you live
in? What type of sharing have you given
this person? What have you told this person
person? What have you told this person
about the idea of self-p
protection? And how strongly have you
stressed it?
Um, well, there have been she's real
popular with all the all the of the
grown-ups at school. And a lot of the
times because I work at the school that
she goes to, they come and and she go
she has an art class that she goes to
and she there's a dance class that she
goes to and there's a lot of activities
that she does. Yes. And they take her on
days that she's not supposed to go. And
what I've talked to her teacher about is
that it's not okay for Katie to go
during those days. That she needs to
stay together. Well, because the other
kids are starting
to tease her and upset her because she's
getting all the special privileges and
they're not right that they go on their
days, but Katie gets to go on all these
other days. So now she is creating the
idea of a reluctance to learn new
things. Oh, she is in this sense therefore not
Oh, she is in this sense therefore not
going with those individuals. is afraid
to go because of the consequences.
Oh, because her inner trust knows that
those individuals will not do her harm,
right? But the fear of the reactions
around in that sense are what she is
incorporating into her own fear
structure. The idea that knowing she is
free, knowing she can learn in different
ways is at this time not acceptable to
the structure of your society. This is
what is represented by her nightmare.
Okay. So, I should just let it go or you
can talk with her about the idea that
first of all, anyone who says anything
that in your terms is a tease or
something negative
are simply reacting in and of
themselves. Perhaps you can explain the
idea of jealousies which those
individuals sometimes are exhibiting.
Yeah. Also, you can teach her that she
can teach them that they also can live
lives like that. If they really actually
like what they see happening to her, but
are simply jealous because it's not
happening to them. Doesn't mean they
have to tease her. Give her back her
power. Do not let her give her power
away by accepting the idea of the
invalidation against her. Okay? teach
her the idea that she can teach her
friends to attract individuals who will
take them places, show them new things.
You follow me? That is one idea. Okay?
Let her know, let her know that she is
learning as she needs to learn. That you
appreciate and enjoy that she is
learning in a unique and different way.
So, she will at least have your
approval. Yeah, you follow me because at
this stage you have taught a child in
your planet that they need the approval
of others. So at least give her yours
even though no one really needs anyone's
approval. And allow allow allow the child to know
And allow allow allow the child to know
it is all right to learn in new ways.
They will know the difference between
when an individual does not have
positive intentions toward them and they
will automatically know when to go and
when not
to. Tell her to trust the
idea of the feeling she has learned in
all of the positive experiences and she
will recognize a potentially negative
one if and when it might be attracted by
her fear. Right? Okay.
But most
importantly, teach her that she is
learning and that if she is enjoying
what she is doing, then no matter what
anyone else
says, that has absolutely nothing to do
with what she is getting out of it or
what she can get out of it and allow her
to tell the others that they do not have
to be jealous and that they can attract
into their lives the same degree of fun
that she has attracted into her.
Okay. All right. That's great. Thank
you. And remember, you are also able to
communicate in your dream reality. Tell
her this. She can change the dream. In her
this. She can change the dream. In her
dream, tell her when you dream, next
time you dream, if you dream that
again, stop everything in the dream.
Tell her to say, "Wait a minute. This is
my dream. You are all in my dream.
I've tried. I will go where I wish to go
and I will do what I wish to do because
I know how to have fun, right? I know
that I do not need to be afraid. Yes,
you may have tried in that sense, but
also remember to do it in your dream as
well and that'll help her. It can. Yes.
Okay. Thank you very much. Thank you.
There will also be some other
assistance. Simply open up and ask for
it and the guides will be there. Okay.
All right. Thank you. Thank you, Sharon.
And to you, I'd like to ask you about uh
the solar plexus. Lately, I've been
interesting. Yes. Uh it is one of the
connections to the future self. It is
the chakra of intention. Okay. Does it
have any relationship at the same time
with the like
um physical attraction of magnetism and
other things? It can related. It can
because a beam if you will speaking
colloquially can be projected that is
the beam that represents the connection
between you and what you are quote
unquote becoming. And if there is a high
degree of activity and energy in that
personalitywise, as you say, it can have
a very magnetic effect on other
individuals in terms of attracting those
individuals to reflect back to you
specifically the things you need to
learn to become that self you are
becoming. So yes, it can be a search
light. It can be a magnetic beam if you
call it a tractor beam if you will to
pull into you the idea of all the
circumstances and relationships and
situations that will allow you to
fulfill and express your intention in
life. Okay. Yeah. What about my case for
instance? I don't know if it's related
to some
negativity. That's Do you mean because
it is uncomfortable? Yes, sometimes. All
right. In a sense, negativity. Yes. But again,
In a sense, negativity. Yes. But again,
mostly habitual rituals, things you are
clearing out. That is all. Okay. As you
open it up, then there will be more than
enough room for the energy to flow. It
is still a little bit constricted. That
is all. Yes.
Allow yourself to be the future self now
that you are becoming and then there
will not be as much constriction. Okay.
You follow? Yes. Is there any like real
or something I could do mainly like uh
emotions or whatever I feel it right
there you know I have a lot of attention
there very good it brings you into the
moment emotion energy motion yes you are
dealing with many old beliefs okay
it is your process you can accelerate it
if you wish to how the way to accelerate
it as we have already said most easily
is to not necessarily think you need a
long process but start acting like the
you you imagine you're becoming now.
Okay. Imagine how you would like to be
and start being that person. Yeah. But
still feel like a lot of emotion even
thinking about that and I feel a little
bit of well I've been feeling something
in there that you know. Well, that's all
right. Let it come. I haven't been so
hungry or something which is all right.
But it's something uncomfortable in
there anyway. It does not have to be.
Okay. And the more you dive into it and
go through it, the shorter amount of
time it will last. Okay. Only assuming
that you don't want to deal with it
makes it stick around and last longer. I
see. Dive into it and you'll be through
it. Okay.
Dive into will be Yes. Like meditating
to something or act through or explore.
Yes. Meditate. Why am I feeling the way
I am feeling? What am I believing? Am I
fearing something? What am I fearing? If
I'm fearing it, what am I fearing? Oh,
that's what I'm fearing. All right. Why
am I fearing it? Well, first of all, I
choose to acknowledge that I have chosen
to fear it. Once I acknowledge that I
have chosen to fear it, it's back in my
control. Do I still wish to fear it? No,
I don't. Thank you very much. On your
way. Okay.
It is that easy. You can process it that
quickly. Yes. If you are simply honest
and clear with yourself. Okay. And
acknowledge what you have created as
your creation because you cannot
transform what you do not own. Yes.
Okay. Thank you very much. Thank you.
Pleasant dream shedding.
dream shedding.
Hi, I'd like to share one little thing.
Sedona before and I had a real
strong interest in going a couple weeks
ago. Yes. Highly magnetic. Yes. But then
I said, "Oh, now I got this business
cycles I got to do this go this week."
All right. So, it's really interesting
that all the business cycles didn't need
to be done that week after all. So, it
turned out that would have been the best
week to go. Trust your instincts.
So that was a small sharing. Thank you
for that discovery. You are now a
completely different person. Good. Now I
have a one question. I'm a
procrastinator and there's Wait a
minute.
Just want you to feel at home. Oh, good.
Very good.
All right. Now, you may continue if you
feel like it.
Would you like to come back tomorrow?
No, I'm here. I'm all right once I get
started here. It's getting started
that's the hard part. Especially one
more time. One more time. It's what?
Getting started that's the hard part.
It's getting started that's the hard
part. Is this another phrase that you
have chiseled into steel? When in fact
it's only written on
paper when in fact it's only a belief
when in fact it's only a habitual way of
looking at things. When in fact it's
only an
assumption. It's getting started. That's
the hard part. All right. Maybe that has
been in the past your experience. But
that doesn't mean that right now it's
still not at this very moment an
assumption all over again from scratch
from the beginning.
It is just an assumption. Why is getting
started any harder than doing
it? Your society has taught you that it
is, but it doesn't have to be. Not
really. It seems like when something is
important, uh, fear comes in. Doesn't
have to, but we recognize what you are
saying. Yes. It goes handinhand with
many of the insecurities, the lack of
deservability that many of you have been
taught to believe in about yourselves. I
can't do that. But again, remember that
if you can imagine it, that's your
signal that you can or you would have
imagined something else.
This seems to be a a pattern like you
say. All right. But again, once you
recognize it's a pattern, it's no longer
a pattern. And that's only an excuse.
But if you recognize the pattern, the
pattern continues. It's still a pattern.
No, apparently. No. Oh, it's not a
pattern. No. Once you recognize it as a
pattern, then if it continues, it's
because you choose to continue it
consciously. Now, if you no longer
choose it, then don't continue it. But
once you have recognized it was a
pattern, it's no longer a pattern.
A conscious a conscious choice. The only
thing that makes it seem as if it has to
continue as a pattern is your assumption
that it must.
That's it. It doesn't have to.
Thank you very much. Does that assist
you? Yes. Thank you for waking up a
little bit more. Good. And besides, you
started this long ago. You're already
well on your way.
Remember also that Starting and doing is
the same thing. It's all one event. If
you cease to think of it as a beginning
and a middle and an ending and in
between here and how long is it going to
take to get from there to there and so
on and so forth. If you stop parceling
it out, it will be more of a single
spontaneous event with the beginning,
the middle, the end, so to speak, all
being very close and sometimes even
overlapping and sometimes even the
ending coming first.
Allow yourself more spontaneity and more
trust and there will not have to appear
to be so many beginnings to things.
Remember remember
remember the end and the means are not
separate. The end is the means. The
means is the end. One and the same
thing. Cause and effect are the same
event. one and the same act right
now. Thank
you. Sing. Good evening, Michelle. And
to you. Hi. Um, I'd like to ask a
question about a relationship I'm in
now. All right. Um, but I'm not sure how
to formulate it. So, I think I'd like to
start with the dream and see if that
kind of opens itself up to You go right
ahead. Okay. Um, this morning I had a
dream of I appeared suddenly in a bar of
a restaurant and it was a very expensive
highass restaurant and um I wasn't I
wasn't sure I was going to be able to
get seating and there was a woman at the
bar that just took to me and came to me
right away and somehow she had some
influence over this fancy restaurant and
she got me a seat. Yes. and she sat with
me and talked with me and she had some
little like a crony or some somebody
with her and um she asked me if I wanted
to go on this little adventure and I
said okay. So we walked outside and and
the the woman was French and there was
something French about the whole field.
And then we walked outside into the snow
and we walked onto a peninsula that
broke off and became a glacier and we
were on the water on the glacier and
when it first broke off I was afraid and
I started to scurry and then her little
crony um turned into a mermaid and said,
"Don't worry, you won't drown. You can
hold on to me here." So that was all
fine. And so it was really great on the
on
the on the um iceberg. And I looked to
the right, I saw on the some land a few
hundred feet away, but it was like a
tropical island, real lush and fertile
and naked people walking around with
kids. And and I remember feeling, "Oh, I
want to go there." And I remember asking
this woman and she said, "Not yet." And
we stayed on the glacier and we went
back and it kind of broke and I to the w
the mermaid and we got back and we got
off and then I went back into this fancy
restaurant. So how exciting.
So how exciting.
Yeah. First of all, the fancy restaurant
symbol of your abundance in a sense of
being supplied. Symbol also that you
belong there and that you have the
connections it takes. French because
that's very classy to you and has been
in many lives and represents the level
of elegance you actually desire in your
life, right? But you have what it takes
or you wouldn't have been in that
restaurant knowing who you know. The
crony was your interpretation of a dolphin
was your interpretation of a dolphin
sharing the dream with you. Yeah, that's
and your friend was simply showing you
that you are on route to create your own
abundant paradise. You are almost there
and you are doing it side by side with
the dolphin consciousness to become the
one society that will be the society of
freedom on that tropical
island. You are almost there.
Okay. In a dream that I had the night
before or a few nights before I had like
my first major out of body experience.
Oh major. Yeah. When I was younger, I
always like would hang about six feet
above my body and and still feel kind
kind of in, kind of out. Yes. Um and
this was the first time I really like,
you know, had the classical out of body
was seeing the threat. Where did you go?
I went out of the planet. Yeah. And and
it felt really great. You sound like it.
Sounds like you believe it. Yeah. And
you know once I got into the stars I had
to try what you suggested about turning
and looking upward because I couldn't I
didn't look to see what was out there. I
my focus was looking at the earth. Well
that's all right. So anyway
but I think it was like after a dream.
So I was wondering well when you're
dreaming aren't you out of your body
anyway? Why would I sometimes yes your
focus can vary. You can be in a sense
hovering within or around the confines
of your oric field or you can be far
more expanded in that sense. Now
remember many times that the dream what
you remember as a dream when you wake up
is your
physiological interpretation of an outof
body experience and not necessarily the
literal experience in the terms of the
dream. You follow me? Sort of. So many
times yes you are out of body but the
way you remember it as a dream is not
necessarily a literal interpretation of
the actual outof body experience but
your conscious mind's
symbology to represent the experience
that you had. Yes many times you are out
of body but what you remember as a dream
is not necessarily literally
representative of the trip you took but
yes many times dream represent out of
body phenomena. So the out of body thing
that I had it felt different from a
dream because I had had a dream just
prior to that which I like in my dreams
I'm reallyware. All you did as we say is
wake up in the dream and realize that
you are always dreaming and that even
this reality your physical reality is a
dream. All right. You have now created less
All right. You have now created less
distinction, less separation between
what you have for thousands of years
called physical reality and dream
reality. Or of course many of you do not
even think the dream reality is real.
But it is. But now you are knowing a it
is real and b physical reality is simply
one form of the same
reality. No other difference.
No other difference. Well, you know, it
seems like I'm more excited in my my
dream state these days. My dream life is
just fantastic and your physical reality
can follow suit. Okay? As long as you
understand there is no separation. And
do not think that the dream reality is
so much better than the physical
reality. Allow them to remain as the
same reality. And your physical reality
will become just as malleable as the
dream reality. You follow me? Yeah. Okay. Wake
reality. You follow me? Yeah. Okay. Wake
up in this dream as
well and see it for what it is. What you
imagine it to be physical reality.
Literally. I am not speaking
philosophically. I am speaking
literally. Physical reality is only what
you imagine it to be. It has no solid
basis without you.
You follow me? Yeah.
It is you. You are it. Physical reality
is the dream you are being right now.
So that's why I went back to the to the
to the French restaurant because I got
it. Okay. Thanks. Thank you very much. At
Okay. Thanks. Thank you very much. At
this timing, you may all enjoy a short
break and we will resume contact
momentarily.
How's it going?
Please have a I feel a short break,
Darl. Is that fair to say? Yes. Short
break. And when I
call I'll say
continue. I'm to you.
Better. I have this interesting
phenomena that's going on in my life
right now. I sort of emptied my vacuum a
few months ago and it's been filling up
at a pretty fast clip. But I find myself
if I'm not mentally activated or
physically activated wanting to be
asleep. And sometimes again this will be a
And sometimes again this will be a
typical symptom for now for many of the
connections you allow yourself to make
with different aspects of your
consciousness. For some of you still are
more easily made while you are
unconscious while you are asleep. So you
will sleep very often to make all those
connections and as soon as the
connections are made you will then have
more energy more awareness of those
connections when you are awake and you
will find yourself sleeping less. I see.
Thank you. Thank you. One other quick
question. In this lifetime or in my
lifetime, will we be sitting down to
dinner with aliens such as yourself in
your natural form? Yes. Although we may
not eat what you eat,
but it is a high probability, as we have
said, within what you call the next
decade of your time, two decades of your
time, there will be far more opportunity
for blatant interaction, as you call it.
And within the format of three decades
maximum, there will be a whole series of
interactions going on in your society
between our respective society. That's
wonderful. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you for creating a
conducive atmosphere to allow us to
share with you the ideas that you are
sharing. Hello Bashar. And who to uh at
one point you mentioned that this is the
only planet that has religion as you
understand it. Yes. That does not mean
that there are not different societies
that have various forms of symbolic
relationship representation between
themselves and infinite creation. But
the idea you call religion in the sense
that you somehow do not think that the
capacity for the relationship exists
directly within you and place that
capacity within someone that you follow.
That we have rarely discovered anywhere
else and never in the form that your
society exhibits
it. You follow me?
More or less?
Uh it'll come. All right. The notion
that we find most different is the
apparent belief in a
disconnection between yourselves and the
infinite creator. In other words, that
God is outside of you instead of the
fact that you are God, that you are made
of God, that everything is God, that
there is no separation, that you do not
need to follow someone to do such and
such a thing and that that such and such
a thing is the only way to be God. That
is what we find different about your
planet. That individuals because there
is such a high degree of limitation and
separation in your history have simply
created ideas and patterns that there is
only one way to relate to the idea of a
God that is separate from you to begin
with instead of the idea that everything
is God and therefore every way is
another way that God has to be
itself. You follow me? Yes. Does that
define the difference? Yes. Does that
serve you? It certainly does. Um just
the final part of that question is are
you familiar with the uh sitta or sitta
yoga? Not by the definition you have given it.
Not by the definition you have given it.
Well, it's a form of yoga and they
basically teach you to meditate and
meditate on the god that dwells within.
Yes. Or the god part of you that's
there. There may be many things we do in our
There may be many things we do in our
society that are similar to many things
you do. We simply do not necessarily
need the awareness of all the specific
rituals that you have created around
certain ideas that may be common to both
of our society.
I see.
Uh
so I'm wondering if there may be a
faster way to
uh to reach spiritual ascendance. The
fastest way is always to do the thing
that excites you the most because when
you do the thing that excites you the
most, you are matching the highest
possible vibration in your reality. And
it is the excitement that always lets
you know what is in that sense the most
spiritual thing you can do if you're
doing it with integrity. That's it.
Anything and everything that falls into
that category is the way to accelerate
most rapidly because remember physical
reality is not
non-spiritual. Your physical body is
your spirit in physical terms. So
anything you do in an integrated manner
using that high accelerated energy you
call excitement will be an act of
spirituality. Follow me. Great. I've got it. Thank
Follow me. Great. I've got it. Thank
you. Thank you. Enjoy. We'll do
chatting. Hello, Bashar. And to you. Um,
let's see
here. Let me just relax a
second because I I'm real excited. First
of all, one thing I want to share is I
think it's really interesting the way
Well, gosh, there's so many things, so
many ideas I've got going on in my head
right now. Let me just start with one.
Right. Oh, please. Thank you.
Um well one is you know you have
reflected this full possibility of I
mean you know I trust my intuition on
things so completely now. Thank you that
uh you know my perspective can change at
any moment which is very nice and it's
also assisting me in the belief that I
truly am living a dream. I mean there's
no doubt in my mind about that because
of this you know ability to switch from
one you know concept and idea to
something completely different you know
and uh you of course have assisted in
this greatly so have you and thank you
and the another interesting phenomenon I
think is that for some reason you know I
I might have some uh questions in my
mind on my way over here and as soon as
I walk into this room and I'm sure it's
because there is just this this is like
the halo of truth or some embodiment. I
mean it's a symbol obviously to me
because the reason you find all the
answers so quickly is because you are
allowing us to simply represent that
vibration within yourself that once you
recognize it and then create for
yourself allows you to center in that
place where all the answers are. Yes.
Yes, thank you. And so I want to thank
you for that. But you know this happens
as well out there in my car, you know,
there. Well, here within me, right?
Within me. All of the out there is in
him. That's right. I guess when I what
I'm talking about is when I'm
recognizing this physical plane, which
that's another new thing that's
happening. And I saw myself getting into
these conversations with people that um
you know I'm really going through this
transition of not looking at the
material anymore. I mean I believe in
the unseen. That's where I'm living now.
And I guess that's what I'm saying.
So I am I am kind of flipping back and
forth now from this what's out there and
what's in here and um ideas
You know, it's like this thing I've been
working on. I I've got two careers that
are happening. Uh, one that I can say,
you know, I co-created as as a total for
a total, you know, a vehicle for my full
expression. The thing I'm doing right
now was something I, you know, believed
would be a good thing. But now I know
where I'm going and what I want to do.
Yes. Now remember, at the time it was
the perfect thing. Absolutely.
Absolutely. No invalidation of anything
you have ever done because it has
brought you to where you are. Thank you.
Yes. All right. Um the the the point the
thing that's happening. Why are you What
are you doing? I'm not looking at you.
Um okay, Bashar, keep it simple. Keep it
simple. Just state it.
I I want to just be doing one thing.
That's how simple I want to make it. And
what is it? This I want to be the king
of my surfware company. Yet I'm still in
this other thing and I've got the whole
deal is sitting there and it's like it's
it's been exhausting me now because I
have to it always is exhausting when you
keep your ecstasy at
bay. When you do not trust yourself
enough to act upon the full 100% idea
you want to be, that's tiring.
Okay, I'm acting as if
uh as if I am the surf king. But do you
believe it? Yes, I do. All right, then.
Um, so why am I still having to check
into this other job?
Why you answer that? Why? Why? Why are
you still creating it?
Why are you still attached to it if it's
not what you want to do? Well, it's you
know something I love what I love doing
this and and the thing not make an
excuse. I know you're going to get me right on
I know you're going to get me right on
the center of this thing and that's why
I'm here. You have already stated the
center very clearly. You have an idea of
what it is that would excite you the
most. And I want it popped into
manifest. I mean it's all there.
Everything is there except No, no, no,
no, no, no. Not there. Here. Here within
me. Yes, it's all in here. Yes.
Remember, if you are willing to act upon
anything that excites you, that you are
capable of acting on, it's connected to
the other thing you may think you can't
act upon right now. So, you may not be
willing to do something that is not the
thing you have described, but still is
more exciting than the other thing
you're still doing. thinking that that
more exciting thing just because it's
not the thing you want to do and because
it's not the thing you're still doing
has no connection to anything, you may
not then act upon it. But anything that
comes to you that is the most exciting
thing at any given moment that you could
be doing that you can act upon is the
thing to do because it is connected to
the other thing that excites you that
you may not be able to do yet. And that
means you need to do this interim thing
and it is not really an interim thing
that it actually is a part of what you
want to do even though it doesn't look
like it. Okay. You want to hear the
thing now? Go ahead. That's the
exhausting thing for me is that I am I
see these things coming at me. I mean,
I'm attracting it and as they come to
me, I with full excitement go into it
and I'm attracting more and more and the
momentum is building and I'm going, come
on, just pop the full picture. But I
know that this is part of the
unfoldment. Well, you know what? Because
I have this belief that once the picture
is there, then I can relax. Oh, pretty
good. Why can't you relax now? Well, I
am. I do. Do you know that if you relax
now, you will let it come?
Okay, thank you. Relax now and let it
come again.
Remember, you are only impatient when
you think you need patience. You don't
need patience if you are doing at any
given moment the thing you are most
excited about and capable of doing in
that moment. When you live in the now,
then you are doing what you want to be
doing. Even if it doesn't have the
definition of something else you realize
you might be doing, it is still a part
of the whole thing. So you are doing it.
Relax. You are doing it. And the sooner
you relax in the understanding that you
are doing it, then the way you wish to
do it will be more probable. You follow
me? Yes, I Remember, you are
always doing right
now and always will be doing right now
the things you want to do, but you will
continuously do in different ways the
same thing. So you are still doing the
same thing right now in a different way.
Not in a way your intellect has created
the structure to expect, but that can
occur only when you allow the structure
it is in now to be validly a part of the
whole idea and not assume that what
you're doing has nothing to do with it.
Okay, that that's what I want to um say
then because now you've got me right in
the center of it. All right. I was, you
know, doing this other job that I have
been doing, a career that I have and,
you know, with full confidence and fully
into it, excited, loving it, knowing
that this other thing is taking care of
itself and I am being who I am, you
know, loving what I'm doing to the
fullest. This other thing is going on
and and pieces and pl people are are
coming together on its own, right? I see
that happening. And then what happened
is that doesn't mean you do not act on
opportunities that present themselves.
However, that does not say that again. That does
that does not say that again. That does
not mean that you do not act on
opportunities that present themselves.
In other words, when you say, "Well,
yes, the thing is happening on its own."
Yes, it is, but you still have to act
upon opportunities that present
themselves. Sure. Yeah. I I I do play a
part in it. Yet, I was like really much
in the middle. Play a part. You are it.
Okay. Um, well, now I feel like I've I've been
Um, well, now I feel like I've I've been
able to, you know, concentrate on one
thing while I have somebody else now
concentrating on this other thing. Okay,
this person went out of town and, you
know, I was confront not confronted. I
know you don't like that.
I do not dislike anything. Oh, that's
that's true. That's a good point.
Neither do I. Um
let us render it down to this if we may.
May we? Yes. Remember simply once again
and keep it this simple if you will. You
are a 100% energy. If you are 90% the
thing you want to do and 10% the thing
you don't, you can only get the thing
you want 90%. And that final 10% may be
the lever that will actually allow the
entire 100% of what you want to do to
fall in your lap. But as long as you
keep your hooks in that 10% out of fear
just to be safe, just because you're not
quite sure, you can take that step into
the 100% direction of what you want to
do. That 10% that
1% even if 99% is on one side 1% because
of the way your belief systems can be
structured can be all that is necessary.
That one little shadow of a doubt can be
all that is necessary to stop the whole
thing from being a complete picture. I'm
not going to say anymore because that's
exactly you already said that this
evening. Yes. But now that you've said
it, and that's exactly what I needed to
hear. Let it hit home. Thank you. All it
takes is trust. I again promise you,
guarantee you it works. Never doesn't
work. You will see. Thank you.
You will see. Thank you.
Shedding. Hello, Bashar. Until you.
Thank you for everything you just
shared. That was one of my questions.
Thank you. um for being so
synchronistic.
It's hard to do that. [Music]
[Music]
Um I'm I want Now one
moment. Do not refrain from saying
anything you wish to say any of you just
because you think I'll pop you.
The only reason I reflect these ideas
back to you is to simply give you an
opportunity to listen to yourselves
because many times the only thing
standing in your way of anything you
want to do is the way you think of
yourself and very often it comes out in
what you
say and what you say is only a belief.
The way you say it is one way it can be
said and doesn't have to be the way you
believe it is. Again, remember you do
not have an opinion or a point of view
of a reality that has existence without
you. Your opinion and point of view is
the reality you experience. Literally,
your opinion is not of a reality that is
separate from you. It is the reality you
experience. So how you think, how you
look, how you see things is the reality
you experience. Plain and simple.
Continue. Okay.
Okay.
Um I talked with you before about what
do cats see and you suggested to me to
do some paintings about that. All right.
And I haven't done them yet and I never
felt inspired to do that. All right.
Perhaps simply talking about it was
enough. Well, in the way that I usually
paint, which is with oil paints. How do
you wish to do it? Well, what happened
was I got this um little intuition to
buy this certain kind of pen and inks.
It was all very synchronistic as usual.
And as I bought the pen, immediately all
these ideas came to me. Oh, very good.
Um for some some drawings and a story.
Very good to see cause and effect, the
same event. Yeah. One cannot exist
without the other.
So the whole story even came to me
really fast. And I I stopped in a
restaurant to write it down because it
was coming so fast. And while I was at
the restaurant, Reeba, who usually comes
here, she's not here tonight, just
happened to be there in this restaurant.
And I got to talk to her. Yes. All about
this thing with the cats and everything.
And um I'm excited about that. I'm also
afraid because I was so totally into
doing the oil paintings and the the kind
of scenes that I do and I love doing
that. And I have this fear that if I do
the do this um the writing little book
and the illustration and all that that
somehow I'm not going to be doing my
full 100% in my paintings. Oh,
nonsense. Not to be derogatory or
judgmental. Why would you choose to
believe that? Why would you choose to
believe that? If it's not what you
prefer to believe,
I don't know. Then don't.
Okay. Everything else has worked out.
So, I'm just going to just keep on
going, trusting all these things. There
you go. And why will you do that? And
why will you assume that everything will
work out? And why will you assume that
everything does work out? And why will
you believe that everything always works
out? Why will you believe that? Because
every time I do it, it does. But
why? Because you choose to. M because
you say so.
You follow me? Mhm. Do you understand
the power you have? Right. It's whenever
I know that it's going to work out. That
I know I'm going to do this or I'm going
to do that. It does. And when is it that
you know it's going to work out?
Whenever you want to know it. Whenever
you choose to know it. So, how often
will it be that you will always choose
to know it will always work out? How
often? Always. Why
not? Why not? Nothing. Nothing. Nothing.
Nothing is too good to be true. Nothing.
That sounds much more fun than the way
that I've done it up until now. Well, if
you like it, then live
it. Remember that. If you like it, live
it. It's as simple as
that. Guaranteed 100%.
Right in the middle of getting this idea
for this story and all this cat stuff
that's going on, my cat got sick. Yay.
And she's at the vet right now. All
right. She has to spend the night, which
I don't like her being away. I feel
uncomfortable. And what I want to know
is how can I assist her to get better by
being the
cat and taking
responsibility. Act like the cat. Act
like the energy that now in a sense she
the cat in that sense is reflecting to
you simply the last shreds of doubt.
Be the cat. Be spontaneous. Be in the
moment. See as the cat, trust it. Trust
it. Trust it.
The cat has done its job in reflecting
to you the energy that you can mimic.
Now it is going through the
transformation you are going through,
but it is taking upon itself the
negative aspects you might have felt for
yourself so that you won't have to. So
it won't slow you down from writing the
story. The cat will do that for you. All
animals will do that for you.
The cat will say, "Go ahead. Right. I'll
hold on to this transformational
negativity for
you because I know," the cat says. I
know I can transform it. You may not be
too sure yet. I love you enough to do
this for you. So, while I'm doing this,
what are you waiting for?
The longer you take to be who you are
and write that story, the longer I'll
stay at the vet.
Understand? Yes. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
And by the way, there is some very very
very very
strong what you call Japanese influence
in that artistic style from other lives
that you have.
shedding. Yes, Bashar. Yes. I just would
like you to know that I enjoyed my six
weeks in Europe and uh it's nice to be
back here and I Well, fine. Just wanted
to share with you the
um the wonderful feeling I get. I just
you know I I come here this evening and
and Can you share one thing you have
discovered about yourself in your
journey? ah that
I I enjoyed everything. I mean it's I am
capable of Oh my.
No, it's it's like I I I'm capable of
taking anything and making it joy.
Well, well,
it's like there were no negative
experiences really, you know. Now it
sounds like I'm home.
Thank you for creating a home for me to
come to as well as for you to come to.
Oh, you're very welcome. Well, thank
you. Thank you. By the way, next week of
your time will be entitled
Revelation and Anima will join us.
Wonderful.
Thank you for your sharing. chatting.
Hello, Vashar. Come to you. I'm still
kind of hung up on self-imposed karma.
Hung up on self-imposed karma. Is that
Are you comfortable up there? That's
what I'm wondering about. Is it
self-imposed by the higher self
or this fragment of the high self?
Again, there are two types of free will,
two types of recognition. the higher
self, quote unquote, who you are when
you are in between lives because then in
a sense there's really no distinction at
all between the higher self and
you uses the general
theme to represent the continuation of
the momentum and the balance that is
necessary to continue what you call the
karma which is only a representation of
momentum. The physical you you become utterly has
The physical you you become utterly has
the freedom to determine how you will
play that general theme out positively,
negatively, quickly, slowly, alone with
friends. You follow me? I follow you. So
the general themes you are exploring in
your life generally will remain
throughout the life and that has been in
a sense determined by the higher self
you. But the way you go about it is
utterly determined by the you you are
now here. This physical consciousness I
see. But it it seems to me like it's
different when you get to the point of
the group consciousness karma. This
isn't something you get over by
yourself. But you are all doing it together and
But you are all doing it together and
you can still do your part at whatever
rate you wish because as an individual
you can accelerate quote unquote ahead
of someone else or stay behind someone
else and you still cut the average rate
at which the entire group changes. Okay.
But think you don't have to in that
sense hold yourself back just because
someone else might be choosing a
particular rate. Yes, there is an
overall average rate, but within that
there's an awful lot of leeway as to how
quickly or slowly you can go as an
individual because it will all average
out. Okay. One concept I've been
dwelling on is the possibility that the
con the group every being in the group
consciousness karma that has been
involved in a destruction of a
civilization or a planet. Yes. I'm
wondering if this goes back as far as
even the Orion confederation that
they've Oh, yes, absolutely. Any one of
these here, any being that was involved
with this has ever transcended to fourth
density, left third density. Are they
still locked up in third density? Not
all. No, some has without going through
the group karma. Yes. But then it will
depend upon the reasons for why that
individual has created what they have
created. And what they have done has
still added to the overall ability of
your entire consciousness to go where it
wishes to go. Okay. I had heard on one
of the tapes that someone had asked you
if on the raw material someone had said
no one had ever left this density since
Jesus's time.
That is simply an analogy to the idea
that you have become extremely highly
focused since that time and you have
elevated to slightly different levels
and have basically all decided to remain
and return because the transformation is
so attractive and exciting. It is not so
much that no one has been able to leave.
It is that no one has wanted to because
well as you say you are where it's at.
I see your planet is going through such
a strong transformation that not only do
the individuals on your world not
necessarily want to leave because they
want to be a part of it on some level
physically or non-physically but you
have attracted the attention of
thousands of other civilizations and
dimensions of consciousness to watch
what's going on.
I see. So that is simply the idea that
you are contained within a particular
type of focus that you have all desired
to add to the momentum of the group
karma of the transformation.
Okay. I gather right now we're on
there's one theme. The way out is the
way through. We're on the process now of
going through. Yes. But we were going to
build up to a point of war and decide
not to have a war this time.
There may be some small skirmishes, but
you have already decided not to
annihilate yourselves. That is long
since passed as a decision. Even though
many of you may not even realize it
consciously, but the decision has
already been made. I know you said not
the planet, but that also a means of
civilization. It also means that. Okay.
Thank you. Thank you very much. Sure.
Hello, Bashar. And to you. Um, in the
last few days, I've had two sightings
that were very different from each
other. Both were light, but but but the
visual and the energy was very different
in each case. All right, define. Well,
the first was extremely ecstatic. I was
with two other friends and we requested
a sighting and we waited and there it
was. You want to hear more details about
it or can you already see it? You know,
second. What? Oh, the second uh the
second I I was with another friend and
there was a very very bright light and
we had also asked for a sighting all day
and we saw it at night and um what was
the feeling this time? Just really
excitement and confirmation that in fact
we we can communicate. What was so
different about the second from the
first? Well, the first was very lengthy
and it looked very different. Uh the the
first one was many lights. Many lights
and also movement of those lights and
almost a web like or membrane kind of uh
effect of the stars. It was like the
stars were woven into this.
All right. Whatever. All right. Quite
incredible. It was like a big web that
filled the whole sky. All right. Okay.
The holographic nature of reality. Go
ahead. Yes. Exactly. Um, [Music]
exactly. Um, so my my question is um is
is there a message and where where were
these people or or these beings from? I
mean no labels for now except the
association. Uhhuh. All civilizations,
all levels of consciousness that are now
focused upon your planet are all
represented in every interaction going
on. The majority of what you are
experiencing are energy interactions,
literal projections of consciousness
within your electromagnetic field that
you are allowed to perceive that you
have elevated yourself to the level to
be able to perceive. When we say
allowed, that means you have allowed
yourselves. Yes. to perceive the
interaction, the intersection of
consciousness. Now in your reality, much
of what you perceive as these lights are
that the intersection of consciousness
without the idea of physical materiality
as you understand it. That's what they
told me. Yes. They they said we do not
fit your laws of physicality. No. Do not
try to define us. Yes. Thank you. Yeah.
Okay. So allow yourself to recognize
simply that you are a part of the web,
that you are connected to it in that
way. Use the energy in whatever way,
shape or form represents what excites
you on the planet and you will be
drawing the web closer together. Well, I
feel that I am a connector for human
beings and this energy I mean two to
that is what I just said. Yes. Use the
energy in whatever way represents what
excites you the most and you will be
tightening the web with regard to your
planet. Okay. Thank you very much. Does
that serve you? Oh yeah. Oh thank you
very much
for lighting up your life. Sharing
Bashar, I just want to share uh thank
you for six months ago telling me that
my flute would be my magic wand and it
certainly has been. Well, thank you,
Maui Mary. And also the party happened
that you described and the friends were
there that I didn't know at the time.
Did you have a good time? A wonderful
time. Thank you. and I'm just ready to
go back and I want to know if you have
anything to share with me about my role
in the harmonic conversion on Maui and
what I should be doing. There is nothing
that I need to say and there is nothing
you should be doing. You will do what
your heart moves you to do. You are
after all as I have already said Maui
Mary. Thank you. Thank you
Jing. Good evening, Bashar. And to you,
I have been taking a lot of the things
that you've said on your various tapes
seriously. Oh, thank you. Number one is
take action. And I found out that when
you go out and actually take action that
what is said on the tapes or any place
else then becomes your own and becomes
real. Yes. So I decided what excites me
that I can take action on. Yes.
I decided to get people together in
groups out camping so that they could
connect with the earth and the universe
and have common experiences. Oh,
exciting. Yes, we had a wonderful,
wonderful, wonderful weekend last
weekend. Oh, three wonderful.
The triad of wonders.
You also said that we should be
networking. So, we thought not should
should. Okay. We we wanted to. Yes. That
we could we could start breaking down
the barriers between how people saw
themselves. Yes. So we set up a program
whereby um the some Indian teachers
would teach us how to how they relate to
the earth and the animals and all that's
in physicality. Nice. Um, we had a
wonderful astrologer that helped us see
that all the the heavenly bodies are
alive and what their connection is to
us. Nice. And then we had a John
channeling. Nice. And during this whole
weekend on this top of this mountain,
which was at 7,600 ft with these great
big huge cedar trees and and blue sky
and fresh
air, everybody started helping everybody
else in every imaginable way. It was
absolutely beautiful.
I don't think I've ever seen so much
love expressed back and forth. And
people were on many different paths,
which is what we had in mind. And they
shared their paths with each other and
they learned that all paths go to the
same place. And there was so much love
and sharing. It was absolutely great. My
your planet is becoming so much like
mine. I just might hop over a little
sooner than I thought.
Well, I thought you might be looking
down on us because the last time we
converged as a group on the top of the
mountain, which was after the John
channeling, we formed a great big circle
and the leaders started inside the
circle and we did hugs all around until
everybody was just absolutely glowing
and I could feel the energies around us.
I could feel the it was it was like
sixth density not spaceships but
energies and it was like they were
jumping up and down and laughing and
hugging each other while we were
it brings us great joy to see you in
such great joy. And so I thought of the
geometric progression that you had
talked about and and I thought with this
kind of energy going up and out into the
mass consciousness, I thought now
there's a whole bunch more of total
acceptance and loving allowance that the
whole planet can grab onto and use for
their own purposes. Yes. Thank you for
creating that effect and that impact.
Again, every single individual has an
impact. together. You are overwhelming.
And so we're going to do it again on the
same mountain at the convergence. Thank
you. We shall be there to receive our
hugs. Good. Wonderful. And to give them
out. Good. Feel yourselves wrapped in
the energy of all that is of the
association. We embrace you.
Thank you. For sure.
One moment. One moment.
How many of you signify by saying
yes have a strong
desire for your government to release
the information it has regarding
extraterrestrial contact upon your
planet? How many of you have written those
How many of you have written those
letters?
Don't know what that's about.
As we have said, it is about being in
love in a loving
way, sitting down and in your own loving
words letting your governments, which
after all are you, know that you now
desire them to release that information.
You now desire to know what is going
on. Use your own words. You know what
you want to say.
Now, this is simply to some degree an
indication, an indicator of the
degree of what may be called a
difference between the idea of knowing
what you want and being willing to act
upon it. In no way, shape, or form are you
it. In no way, shape, or form are you
ever a disappointment to us. However, we
simply do a little checking from time to
time to let you know by simply hearing
yourselves as to whether you really have
the convictions you say you have.
Because if you do, you'll act on them.
How many have written? Say yes. Yes. See
the difference. Thank you very much. Just
difference. Thank you very much. Just
checking.
Shedding. Hello Vashar Lamb to you. I
was um understanding that there is a
Syrian energy that's occurring either
now or um I actually was told a date of
July 23rd and I was serious energy yes
is being sent to your planet all the
time. Oh all right. Well, um I guess my
question was that if um if there was a
stronger energy being sent on the July
23rd or you got something in the mail on
this, there is what you call a
juxiposition between your solar system
and their solar system around that time
frame. And because of what appears to be
a link up, a closeness, a harmonious
overlap spatially, then that is an
indication that there is a doorway, an
interface that makes it perhaps more
conductive or conducive for
transmissions to be picked up by you on
the mental band, but they are always
being sent. You follow me? Yes, I do.
But what kind I don't understand what
kind of energy it is. I guess I just
don't know enough about is the energy of
play, the energy of joy, the energy of
love, the energy of creation. It is
energy for you to create and sculpt into
whatever you desire your reality to be.
It is also very strongly connected to
the energy of your dolphins because they
are the other alien species upon your
planet. And when you form a quote
unquote association, a federation with
them, then you will be one world and can
interact with other whole worlds. The
energy of Sirius is very closely
connected to the dolphin energy because
the dolphins swim in a physical sea and
the sixth density beings of Sirius in a
sense exist in an energy sea. You follow
me? Yes, I do. So they simply send love
and light much light for you to do
whatever you wish to do. Some
individuals simply vibrate more in
accord to their particular frequency
than someone else and so they will
derive best benefit from that particular
wavelength. So they send it knowing that
there are individuals who will identify
with it.
Follow me? Yes, I do. Does that serve
you? Yes, it does. Thank you. Thank you
very much.
There will be but a few moments
remaining for this
interaction. Sharing.
I'm Sarah and I'm going to ask about the
energy that we were working with in
October from
Sirius and the energy that came from
Sirius and we have it on the four
stations and one in Washington
uh
Moscow in on the mountains up near
Geneva and in Shambala.
uh
the um the Gobi area. Goi desert. Yes.
And that energy been here since
uh
1981 and I wanted to ask what you have
to give us on that energy. Japa came
last time and told us about it. It is a
specific frequency that has to do with
creating a vibration in your reality
that makes it more conducive to begin to
experience telepathic links among your
own members of society. to unite
specific projects that are going on,
specific interests that are going on
around your globe so that the
individuals with the same interest will
be in touch with each other, will draw
each other closer together and form a
unity and a momentum so that those
particular projects can come to
fulfillment. It is therefore a strengthening of a
It is therefore a strengthening of a
telepathic bond among many members of
your society. That is primarily what the
particular frequency is for.
Thank you. But thank you. You have to
avail yourselves of it in order for it
to do any good. Yes. And thank you for
availing yourselves. Yes. And that is
work. We're working to help make this a
sacred planet. It already is. Yes.
That's good. Thank you very much. And
thank you. At this
you. At this
timing, allow us to extend to each and
every one of you a reflection of the
love that you are, that you are waking
up into knowledge of. But let us remind
you that if you are willing to be that
love, then act it out.
expand, interact. It is the
relationships that you are in your world
that create the
changes. The relationship between
yourselves and any idea that you now
acknowledge to be a part of you. Be your
side of the relationship fully by acting
in it, by acting as it. It is the action
that makes a difference. The intent is
very strong. The desire all well and
good. Your hearts in that sense are
behind it. Now move your
bodies. We thank you. our unconditional
love, energy and excitement to you
all. Pleasant and exciting dream lives
and life
dreams. Good day. Good day.
How'd it go? Wonderful. Wonderful.
Thank you all for being here tonight.
Thank you all for coming. Remember next
week is revelation and the female energy
will that will be coming through that
Bashara mentioned is Anima who is a
social social scientist on her planet on
the planet of Esasani. And if you want
to take