How are you all this day of your time as
you create time for each
day? I want us to begin this interaction
this evening of your time with the
laying of a
foundation between them. This foundation
will consist of an exploration of a
definition of what you call the
imagination. Now all of you generally realize you
Now all of you generally realize you
have an
imagination but most of you have to have
perceived your society are usually never
taught what the imagination is really
for. Why it really exists how you can
really use it in connection to the
creation of your experiential reality.
In other
words, some of you already understand
and some of you may not understand, but
the fundamental to everything we will
share with you is the discussion of the
idea that each and every one of you
individually and collectively are
absolutely and utterly responsible for
the creation of your experiential
dayto-day reality. Your physical
reality, it's your creation, your
projection. You have been taught for thousands of
You have been taught for thousands of
your years, tens of thousands of your
years, that what you call physical
reality exists outside of you. That you
exist within it. That it is separate
from you. That you in a sense are
separate from it. But even your own
scientists now are beginning to discover
it is
not. They are now beginning to be aware
of what I have been sharing with you.
that what you
call seemingly exteriorized physical
reality is actually a projection of what
you imagine it does. That physiological
reality does not really empirically
exist apart from your definition of it.
That physiological reality, what you
have for so long being to be the solid
exterior world actually is created out
of the
definition. The idea therefore to
understand how strong an impact
definitions and
belief have in creating that
physiological reality.
All that you experience and what you
call your day-to-day life is the product
of what you have been taught to buy as a
belief about what it ought or ought not
to live. Only these definitions are what
give physical reality its seeming
solidity. Seeming solidity for solidity,
physiological solidity is also only one
of the
definitions that create your experience
of physical reality. Physical reality
can be very malleable, very
fluctuable, very flexible, does not have
to be as seemingly unchanging or as
slowly changing as many of you have
thought that it is. This definition of
slow change of solid matter is simply
the product of thousands of generations
in your society of the habit of thinking
of it that way.
But now now
now you are awakening as a society to
the exploration of different levels of
what you call consciousness and
spirituality and are beginning to
explore and recognize that you have many
more levels I shall say for now of
consciousness than you previously were
taught that you have. You are beginning
to discover different aspects of
yourself in a way that allows you to
think differently beyond what you are used to
differently beyond what you are used to
using as your senses. You are now
discovering you have the capacity to
sense more than you used to think you
have. And in this application, in this
exploration, you are now beginning to
realize many things about the
connectedness between your consciousness
and physical reality that you have
hereto for not understood exist. That
consciousness and physical reality are
not really separate ideas, but that
physical reality, what you call physical
reality, is but an expression of the
consciousness that you are. one
expression and you have many of them on
many different levels in many different
dimensions of experience and they are
all real and all
true expressions of yourself of the
consciousness the total being that you
are of which this
personality is but a fragment and
aspect an expression one facet of the
multi-dimensional crystal that each and
every one of you are individually and
collectively. Therefore, the majority of
what we will be discussing this evening
of your time will all basically be laid
upon this understanding, this foundation
that you create your own reality and
will basically all be directed generally
speaking into the understanding of your
imagination. For it is your imagination
that is the prime tool, the prime
ingredient out of which and through
which you can learn. A that you have
always created your reality through it
and that B you can create any reality
you desire from this point forward by
getting in touch with how you have done
it in the past. what the mechanism of
your imagination is actually all about
and how you can use it consciously to
create the reality you
want. Imagination it is the prime tool. It is
Imagination it is the prime tool. It is
the dimension of all experience of all
possible reality you could create
yourself to live. Fundamentally speaking
it works as follow.
You have a picture in your mind of
something you would like to do. A
visualization you call it. Now this
visualization will
usually contain a picture of
contain a picture of
yourself doing the thing you want to do.
You will daydream it as you say. You
will picture it, visualize it, imagine
it. You will see yourself doing the
things, having the things that you
want. Well, recognize something that you
may not have recognized before. Your
society has taught you, well, all right,
that's all well and good. That's your
imagination. Your society usually says
that's just your
imagination. And that that picture you
have isn't really
real. Oh, it's a nice thought, a nice
wish. Oh, but face reality. reality is
not
like but you have been taught to believe
it's not. You have been taught to
believe your imagination is not real.
But understand
this, your imagination, what you call
this visualization, this picture in your
visualization, this picture in your
mind's eye, this seeing of yourself in a
situation you would prefer to be in is
the viewing, the observation of a real
reality, another probable you. I say
probable only because you don't believe
it actually exists. It does exist. It is
another you.
And if you begin to understand that it
is a real
reality, then what you can simply do is
recognize that it represents another
vibration, another frequency, which is
the only thing that defines one reality
from another. And if you recognize the
another. And if you recognize the
difference between the frequency that
the picture represents and the frequency
you have been living in, then you may
realize something else. If you wish that
picture in your mind's eye to be the
real reality, the experiential reality
of your day-to-day life, then all you
have to really
do is watch the you in that
picture doing the things you say you
would prefer to
do and mimic the you in the picture in
terms of its attitude, in terms of its
approach to things, in terms of how that
you you say you want to be would handle
the circumstances and situations that
have occurred in your life. If a
situation comes along and you don't know
what to do with it, create the you in
your imagination that you prefer to be.
Hand the situation to that you and watch
in your meditative state what the you,
the idealized preferable you in your
imagination does with that situation.
Watch the attitude. Watch how that you
handle the situation. Watch, daydream
out how that you will allow that
situation to come to a successful
conclusion. Then mirror it, match it,
mimic it, and you will get the same
conclusion because you will be being
that you. That's what your imagination
is for. to create the template and the
blueprint that will show you beyond a
shadow of a doubt what methodology will
work for you to be able to transform any
situation, any circumstance into the
outcome and manifestation you prefer it
to be. If you trust that in your
imagination what you are seeing is a
real you and you start acting like that
you, you will have the life of that you.
You will be that
person literally immediately and you will get
literally immediately and you will get
the same outcome. You will get the same
effect that you see in your
imagination. This is not a philosophical
discussion. This is not an
analogy. This is an actual mechanical
physical description of how it works. It
is that easy. It is that simple.
We are discussing physics. We are
discussing mechanics of how you create
your physical reality. You do this all
the time. Anyway, it is simply that your
society and not believing that your
imagination is real has allowed you to
forget to place in your unconscious self
the idea of the imagination, the ideas,
the beliefs, the emotions that create
your reality. When you're not in touch
consciously with what those beliefs and
imaginings are, then you do not
necessarily see the connection between
your outer exterior
[Music] experiential experiential
dayto-day
reality and imagination. [Music] This This
understanding, this
connection, this
allowance, this
remembering that your physical reality
is created By your belief, through your
imagination, whether consciously or unconsciously are
allow to use it in a conscious
way to know beyond the shadow of
the clear observ
transparent that you create your
physical reality to watch it happen to watch
reality to watch it happen to watch
yourself
doing function
consciously moment by
moment day by
day. And to
know that you
are each and every one of
you an expression of the infinite, an
expression, an aspect of
creation. Your own literature
tells that you are made in the image of
God. What does that
mean? It means from our
perspective that you are a reflection of
the infinite creation. And if you are a
reflection of the infinite
creation, if the infinite creation is a
multi-dimensional being, a
multi-dimensional creator, then if you
are made in that image, you yourself
must be a multi-dimensional being, a
multi-dimensional creator. You are an aspect
creator. You are an aspect
of you have that power. You are that
power. All beings within
creation are all the different ways that
the infinite creation has of expressing
itself through it through the
imagination. It
is all of you, all of us are all the
different ways that the infinite has of
expressing itself through its
imagination. You have the same
capacity within your own experiential
universe. That is how you do create your
That is how you do create your
experiential universe because you are
co-creators with the infinite.
It is
this that we have come to reflect you to
remind you so that you in taking back your
you so that you in taking back your
power in acknowledging the aspect of the
infinite creator that you are can live
in a sense as you were meant to live
which is in absolute ecstasy and joy.
No one has to struggle. You kind of
create it if you wanted. You have
created it perhaps out of the belief
that you need it to. But now you are
waking up. Now you are beginning to
realize that no one has to struggle. No
one has to
suffer. You are now realizing that
ecstasy is what you are created from and
it is your
birthight. Nothing is too good to be
true. Nothing is too simple to be
Nothing is too simple to be
true unless you believe it must be
discovered. Then believe me, you will
get it. You will always get in your
it. You will always get in your
experiential reality. The thing you
believe or have been taught to believe
is the most likely reality you will
get. Getting in touch with that allows
you to pick the reality you prefer.
Now at this
time we extend to you our deepest
appreciation in allowing us to interact
with you this day of your time. To us
you are a gift. We learn from
you. Everyone learns. Everyone grows. It
is
unending through you. Our civilizations
are given an opportunity to see that
many more ways that the infinite
creation can express itself to me.
Therefore, we thank you for functioning
as ambassadors to your society for that
is what you are right now
literally and we thank you for allowing
us to function as ambassadors of our
respective world in the association of
world for bit by bit and day by day
through these interactions we may
cocreate with each other a conducive
atmosphere that will allow us to
interact more openly more blatantly We
have to take face to
face. Our faces externally may be
different for our hearts and our souls
are the same. And it is on that level
that we can relate and that anything can
be
understood. In return for your
willingness to co-create this
interaction with us this day of your
time, I ask you now, how may I serve
you? Thank you.
You say that you got to speak up so that
all may share. You say that there are
many aspects that we are
aspects that we are
we are living different lifetimes at the
same time. Yeah, time is real while you
are in it. But it is your creation.
Linear time is in a sense your illusion.
It is your way of experiencing physical
reality. So all the
lives you know you are living as you say
have lived or will live do actually all
exist simultaneously. You can use if I may
simultaneously. You can use if I may
before you go on what we have referred
to as the radio
analogy. Now you all are familiar with
the device in your society call radio.
Yes. Recognize that you know all of the
programs are there all at once.
You don't actually assume that when you
turn the dial the program exists just at
that time only for you. You know that
you simply receive the one you have
turned the dial to. But you know all the
programs are still coming to the radio
all at the same time. They all overlap.
And the reason you can get any number of
them is because they are all there for
you to receive.
Similarly, what you call different light
kinds are simply different programs,
different frequencies of the total
consciousness that you are. Different
perspectives and points of view of the
total being that you
are at any one
time. Each channel may only perceive
itself, but your overall consciousness
has the ability of switching its diet to
focus on any one of the programs or all
of the programs if it wishes. and allow
ourselves to receive the information
from any number one of them because they
do not really exist in a past or in a
future. They all exist now. They're all
overlapping and it's simply a matter of
adjusting yourself and aligning yourself
to a particular frequency that allows
you to perceive information that belongs
in another program. You follow along.
Yes. Um well, that was going to be my
question. How can I tap into other
aspects of myself in order to help
myself in this present? Thank you very
much. Now, first of all, remember as
I've said, the first way to understand
that it is easy to do is to understand
that it is not as if you have to really
delve into some deep dark past breaking
through barriers or some dim distant
foggy future breaking through barriers
of time because time is your illusion to
begin with. If you begin with the notion
that everything is right now, it brings
it that much closer to you because you
understand it all exists within you.
Secondly, however, allow yourself to remember very
however, allow yourself to remember very
importantly the following
idea, you the you know yourself to be
exists in the present.
Now each and every one of you are a
complete kit as you are. You have all
the tools and all the ingredients you
require to fully understand and live the
life you are living now without
necessarily exploring ideas or
connections that you may call the past
or the future. We will be willing in
this sense to explore any of these ideas
with you to some degree. But you will
always find us somewhat hesitant to
focus you in the past to focus you in
the future because generally we have
observed in your society. You think you
need to understand those connections in
order to understand yourself in the
present and you do not really need them.
It is a valid way to understand
different ideas but it is not essential
in the sense that your past controls
your present. You will always exist in the
present. You will always exist in the
now. Now is the only experiential time
there ever is. You are actually creating
the past from the present, not the other
way around. So whatever you choose to
define yourself to be in the present is
what determines what past you will
discover about yourself. So you do not
really need to go to the past to
understand. If you simply define what
you want to be now that will give you
all the ability you need to be whatever
you want to be now. Just defining that
knowing you have the power to do so and
living that life that you prefer to live
right now.
But if you desire this type of
exploration, then simply realize it is
all real, that your imagination is real,
and if you simply relax in a centered
and meditative state and drift and
daydream, as we have said, then if you
put out a desire for a specific
direction, your imagining, your picture,
your inner knowing self will drift into
those areas, will pick up on those
frequencies. And if you don't analyze it, if you just
And if you don't analyze it, if you just
let it come, just watch it, you will see
pictures flowing through your
imagination that will generally be
representative of different lives you
have lived that may have some bearing on
the life you have created yourself to be
in the present. Sometimes they may come
at first in very brief flashes.
Sometimes they may play themselves out
in entirely unfolding, rich and sensory
daydreams. Do not overanalyze
Do not overanalyze
them. Let them play themselves out in
the way they most naturally come to
you. Feel the essence of the idea and
apply the essence to your present life.
You do not necessarily need to
understand analytically speaking every
last detail of what you are experiencing
to understand how. You can simply use
the essence the feeling you are getting
in a way that you can apply in your
present reality. You understand? Yes.
The mad assistant. Thank you. We find
you sharing. You say you
All right. Go right ahead.
Dad. Um. Oh, one more. One more. Each
and every one of you do
remember there are no
accidents and
anything any of you has to say on some
level to some degree can be applied by
each and every one of you in your own
lives. Just because you are not asking
the question does not mean it doesn't
apply to you. Remember there are no
boring situations only bored minds.
Proceed. Um, last time
I had to counter
guys. Um, I needed to elaborate on the
multiart.
Oh, it is simply an analogy. The idea of
referring to as a multi-dimensional
crystal in the sense that if you simply
think of a multiaceted crystal, you can
understand that each and every facet
represents what you would call a
different light, a different aspect of
the same crystal facing in a different
direction with a complete different set
of experiences. Yet they are all part of
the same single crystal. Understand?
Yes. Now, can I tap into that knowledge
of
Yes, you can. if it really applies into
your present life. However, if it is
something that does not immediately
apply, then there may be a little bit of
difficulty. But you can tap into
whatever portion may apply. It is simply
that we are suggesting you do not put
necessarily upon the expectation that
all of it must
apply because all of it probably will
not understand.
Or you can tap into it as they have said
but by definition because you are the
light you are here you will get whatever
portion of it will work for you here
otherwise it wouldn't serve a purpose
understand what I know that
does it really matter
sometimes you may and sometimes you
won't but since it doesn't really matter
since you will simply be able to do what
it is you need to do the label many
times will not be that important. You
may know and you may not know but in
effect since it doesn't really matter
you can simply do what you want to do
with whatever it is however it comes in
terms of information
understanding you can use it however you
can use it as a
direction if you know let's say in the
way of suggestion that the idea may hold
something for you then use it as a model
whether it comes from there or not will
not necessarily be crucial, but you can
use it as a model to direct your basic
thoughts to simply use it as a model to
form the ideas you desire to
experience. It can be used that way and
even as a model, it will allow the
information to come from wherever it
needs to come from even if it doesn't
come directly from the model you have
represented. Understand? Okay, let's say
uh I can see my imagination there. Okay,
will that help my imagination? It can.
Yes. Again, remember that even though
you do not necessarily have to
analytically know everything that's
going on in all of your lives to live
the life you're living now, there is
always what you may call bleed through.
Always. Each and every life you have
hundreds, thousands, millions of
experiences in ultimate dimensions of
reality are all constantly feeding
information to all other lives. It is
holographic in
nature, multi-dimensional in nature.
There is information being exchanged
between all of your aspects
simultaneously. And whatever portions of
the information applied to any one
particular aspect are the portions that
stick in that particular life.
Understand? So to use a further analogy,
the idea may simply be that sometimes
when you find yourself being inspired by
something that seems to be out of the
blue as you say. That inspiration may
directly be connected into a realization
or discovery that let's say a future you
has made. Understand?
Does that assist? Yes. All right.
Welcome.
I'm sorry. Hey, I'm saying
something reality. And one thing I heard
you say that everything in reality like
what somebody else has to do with you.
you are attracting it into your reality,
cocreating it with them. Now, there
could be different reasons for this, but
you are and must be of agreement in
order to experience anything. Right.
Right. I understand. And what I'm trying
to more is the idea with another
person's creating their reality and
you're creating your reality. And you
both say that I mean you obviously do
have to some degree a consensus reality
on some level otherwise you wouldn't
even perceive each other. You are
obviously agreeing to some things. Do
not forget all of you now we perceive
are sitting in what you would call some
sort of a room. Yes, you all have to
agree that you are in order to
experience that similarity.
So obviously on some level there are
already many things you all agree are
the definitions of the reality you call
your physical
universe. It is in some specifics that
you disagree. But even sometimes when
you disagree, you do not necessarily
disagree to the point where you don't
experience at all what they are talking
about. You can allow them their
experience of it. You can acknowledge
that it exists for them. While it may
not fit directly into your life, you can
still recognize that it is quote unquote
a real reality for them, even if it's
not your
lifestyle. Individuals who literally
Individuals who literally
directly do not
perceive the consensus
reality are usually what you label
insane. Now they are perceiving realities that
Now they are perceiving realities that
are just as real. It is simply that
those aspects are not part of the
consensus reality. But it is just as
real. The reason that more often than
not they have what you call difficulty
in their lives is because your society
teaches them and has taught them from
birth that what they are experiencing is
not valid. They know it's real. They
can't fight that. But the society you
are in does not give them a way to
communicate that information in an
applicable way in an applicable manner.
So they lock themselves in their own
cycle, their own perceptions, their own
private world and become discommunicated
from your planet, from your society.
They become somewhat removed from the
general consensus somewhat. Obviously to
some degree they agree on some level
otherwise you wouldn't even perceive
them at all.
Now that is why we have all recognized
there's a very fine line between what
you call insanity and genius because a
genius is seeing different realities
perceiving different ideas in every way
shape or form sometimes is what you call
the insane individual. It is simply that
the genius has found a way to
communicate in an applicable manner the
ideas they are perceiving to the
mainstream of your society.
understand that is really the only
difference. Now, does that answer some
of your question or some specific idea
you wish to discuss? Well, I think
there's another idea, right? It's like
um consciously creating. Yeah.
How real? I understand. It's really real
to me that I'm creating. I just don't
always understand why I'm doing it.
All right. One simple way, one simple
methodology to begin to allow yourself
to understand is to simply ask yourself,
all right, I have cocreated the
situation or created the situation.
First, own it. If you don't own it, you
can't know it. You can't transform it if
you don't own it. First, once you have
owned it, ask yourself, what am I
learning about myself by being in this
circumstance? What belief system within me is this
What belief system within me is this
situation showing me I have? Is it
showing me a belief system I no longer
prefer? If that is the case, therefore,
obviously, one of the main reasons why
the situation is happening is to show me
I have a belief I don't prefer because
that belief created this reality. And
now that I am consciously aware of what
that belief is, I can change it. I can
rewrite it. I can redefine it. And in
redefining it, it will rewrite the
physical experience I will have. That
can be one reason. But simply ask
yourself in any given circumstance that
you are wondering why you are in, what
am I learning about myself? What am I
experiencing here? What type of a belief
would I have to have in order to create
this reality? Then it will put you in
touch usually with exactly what you need
to be looking at.
Because the idea of an unconscious and a
conscious mind is also only your
invention. An unconscious mind is not an
inherent creation. It is a convenience of
creation. It is a convenience of
definition that all of you have created
to have a place to put things you don't
want to look at consciously.
You are not really composed of a sub and
unconscious reality. You are one
consciousness. So the idea is to simply recognize that
So the idea is to simply recognize that
physical reality and physical
experiences are your way of safeguarding
that you will always allow eventually
anything you have relegated to your
unconscious mind to be shown to you in a
way that will allow you to bring it into
your conscious
realization because that's what physical
reality is a reflection of your
strongest beliefs.
Now on the surface when certain
situations and circumstances happen to
you if it seems as if what is going on
is negative. Remember that many times
that doesn't necessarily mean that's a
onetoone reflection of the fact that
you're doing something negative. It can
be that sometimes you attract
individuals into your reality that seem
to be functioning negatively. So perhaps
if you know you are functioning
positively, you can serve as a living
example to them how they might also
choose to change into a positive
manifestation. Just because an
individual is attracted into your
reality that is functioning negatively
doesn't mean that you are understand.
But it's still a co-creation for a
purpose for a reason that may serve you
well. So simply ask yourself, what
belief would I have to have to create
this reality? What am I learning about
myself in this
interaction? Understand? That will
usually give you the understanding of
why what is going on is going on.
Because remember, life doesn't happen to
you. It happens through
you. Does that serve you? Well, thank
you very much. You and then you and then
you. What is the best way to get rid of
those programs within us that prevent us
from creating from really material? No.
Fine. Fine. Fine. Now, first of all,
just a little bit of red
definition. You cannot really get rid of
anything. I know what you mean. But many
times when individuals in our society
say, "I'd like to get rid of
this," it really means they would like
to push it away as if it had no purpose
in their lives at all. Many times that
idea of that attempt to get rid of
something is a denial. Therefore, if you
recognize there is no outside, there is
nowhere to get rid of anything to, then
it will begin to perhaps dawn on you
that what you're doing is not getting
rid of it. You are transforming it from
a negative into a positive. It's the
same energy but it will take on a
different aspect, a different face, a
different presentation to have not
gotten rid of it, but to no longer
experience the negative effect from it.
Understand the difference.
Now one of the simplest way to transform
a negative into a positive is once again
as we have said ask yourself what are
you being told by yourself by being in
that circumstance. What belief systems
do you have that would have created the
situation? If you
find that it is because you have a
negative definition, a negative
belief, then simply once you are in
touch with what that belief
is, literally in your
imagination, rewrite it. Ask yourself,
well, if this is the belief I had, what
belief would I prefer to have? I prefer
to have this belief. And watch yourself.
Sometimes an individual will still
create a
negative. In other words, as an example,
you might be dealing with the idea, I
never succeed. I never
succeed. I never succeed.
Now, if you get in touch with
that, an
individual might in rewriting it still
be tempted to
say, "I do not never
succeed." But that's still a negative.
It is still a denial. Rather than simply
saying the absolute polarity, I always
succeed. I always succeed.
Here is where it can get a little bit
fine. Watch your definition of
success because many of you have
different definitions of what that type
of a word
means. So many of you may find that even
when you say I always succeed, you may
create an expectation of what that's
supposed to be like. And if you don't
see it the way you expected it, you may
not believe you're actually succeeding
like you need to. Or many of you may
have a definition of success that's
actually very scary for you and
therefore you don't really want to
succeed and that's why you
don't. Clarity of definition is very
critical about what it is you would
prefer to
be. Here is the whole formula as it
basically stands.
Clarity of
intention. What is your overriding
intention? Clarity of
definition. How are you defining the
terminology of your overriding
intention? What are the definitions of
these states of being that you say you
do and don't prefer? Be clear on what
they mean to you, what they represent to
you. For example, again, some individual may
For example, again, some individual may
say, "I wish to be rich. I wish to be
rich. I wish to be
rich." And they are not getting
abundant. They are not getting that at
all. Then if they examine their definition of
Then if they examine their definition of
what it means to be
abundant, all of a sudden it may dawn on
them that they have been taught or they
have taught themselves through life to
associate the
idea of being rich with also carrying a
personality trait that they don't want.
Perhaps they have observed individuals
in life that are
rich that perhaps acting matters they
don't want to act in and they have made
for some reason an assumption that if I
am rich I have to act that way because
all the rich people I see act that way.
So they are connecting something they
don't want with something they do. In
clarifying the definition they can say
wait a
minute why must I assume that just
because I might be rich I would have to
act that way I don't have to assume that
now that I am clear on what my
definition has been the assumption that
to be rich is also to act in a way I
don't want to now I can redefine it I
can understand I can be rich in the way
I want to be
rich and I don't have to be any way I
don't want to be once the definition is
clear. You can allow the reality to
manifest more quickly because it is only
your definition very often that keeps
the reality
away because you might assume it
contains something you don't want along
with something you
do. Next, clear desire. Clear desire. In
other words, do you really want it? Are
you really sure you want it?
Again, some individuals may not
absolutely be sure they want the thing
they say they want. Here's another
example. An individual may have within
them a
belief that once they get what they
want, why no more excitement, no more
excitement of the chase.
And if they believe that more
strongly than the excitement of getting
it, then they will always just prevent
themselves from getting it because they
believe that trying to get it is more
exciting because they believe that once
they get it, that's
it. If you always understand there will
always be more, you won't have to worry
about that.
But that may be one reason why an
individual even though they say I want
it, I want it, I want it, may not really
clearly desire
it. Third, in the middle of the 3D of
definition and desire is clear
deservability. Do you believe you
deserve what you say you want? That's a
big issue for many of you. Many of you
do not think that you have a right to
have what you
desire because your society has steeped
many of you in notions of guilt, in
notions of
worthlessness, in notions of having to
struggle in order to earn happiness.
That conditioning though has something
that years of conditioning. Now we are
getting to that one more time.
After you have a clear intention, clear
definition, clear desire, clear
deservability, the only thing that
really remains is clear action. And all that
remains is clear action. And all that
simply means is once you know what your
intention, definition, desire, and
deservability are, acting with
conviction on the opportunities that
come into your life that excite you is
all it takes to bring you what you want.
Now, you have brought up the issue of
habits. Patterns. All right? We
recognize that your society has been
conditioned for thousands, millions of
years. So
So
what? Now let me explain
that. A habit, a pattern in that sense
that you call a habit is something you
do that you don't know you're
doing. Once you recognize you have a
habit, you don't have it anymore because
you have to be beyond it in order to
know you have it. It is only your
assumption that the recognition of a
habit is not the sessation of the habit
that allows you to keep repeating what
you have always done. It is only your
assumption that it must keep repeating
itself that allows it to keep
repeating. Understand? Once you know you
have a habit, at that moment of
realization, you no longer have the
habit. And only your assumption that you
still do allows you to keep experiencing
your life as if you still
do. But if you know you have broken it
because you have recognized
it, then allow yourself to understand
you are beyond
it. As soon here's where the clear
action comes in. As soon as you know you
are beyond it and you use your
imagination to picture how you would
prefer to act, all you have to do is act
that way and you will get that result.
Now what do I act upon? Many of you said
here it is plain and simple.
What you call in your life, the feeling
of
excitement is always the thing to act
upon
first. Absolute conviction of
action. You will
effortlessly and
abundantly always automatically be
supported in the doing of that
thing always. There are no
always. There are no
exceptions.
None. Everything else. and that you are
always in the right place at the right
time interacting with exactly all the
individuals. It is appropriate for you
to interact with to represent your
ability service to them in the way they
need to be served and to represent your
ability to be served by them
automatically in the way you need to be
served. You are always in the right
place at the right time. Always.
But always that place and time is
representative of what you believe most
strongly in will be the reality you can
expect. Understand? Remember that you are always
Understand? Remember that you are always
using trust. We aren't telling you to do
something you have never done before. We
are not telling you to do something you
don't know how to do. When we say use
trust, act with conviction on these
things. You have always used trust to
create everything in your reality. Just
depends upon whether you trust in
negativity or
positivity. But you have always used the
mechanism of trust to create your
experiential reality. What you trust in
most is what you
get. Understand? Does that serve you? It
Understand? Does that serve you? It
does. Thank you. Thank you very much. That's universe. Yes. All of
All of
them. Do you mean within your particular
time frame? Again, you can get in touch with
frame? Again, you can get in touch with
them through your meditation if you
wish. Understand? Yes. How long does
this time frame go?
Yeah. But when we talk about your time
frame, we are referring specifically to
the idea, if this is what you ask, about
a cross-section that represents your
present. In other words, you have
counterpart aspects
existing coexisting presently with you in many
coexisting presently with you in many
different dimensions of experience. But
you also
have coexisting aspects in many other
time frames that you might call the past
and the future as well.
Understand? Some of them are simply your
contemporaries and some of them are
not. Is this making some sense to you?
question why this planet here and not the other
why this planet here and not the other
aspects because this is the definition
of who you are here. They feel
themselves to be in that sense focused
on themselves and you are nebulous to
them because that's the definition of
this experience. Some experiences are
aware of more than one aspect of
themselves. But the definition, at least
the definition that has existed in your
physical reality, is to be focused only
as the persona you imagine yourself to
be in any one life at a time. That's the
definition of your physical reality. And
that's why you're only aware of the
particular persona you are at this
moment rather than being aware of many
of the personas you are simultaneously.
But your society now is changing its
view of consciousness. And many of you
are becoming more aware of many of the
other simultaneous personas. You are
understand it has simply been your habit
of definition to create the idea of
yourself to be the only persona therein.
So that's what you get that limitation
of the list. Understand? Does that
answer your question?
Thank you very much. Yes, I would like
to add a question on to that. No, what
are you saying then the more expanded
our consciousness the more likely we are
to be aware of other existences
occurring at the same time? Yes. Not
that you necessarily need all the
details. Otherwise, you would not
necessarily be able to remain focused in
this particular
reality, but you will be more aware of
the fact that you have an infinite
number of connections. But we also have
connections with certain persons or
other personas that we are connected to
at this existence. In other words, yes.
That is what is literally called
counterparts. So that people that we would feel very
So that people that we would feel very
close to or we would the cliches of
soulmates, the cliches of I I feel like
I've known you before or I feel like I
know you. It can be that. It doesn't
have to be that. Sometimes you do not
necessarily or have not necessarily
liked a counterpart of your own
soul. Now that is not something that has
to be that way, but it has happened.
But yes, generally speaking, it can be
for that reason. Although it does not
directly have to be. You can have formed
association with what you simply may
refer to as a another soul in so many
different lifetimes that you're simply
extremely familiar with each other. And
that recognition can come from that as
well. Even though of course on one
fundamental level everyone is the same
one soul. Understand? I do. Does that
answer your question? Yes, it does.
Well, thank you very much, Shann.
Y would that be along the same line of
thinking what you don't like in someone
else maybe what you don't like within
yourself and you fail to correct
recognize it. Correct.
Thank you. Thank you very much. Now,
although you can recognize a preference
and a preference does not necessarily
have to be an invalidational judgment.
In other words, someone may be doing
something very negative and you may
recognize that you don't prefer that in
your life. You don't prefer to exhibit
that in yourself, but you recognize you
have that potential. Doesn't mean you're
actually doing it. Doesn't mean you're
not facing up to the idea that you are
doing it and don't want to look at it
just because you see it in someone else.
The idea usually is is that if it makes
you uncomfortable, however, then there
is some aspect of what they are doing
that strikes a chord within you that you
do need to look at. Whether it's
identical to what they're doing or not
is not always so. What if it makes you
uncomfortable? If you cannot, in other
words, allow them to be who they are
unconditionally, knowing that what they
are is not necessarily what you prefer
to be. If it makes you
uncomfortable, then perhaps that is an
indication that there's something within
yourself you're not looking at.
Understand? Yes. Does that answer the
question sufficient? Thank you. Yes.
Thank you very much. Okay. Yes.
Yes.
In what sense do you mean that?
You wouldn't recognize us as such.
Although we as a society are now in a
transition wherein we are coming from
physicality and becoming
non-physicality, you are going through
your own transformation and becoming
slightly less physical. What we refer to
as fourth density physical, more energy,
less dense material. We are already
lighter bodies and are becoming
non-physical altogether. Although to
some degree you would still translate
our physical form as having a chemical
counterpart that you would recognize as
a physical body. We are of average 5t
tall of your height in counting. White
whitish gray skin coloration very wide
upturned eyes with very enlarged field.
Males have no hair. Females have hair
usually tending to white although there
are some exceptions. We are rather
slender in aspect. In your terminology,
our bodily form would seem to be almost
undeveloped to any great degree. The
idea, if you wish, a similar analogy to
any racial type you are familiar with
upon your world would be Mongolian, but
not exact. Not exact. Similar, but not
exact. Well, that
how do you define your beginning or end
of
your chemical? Oh, it can be measured in
your terminologies of time. We are soul
in that sense like you are. Not
identically are we born into physical
materiality but similarly to you and we
have what you call an ending of the life
but it is under conscious control,
conscious recognition. There is no pain
involved. There is no old age involved.
It is simply that when our purpose in
expressing ourselves as a physical being
is completed, we simply transform back
into non-physicality and the physical
body in that sense reconverts into
energy in a flash. There is no slow
deterioration. Our average lifespan,
although this can fluctuate, simply the
lifespan that suits the general
definition of our society is
approximately what you would call 300 of
your years in
general. Understand? Those answ
there are many different degrees of
physical dimensionality.
We are not in your dimensional plane and
yet in a sense we can express ourselves
with a degree of physicality. One moment
we will scan for the idea that seems to
be closest to your vibrational
frequency. None immediately in your
dimensional frequency. However, in
fourth density frequency to some degree
transitional fourth density fifth, what
you may call a quasi physical reality
various consciousness. It does not
necessarily have an absolutely solid
format. It can express itself similarly
to what you would call a humanoid
form. To some degree, we are what you
would call humanoid. Although if I may,
I could say you are simply
esasaniish. The idea is that they will
mostly be what you would call an energy
construct. They do not have a solid
physical form as we perceive
them. Understand? Does that assist?
Yes. Uh we call you Bashar was described
in the beginning. But what is your real
name on the planet as described? As was
also described to you, the word Bashar
was chosen because we do not have names.
We are telepathic and therefore do not
need in that sense to refer to one
another by what you would call a
linguistic manner. Now, we do have a
remnant language that has not been used
for quite some time. But since
that remnant language went out of use
before I became physical, I never had a
name. Understand?
On our planet, we call it we have a name
that's given to us at birth. Yes. But do
we also have names that correspond to
our higher self or sometimes? Yes.
Spiritual being sometimes. And sometimes
what you call the vibrational name that
is given to you at birth can be
representative of the overall vibration
of the higher self or the oversoul.
Doesn't necessarily have to be but
sometimes it can. Sometimes individual
will go through changes in life wherein
they will recognize that their
vibrational frequency has shifted and
thereby desire to call themselves by a
different name as a representation of
the shift in frequency they now know
they are exhibiting.
Sure. this. Yeah.
A number of us have used for for many
years, many lifetimes, whatever uh for
consciousness raising. We work with
sounds with words perhaps sound. Yes. Of
the old age, the new age. Could you tell
us about meditation for the new age?
Well, the idea simply, especially with
regard to what you call sound, is that
everything is made of
vibration. There is one primal energy.
Out of that energy, all differentiations
of what you call material objects are
created by simply different frequencies
of the primal energy. The only thing
that makes a this different from a that
is the frequency of the vibration of the
primal energy. So what you call sound in
that way is simply one way to manifest
the idea of vibration.
Sound in that sense is very powerful in
being able to
create vibrational matrices or if you
wish bubbles that can
bubbles that can
allow a breakdown to
occur within any particular universal
matrix and allow there to
be that matrix to go back to its pure
state of vibrational resonance and then
recreate the vibration within. in that
matrix and allow anything else to be
solidified out of it. Sound in that
sense is one way to identify to
synchronistically align to
harmonized with the fundamental primal
vibration of creation and therefore
through the idea of sound. You can
transform and
transmute any idea of physiological
reality. That's what the original idea
of incantations is all
about. What you call incantation,
magical incantations, are your society's memory
incantations, are your society's memory
of an earlier
civilization's knowledge of what sound
could actually
do. Understand? Yes. No. Maybe. Yes.
Understand? Yes. No. Maybe. Yes.
Does that serve to answer the question
city?
Sure. You and then you
something totally different. Maybe we
are living in a society whose economy is
based on fossil fuel. Yes.
Is there
any are we close to another kind of
uh economy based on Um,
magnetism or
people economy based on
services in a sense as it used to be on
your society but in a more expanded
way. But yes, in a sense, economy based
on the idea that you will, as we've
received your energy within the next
approximately three to five of your
decades, be using the actual
electromagnetic power of your planet in
a way that will allow power to be
available in unlimited quantities to
anyone, anywhere,
anytime. And you will not have the same
economic system at all. In fact, you
will have nothing that you recognize to
be an economic system even as we do not
because everyone in having that
unlimited power will be able to simply
do what they need to do and will simply
interact with everyone else directly
being of service in the way they wish to
be of service and being served in turn
directly without the middle ground
symbol of what you call material
money. That is our perception of your
energy as a society within the next
three to five of your decades.
Will it come
through war and assassinations or can it
come through more peaceful means? It can
come any way you wish it to. Now there
may be here and there upon your planet a
few of what you might call negative
upsets. Eventually, it is our perception
that within the next 30 of your years,
it will all level out and begin to lay
down a
foundation where it can be done very
peacefully and very quickly. As a
result, there may still be up to the
point you call your year 2011,
2013, some idea of what you call
political skirmishes, economic
skirmishes here and there upon your
planet. Although once again it does not
really have to be that way but that's as
we read the energy of your world now but
it is not necessarily a worldwide thing
in terms of a negative effect. What may
seem to be at first a destruction of
economy will eventually be understood to
simply be a
destructurization of your economy. And
when it is understood as a
destructurization, it will be understood
that it no longer needs to be expressed
as
destructure. All of these things can be
realized can be realized within the next
10 of your years. It is our perception
they will all definitely be realized
within the next
30. Understand? Well, we can always
program for a peaceful transition. Yes.
But the programming of it is not
sufficient. The programming must also be
linked with the action because you live
in a physical world. Therefore,
programming is the first step and then
acting upon it. Doing something in a
positive way to bring it
about. That is what it will
take. Understand? Thank you. Yes. It
seems to be a a very important facet of
of our life right now. Well, they all
are. Yes. But all these things as you
say are coming to a point now because
you are in the transformational age and
there isn't very much time left in which
to experience the transition.
You are accelerating as a society at
such a rate that you only have about 30
years in which to transform your entire
society because your energy is starting
to recristallize again. You have put it
into a limbo state and now within the
next 30 years it is going to
recristallize into whatever format it is
in at that time. it will solidify again
and the acceleration will be indicative
of that reality at that
time. Understand? Yes. Thank you. Thank
you very much.
Oh, um I will expose something to you
about health.
Don't fight much cuz I get in trouble
with you when I do that. All right. Um
not with me with your phone. With
myself. A year and a half ago, uh when I first
A year and a half ago, uh when I first
started coming to the channel, uh I
started working on um trying to explore
and understand exploring and
understanding the excessive weight gain
that I've had.
Uh discovered a lot of allergies were
connected to it to sugar and chocolate
and caffeine and began eliminating all
of that from my diet. And then was able
to stopped bing a lot of wonderful
things happened with my help from my and
was prepared then to go on to the fast
that I've been on for the last five
months and that's very successful a
couple of months ago um I asked the
clinic if I could have something more to
take some of the taste away just vanilla
fasting and they said well you can drink
diet sodas and things made with
chemicals
and I began doing that a little bit at a
time just to change the to diet. Um, a
few later there was discussion at the
clinic that Neutri
Sleep off the same kind of insulin
reaction in some people that chocolate
and all the other real sugars sometimes
sometimes a different reaction because
of what you define the idea to be as an
artificial chemical. Right? And so there
was a part of me that said, "Uh oh, I
better be careful." Uh but anyway, what
started to happen was I began to crave
more and more of these diagrams. For one
a week, you got to one a day and more
and more. And this week I find myself
uh in this very difficult situation
where weight loss is going beautifully,
but I'm starting to become hungry. Yes.
Um I'm now struggle with staying
compatible with your fast. Yes, I feel
strongly that it has to do with the
nucleus that the insulin reaction has.
Remember that your bodily form now
because of your fast is hyper sensitive
to any change
and therefore will react very quickly
especially with whatever portions of the
mass conscious momentum is going to
represent your own fears as well. That
definitely happens. What I need some
help with is uh I am attempting to stop
this. I want I know I know now very
strongly all the doctor doesn't agree
with me and I don't care but I feel very
strongly that I need to get clear of all
that like I did all the sugar. Go ahead.
But I'm having a tough time doing that.
I I just finished a diet soda a few
minutes before I saw right because
there's that craving that's come up.
Yes. That feels very Yes. But remember
remember when you
define yourself at any given
moment as the new person you prefer to
be. If you really start acting like that
person, it will usually only take
approximately three of your days to no
longer sense what the old person sensed
because you literally will not have the
same urges that the old person had
because you will not be the old
person. Literally, again, this is not an
analogy. a person. What you call yourself as a
a person. What you call yourself as a
persona, remember, is an artificial
construct, a projection of your
consciousness. And any change you make
in the definition of that person, even
though you may think you look the same
outwardly, makes you a different person.
Literally. Literally. Now as we have
Literally. Now as we have
discussed we know of societies that when
they make a change in their
personality they outwardly look like a
different person as well. Your society
simply contains the convenience of
maintaining an
exterior example or
projection that seems similar moment to
moment to moment to moment to reinforce
the sense of
continuity that you desire in your
reality. But you are a different person when you
But you are a different person when you
define yourself to be so. So sit down,
relax, create the definition of the
person you desire to be. And remember,
watch the negatives. Don't frame the new
definition in this format. I don't want
to do that. That's a negative. Frame it
in this way. I want this or I am this.
Understand? Not I don't want to be
that. I am this. Not I am not
that. Sit down and redefine the person
you desire now to
be. Feel it with all of your senses.
This is important. Get into it. As you
say, live it. Feel the excitement you
know you would feel if you knew you were
that person. Conviction. Trust. If you
really believed you were now that new
person, you would be excited, wouldn't
you? Yes. Let yourself use all your
senses. Feel it. Feel the level of
frequency change. Feel it vibrate within
you. act like that person and you will no
act like that person and you will no
longer have an urge that the old you
used to have because you will no longer
be literally the old
you understand. Yes.
I as you're speaking realize that the
new me looks very very different and
that I have not been experiencing or
allowing myself to experience excitement
about this new body. Why? Why not?
I discover I'm too busy to go shopping.
I'm too busy.
Very good. You are discovering your
definitions. Very good. Facing your fear will allow
Very good. Facing your fear will allow
you to integrate the reasons why you
have created fear.
I also feel very one thing I feel very
good about is that um the old
would have gone into a real
direct horrifying fact that I was getting
horrifying fact that I was getting
hungry and I would blame a lot of
psychological things on that and listen
to every doctor at the clinic tell me
you were really bad this week for even
thinking that you wanted to eat
something and the new me is saying wait
a second I feel physiological thing
going on. I've experienced sugar thing
before and I know now that it's this new
sweet. Yes. But now that what you have just
Yes. But now that what you have just
called the new you is now going to be an
old you. Understand?
you. Understand?
Because now you don't necessarily need
to be the new you that believes there is
difficulty in transforming the
situation. You will now be a new new
you. A new Yes. Remember, every moment
you are a new you. Every single moment.
Any apparent carryover from the last moment
apparent carryover from the last moment
is your choice to
recreate those things from the last
moment over again in the
new. Understand? Redefine
Understand? Redefine
yourself. As clear as your definition is
will be the persona you will be. And if
you really are that new persona and act
like it and feel it, you will not have
the feelings, the beliefs, the thoughts,
the experiences, the urges of the old
you. They simply won't be
there. So you won't have to worry about
it. It's not a matter of how can I stop.
It's a matter of being someone who
doesn't have those urges. So it's not
even a
question. It won't even come up. Of
course, I don't have to worry about how
to stop. I don't do that. I never
have. Understand?
That is what it really means to be a new
you. You have a new history. You never
have had that difficulty.
Understand? I I understand. I will spend some time
I I understand. I will spend some time
in if you insist.
Why would you need to spend some time? I
I won't.
It's up to you. You don't have to do it
instantly if you don't want to.
I can change the next few seconds. No.
and remember you have just pointed out a
remember you have just pointed out a
technique a process that many of you use
many times and that is you may not allow
yourself to really believe you can
change instantly until you finally get tired
instantly until you finally get tired
enough of the way you don't want to be.
That's just the way some of you do.
You have to get good and sick and tired
of it before you will finally say, "All
right, all right, all right,
had enough."
Always we are in that sense willing to
enjoy interacting with you in any way,
shape or form. And at this time you may
simply enjoy your break. We will
resume contact with you in approximately
what you call 10 of your minutes. Continue. All right.
can be a few different ideas.
One may simply be an individual may have
been brought
up in your life to believe or may not
carry with them from another life a
belief that you do not necessarily fit
in this life. do not necessarily belong
in this life. And the idea of the
allergy may be a rejection reaction to
the natural surrounding of things you
find in this life. The idea that you do
not necessarily fit in smoothly and find
yourself rejecting and being rejected by
major in that sense. All right.
All right.
The I always can represent a hyper
sensitivity to certain things. Now may I
ask you a personal
question? What does the idea of perfume
symbolize to you? What does it
represent? What does it mean? What
meaning have you given to it? Artificiality.
Then that is something you wish to
reject. That is something you wish to
ensure doesn't happen to you. That you
do not express yourself with
artificiality. Now not that this is
necessarily specifically the case or all
the aspects to it, but sometimes as an
example of this analogy, some
individuals will develop an allergic
reaction to things. Once again, as we
talked about to some degree before to
things they do not want to have in their
life and believe for one reason or
another, that if they do not develop an
absolute barrier to it, that they might
somehow when it creep in, that they
might somehow be affected by it, that
they might pick a symbol to represent
all the things they don't want and
develop a symbolic allergic reaction to
it. Now if you recognize that this idea
might represent something that you
simply do not want to become then you do
not necessarily have to create such a
strong rejection symbol for it. You can
simply recognize it is not your
preference. And in recognizing it is not
your preference. You don't have to
preference. You don't have to
necessarily create such a strong
dichotomy between yourself and the
symbol. You can simply know beyond a
shadow without doubt and in all
assurance that if it isn't your
preference, you will not be created in
your reality. You will not become that
thing and you do not need to create such
a
strong insurance through the reaction
that you will not adopt that into your
lifestyle. Understand?
It is not the idea of the perfume itself
but what it represents to
you. And therefore if you simply know
what it means what meaning you have
given the symbol and simply understand
that that idea that essence is not what
you want in your life but you do not
prefer it then simply know because you
have chosen to not prefer it. You will
not express it and you don't have to
worry about expressing it against your
choice. And in that sense, you can allow the
And in that sense, you can allow the
substance or the symbol that has
represented your fear to carry the
physical reaction that it has.
Understand? Once you know what a symbol
means to you, once you understand what
meaning you have given to a symbol, for
no symbol has its own meaning. No symbol
have built-in meaning. They are all
neutral. They don't mean anything. You
give them the meaning you have been
taught to give them.
Once you understand what meaning you
have given it and can extract the
essence out of it in another way, then
that symbol does not have to continue to
create the same idea, the same reaction
in your life. It can transform.
Understand? Yes. Does that serve you?
Yes, it does. Every other 1986 names
ages in your county.
when they died.
Daddy was 87.
No, it is our perception that they are
still experiencing under what you might
call tutelage the idea of getting used to
tutelage the idea of getting used to
non-physical reality and beginning to
explore many different variations on
that. time to time have functioned as
spirit guide for you, as reminder for
you along with many other guides in that
sense. But it is our perception from our
point of view that they mostly have
retained in your terms of thinking of
them the you are used to thinking of
them as
non-physicality. Understand?
All we are saying is that obviously on
some level they have physical aspects
since all lives are simultaneous. But
the way you are used to thinking of
them, the beings you think of them as
have not reincarnated.
Understand? You
You
I have a question about your race. Do
you reproduce? Yes. Similar but not
identical.
I also have a question about your
physiology. Yes.
non now it's mostly a direct energy
absorption there used to be the
consumption of what you call
physiological food much in a similar
manner as you and then it came down to a
very simplified version of this idea in
the following manner out of society out
of its mass
consciousness created what you would
call a natural artificial food it took
the form similar to what you would call
a vegetable form and it was not natural
to the planet to begin with but we
created it with our mentality and in
that sense it was not artificial. It was
natural and then it grew. We ate of this
substance and sustained our society with
all the nutrients it required for quite
some time until now we have grown out of
the meat for any symbolic form of
sustenance and derived the sustenance
directly from life itself. That is
because we are becoming non-physical as
a society as someday you will become.
Does that answer your question?
Yeah. Do you pretend? Yes.
And also how do you
It is similar in the sense that there is
justation what you call the child's car
in the female womb. But the idea of
conception is now more of an energy act.
There is touching. There can be in that
way physiological touching and intimacy.
But the idea is more of an exchange of
energy that allows what you call the
seed within the female to spontaneously
generate and carry all the traits that
it needs to to create the crystallized
physical form that will represent the
projection of consciousness into our
society. Approximate in your terms of
the gestation period will be seven of
your months and not nine.
It is bored without the pain in a
similar fashion easily and we are in
telepathic contact with the child before
it becomes physical during and
after upon the idea you would call
approximately three of your years of
age. The child is sufficiently oriented
into the physical reality they have been
born into and allow in that sense to
simply go about their business
interacting with whatever individuals
they need to to pick up the knowledge
they need to pick
up to be the people they have decided to
be in our society. Since we are always
telepathically connected, no one is ever
in your terms out of sight. All adults
are the parents of all children. All
children are the children of
all. Understand?
Does
that Thank you for
sharing. My wife and I are expecting our
first and I'm wondering either in specific or
and I'm wondering either in specific or
in general terms what spirit or being
with this physical
you can get in touch consciously. Have
you not had conversations in your dream
reality already with what seems to be a
very familiar very familiar
energy? No. No. Right. You have, but
you're not aware of it. Allow yourself
to recognize again that it is not a
child right now, so to speak. It is like
you fully alerted conscious being. Allow
yourself in your dream realities to be
aware of that communication. Get in
touch with it. It is a being you have
had many wives with before in various
ways, various circumstances, taking
turns being each others, different
members of different families and
friends and associates. It is simply now
your turn to be the parents. It's turn
to be the
child. Get in touch with the feeling,
the essence of the agreement you have made.
essence of the agreement you have made.
You can feel think think of the child.
Think of the idea of the child when you
go to sleep and allow yourself to be
open to communication so that when you
wake up, give it three days, you will
then start to retain images, feelings,
aspects of the conversations you are
having so that you can remember the
agreements you made to have this child.
Now, some of this may come in terms of
flashes of what you may recognize as
past lives in which you have been
together before. And therefore, by
getting those images, it will tell you
something of the relationship that you
have had. And sometimes that can tell
you something of the relationship you
will have. Understand?
But that's interesting.
The second question
is related to the child. You're here
sharing your experience with wisdom
strength and hopelessness which to me is
a very spiritual act. Well, it's only a
reflection of your own wisdom and
strength and spirituality.
I perceive that as
being part of my function is in having a
child in this world. Yes, it is one way.
I'm wondering
what the question are the other ways
to do what excites you the most. with
integrity. That's
it. The thing that excites you the most
is the complete fulfillment of the life
you chose to lead. Many of you ask the
question, what is my purpose in life?
What is my meaning? How do I fulfill my
purpose? It is very easily answered.
Remember that even though you are a
reincarnational being, you have never
been this you before and you will never
be this you again. So the fundamental
purpose to this life is to live this
life as fully as you can. And the way
you do that is by doing the things that
excite you the most with integrity.
That's it.
it.
Understand? So having a child is one
way. Any other way that occurs to your
imagination that represents a very
exciting thing to
do. That's the fulfillment of your
purpose. That's how you will be your
best service. But if you're not being
fully yourself, you can't be very much
anyone else, can you? Does that answer
the question?
My question is you're familiar with our
space program. My question
My question
is is there other planets within our
universe? What are you referring to as a
universe? We perceive that your local
may be misunderstood.
Our solar system. Yes. Okay. You are
referring to the planets that orbit your
central star that is a solar system.
Universe is everything everywhere.
Universe. Yes. But you can still call
the whole thing a universe or if you
wish a multiverse.
Then a solar
system. Galaxy made of many solar
systems. Universe made of many galaxies.
Multiverse made of many universes. How
about Milky Way?
Of many solar systems in what you call
Milky Way galaxy that are many many many
many
expressions of life for. Yes. Is there
any that we're obtain or we can reach by
our means now? No. Okay.
except by the means you possess
naturally and that is your
consciousness.
No, understand that there is no other
indigenous life in your dimension on any
other planet in your solar system. There
is life on other planets in your solar
system in other dimensional planes. But
you have to have the quote unquote
technology in order to shift your
dimensional frequency in order to
experience them. But in your dimensional
plane, there is no life that you would
experience as light on any other planet
in your solar system. At least not in
terms of what you would call a sensient
being or
are you talking about the idea of your
attempt at radio
communication or are you talking about
once again your actual space vehicular
program? I guess our the way that we are
able to communicate now with other life
forms and other radio. Yeah, it has not
completely given up. But understand
something in terms of utilizing radio
reception, it is not conducive to
necessarily perceiving many other life
form. First of
all, radio technology in our experience
usually occupies a very brief period in
the history of any technological
civilization. Not every civilization
expresses itself technologically as you
have either. There are many other ways that
either. There are many other ways that
communication can occur without being
radio in nature. And thereby if they do
not radiate as a civilization radio
there will be nothing for you to
receive. Also the amount of
civilizations within what you would call
the immediate neighborhood of
stars. Many of them are either not yet
at the point where they have radio
technology nor is that an assurance that
they will develop it. And the majority
of them are already beyond radio
technology.
you are not sending anymore on that
frequency that you are listening
on. So in a sense you exist for lack of
a better term in a radio desert.
Now, if not really because if you begin
to realize that the way you will tap
into an absolute cacophony of
communication is by using your minds,
you will understand that the vast
majority of consciousness we are in
touch with communicate telepathically.
And when your scientists begin to add
consciousness into their equations, they
will begin to receive the communications
even as communication is being received
through the present
channel. Many of you now think that this
is a very esoteric form of communication
if you believe that it is real at all.
But what you are perceiving is actually
the standard methodology of
communication because human I will say
or any living being is the best receiver
and sender there already is. So why not
use it? The mind is infinite in that
way. Why not use the wavelengths that
already are connected
everywhere? Those of consciousness
itself. That is how the vast majority of
civilizations we are aware of actually
communicate. Understand? Yes. I think
that we're searching more for a physical
contact. Yes. And in a sense you will
get it. But the idea will go hand in
hand usually with an understanding of
consciousness and basically for the
following reason. Since every single
civilization really exists on its own
frequency band, no two civilizations
actually ever meet or are capable of
meeting each other in what seems to be a
face-toface encounter until those
civilizations match
frequency and therefore that is an act
of
consciousness. Understand? Mhm.
So I I don't think I don't know if this
is true. I don't foresee it happening in
my lifetime. Oh yes, very likely again
within the next 30 of your years. Now do
understand something. Your society has
already been physically contacted by
many of us. Correct? Just very
sporadically for now. And do remember
your governments are very very very well
aware of our existence. deny it. Yes.
Because of what you have created your
government structure to
be. Because of what our societies
represent to the way of thinking you
have created your society to be. The
majority of your society does not want
interaction with what you think we
represent because it would mean an
absolute and abrupt change of almost
everything. You
know, many of you are simply not ready
for that. However, you are accelerating
at a very very very great pace and as we
perceive your energy now within
approximately the next three decades
that will be
sufficient and we will be interacting
very blatantly with you.
Is there any way that I myself can
interact with another?
It is possible that any of you can. But
first be very clear about the
idea of who you are, why you want
that because it will demand an equality
of you. Secondly, one of the easiest
ways if you wish that interaction in a
blatant way on an individual level is to be
way on an individual level is to be
somewhere alone.
out where you can be
reached. Understand? Yes. Conducive to
this is being somewhere out in the
middle of one of your deserts. Are you
like saying that I can go out there and
like meditate to somebody? Yes. It is
far more likely that you will be met
that way than remaining in what you
would call a crowded city.
Understand many of you are under the
notion that it is
extremely simple for us to simply pop in
and out where we
wish. It can be done, but it is still
easier to make contact with someone when
they're not surrounded by an entire city
of people who do not necessarily need
that contact. Understand?
contact. Understand?
So being alone obviously is more
conducive. It's not that it guarantees
it, but it is more conducive.
Yeah.
Kind of [\h__\h] the same subject about
the universe or or space.
We've gone as far as the theory of
relativity. Yes. We still don't know.
You have gone farther than that. But but
the limits are still not defined in in
human physics or or science. Not all of
them. No. You know, we're going into the
closed cold space and and all all
theories. But
why aren't we sure that we our our
consciousness is not opening up to
understand in a sense? Correct. You are
simply limited by older definitions that
you have not yet worked your way
through. Can you describe the real
physical or level of the universe as as it exists
or level of the universe as as it exists
or well to some degree although of
course that will be somewhat of an
analogy. Our
perception is that it is all right here
right now within you. It is holographic
in nature. That simply means that any
one point contains the totality of the
whole. To put it on another level,
traveling in outer space is actually
traveling within. It is understanding the
within. It is understanding the
following
idea. Everything is the same one
Everything is the same one
thing manifesting itself in all the
multitudinous multi-dimensional ways it
simultaneously can. So experiencing anything any
can. So experiencing anything any
portion of the whole is a matter of
adjusting your frequency to that portion
and then you will experience that
portion right here where you
are understand.
Yes. Does that explain it to some
degree? Yes. So it's basically we have
to expand our consciousness first. Yes.
Yes. I mean you can do it
physiologically as you have been doing
it but because your exploration if it
remains in the physiological realm of
time and space will then by definition
take more
time to expand the consciousness to
include space and time within it will
mean you can traverse the idea of space
and time in an
instant because distance is only as you
define it to be yes in a sense what you
call the speed of light is the
definitional barrier of one particular
universal frame of reference but that
doesn't mean you can't go around
it because it is only the definition of
one universal frame of
reference. It is a limit within that
universe. But you can always enter
another idea in a sense picking yourself up out
idea in a sense picking yourself up out
of the universe and redepositing
yourself anywhere else in it without
necessarily truly having traveled in
that universe to get there. So it's not
like you're really violating the speed
of light in a sense you're avoiding the
issue altogether. Understand? Yes. brings a
altogether. Understand? Yes. brings a
question of how yes in in your
definition the expanding and and
compression of the universe yes
sical basis how how do you define
that again it goes back to the fact that
everything is vibration everything is
vibration let's put it this way if you
have an
object in one location and you measure
in every way shape and form that you can
the vibrational signature of that
object that same object will have a
slightly different vibrational signature
in this
location. Therefore to us the idea of
location is not a space and time that
the object exists
within. Location is one of the
vibrational properties of the object
itself. It is one of the vibrational
definitions of the object itself. If you
can isolate that vibrational variable in
the vibration equation, the whole object
is and replace that vibrational variable
with one that represents the vibration
of a location somewhere else. Then the
object by definition will simply have to
cease existing at one spot and take up
resonance at the other spot. You have
imposed the vibrational location upon
it. Understand? Yes. Does that explain
the issue? It is a matter of redefining
the self. And when you redefine the self
that completely, you must also
automatically redefine the where and the
when of you because that's a part of the
overall definition that you are. It's
not a space you actually exist in. Where
and when you are. Location in time and
space is actually a part of the
definition you are. So change that
definition and you change your location
in time and space. That's how you expand
quote unquote and collapse the universe.
You're simply redefining what it is to
you or I shall say perhaps more
precisely what the universe is within
you. Did our past civilizations know about
Did our past civilizations know about
this? Some past civilizations on your
planet did. Yes.
In
fact, a
few of what you call UFO sightings are
actually from civilizations on your own
planet, both past and future.
Understand? No.
Take it as I have said it.
Some of what you call UFO sightings,
understand spacecraft that you may see
in the sky are not from other planets.
They are from your own planet. From
civilizations in the past that have
transcended time or civilizations in
your own future that have transcended
time. Where do they come from? Earth. I
mean, on our planet, where where are
they hiding?
They're not hiding.
They are in what you call your future.
Understand? Or your past. They're
transcending time. They are transcending
through time. That's a good that's a
good trick. It is a very simple thing to
do when you understand that time is
within you.
Understand? Yes.
Does that satisfy the question?
Just bring more questions. Yes.
Yes.
I have a side of me that delights in
hearing you and I have another side of
me that I wish wouldn't be listening to
you because it gets all crazy with
ideas. All crazy with ideas.
What's wrong with being crazy with
ideas? Well, I am crazy with ideas
myself. I enjoy being crazy with ideas. Yes, I
I enjoy being crazy with ideas. Yes, I
do too. Unfortunately, why
unfortunately? Um I have you know my
life is is wonderful as everything has
come together so beautifully. Well thank
you. Yes. Then why is it unfortunate?
Because when I hear you talk about all
the possibilities that exist and then we
can have whichever ones we want and
energy into them. Yes. Then then I go
crazy imagining all these exciting
ideas. Yes. So, and uh
do the one you are capable of doing.
Well, but then I started telling myself
I should be doing these others
because they're more expanded. They
serve people better. They my my my my I
have a very simple formula for you.
It begins with a
question. Answer the question any way
you wish. Your answer will not be wrong,
but I am looking for a specific
answer. Some of you know this, so be
quiet. What is the most important thing
of all?
Serving consciousness. You know, raising
consciousness. Correct. But not the
answer I seek. Would you like to give
another answer?
What is the most important thing of all?
Raising my consciousness. Correct. But
not the answer I seek. Would you like
one more
opportunity? I give you three.
What is the most important thing of all?
What I want to do. Correct. But not the
answer I see. Repeat after me.
What is the most important thing of all?
The thing the thing I am I am doing
doing now. Now
that's it. Whatever it is you are doing in your
it. Whatever it is you are doing in your
life right now is the thing you need to
be doing.
When you fully extract from the now
whatever it is you need to get out of
the now you are living in that will
accelerate your ability to create the
next more expanded now. So by all means
examine all the probable realities.
That's what your imagination is for. But
remember that whatever it is you are
doing now is the most important thing of
all. And if you do it fully, that's what
will most quickly get you into the
circumstance to do any and all of the
other things you have
imagined. Living in the present is where
you belong.
That's what paradoxically accelerates
your ability to have any other kind of
reality you desire. But only when you
don't deny that what you're doing now is
what you need to be doing. Understand?
That's when I'm most happy. Yes. When I
accept that. Yes. I've been writing
letters to myself. Not a use for my
computer. Write letters to myself from the point
Write letters to myself from the point
of view of of my uh higher self. Yes.
Very good. And so I write to Ron and I
explain to him how it is. Very good. Do
you know what you have done?
I'll tell
you. You have in a sense predated
symbolically the whole idea that your
society will discover about when it
utilizes quote unquote
invents. the notion you have called
artificially intelligent
computers. What you will discover in
creating these artificially intelligent
computers is that you will simply have
created a mechanical
symbol through which you will allow
yourself to communicate with your higher
self. That's what will be talking to you
through the computers.
Understand? Mhm. So you have in a sense
created that scenario already for
yourself to some degree predating the
idea of your artificially intelligent
computer. The idea again remember is in the
The idea again remember is in the
now in living in the now to simply at
any given moment do the thing that
excites you the most that you are
capable of doing something about with
integrity and it will automatically lead
you to every other thing you will ever
do that excites you because excitement
is a thread. It is connected to all
other excitement and you will miss out
on none of it. You don't have to be in
such a rush. You don't have to be
scanned. If something really excites you
and represents the life you truly have
created, you will find a time to do it
because you create your own destiny and
you cannot miss a date with destiny by
definition. So there is no rush. have
all the time in creation because you
create all the
time. Relax. Live in the now and do the
thing you can do that excites you the
most. It will lead you into the
capability to do whatever else will come
along that will represent your expanded
idea of what then at that point is
exciting you. Understand? I need that.
Well, thank you.
Not about me. My my daughter just went
with us to the ashram that we went to
for a week. Yes. And uh had a real um
spiritual awakening. I mean just
absolutely alive and excited about
herself as she has had many lives in the
area you call India.
Oh that's where she's going. She's going
over there now for a she will discover
many things that are familiar. Oh good.
But you know what she told us today was
interesting because she went through a
period where she thought she was really
crazy because she was frightened. And I
wonder where she got the idea of being
crazy. Um
Um
I don't know. I I think because she was
so frightened of all Yes.
Yeah. She did not. Nor did we. All
right. And now she says, "I'm
experiencing exactly the same thing, but
has this new framework, which is that
she's spiritually awakened and bounded
on to all the synchronicities and yes,
pointing them all out, but she's she's
so loose. She seems so uh loosely
wrapped that she will balance out. I
have concern a little concern about how
she'll handle the ash in the
all. It will balance out. Remember, what
she has going for there is a familiarity
with the area.
She will be at home. And you know that
when you're in your own home, you can be
as crazy as you want and you're still
safe. Understand? I sure am. So simply
Understand? I sure am. So simply
understand that she is in her own home
in that area. She will balance out.
Trust, trust, trust. Yes.
Female. Bashar. Um, yeah. I have two
questions. One is that u my sister and
brother-in-law went down in a private
plane last year and um it took six
months for them to be found. Oh, what?
And they were the plane was found. They
were they were killed on impact. Um it's
been very unsettling for me in thinking
of that. It was so abrupt and yet they
were found only 3 minutes away from
their home and it was just strange the
whole place. Is there anything you can
tell me about that? May I ask you a
question? Sure.
If as obviously they did on one level or
another decide that that was the timing
to end the physical life and become
non-physical, would you prefer that they
had lingered? Would I have prefer that
they had lingered? Yes. In other words,
would you prefer that the death was slow
and or painful? No. All right.
Allow the idea to sink in. That everyone
has chosen the timing of the death and
that individuals who many times create that
individuals who many times create that
particular form of death do so because
in your terminology it is
rapid and because at the time in a sense
they are doing something they love to
do. Understand? Yes. And
therefore, I shall say it this way, they
go out in
style. They go out
flying. I do not mean to be making a
joke. You understand? I do. It is simply
that everyone has the
timing already in that sense set. Not
necessarily the time, but the timing.
Therefore, individuals who simply know when their
individuals who simply know when their
timing is through in that sense in the
physical plane and who have no need to experience
plane and who have no need to experience
the
lessons and
ideas of those methodologies which would
cause lingering or cause pain will
simply be quick and efficient and get on
with. So then it was an appropriate ending
So then it was an appropriate ending
rather than an interruption. There are
no interruptions. No accidents.
None. Never. Never accident. Suicide.
Suicide to some degree. What you call
conscious suicide to some degree represents what
suicide to some degree represents what
might be at best termed a postponement.
But usually in what you call
99.9% of those cases once having
returned to the state of non-physicality
in which they originated the choice of
that life they will project themselves
right back into physical materiality
born all over again into exactly the
same circumstances in order to face it and
circumstances in order to face it and
understand that there is no running from
it and that they do not have to create
negativity in the life but they can
create the life that they prefer.
Suicide in that sense may be considered
to some degree the only exception to
what we have said. But even then it
still concerns a part of the learning
experience of the soul and does not
necessarily have to be seen as an actual
interruption but may be simply more of a
diversion. Understand? Yes, we do.
Because ultimately it will be worked
out whether it takes one, two,
three or a large number of lives. It
will be worked
out. But in the overall sense, no, there
are no accidents.
No. Thank you. I have I have one more
Thank you. I have I have one more
question too. If one if one is afraid of
encountering an extraterrestrial Yes.
um and one is not clear about their
intent or doesn't have a trust, would it
be very likely that someone would
approach um someone who had that kind of fear or
um someone who had that kind of fear or
that kind of distrust? No.
Now, sometimes you will find that some
of the contacts between members of your
society and members of extraterrestrial
society will bring up a great deal of
fear within the members of your society.
However, let's look at it this way and
put it in relative
perspective. Anything you are aware of
that we have labeled the fear that may
come up in one of the members of your
society in such an interaction will
usually actually
represent a very small amount of fear
that might remain in the individual. No
matter how much fear that individual may
seem to be exhibiting, that contact is
usually not undertaken
unless there is actually not a great
deal of fear in that individual or that
on some level they will be able to
assimilate it at some point in their
lives which means they have actually
even though they do not think it worked
out much of that fear already.
Understand? Yeah. Well, thank you very
much. for sure you why have we created
uh the disease AIDS on our planet and do
you foresee a cure in the near future?
In a sense there can be but remember
this no matter what you call a
physiological cure it will always only
be representative of the willingness to
heal yourselves within your
consciousness. Now in general this will
be brief because we have talked about
this many times and the information is
available on some of the other tapes
that we have created with you. However,
in general that disease represents the
inability or unwillingness of your
society to blend and balance the male
and the female energies within every
female and male. It is a fear of
intimacy in a sense. That blending is
now going on in your society in an
enforced way through the recognition and
creation of that
disease for it has dropped all your
immunity. And now you must begin to
interact as one
society. If you will not allow joy and
ecstasy to bind you, then you will allow
fear to bring you together. And that to
some degree is what you are doing. When
you start learning to blend and balance
the polarities, the seeming
dichotoies of positive and negative
within each and every being, of maleness
and femaleness within each and every
being, which does not mean you will not
express yourself as a male or a female.
But the idea of the blending of the
energy within each and every person, the
validation of each and every person will
allow there to be a strengthening of
society. To some degree, it also goes
hand inhand with the definition you have
given to
vulnerability. For most of you see the
word vulnerability as meaning weakness,
the dropping of value. When in fact
vulnerability can be defined as a
complete and total openness and complete
and total trust, a connection into the
infinite of all that is. And a
connection into all that is is absolute
and total
power. Not. So you are examining all these
Not. So you are examining all these
things at a very accelerated pace with
the creation of that disease. Now, it is
our perception that there can be what
you would call a symbolically
representative physiological cure within
what you call 6 to 18 of your
months. But again, it will generally be
representative of your willingness to
blend the idea in your consciousness
first. Almost any
disease can be quote unquote cured if
the individual's belief system believes
that it will work. Whatever that cure
may be, no cure will work if the belief
system won't buy it. Understand? Oh,
definitely. Also, one of the ways that
will almost work for almost any disease
because it is symbolically
representative of a foundation belief
many of you understand and are connected
into is the placing of an individual in
a strong pulsing electromagnetic field
operating at approximately 7 and 12
cycles per second. It will align you
with the earth frequency, crystallize
you. And in being so balanced and so
centered, almost no notion of imbalance
or disease is capable of existing when
you are aligned with the total
electromagnetic field of your planet
with the natural frequency of your room.
Understand? Yes. Thank you. Michelle,
would that be like being in a pyramid or
something like that? Some It can be.
Yes. Even some of what you call your
medical device magnetic resonance imaging
device magnetic resonance imaging
scanner has the ability to be tuned to
not only diagnose but to
cure. Some of you are just beginning to
recognize this and or that electrical
pulses on very mild amperage can be sent
through your body to blend and balance
the electrical potential in your body
and in a sense bring it back to a
centered state of polarity balance.
Accept some of these cures more than
others. And perhaps for them these cures will
And perhaps for them these cures will
work and perhaps for other cultures it
will take some
time. Does that assist?
Yes. There's a machine called the acu
scope. Is that noted to be a good source
of electrical impulses to feel? Define.
Um can you define the smoke? It reads,
it's like a computer. It read you, it
has two probes and you put the probe on
the touching the skin to the area that's
in pain and it feeds information into
the computer base about how the dead
cells in that area and then it
probes placed in that area or is one
slightly removed into an area that would
represent healthy tissue?
I think
okay I think goes on the healthy part
one on the healthy one yeah one healthy
one on on the area that's in pain then
that can be indicative of reading the
electrical imbalance of the body and a
small trickle
of positive charged electricity in the
area of the damaged tissue can create a
rebalance yes it can be utilized that way
yes it can be utilized that way
and I I also have a bed that has magnets
in it. It can be aligning but again
mostly it will depend upon the belief
system of the individual. Now listen the
idea of magnetic alignment and crystal
and alignment either using the idea of
magnets and or crystals which sometimes
can be used in that way will accelerate
the blending and integration of an
individual's consciousness. Sometimes, I
do not mean to scare you. Sometimes if
an individual is focused on the idea of
negative belief, it might accelerate
those as well to get them to face their
fears and integrate it. Understand? Yes.
It depends on how the individual is
focused when they are in the magnetic
field. Generally, it will make a move toward a
Generally, it will make a move toward a
positive alignment. But the move toward
positive alignment may of necessity
carry the individual through their fears
in order to get
there. Because the only way you can
balance is by going through what you
fear, not avoiding it. Understand? Yes.
Which doesn't mean you have to
experience the negativity. It simply
means facing the reason you have created
a fearful idea.
But the magnets also create an
ionization of the blood in the system.
Sometimes sometimes not always people
depend upon their alignment, their
strength, their resonant capabilities,
their purity and many other factors.
Does that s Yes. How does one test it
though in that capacity? There are many
various ways and for now they will be
too long to ruin.
Okay. you. Thank you. Um, a couple months ago,
you. Thank you. Um, a couple months ago,
my husband and I decided to buy a house
closer to San Francisco because he
commutes and the idea was exciting and
we really felt like it was following our
excitement. Yes. Well, the whole damn
thing is just falling apart. In the
meantime, we haven't found a house. We
couldn't find a location. We got
inundated with ants in the house with
ants and our cash flow. [Music]
[Music]
Not necessarily. However, remember this.
If we're talking about totally trusting
the reality you get as a part of the
path and not an interruption in it, then
you will recognize that many times
certain circumstances that are exciting
at first are exciting not because they
have to be carried through, but they are
excited because it leads you in the
direction you need to
go. You don't necessarily have to create
the expectation that just because it
excites you at first means that it must
complete itself.
It is that expectation which can be
causing you to not see the path it is
creating for you as a path and instead
is allowing you to see it as a
divergence or an
interruption. In other words, the
unexpected has just as much right to
belong in your life as what you expect.
And very often the unexpected is mostly
what you will get. But if you trust that
the unexpected is representative of the
path, you will then allow yourself to
see how it fits and will not
automatically at first label it to be an
interruption that has no business being
in your life.
That is what trust and conviction is all
about. If you know that you are following your
If you know that you are following your
excitement, then by definition, you must
assume that however it manifests is the
way it needs
to to get you to look at what you need
to look
at at that moment. The sooner you are
willing to accept that it is a part of
your life and get out of what you need,
the sooner you can get on with what you
prefer. Understand? I think so. So
essentially what you're saying is like
the idea of buying the house was
something to get us moving in some
direction but not necessarily it may
play out but it doesn't necessarily have
to. The idea is to
The idea is to
understand let's say to approach it with
more of a curiosity and a
fascination to be excited by the
unexpected to say well this did not go
the way we expected. How fascinating.
What does this mean? Why do you suppose
it did go this way? Now, I know beyond a
shadow of a doubt, it must represent a
positive direction because that's the
choice. I am a positive being. I may not
know exactly how it fits, but I know it
fits. If you maintain that attitude,
then you will see very quickly how it
fits. But if you automatically react,
this doesn't
fit, then you will not give yourself a
chance to see how it could have fit. I
saw how I I did that with everything
except the ants. I didn't see how
[Music] what do they represent to you?
what do they represent to you?
I don't know. What meaning do you give
them? Well, think about it. Chaotic
little things. chaotic,
busy, right? So, they seem to be
disorganized. Yes, they did seem to be
disorganized. Sometimes they're very
organized. You know, they follow each
other, you know, on my kitchen counter.
They're just all over the place. And I
studied them to see where they were
coming from, and they just came from
everywhere. There's no organization there.
There's no organization there.
Now, in any way, shape, or form, do you
believe that represents how you think of
yourself? [Laughter]
I suppose I should take that as
we are very happy you are capable of
having such a wonderful
[Laughter] time. Yes.
time. Yes.
Are you beginning to get the picture? All
All
right. Thank you for enjoying
self-discovery.
What kind of contact exactly do you have
with members of governments like in the
United States, Great Britain,
States, Great Britain,
France, Russia?
Have you made yourself uh clearly u
members of other
civilizations have actually had
face-to-face communication with many
members of many governments on your
planet? Your
governments do understand but they are
afraid. And to some degree there is also
on some levels a mutual
consent to some degree between some
members of your government and members
of our association of worlds as to the
rate of exposure of our existence that
would be comfortable for your world.
The more you are all willing, not in an
attacking way, not in an accusatory way,
but in a loving, equal, sharing, excited
way to allow your governments to know
you are ready to know we
exist, then the information can be
brought to the center. The sooner you
all realize you are your governments and
open up lines of communication between
what you call your public and your
governments on this
issue, then the more you can allow your
governments to understand there will not
be panic. There will not be chaos. They
will not lose their power but will gain
self-empowerment along with all of you
in an equal
way. Understand?
Yes. Uh this is uh it's important
uh to know that there have been those
contacts there have been
because then it's um it's a big uh help
for maintaining peace on earth if those
the members of those governments know
that you do exist that you have a
superior Oh one moment one
moment it is precisely Precisely for
that reason that we usually keep
reason that we usually keep
ourselves
unobtrusive because the decision to
create peace on your
planet is not reliant on whether you
know we
exist. It must be reliant on whether you
choose peace or not. The decision must
be yours without our direct influence on
you. For it is your planet. It is your
For it is your planet. It is your
world. It is not up to us to decide what
you will and won't do with it
directly. So the idea must not be based
on whether we exist or not. The idea
must be based on whether you desire
peace for yourselves or not. That is why
we are to some degree remaining
relatively unobtrusive.
So that we will not be the reason you
choose peace. So that you will choose
peace because that's what you prefer.
Because that is what you want to work.
Uh are you not worried about uh the
possibility of nuclear war?
No. Now I will share this with you.
Now I will share this with you.
Only now at this timing are we allowed
to share this with you. Because as a
society, it is our perception that as of
at least 10 of your years ago, even
though this decision may still be
unconscious for most of you, as a
society, you have already decided not to
annihilate yourselves by nuclear war.
That is our perception of your energy.
And so we can at this time share with
you that the one
exception to the idea of our direct
influence within you and your
society now that you have made the
decision by yourselves is that you never
would have been allowed to have a
nuclear war.
war.
Because even though it is your world,
and you are certainly welcome to destroy
yourselves utterly if you
wish, the one reason it would not be
allowed to be done by nuclear
annihilation is because it wouldn't
remain in your own backyard, so to
speak. It would upset the fabric of
interdimensional space and time and
affect other civilizations other than
your own. And that is not allowed. You
may destroy your civilization in any
way, shape, or form you wish. other than
a way that will directly affect other
civilizations that have nothing directly
to do with you, which nuclear
annihilation would
do. Therefore, that type of
imbalance would not have been allowed.
Now your
government was given a few
demonstrations now and
then to paint some of the
picture that it would not be possible.
This was done when it was already
understood that enough momentum existed
in your society's consciousness to
already choose to not annihilate
yourselves that way anyway.
It was simply reinforced with a
demonstration in what you call
approximately your late
190060s. There was demonstration over
what you call a
few missile
bases. sightings of many of the craft of
the Association of Worms over your
missile bases. When those craft left the area
bases. When those craft left the area
and your military personnel inspected
the missiles, they found that all of
what you call the launch codes have been
erased electromagnetically and made
electromagnetically and made
dysfunctional.
They understood then and
there that simply had anyone had the
notion to push what you call the
button, it wouldn't have
worked. But we have the capability of
electromagnetically suppressing any
electronic activity at all anywhere.
Now again these things can be revealed
at this time only because as a world you
have already decided you will not
destroy yourself. Anything you are now
yourself. Anything you are now
recognizing as an escalation of
skirmishes and apparent violence upon
your world in a sense is an acceleration
bringing things that were formerly
hidden to the surface. Getting it all
out of your system because in a sense
you now know it's safe to do so because
it will not lead to total destruction.
You are going through the last remnants
and vestigages
of is basically all a
show because they are still posturing
out of fear because they still do not
want to lose what they perceive to be
your confidence in them.
But to some degree it has been on some
levels choreographed. For understand, if
you really stop and think about
it, if you did have such a war, it
certainly would not be to the advantage
of anyone. Your governments know
this. And there are many areas in which
many of what appear to be enemy
governments are actually working
together that your public is simply
unaware of.
understand. Yes. It's very good to know
that this is all coming to light and
again within what you call the next
three of your
decades in a sense this will all be
behind you.
But you will but the uh
extraterrestrials will help which you
have said in the 60s they this is now
the way we are helping right through
this means of channeling. Yes. For it
gives you the opportunity to hear and
discuss perspectives and ideas that you
might desire might desire to
choose to manifest upon your
world. But we are doing it in a way that
does not force you to believe. You have
to choose it. Because there is no way
right now to prove that we are who we
say we are. Because we do not want you
to believe anything we say just because
we say it. We want you to believe it
because you choose to.
That is how we are helping you now to
remember your own
power to look to us to be your saviors
because you don't need
savior and we will not save you from
anything else at this
point. Understand?
Thank you. Yes. Yes. Could you uh define
for me the relationship
between soul consciousness and mind?
It is only a definitional one for they
are all really simply different
expressions of the same one
consciousness. Consciousness is simply
the awareness that you are the primal
creation that you are the existence
itself that is aware of itself. That is
consciousness existence itself.
Soul and mind are differentiations of
convenience in a sense projections of
consciousness. Soul can be simply called
the non-physical aspects of being
non-physical aspects. They can be as
broad or as focused as you desire them
to be. Anywhere from a collective idea
down to a singular idea. Mind is
generally the
intersection let us say for convenience
sake of consciousness in physiological
reality. The electromagnetic field the
intersection of consciousness with the
electromagnetic field creates mentality
or mind. Mind is the expression of
consciousness in physical
terms. Understand? Yes. But all these
things are simply definitional aspects
of the one consciousness that you
are. Different frequencies, different
methods of expressing the self,
different ideas of the
self. In other words,
remember your spirit does not really
exist inside your body. Your body is
your spirit in physical terms. Your
consciousness does not really exist
inside your body. More precisely, your
body exists within your consciousness
and so does your spirit and so does your
soul. They are all ideas of
yourself. Understand? Yes. Thank you.
Thank you. Yes. Have any civilizations
destroy themselves? Oh
yes. Oh yes. And there was also one in
your own solar
system referred to in ancient
terminology as
Malbeck. It occupied the orbit between
what you now call your Mars and your
Jupiter and is now represented by your
asteroid belt.
From that destruction, many incarnations
upon Earth came from and much of the
what you would call negative
confusion has
resulted for in creating such an
imbalance of destruction. Then that was
to some degree responsible for a lot of
the negativity and imbalance that your
society on earth has also experienced
for many tens of thousands of years. The
continuation of that momentum from that
destruction took a while for many of you
to reincarnationally work through.
In your terminology, it was very very
long ago and we were at that time not
ago and we were at that time not
involved to the level that we are now.
Understand? Yes.
Yes.
Question that you say are are involved
in helping Earth. Yes. Is there general
agreement or consensus as far as
peacekeeping for whatever the idea is
amongst all these civilizations that are
coming? Generally, yes. And are other
worlds being helped also? Oh yes yes yes
yes. I interact with many worlds not
just Europe. And by no means to use a
colloquial phrase, and I do not mean to
be judgmental or invalidational to any
world at all by using this phrase, but
by no means are you on the bottom of
what you call your token
pole. There are many worlds that are
steeped in many different degrees of
limitation, many different degrees of
negativity. You are far closer to an expression of
You are far closer to an expression of
ecstasy on your world than many of you
may think. Remember that great
transformation is not the product of
mediocrity. Use what we have used as a
rubber band analogy many times. You can
take one of your rubber bands and pull
it back very far in your negativity.
Once you finally let go, that is an
indication of how fast and far you will
snap into the positive side. You are
right on the threshold of letting go.
The same energy and momentum that you
have used to generate the negativity,
the focus of limitation on your world
will now snap into creating a positive
alignment. And that will push you very
far, very fast. That is why there's a
high degree of interest in your plan at
this time because your world can in a sense
time because your world can in a sense
within a relatively short period of time
become one of the strongest members of
the association of worlds and do the
greatest service to many other worlds.
Because of the experience of negativity
that you have
had, you will be able to assist many
other worlds in the negativity they may
be
experiencing. We have in the association
a little nickname for all of you. And it
is not meant to be derogatory. In fact,
if you examine it the way we mean it in
a positive sense, you will understand
how we have applied it to you. You are
called masters of liberty.
Your world, your
earth is one of the most highly focused
worlds we have ever discovered within
its limitation. And therefore, you will be
limitation. And therefore, you will be
very well-rounded in your experience in
helping other worlds through there. In
other words, let me put it this way, and
again, not meaning to be
derogatory, but the degree to which
Earth has experienced negativity will
make almost any other world you come
across that you will help in your own
good timing seem like child's place.
How will we reach them? As your own
consciousness expands and your
technology develops along lines similar
to ours, you will in time, relatively a
very short period of time, be the UFOs
of other civilizations.
Now, as we perceive your energy, now the
most likely candidate for another
planetary system that your world will
begin to interact with in a similar
manner to the way we are assisting you
now will be a civilization on a planet
orbiting what you call in your
nomenclature the Barnard star.
They are relatively speaking, if you
wish, some sort of a chronological
historical analogy, somewhere
approximating right now in their
civilization where you were in what you
call your Renaissance
era. By the time you are traveling in
space and assisting other worlds, they
will have arrived at a point
approximating where you are now. And
they will be ready to receive the
understanding that there are other
civilizations in creation. And you will
be one of the first
ambassadors even as we are ambassadors
to your world. Now
we'll play your part. How do you
perceive us right now as you're coming
through Daryl? How do you perceive us
sitting here? I perceive you as a
relationship, relationships to each
other. I perceive
individuality as defined by all of the
connections it is to everything else. I
perceive patterns of energy, patterns of
momentum, patterns of likehood, patterns
of intention.
I also perceive you as living
light as joyful
children as wise
masters. That is how we proceed.
So you basically are feeling the energy.
You're seeing the energy not the form of
it is an orchestration
and in a sense we are playing conductor.
Understand? Yes. Thank you. Thank you.
You and then
you why why have you chosen English as a
medium for I have not I am not speaking
your language. The channel is programmed
with English. Other channels around your
planet in other cultures will allow
their own language to come through in
the translation of our thoughts. And we
are channeling through many more
channels than the one present before you
now. But we are not speaking your
language at all. It is simply that
whatever language the translation device
the body of the channel is programmed
with will be the language you hear it
in. Understand? Will this channel allow
you to speak your world language? That
to some degree can be done because there
is no expectation on the part of the
channel as to what it might or might not
sound like. And because it is my quote
unquote natural language to some degree
it can be done. Could we can
I love you?
Can you say it again?
Do you sing? Yes.
Or in that way
directly. It is more of what you simply
call a vibrational channel. You are
familiar with some of these
ideas. Now another phrase may simply
bear the experience of one is the
experience of all.
If you wish to
shimmy Kashimi roll shimok
seal 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 S
10 S
that planet you were referring to that
became an astereroid because it was
destroyed. Malbec. Yes. You call it
Maldc. Maldc. Is there not another name
for it like Lucifer?
It is an old nomenclature. Yes. Okay.
There are also many other variations of
that terminology. Some in your ancient
terminology. Some in your ancient
society have referred to it as Marduk
as well as Mald. These are all ancient
Roman clatures in your own tongue, not
ours. and many of his
and many of his
inhabitants reincarnated on Earth. Yes.
In southern Russia and what is now Iran
and the Middle East. All all over your
planet. No one specific
local all over your world. Are any of us
here understand that at this timing that
has been so much blending and so much
transforming that it would be just as
valid to say that all of you are as none
of you
are. You all now are on the threshold of
a completely new vibration of balancing
that polarity. So in that sense you all
might as well be since you're all
basically moving in the same direction
now. You're all matched in frequency.
You are all now of
Earth and you all have connections to
everywhere else. But basically, yes, all of
else. But basically, yes, all of
you. Would we be as the same in our
relationship with one another as the
Atlantans may have been on this
planet? You are becoming as it was in
early Analanti. Much of the let us say
Analanti. Much of the let us say
incarnation of negativity also took
place during midalanteanian times and
was responsible to some degree for the
diversification of polarity which caused
its destruction. A repetition of the
malbeck scenario on
earth. Now you're at the end of that
cycle of
negativity begun approximately 30 of
your thousand years ago which culminated
in the destruction of Atlantis
approximately 12,000 of your years
ago. You are all in that sense
Atlanteanss. Idea now is that you are on
the threshold of the same ability to
destroy yourselves but now you are
choosing not to. You have played out the
limitation, played out the negativity,
played out the
destruction. Now you have created an
awakening within you. You are now waking
up to the godhood that you are. And now
you are creating heaven on earth.
How did you find the harmonic
convergence that just passed this
August? Well, very simple
actually. All we had to do in that
sense was home
was home
in on the overall idea of all the
blending of all the patterns of all the
frequencies, all the vibrations of
consciousness, physical and
non-physical that your planet represents
at this
time and allow ourselves to join in in
that participation in joy and
ecstasy in the simplicity of
creation in the simplicity of
self-revelation to aid and assist the
accelerated momentum that your world is
now utilizing. Now remember that what
you call your harmonic
convergence is in a sense part two of a
four-part harmonic. 40 of your years ago
harmonic. 40 of your years ago
approximately was the first phase
harmonic initiation.
Now, harmonic convergence, the coming
together of all the vibrational
frequencies, the limbo state, a
transitional state that allows you to
recognize all the probable realities you
could become 30 of your years. Hence,
harmonic identification, the
solidification of the reality you are
choosing now to the point where that
will be the only reality you will
experience upon your planet. 10 years
after that completing the second 40-year
cycle harmonic
synchronization full interaction with
the association of worlds as the planet
you are as one world as
earth understand
so we found it most
joyful that it represents the idea now
of the willingness of each and every one
of you individually and collectively to
choose the reality you prefer
and with
conviction to live
it, to
be and in creating a reality that may be
similar to
ours, allowing us to experience the
joy of knowing that we will be
interacting with you.
Bashara, when I was at Mount Chasta
during that time, I saw quite a number
of UFOs in the sky and they were going
there were starships going to the
mountain. There seems to be a lot of
inter reaction interaction with
starships at Mount Chester. Yes, it is a
high energy vortex as are many areas
upon our planet that make it more
conducive for the electromagnetic lines
of flow that our ships travel on to
travel on them. However, not everything
you see that you think is a ship is a
ship in the colloquial sense. Some of it
is simply projections of consciousness
that you interpret in physiological
formats. In a sense, it can represent
other consciousness, but it is not
always colloally a mechanical device.
100%. Yes, it's I really didn't see it up
Yes, it's I really didn't see it up
close. It was very very high up as a
ball of light moving. And many assume
what you call spheres of life will
actually be representative of
interactions with your dimension of
reality with other consciousness
directly. It is simply that you
interpret them that
way. Some of them are what you call
mechanical crap, so to speak. But of
course anything physical is a projection
of
consciousness. Understand?
But there are many strong gateways,
vortices, electromagnetic gates upon
your planet. And these gates can allow you
planet. And these gates can allow you
align with all levels of yourself and
accelerate your vibrational energy
upward. Yes.
So like name.
Name the thing.
Name that tape.
Oh, the
idea, if you
wish, can be simply what we began with
this evening of your
time. You can call
it images.
S what do all of the fires in Northern
California represent the sun? Again,
there can be many different reasons for
many different
things. Some of them can represent
release of energies. Some can represent
what we call
purification, clearing of the
way. Some of them can also simply be
expressions of negativity and release in
that way.
Some of them can be
beacons that allow individuals to
recognize the accelerative
transformation that is going on. For
fire represents a rapid oxidation, a
rapid change of things. It can represent
to some degree the release of the fear
that too rapid an acceleration may burn
you out. Though you do not have to fear
out. Though you do not have to fear
that, for you will never get more than
you can really handle.
It represents all of these and many
things depending upon all and each of
all the individuals that witness them.
Remember again fundamentally it doesn't
have a meaning unto itself. All the
different individuals that witness such
a thing have co-created it and will
assign individually all the meanings
that are apppropo for all the
individuals witnessing
there. You understand?
So the idea is to get in touch with the
personal move and allow yourself to simply
move and allow yourself to simply
recognize how it moves
you, what it represents to
you and to
remember that these
images are simply
that different aspects, different
images of You different symbols that you
use to reflect back to yourself in the
mirror of your reality. The idea you are
being at any given moment for the
purpose of deciding if that is the idea
you choose to continue to be or if you
choose to transform
it. Use it as you will.
that this
timing we will extend to each and every
one of you individually and collectively
our deepest appreciation and
unconditional love in cocreating this
interaction with us this day of your
time. We remind you simply once again to
remember that physical reality is what
you imagine it to
be. You are dreaming right
now. Wake up and live the dream you
prefer to dream. It is up to
you. Our hearts to
you. We bid you exciting dream life and
like dream a bond and loving good.
Thank you.
Go. Excellent. Thank you. Thank you,
Darl.
Thank you for being here. It's a
powerful session.
Historical analogy somewhere
approximated right now in their
civilization where you were in what you
call your Renaissance
era. By the time you are traveling in
space and assisting other worlds, they
will have arrived at a point
approximating where you are now. And
they will be ready to receive the
understanding that there are other
civilizations in creation. And you will
be one of the first
ambassadors even as we are ambassadors
to your world. Now,
we'll play your part. How do you
perceive us right now as you're coming
through Daryl? How do you perceive us
sitting here? I perceive you as a
relationship, relationships to each
other. I perceive
individuality as defined by all the
connections it is to everything else. I
perceive patterns of energy, patterns of
momentum, patterns of likelihood,
patterns of intention.
I also perceive you as living
light, as joyful
children, as wise
masters. That is how we proceed.
Understood. So you basically are feeling
the energy. You're seeing the energy not
the form of it is an orchestration
and in a sense we are playing conductor.
Understand? Yes.
Thank you.
You and then you
Why why have you chosen English as this
medium? For instance, I have not I am
not speaking your language. The channel
is programmed with English. Other
channels around your planet in other
cultures will allow their own language
to come through in the translation of
our thoughts. And we are channeling
through many more channels than the one
present before you now. But we are not
speaking your language at all. It is
simply that whatever language the
translation device the body of the
channel is programmed with will be the
language you hear it in. Understand?
This channel allow you to speak your
world language. That to some degree can
be done because there is no expectation
on the part of the channel as to what it
might or might not sound like and
because it is my quote unquote natural
language to some degree it can be done.
Could
we love you?
Can you say it again?
Do you sing? Yes. Would you give us an
example? In that way
In that way
directly it is more of what you simply
call a vibrational channel. You are
familiar with some of these
ideas. Now another phrase may simply
be the experience of one is the
experience of
all. If you wish to
shimmy Kashimi gets roll shimok
seal 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 S
10 S
that planet you were referring to that
became an astereroid because it was
destroyed. Malbec. Yes. You call it
Maldc. Maldc. Is there not another name
for it like Lucifer?
It is an old nomenclature. Yes. Okay.
There are also many other variations of
that terminology. Some in your ancient
terminology. Some in your ancient
society have referred to it as Marduk
as well as Malbeck. These are all
ancient nomenclatures in your own
tongue, not ours.
And many of these
inhabitants reincarnated on Earth. Yes.
In southern Russia and what is now Iran
and the Middle East. All all over your
planet. No one specific
local. All over your world. Are any of
us here understand that at this timing
there has been so much blending and so
much transforming that it would be just as
transforming that it would be just as
valid to say that all of you are as none
of you are. You all now are on the
threshold of a completely new vibration
of balancing that polarity. So in that
sense you all might as well be since
you're all basically moving in the same
direction now. You're all matched in
frequency. You are all now of
Earth and you all have connections to
everyone else. But basically, yes, all of
else. But basically, yes, all of
you. Would we be as the same in our
relationship with one another as the
Atlantanss may have been on this
planet? You are becoming as it was in
early adalanti. Much of the let us say
adalanti. Much of the let us say
incarnation of negativity also took
place during midalantean times and was
responsible to some degree for the
diversification of polarity which caused
its destruction. A repetition of the
malbeck scenario on earth.
Now you're at the end of that cycle of
negativity begun approximately 30 of
your thousand years ago which culminated
in the destruction of Atlantis
approximately 12,000 of your years
ago. You are all in that sense
Atlanteanss. The idea now is that you
are on the threshold of the same ability
to destroy yourselves but now you are
choosing not to. You have played out the
limitation, played out the negativity,
played out the
destruction. Now you have created an
awakening within you. You are now waking
up to the godhood that you are. And now
you are creating heaven on earth. How
did you find the harmonic convergence
that just passed this August? It was
very simple actually.
All we had to do in that
sense was home
was home
in on the overall idea of all the
blending of all the patterns of all the
frequencies, all the vibrations of
consciousness, physical and
non-physical that your planet represents
at this time.
and allow ourselves to join in in that
participation in joy and
ecstasy in the simplicity of
creation in the simplicity of
self-revelation to aid and assist the
accelerated momentum that your world is
now utilizing. Now remember that what
you call your harmonic convergence is in
a sense part two of a four-part
harmonic. 40 of your years ago approximately was
40 of your years ago approximately was
the first phase harmonic
initiation. Now harmonic convergence,
the coming together of all the
vibrational frequencies, the limbo
state, the transitional state that
allows you to recognize all the probable
realities you could become 30 of your
years. Hence, harmonic identification,
the solidification of the reality you
are choosing now to the point where that
will be the only reality you will
experience upon your planet. 10 years
after that completing the second 40-year
cycle harmonic
synchronization full interaction with
the association of worlds as the planet
you are as one world as
earth understand. Yes. So we found it
most joyful that it represents the idea now
joyful that it represents the idea now
of the willingness of each and every one
of you individually and collectively to
choose the reality you prefer.
and with
conviction to live it, to be
it, and in creating a reality that may
be similar to
ours, allowing us to experience the
joy of knowing that we will be
interacting with you.
Bashara when I was at Mount Chasta
during that time I saw quite a number of
UFOs in the sky and they were going
there were starships going to the
mountain and this there seems to be a
lot of inter reaction interaction with
starships at Mount Chester. Yes, it is a
high energy vortex as are many areas
upon our planet that make it more
conducive for the electromagnetic lines
of flow that our ships travel on to
travel on them. However, not everything
you see that you think is a ship is a
ship in the colloquial sense. Some of it
is simply projections of consciousness
that you interpret in physiological
formats. In a sense, it can represent
other consciousness, but it is not
always colloially a mechanical device.
100%. Yes, it it I really didn't see it up
Yes, it it I really didn't see it up
close. It was very very high up as a
ball of light moving. And what you call
spheres of light will actually be
representative of interactions with your
dimension of reality with other
consciousness directly. It is simply that you
directly. It is simply that you
interpret them that
way. Some of them are what you call
mechanical crap, so to speak.
But of course, anything physical is a
projection of
consciousness. Understand?
But there are many strong gateways,
vortices, electromagnetic gates upon
your planet. And these gates can allow you
planet. And these gates can allow you
align with all levels of yourself and
accelerate your vibrational energy
level. Okay.
And so would you like to name the tape?
Name the tape.
Name that tape. All
right. The
idea, if you
wish, can be simply what we began with
this evening of your
time. You can call
it
images. S. What did all of the fires in
Northern California represent? Again,
there can be many different reasons for
many different
things. Some of them can represent
release of energies. Some can represent
what you call
purification, clearing of the
way. Some of them can also simply be
expressions of negativity and release in
that way.
Some of them can be
beacons that allow individuals to
recognize the accelerative
transformation that is going on. For
fire represents a rapid oxidation, a
rapid change of things. It can represent
to some degree the release of the fear
that too rapid an acceleration may burn
you out. Though you do not have to fear
that, for you will never get more than
you can really handle.
It represents all of these and many
things depending upon all and each of
all the individuals that witness them.
Remember again fundamentally it doesn't
have a meaning unto itself. All the
different individuals that witness such
a thing have co-created it and will
assign individually all the meanings
that are apppropo for all the
individuals witnessing their creation.
You understand? Yes. So the idea is to
get in touch with the personal
move and allow yourself to simply
recognize how it moves
you, what it represents to
you. And to
remember that these
images are simply that different
aspects, different
images of you.
different symbols that you use to
reflect back to yourself in the mirror
of your reality. The idea you are being
at any given moment for the purpose of
deciding if that is the idea you choose
to continue to be or if you choose to
transform it.
Use it as you wish.
At this
timing, we will extend to each and every
one of you individually and collectively
our deepest appreciation and
unconditional love in co-creating this
interaction with us this day of your
heart. We remind you simply once again
to remember that physical reality is
what you imagined it to
be. You are dreaming right now.
Wake up and live the dream you prefer to
dream. Our hearts to you.
We bid you exciting dream life and like
dream a bond and loving good day.
Thank you.
Excellent. Thank you. Thank you. [Applause]
It's a powerful session tonight.
Thank you all for being here and