How are you this day of your time As You
create Time to ex
all Us to this interaction your
by Each one of you that
We appreciate very much always
always
more with you It is Because of the
simple Reason that all we want to do is Play therefore
Today We will be Playing
in Any Way shape that you care to create that play
to be Whatever We talk
about Whatever You decide is important
to you shall be What is important What is
in your heart is what is
determining your life how you will your
life And The Things in your life you
will explore As  You Grow and learn Now You
have whether you can Remember it or Not chosen To be
born into your Society
your parents Have chosen you you have
chosen them for your own Reasons You have made
these agreements with your
parents before physical
while you are Still in a non
physical state while you are Still in what
you Call Spirit for and as a spirit
You have many times A different type of
View A Different Way of looking at Things
You See a broader perspective you
see all the Reasons for Why many things
are going to take place in the lives you
will live and you choose Those lives
Because you know  when you are ready to
have  the way that you will a
Help the CH to B much more more
Things consciously
outer happ of years and
Being this CH
be High excitement High acceleration
When many many things are occurring all
around you so that you will have many
many things to choose from in terms of
the Things You Want to do in life in
terms of the Things that Excite you in
life you Many of you are Being Born into
a World That is far more allowing of
these type of ideas To Go On The very
fact that We Can communicate with you
ind up more more Communication to be
Real to be true to  be available to Be workable
So that you have available to
you many more ways that you can choose
to Live your lives and allow your lives to
be that much more exciting that much more
diverse Less Limited Less focused more
Open more exting more ex
Many of
you Who are bor Now And are very young
in your terms Now are going to see very
large that take place with the next 30 of
your Years upon Planet that some the
Individual upon your Planet do not
even believe are possible Many of you
will find Quite
Common interact youry oury that taking
Because  you up to that knows Space ex
that knows that other  cations ex that that
seves it is high
possible to Meet other Being from
other
of Will under S
the dolin for They are like you
beings like yourselves Who feel Who think Who
love Who
and they To Share the world with you
They Wish you to know them
to and
You Can with yours and Sisters in the
sea for They are very much like humans
but Simply Of A Different for you are
very much like the Dolphins but Simply
Of A Different for you are the ones who
Play On The land They are the ones who
Play in the sea but you  can Blend together You
Can Play Together and they
can Teach you much about How to love and
live and be in your excitement
and they can all you to Trust What is
deepest with your heart about the Things
You Know You Want to do in life Because
you can do anything you want anything you want
Everything you want the only
Things in your Society that might
prevent you from doing what you want to do you
want to do some
some
can want to do is you just Because of
the Way perhaps You might believe that
Something Can't Be done You might believe that it is
hard to do something that
is  difficult to do
something but That
is you the growing
some Reason  does
note but for some Reason that you would
believe that it might be hard to do something
that it might be difficult to
do something that it might have to take a
long time to do something you want
These Are only Fair Stories myths like
anything else Everything in a sense is a
Fairy of vi Real
Yes there seem
a Real that allare canou T feel he
Smell but that in a
sense is a g
You are all Spirits of infinite power
and you have all
together
Toci of the real
You have all together And Said Let's
play a  g let's
pretend We in a World in a
We in a World in a
reality that seems very Solid Where you
cannot pass through Things Where you can
Pick Things up Turn them Around put them
down touch them taste them Smell them
hear them and Let's play In A
world seem isate isolated
seem isate isolated
Body And are and we can other let
that When you decide to play that game you
Discover some Very interesting things
about that game one of the most powerful
things about that game is that When you start playing it
you can Forget that it is a
game That's what allows you to
really it to have  forg Yes
Dream
Where My Mom my dad and Me were
ducks
and My Mom out have a Ja a w yeah
She Came Back and
she Found Babies
Uh She thought It was For Me and she
Gave Me this Big Blob Rainbow Thing and I
saw this tricycle I threw it at it and
ited going like that
and with Rainbow sticking out like this you
feel When you W up and
Remember did you feel White and
Happy I Gu you You
don't When you think about Dream Now How
Do You
Feel does it make
youle does it make you
confused How does it make
you
Conf all the Things in  the dream
enjoyable to you the tricycle the rainbow
the ducks yeah do These Things make you happy
yeah then Can you know
that Of course Over the dream is a happy
Dream if Things in the dream make you happy is
that not a happy Dream to
you don't you don't know all right you
can know do you wish to know Right
Let's make a deion right now and
Show you that you have the power to
decide What These Things me to you
now do you right now decide that it is a happy
Dream or an unhappy Dream Happy
all right now that was Easy  Wasn't It
yeah all right now  If you have decided that it was
a happy Dream let Make you feel think
about think about the Cle think about the Row and feel happy that
you are seeing
Things imation They are beautiful Things
rainbows are a great blending all the all vi
all the Spectrum They are all the
possibilities in life all the Things You
Can Do all the levels You are connected
to Rainbow means that for you Nothing is Impossible
Nothing the tricycle means that you can
Get there very quickly and that you are
very stable three Wheels you don't have to
worry about your Balance AS are
balance a Cycle You are on a
Cycle whs firmly on the Ground And So
you can as Fast As You Want any you want
to
go the du
simply represent the that
you are Still qu under your parents
Wi that you are Still drawing
Learning from your parents nurturing
from them nurturing from to give
for your own
ducklings in this way to Bring Into the
world many ideas of all col shapes and
sizes to S and let life the Things that B
People How say R things things
People Because you whelm
firmly on the Ground and you are  Ping
very quickly along a Rainbow Road of
many possibilities Doesn't  that S
exting Don't S
exting Do you think do That is
what the dream might me for
you or your Imagination say There is
something about the dream that you wish
to talk about or does that feel correct
to
you don't guess don't guess be Bold It
is correct It is not correct It is a
simple decision to make it feels correct
but There is Something It doesn't feel
correct at all there are any number of
Things You can say we are not telling
Yes that feels Right to me Or no that
Doesn't feel right  to me then sck to that put
out you don't have to be wishy wasy
about you can go as Fast As you
want so
decide Things Right to you you want to give
does or not right why why
it feel runs happ
One more Say it again was happ One
more say
again Yes and
Now and From this moment for even When
you are Awake is a happy
Dream and always can be a happy
Dream does that S
exciting Yeah yeah does
it S exciting to know that you
can really do anything you really
want Yes Yes is there Something you to
do  Life yes no
yes no
Maybe Maybe Maybe
Imagine Yourself at any  time you
feel that You might be getting into
Trouble with Life Imagine Yourself on
that tricycle on that Rainbow Ro and just keep Ping you get Where foring Our love SH always what I my life was if
in what you Call Your Arizona state New
Mexico state will have many many many stings of
state will have many many many stings of
Our
CR Within your immediate area also the
area you Call shasta in your Northern
California all right
right
Yes outside of your country That is very conducive
also Because The individuals
Who live in That Country are more
willing to understand that We exist and
therefore they are able to see us more
often than other indiv In Other places
Who Do not necessarily believe that we do
In fact Sens to
a frequ and at the time Another
indiv next to them may not see us at
all  because we exist in Another type of
dimension  frame and if you are to that frame
You can see us If You are not you there are generally notes That Trace Trace
airs
under our ships Do not use the same type
of propulsion that yours do We use electromagnetic
Energy we do not have to
worry about the idea of ​​Rocket flames
and fuels and the like there are no
openings that are Craft in That sense
for water to get in or Air to get out
therefore We can go our Ship
canate a particular Ty of
Vibration that puts Us If you will Out of
phase with Solid Matter so that
Sometimes our ships can even Go into
Solid Matter or through it or into other
dimensions Within
it does that answer your Thank
You Very
Yes I am I love Horses very much and I
love to ride with them
and I am I love Horses very much and I
love to ride with them Yes and I can't understand Why
Lately I Haven't been getting to be
able to be with them as
much as I used to Well you are Learning
First of all to be the horse Yourself To Be the idea that They represent
Horses represent the new way Freedom You Are
represent the new way Freedom You Are
Now allowing Yourself  more freedom in
ways you are Learning What the  horse Has
taught you once You have learned What
the Horses Have taught you about Being free
Yourself then you will be able to
associate with them more often again but
Now It is Up to you so that you will not have to
rely on them for the Freedom but
can learn to R on Yourself for the same degree
of Freedom once you know you serve
you does have
Another there will be an Opportunity for
this One More and then our timing I
timing I
was my
question We will do
not think to hard like to Know
About One of my Past Life I
don't  I don't know which one It was but I
know the year
1950 That the
somew and have communicated
different you aer of anals
and Still that caries very
strongly in this
life making connections between
Nature and
Society can be one of the Things You can be
of service of mostly in this life connections between
What your Society
thinks is normal
and what you know to be Natural
You understand I do Thank you that have served you
yes we Thank you very
much Each and every one of you And we
will remind at This time the
remind at This time the
adults that you are
all
childrenin and to live in a Child like
not  childish But Child like Way means to
Trust to feel to play to spontaneously create
and we than All of you children
and adults al fora relation and inters
you have
created alled Us
all and send You All our love and Simply
remind you that physiological Age though
it has some symbolic reflection of Experience does not
always in of mean
that There is not wisdom
Well I out distance Many of you in that respect
for in your terms I am
158 Years of your
Counting I am still and always shall be a
Child and I would never Desire to be
anything El  It is a that knows there will always be
El  It is a that knows there will always be
something new to learn
We Thank you all and send You All
our Unconditional loves and b you all
exting Dream lives and Life Dreams Remember Wake
up and live the dream you
prefer to dream because physical reality is
what you dream it to be
literally our love to you we you all a f
and Loving Good Day ah thank you thank
you All for Being here
Today time is it
now have a good time Yes
I don't Will Ask her Where They CH