Crea so that you can experience the idea
of a physiological reality because one
of the definitions of physiological
reality is the concept SpaceTime those
limitations those definitions create
your ability to exist as a physicalized
being but we have also talked about that
because time is an illusion all the
different lives you have ever lived or
will ever live in any dimension
experience all exist in a sense now
simultaneously they all have their own
reality they are all a part of the you
the whole you the total you that you are
but in choosing to experience a fragment
of your Consciousness in a linear
fashion then you relegate that portion
of your Consciousness so to speak to
experience that totality in a stepbystep
linear fashion one after another rather
than all at once which is the
perspective of the non-physical
Consciousness that you also are which
you colloquially refer to as the
oversoul the oversoul in that sense can
be viewed as we have discussed many
times as the
projectionist and the lives can be
viewed as the film strip as you call it
each frame on the film representing
perhaps a different life or a different
moment in one life now to the portion of
the film that exists within the film
itself from frame to frame it only knows
the frame it is in in any given moment
has what you call a memory of frames
that have gone by and in that sense only
a dim understanding of projections or
predictions of the frame coming up based
on past continuity but the projectionist
sees the whole film all at once and
knows that all the frames exist right
now from beginning to end as you say and
only the characters on the film are
isolated to the particular frame in
which they exist until the next frame
creates the illusion of movement and
change and continuation and momentum
this is a similar analogy to physical
reality continuity is simply your
projection your illusion in that sense
your rate of flow of transformation of
creating a series of different Nows in a
different format in a different shape
even from what you call a movement here
here to here may actually be the
creation of many millions of different
realities in between to create the
illusion of continuous movement from one
point to another no one really moves
anywhere no one really goes anywhere
Motion in that sense is completely a
true illusion the idea is that you simply
illusion the idea is that you simply
recreate the reality over and over and
over again discontinuously now now now
now now now now now to create the idea
the sensation
of physical reality that defines its
coordinates by space and
time now the
idea also is that we have discussed that
you since you exist only now only in the
present experientially actually create the past
experientially actually create the past
as well as the future from the
present because now is the only time in
which you actually ever really
exist the idea of memory
whether it be something in your
particular present life in the past or
whether it be the idea and notion of a
particular past life in the
linear let us say film of your existence
all of that memory is still created in
the present when you create memory you
are not actually in a sense thinking in
the past you are thinking of an idea
called the past but you are creating
that memory in the present all creation
takes place in the present always it is
always to put it very simply now and it
is never any other time but now that is
the only experiential time that
exists now this visual aid can show to
some degree by a mechanical
degree by a mechanical
analogy how the idea of the
simultaneousness of all your lives can
be interpreted in a linear fashion in
the physical reality you are used to
experiencing but
remember this is simply an analogy for
this particular visual aid is in a sense
simply a two dimensional
presentation of a threedimensional
representation of a fourth dimensional
concept of an infinitely
interdimensional structure so while many different
structure so while many different
degrees of dimensionality are removed
from this particular mechanical visual
aid it will serve to get across the
basic idea of the
mechanism are you
ready y very good
now what you will first observe is
simply a
representation of either now you can
take this either way many different
lives each one represented by a
hexagonal format of six arrows pointing
in six directions leading to every other
hexagonal Arrow pattern so each of those
can be aike each of those can be a
different version of you in a different
dimension past present future alternate
reality call it what you will it does
not matter it is a holographic
representation of the simultaneous
existence of every single probable
reality and possible way that you can
exist and do exist on every Dimension
there is to exist upon it is referred to
as a holographic
matrix holographic in the sense that
every point in that sense in one sense
is equal to every other point from any
point you can proceed in any direction
and in a sense all points connect up to
all other points in other words each
spot contains the information of the
whole and basically is a microcosm of
the whole now this represents the view that
whole now this represents the view that
your non-physical oversoul has when it
looks at all the different lives that
you have simultaneously going on it
simply looks and says all right 1934
1987 1992
2500 all these ideas are all
simultaneous to the overso they are all
extensions of the oversole simultaneous
extensions in much the same way that
your fingers are simultaneous extensions
of your hand each finger has
Independence in a sense and represents a
different idea but they all lead back to
the hand
are all part of one
idea now if you will apply or hold up
the kic overlay template what you can
see is a symbol a strip that contains a
particular idea this is the
representation of physical reality
linear SpaceTime with arrows moving only
in One
Direction the central Arrow represents
your idea of now
the two arrows in that sense on what you
would call your left represent past and
the two on what you would call your
right represent the future in this
indication is simply indicated past
negative 1 past Nega -2 future positive
one future positive to to indicate
different either moments in one life or
different lifetimes you can take it
either way this chart can be used to
represent whole lives or moments within
one life you follow along so
far now if you over over lay the idea of
the karmic template upon the holographic
matrix you will understand more
precisely that karma is simply literally
pattern recognition that is all it is it
is a pattern overlay that you decide
represents the present life you are
living you thus by overlaying that
particular format or pattern or template
upon the present idea you now decide to
be determine with that overlay what
connections you have in the past and
what connections you have in the future
for it illuminates a particular set of
arrows in other simultaneous existence
both now that allows you to call it the
past and simultaneous existence that now
allows you to call it the future because
you are looking through the filter of
the overlay you now only see these
simultaneous lifetimes in a linear
fashion before now after because that is
the definition of physical reality and
the definition of the karmic overlay it
is a pattern that you impose upon
yourself now this is why in having
chosen that particular pattern you can
see mechanically that you have
determined which simultaneous of lives
will be represented as past lives and
future lives to this life you are
creating angle the karmic
template now you can say that this is
perhaps another idea another lifestyle
another personality that you chose to
be understand how being that other
personality still allows there to be
the bleed through of the holographic
matrix to create still the illusion of a
temporal momentum
but now you have a different set of past
lives a different set of future lives
and the new person that you are
literally determines the fact that you
will then relate to a completely
different past a completely different
future so the idea of having this life
now and then assuming that that perhaps
you die and
reincarnate doesn't necessarily mean
that the life you're having now will
literally be directly connected to the
next life you have you can actually
diversify very radically by altering the
idea sufficiently so that the next
person you are will actually have a
different past life than the one you're
living now understand the mechanics and simply
now understand the mechanics and simply
see that the lineage always follows suit
and also if you take this as an analogy
for even the moments in one life then
the change in Direction can represent
changes in the patterns or ideas that
you are being at any given moment and
you can see that by a change in the
pattern you change the feedback all the
way back and all the way forward and
create literally within one life a
different past a different future for
the vibrational frequency you have
dialed yourself to at this particular
moment and also it shows you how in the present
and also it shows you how in the present
what you call the center
point small changes in Direction create
large changes in the past and large
changes in the future because you can
see the sweep of the arc is a mechanical
analogy that a small Divergence of
pattern in the present will compound
itself both in the future and in the
past to create large variations you
understand the angle of incidence
the idea therefore is to
recognize that you do not have to create
overwhelmingly obvious changes in your
present to create overwhelmingly obvious
changes in your past and your future a
small Divergence in any direction in any
frequency in your present will manifest
as a widely different idea or outcome in
what you call the future and a widely
different idea and outcome in what you
call the past because as you understand
past you have based your experience on
what will happen on what has happen this
is the illusion you have created so
simply understand that if you change
yourself even minutely in the present
and that small change creates a great
Divergence in the outcome in your future
then it by definition there must be a
large Divergence in your past to have
initiated the type of foundation that
would create such a large Divergence in
your future you
understand the idea simply is to
recognize that you are
multi-dimensional multidirectional and any subtle change
multidirectional and any subtle change
you make within any one life or any
change you make from life to life will
connect you to a whole other series of
incidents and events that have to do
with the life you are living at the
present so when we talk about the idea of what
so when we talk about the idea of what
your past lives were that does not
necessarily mean that in the next life
you have if you have one that you will
have the same lineage and it does not
necessarily mean that the quote unquote
past life you were has the same future
life that you consider yourself to be
they Branch out multi-dimensionally
holographically in all Dimensions at
once and you can take any route any path
and they will all be real all directly
connected to you whatever idea you are
being at the moment determines utterly
any other ideas that are capable of
being perceived as being connected to
you now whether they are in what you
call the past or the future you are the
dial and the dial for your reality is
always in the present with you it is
never in the past it is never in the
future it may in your terms affect what
you call the past and affect what you
call the future but that control and
that malleability is with you in the
present you all follow along does this
mechanical analogy illuminate some of
the ideas for you that we have
discussed we can go into this perhaps
further at another time or perhaps
according to anything you might
specifically wish to apply to this idea
but for now it will do and it will sink
into your Consciousness on whatever
level it needs to thank you very much
assistant and at this timing in exchange for your
and at this timing in exchange for your
willingness to allow us to share with
you the reflections of the ideas that
you all
are we will ask you now how may I serve you hello