All right, I'll say how are you all this
evening of your time as you create time
to
exist. Allow us to begin this evening of
your time. Well, do you mind for a
moment if I talk a little
shop? All
right. Therefore, let us speak about the
concepts you have held upon your planet
regarding what you colloqually call
extraterrestrials.
First from another point of view allow
us to delineate a time when we first
discovered a
civilization. The
civilization we discovered had life form
upon it. That was to use our
it. That was to use our
term
esasaniish in form.
They however instead of our average of 5
ft of height
range more average five to six and 1/2
of your
feet. Whereas we exhibit generally
though there are
exceptions overall white whitish gray
skin coloration.
This civilization exhibited wide range of
colorations. Are you catching on so
far? All
right. Simply to give you the
perspective that you
yourselves considered from other points
of view are the
alien. that your world to many other
civilizations is
unknown, different, unusual, unique in
many ways. And that there really is no
need when considering us or any other
civilization to think any more highly of
us than you are willing to think of
yourselves. For you are unique and
different in your own way. You are just
as valid an expression of form of light
as any other form of light that has
chosen to express itself in physical
reality or any other level of
consciousness. You are an alien
civilization to us. We are an alien
civilization to you. But on other
levels, we are the same.
The way we choose to express that
sameness is what creates the different
societies. But it is that sameness that
allows us the opportunity to create
different expressions. It is because we
all draw from the same source of
infinite creation. It is because we are
all the same type of soul, if you will,
that allows us the opportunity to
express ourselves in such a wide
diversified range of
experience and life.
Now, many of your years ago, when your
culture even thought of the idea of what
you call
extraterrestrial, you would usually
design your awareness regarding what
these extraterrestrials looked like to
be something always quite
different from your own human physical
thought. And usually, at least as we
have observed, imbued in these nonhuman
physical forms, a certain degree typically of
forms, a certain degree typically of
malevolence towards your
society created these extraterrestrial
forms to be terrorizing things.
Now that you are beginning to change
your attitudes and ideas about what
other life forms can be experienced by
you, may now possibly be encountered by
you. You are beginning to think more in
terms of your own human
form and have discovered that many of
the so-called interactions and contacts
that have taken place seem to involve
more often than not extraterrestrials
that are at least in your terms humanish
humanoid in
form. Now there may be many individuals
who say well why should this be so? Just
because we may think that
extraterrestrials may now be able to be
friendly as opposed to possessing a
desire to consume
us does not necessarily mean that they
must appear in human form or humanoid
form. And this is
so but the reason basically why now that
you are becoming closer and closer and
closer to the reality wherein you can
interact with extraterrestrial
consciousness. The reason you are now
seeing many of these contacts take place
between your form and forms that are not
truly very dissimilar to your own is
because of the nature of reality. nature
of the universe as we have discussed
everything is the product of different
rates of frequency and it is those
different frequencies that determine the
material constructs that are designed
and created out of the primal
energy. Therefore recognize when any
civilization, at least the majority we
have encountered, first begin to venture into
encountered, first begin to venture into
space, first begin to realize that they
may in fact encounter other forms of
life. They will usually at first encounter and
They will usually at first encounter and
attract those forms of life that operate
closest to their own frequency and thus
by definition will usually reflect a
similar physical structure.
Do you follow me?
This is in no way, shape or form to say
that there are not life forms throughout
the galaxies and the
multiverses that are very different from
you and I in physiological form. It is
simply that at first you allow yourself
to encounter that with which you are
most familiar, so you can, so to speak,
get your feet
wet without startling yourself too much.
Because many of you may out of the old
habits, if you were to encounter
something extremely different from you,
recoil back into the idea that it might
want to eat
you or vice versa. But
versa. But
recognize if you are open to it and the
more open you become and the more you
use your heart as a
sensor, you will realize that there are
many different ways consciousness can
express itself as a physiological form
and still
radiate deep love and integrity.
And the more open you become and the
more you explore all the different
ranges of frequencies in which life can
exist, then you will begin to encounter
many of these other variations, as you
would call them, upon your theme, and
life forms that in no way, shape, or
form are based upon any ideas that you
are familiar with at
all. So much so that you may not even
recognize them for what they are when
you see them.
But encounter them eventually you will
as you expand your sphere of
understanding and your sphere of
consciousness. Do not forget there are
many civilizations that are expanding in
a similar
manner. You will not be the last to
arrive. There are many
There are many
civilizations that will take many
thousands of your years to arrive at
places you were at thousands of your
years ago. And perhaps if you are
ago. And perhaps if you are
willing, you will be their
UFOs. You will be the ones who bring
them the understanding that no matter in
what way their consciousness has chosen
to express
itself that that consciousness being a
part of the infinite creation always has
the opportunity to create whatever
realities they are creating in whatever
way they wish them to
be. You follow? Yeah.
We thank
you for allowing us to reminisce sharing. Hi. Hi.
Hi. Hi.
I would like to know if you can give me
some perspective on the fact that I've
been having some difficulty with my neck
off and on for how long? About a month.
Is it in the area base of neck between
shoulder blades? In the back of my neck
and between the shoulder blades. A very
strong gripping sensation at times.
recognize that typically you will find
this to be a symptom of when individuals
begin to allow more of their higher self
through to begin to channel and reach
two different levels of consciousness
and allow these different levels of
consciousness to manifest themselves
through your physical body. That
particular area is what may be
colloquially referred to as the
channeling chakra of your body. the
channeling gate, the vortex that opens
up to your higher self in many different
ways. It is the
facilitation station if you
wish. Recognize therefore that because
your individuals many times have ideas
about yourself that you are somehow less
than that energy you unconsciously
perceive is more than you. And do not
think that you can necessarily handle
the increase in energy. Then when the
energy flows through that valve through
that gate, the constrictions upon that
gate that occur that result from your
lower estimations, your habitual
invalidations of yourself, I am speaking
generally will usually cause that energy
to have to force the gate open a little
bit wider. friction will result and that
friction in your bodily terms may
translate out as heat, fever and or
pain. As soon as you allow yourself to
acclimate more and more to that energy
and begin to exemplify in life the
things that truly move you so you can
use that energy, allow that energy to
flow more freely, then you will increase
your rate of vibration to match the rate
of vibration of the energy coming in.
You will not feel that you are not
capable of handling it. There will be no
friction between a slower idea of
yourself and a so-called faster idea of
yourself that you think you are
becoming. And when you remove that
dichotomy and comparison, then there
will be no friction. There will be no
pain. You will acclimate. You follow me?
Yeah. I
wasn't um We are not necessarily talking
about the idea of channeling in the way
you are seeing it presented before you.
No, I I feel like I've addressed a lot
of those issues and have come to an
understanding about them and not in a
sense to block them off but more in
terms to integrate them. Yes. I also but
do remember that everything that you
discover and everything that you
integrate automatically takes you to a
new level. You are not repeating the
same old things at all. It is just that
you haven't yet realized exactly how far
that gate can open.
And therefore you are opening it all the
time wider and wider and wider and
wider. But each and every time more and
more energy will come through. Perhaps
if I may, I will put it extremely
simply. May I go right ahead? Oh, thank
you very much.
Perhaps you have not yet completely
conceived of exactly how powerful you
are. And so perhaps you are reluctant
and hesitant to give in to the level of
hesitant to give in to the level of
power that seems to be knocking on your
door. You follow me? Mhm. Um, I had a
dream about asking you this very
question which manifested itself quite
differently than it has right now. Um,
all right. It's in the channel's memory.
He also had a similar dream that
involved another part of my dream and so
did our other roommate manifest her own
version of the dream. Would you comment
on that? First of all, what we have said
is analogous to what you understood in
the dream. In allowing quote unquote us,
your symbol of us, to place the hand
upon the spine and activate more energy
through that gate, you received an
increase in pain in the dream because
there was now more energy coming through
the gate than the gate would allow to
pass. So, it was an indication that more
opening is required. You follow me?
The idea of what you perceived to be the
other energy
has to do with a collective foundation
that you all are involved in as a triad
for you are a triad in many ways and
that collective foundation is very
ancient. Do you remember the
facilitation? Yes, I know what you're going to say.
Yes, I know what you're going to say.
All right. Then you are understanding to
some degree the type of ancientness we
are speaking of.
Almost pre- ancient if there is such a
term in your language. Why did it seem
to manifest itself in such a demonic uh
animalistic way? Because when you first
entered the sphere of the earth
reality, it was very very powerful and
very powerfully negative.
You follow me? Mhm.
It is an ancient dream, an ancient
understanding of power. And because it
represents the very beginning of the
path you have been on earth, it carries
with it the full load of the reason you
even came to earth to begin with.
It is the primal self expressed not only
in a negative way but in a positive way.
But it is also that very very natural
self, the primal energy self that can be
represented as an absolute polarity one
way or another even presented in the
quote unquote anim animalistic form. It
can exhibit both positive and negative
traits. But it is simply an indication
that the increase in energy has allowed
you to know that you are now dealing
with levels that you have not dealt with
literally for hundreds of thousands of
years. You are opening up ideas that
have had no quote unquote business being
in your lives until now. Because this
life now is, and this is to generally
all of you, this life now is the life
you have been waiting for for hundreds
of thousands of years. This is the
transformational life. And so as you
reach the point of transformation, as
you reach the end of the cycle of
negativity, you will of course hearken
back to its beginnings.
You follow me? Yes, I do. Thank you very
much. Has this assisted you? Yes, it
has. I'd also like to say even though I
know it was my own creation, thank you
for the dance. You are most welcome.
Sharing. Hi, Bashar.
Uh there's something uh my life's been
wonderful lately. Uh as the past tense.
No, it is. It is. But I mean, it's been
going on for a while now. Quite a while
now. Yes. And as you may know or
remember, I I had been in a leave of
absence from my job. Yes. And one of the
reasons I did that is because I thought
that something would come through. Yes.
To let me know what really would excite
me to do for the rest of my life or or
at least for a while now. Yes. If you
were willing to act at any given moment
on what excited you the most that you
were capable of acting on rather than
just sitting around and waiting. Well, I
I was in fact I did a lot of meditation,
a lot of exercises. All right. And I did
a lot of um code programming to open up
the channels to my higher self and so
on. All right. And um and so well
nothing was happening and now one moment
uh you just said you were doing lots of
meditation, opening up different areas,
doing a lot of programming. What do you
mean nothing was happening? No, a lot of
was happening. But I'm what I'm saying
what I'm want to say is that I was expecting
I'm want to say is that I was expecting
some information to come through. Okay.
So a week ago Saturday um I decided well
I'm really ready to go back to work and
do some work. All right. And I'm going
to start programming quote for for
getting a job. All right. Uh I've used a
lot of the Lazarus techniques to get
various kinds of information and so on
and um so what will you do? So I I so on
Monday I thought I had to go back to my
regular job for a while anyway on Monday
and I went in and I was wrong. So I came
home and I read the paper. I I started
reading the paper and there was an
article on various school programs for
drug prevention. All right. That how
they haven't been working very well. All
right. And does that excite you? That
excited me very very much. Oh, very
good. And I thought, well, this is
really something. I don't know the the
subject matter very much, but since I'm
interested, it's easy to pick up and I
do have the right academic background to
do research, testing, and evaluation in
this area. What a coincidence. I know.
So, I was very excited. I thought, ah,
he came
and and I was I was going to uh start
making some phone calls to find out how
I go about getting a job in that area.
Yes. And the very next morning my boss
called and said oh guess what something
came through yes at my regular job from
which and that was very exciting too
because it's a very interesting task.
All right which one excites you more. Uh
well see I didn't know both of them
excite me a lot. All right then once
again as we have said if two things seem
to excite you equally act on any one of
them. It obviously does not matter which
one you take. And when you make that
decision, it will be obvious which one
actually excited you more. Well, what
happened is I this task is a very
specific task that's only going to last
three and a half months. All right. And
I thought, well, while I'm doing that
task, I will making make some phone
calls by all means and find out. Well,
anyway, so I went back to work on Monday
and I got to my car and my battery was
dead and and I was wondering why you
were wondering why. Why? Because it
excited me to go back to work for three
months. I mean, it's not a long boeing
job. It's an exciting interesting job
that's going to all right require some
traveling and so on. And why was my
battery dead?
Perhaps because you need a new one. Oh,
well, I just had a new battery put in
four weeks ago and it was a defective
battery and ah and what I thought was,
well, maybe I don't need batteries to
run anymore to some degree. Very good.
There is no need to rely on the idea of
externalized power sources. You have all
it takes within you. That's that's sort
of what I saw. You are in touch with
what your symbols mean to you. Okay. If
you are willing to simply trust it. But
again, allow yourself to
recognize that your reaction, at least
as we are perceiving it, seems to
indicate that your first inclination was
to treat that as a negative. Yes, it
was. All right. Then it gives you the
opportunity to activate the other pole
of the battery, the positive one. Well,
I I think I did. Then I I thought, well,
there's no way I'm not going to do this
task because it is interesting. All
right. And it's only for like three and
a half months. All right. So why was why
was a battery dead? I don't understand
really why it should have died.
Again, the idea is to simply show you
first of all that when you allow
yourself to act upon the things that do
excite you. That does not mean that
circumstances are not going to continue
to allow you to grow in other ways. And
it does not mean you will not continue
to show yourself different portions of
yourself that you have not yet seen.
Right. Very good. and particularly
because it is a symbol of the idea to
you of power used in either the negative
or the positive pole. So it was a
reflection simply an opportunity for you
to treat it in a positive way. But as we
have said your initial reaction was to
think of it as a negative circumstance.
Not for very long but yes I did not say
that right we understand that you are
capable of recognizing these things.
Yes. But simply it is no more mysterious
than that. It doesn't have to have a
deep secret meaning. Okay. Great. Let it
be light. Let it be on the surface. Let
yourself know that just because these
things happen. Just because you create
them still does not mean they have the
same old meanings and does not mean that
you need to get any deep dark secret out
of it. Allow the likeness of your
understanding to be sufficient.
Okay. Thank you. It did not stop you.
No, I didn't. All right. Right. Uh then
simply take it as a subtle hint of
different things going on within you.
And also you can look at it from a
positive point of view in that the idea
in and of itself was actually a much
lighter version of similar things that
have happened to you in the past that
were far far far more farreaching.
for example, ideas of other ideas
breaking down that are far more
difficult to repair in that sense.
Right. Right. In this way, therefore, it
is all consolidated down to the very
object in your vehicle that represents
positivity and negativity. Oh, you have
whittleled it all down to the prime
symbol. And so, it doesn't take very
long to process through it. That's
right. It is over with in a flash. Yeah,
that's great. Thank you very much. Also,
it can be in your own colloquial
terminology an indication that you have
finally allowed yourself to be
willing to jumpstart yourself
to jump to act upon that which does move
you. Oh, that's wonderful.
Thank you. Thank you. I'd like to
briefly uh thank you very much for those
TV programs you're doing with Million on
Monday. Uh my daughter and her boyfriend
happened to be there and I coaxed them
into watching it with me and it
interested them very much and I was able
to as a result discuss some concepts
with them that normally I wouldn't have
been able to discuss and I want to thank
you for that. Well, we thank you for
co-creating the type of culture wherein
there exists that type of medium by
which we can communicate. Yes, it's
wonderful. Thank you very much. Thank
you sharing
Bashar. Thanks. Great to be with you
again. And you and thank you for what
you said to Rosemary because I had
recently something happen with my car
and it just what you said to her was
perfect. Thank you for cocreating
realities with her. Yes. Also, I want to
thank you very much for your
introduction tonight because it was
totally synchronous as usual. Are you
using ESP these days?
Never touch the stop.
Just kidding.
Um, some of us have read the book that
Daryl mentioned last week, Communion,
and I was quite fascinated by it. And I
had a couple of things I wanted to
explore with you. Oh, concerning it. And
since he's read it, it's in his memory.
So, first of all, uh I was struck by the
fact that the author allowed himself to
have these interactions with aliens, so
to speak. Nice. uh in a very terrifying
way to him at first even though by the
end of the book he had seemed to bring
it together and make quantum leaps and
understanding and realize that a lot of
it was because it was through his own
bias, his own fears. Yes. That he had
created the interactions in those ways.
Well, the initial reaction as you
already know is not unusual for your
society. Exactly.
Um, also the fact that toward the end of the
also the fact that toward the end of the
book he met with many other people who
had had extremely similar if not exactly the
had extremely similar if not exactly the
the same sort of scenarios in their
interactions. Yes.
Now my question would be
um apparently to some extent those sort
of interactions do happen where people
are contacted unexpectedly. Do they wind
up suddenly in their backyard or they
lose time out of their lives or they
wind up in a spaceship as all the
unexpectedness of course being confined
to the conscious reality. Yes, that's
what I' I'd like some reflection on.
Everything is done by agreement.
Everything good. Uh what else can you say about
good. Uh what else can you say about
that? Because my what I was wondering
was how does it serve the
extraterrestrials to contact
um us in what appear to be frightening
ways at least to our conscious minds on
the surface. What can you again as you
have already discussed different
individuals different cultures have
different
methods. Different cultures think in
different ways perceive in different
ways. The intention is always there to be felt
The intention is always there to be felt
for what it is and their
intentions can always be sensed to be in
an overall way
loving. The
methodologies through which those
intentions are expressed, however, can
and do seem alien to you. Their thought
patterns are alien to yours. And so
there is that fear, that dichotomy that
often crops up in your society when you
see something that is extremely
different than
you. Therefore, it is not so
much that they have an absolute desire
to approach you in specific methods that
will generate fear. It is simply that
their particular natural
methods because of your methods do in
fact generate fear. They are not
necessarily about to alter their entire
psychological structure to accommodate
you beyond a certain
point because they know you can handle
it and they know you have agreed to
learn how to handle it. and that
handling that and learning to do so is
one of the parts of the agreement that
many of you may not be aware of. That's
something I felt because there's a point
in the book at which he says to one of
them, you you have no right and she
says, "Yes, we do." Yes. The right was
granted by the agreement that was made.
Exactly. Because the individuals do,
many individuals upon your planet do
wish that contact with us and other
civilizations. These beings, most often
referred to as reticulum beings, are
primarily doing the job of acclimatizing
many individuals upon your planet in the
ways that in actual fact are buffered
ways. Even though the individuals may
experience many degrees of fear, it is
actually a far smoother transition than
they would have experienced had the
alien being simply come to them straight
out. First time full-blown.
Yes. Bit by bit, these individuals have
been contacted over long periods of
their life. Many times from the times
they are children. And bit by bit they
are allowed to remember more and more
and more of the interaction until they
get to a point where they realize there
is nothing to fear. They can handle it
and then the contacts can occur more
openly and more blatantly. Yes. I
thought it was extremely significant
that every person that he talked to that
had had a similar experience even though
some of them were still feeling
frightened about it and didn't know if
it was they were going crazy, if it was
their imagination it was really
happening or whatever. as still in spite
of all that felt love. Yes. And felt
affection. Yes. At this point in his
life. To put it
simply, the aliens are acting within
their integrity to the best of their
ability, but they are not responsible
for the way you have created your
society to be and the reactions that you
often have. Exactly. You have made the
agreement. they are fulfilling the
agreement and they are doing it in the
way that is easiest for you. Well, also
as you have reminded us um excitement
and anxiety are the exactly the same
vibrations. Yes. So what seems to be
fearful is usually just tremendously
exciting as we all know because we adore
fun parks and roller coasters and all
that sort of thing. Yes. So many times
therefore when you encounter those
beings as we have said for the first
time perhaps in your conscious life you
will actually get a reflection on how
powerful you are. Any fear that many
times comes from that is simply a
reaction to the belief that you cannot
possibly contain that much power and
therefore it isn't coming from you and
that it might destroy you. But it can't.
It is an absolute reflection of you.
That is what you are learning.
We thank you. Thank you Bashar. That was
excellent. Bye-bye. Our love sharing.
Hello Bashar. Strawberry. How are you?
Perfect. I'm you. Perfect. Bashar. I
have an excellent talent for being able
to um assist people to uh dissolve the
apparent barriers that we have between
them. I used to give lectures called we
all seek the same god. Nice. to attempt
to dissolve some of the apparent
differences that people create
separation with. Nice. And I want to
accelerate the momentum in sharing that
ability. You are. I am. That's true.
Thank that helps right
there. And
um I am apparently creating some
feelings of running
into non-activity or not not doing this
as much as I would like to. I would like
some reflection on on ways that I can
accelerate that. Well, simply once again
relying upon the imagination we know is
so active within you. How do you
envision you could be more active in
this? Well, I envision I could be doing
some of the te television shows uh
speaking in front of almost any group
that I can get a hold of. All right. Are
you speaking to the individuals with
whom you would be working on these
endeavors? To some degree. Why only to
some degree? Good question. That's one
of Thank you. Do you have a good answer?
No. Well, let's see if we can imagine.
All right, let's imagine a perfect
answer. Well, imagine um uh stubborn and
lazy is a con is stubborn and lazy.
Those are good answers. All right. So,
what you are saying is that stubbornness
and laziness excites you more than the
other ideas do.
Yeah, that seems to be true to a great
degree. All right.
Um, however, from a from a greater expansive
however, from a from a greater expansive
viewpoint, I do want to be sharing.
Actually, when I'm sharing, I'm much
more excited doing the sharing. Well,
all right. May I remind you of
something? Please do.
It is hard work being stubborn. You
better. It's true. Has nothing to do
with laziness at all. That's true. Well
said. Now you can stop fighting and
allow things to start flowing by acting
upon these other ideas. There is nothing
in your way. Nothing at
all. Nothing in your way. The concepts
of stubbornness, the concept of
laziness are old tools lying in the
bottom of your worksheet.
And of course, the physical tends to
reflect those when they're activated.
But in this way, you can simply pick
them up and acknowledge that they do in
fact bear your
name and set them on the shelf. Lovely.
That's of value. Thank you very much,
Bashar. Thank
you. Sure.
Hi, Bashar. Hi.
Um I have recently started or actually
about six about 9 10 months ago started
channeling visually six nine 10 months
about 910 nine 10 all right channeling 9
10 months ago right visually and
telepathically and I'd like to know a lot of different
and I'd like to know a lot of different
entities are coming through I'd like to
know not really
well then I can't identify all of them
good you're not supposed to you see the
idea in your society is the pension for
labeling things. You have to know
exactly who this is, what it is, what
it's for, what it
does, that is actually holding back the
channeling. Ah now you will
Ah now you will
find that when individuals in your
society begin to allow some of this
energy through the reason it manifests
as so many apparently different entities
is because what you are doing is
familiarizing yourself with all of the
different aspects of your own
oversoul that you have not yet
integrated within the consciousness that
you are. Not to say that you are not in
touch with other levels of consciousness
as well, but the first way that that
consciousness will come through you is
to allow you to funnel more of your
higher self through as different aspects
in different ways so that you can get
used to all the different ways you are
as a being and all the different things
you contain. So that you can blend and
integrate that. And when you integrate
that then you will generally recognize
the difference between what you are
doing now and any other level of
consciousness that you may be able to
channel a little bit later.
You are preparing yourself by
reamiliarizing yourself by reintroducing
yourself to all of the different aspects
that you are.
That is why the labels are now
unimportant. Go off of the essence of
the whole idea. The idea behind
channeling is integrative, not
segregative. This is all one energy that
is capable of manifesting in multiaceted
methods and
expressions. You follow me? I do.
I And what I'm sensing is I'm getting
reflections of all the different parts
of myself as myself and also as other
entities both. Oh, absolutely. Always
both for everything is the same one
thing. Is I want to check to see about one
Is I want to check to see about one
entity. All right. Is Zeus still with
me? Always.
Never can leave you. Nowhere to go.
Um I worked on myself about a month ago.
This was Christmas Day, 2 a.m. in a
dream. All right. And there was I was in
a room of light and there was I've been
told there that there was um I what I
was doing was getting back in touch with
the recall mechanism. That is what we
just said, right? And there was a bit of
damage there. Not
really. Only the belief is the so-called
damage. Did that mechanism have to do with
Did that mechanism have to do with
abundance?
One level. one level. You are now
forming an abundance of energy within
you by reaclimating yourself to all the
ideas and all the fragments you have
created yourself to be. When you allow
yourself that
integration, then all reflections of
integration, including unlimited
abundance, will flow into your life
automatically. And and vocal channeling then is
And and vocal channeling then is
available to me when I'm ready or if So
excites you. Yes. Although we perceive
that there may be other ways in which
you can also manifest that energy. One
way may be through the idea of your
hands in a healing balancing frame of
reference. What about the creative arts?
Through your hands in that way.
What I what I'm getting is writing
through your hands. Thank you.
Thank you very much. Thank you.
Happy blending. Thank you,
Danny. Hi. Um, since my early teenage life, uh,
Hi. Um, since my early teenage life, uh,
up until present, um, I've I've been
seeing little tiny lights floating
around in front of me. And, um, I was
just curious of did they serve a purpose
or was it help? No, no purpose
whatsoever. Is it Is it help? Do you believe me?
Is it Is it help? Do you believe me?
Yes. Is it help? You do?
You believe me when I say they serve
absolutely no purpose. They have no
reason for existing at all. You believe
that? Well, it's it's been from early
teenage life until now. And it's
occasionally. It doesn't happen all the
time. So, and I was just curious is is
there first of all, when you say I was
just curious, there is no such thing as
idle curiosity. You are not curious for
no reason. Is is there a meaning for the
all the Yes. When you are in what you
call the area of adolescence, you become
extremely psychically
sensitive. And the sensitization has
allowed you to expand your typical what
is typical or has been typical in your
society. Your typical range of frequency
perception in terms of energy. These
lights represent different levels of
energy that you are capable of seeing
from time to time that are usually
invisible to other individuals. You are
seeing manifestations of creation,
intersections of consciousness as they
impinge upon the frequency of your
reality. You are seeing in a sense the
interaction of other levels of
consciousness with your level of
consciousness. You actually are seeing
an electromagnetic manifestation of that
interaction. Okay. Um, should I when I see the lights
Okay. Um, should I when I see the lights
floating around, um, I get nervous and I
try to wipe them out and get back to I
feel like I'm not I'm on a level of
unconsciousness and I try to get back
into reality. Back into what? Well, it's
like I can I can look at at stop stop.
We understand what you are saying, but
the reason we are interrupting you in
that way is to allow you to listen to
what you are saying. Okay. The words you
are using carry with them very strict
definitions. You are implying that
reality is a particular thing as opposed
to anything else. And it isn't. All
right. Reality is what you believe it is
and that's it. There is no externalized
reality. None. Okay. It is what you
believe it is. That's reality.
Therefore, the nervousness you
feel once again is simply your own
energy, your own awakening, your own
awareness of your connection to the
energy you are perceiving.
All right. The fear is simply the
habitual reaction you have been taught
to have in your society regarding
something you don't understand. Mhm. As
we have said, excitement and anxiety are
the same energy. It is excitement when
you allow it to be what it is in a
positive sense. It becomes anxiety when
you invalidate it in a negative sense
and attempt to run from it. Okay? That
is the only reason you were nervous.
Okay? Reactions, emotional reactions do
not come out of the blue. You do not
ever ever ever ever
ever feel something for no reason. You
feel things because you have an
ingrained belief about that thing.
Feeling is a reaction to what you
already believe to be true. So if you
feel nervous around that phenomena, it
is because you have been taught to
believe you should be fearful, there is
nothing inherent in that phenomena,
nothing built in to that phenomena that
is in and of itself fear generating. It
is simply another level of the overall
energy that creates all realities you
experience and it is an indication of
your ability.
increased sensitivity in many of what
you would typically call psychic way
that can allow you if you are willing to
give full blossom to that to flower and
bloom and branch out in many more
creative expressive ways than you may be
allowing yourself to do now just because
you think that the only reality that is
real is the one society tells you is
real. Right? That's why I had to ask the
question because I wasn't sure what it
was. But now you are. Thank you. We
thank you for your willingness to
explore what is only another aspect of
the total consciousness that you are as
a unique expression of infinite
creation. There is absolutely nothing
you could ever discover about yourself
that could not be applied to the total
understanding of your being in a
positive way. Nothing. Okay? If you
choose to believe that that is so, your
reality is
We are enjoying yours as well.
It was very synchronous this past week
in my um channeling class. Um there was
a very
unexpected incident that occurred. I had
I was expecting um I guess some flowery
little entity of some sort. I don't know
what. And I flowery little entity,
something really soft and lovey and that
sort of thing. And all of a sudden, this
tremendous voice came through and said
it was from Syria, but it said also that
it would be having something to do with
the idea of our beginning to interact
more with other civilizations. And I
thought that was very interesting. Yeah.
And again, primary among those quote
unquote other
civilizations is the dolphin
civilization upon your own world. Aliens
in your very backyard. Right.
And that is why the strong serious
connection. Mhm. Thank you. We thank you
very much. Um I want to ask you about
something. week before last in the the
entitlement of the Golden Gate, there
was a statement that you made and I
listened to the tape a few times and I I
want to ask you about this particular
thing right I'm going to read it first
and then I'll ask you about right okay
you said uh the gate that you are that
you are is bipolar in an opposite way to
the way you're you experience your
reality and the way that the materials
are set up to create that experience
what did you mean by in an opposite way
to the way you experience your reality.
In other words, to use the analogy we
use, your physical reality is like a
crystallin form of a liquid.
The liquid is the potential reality. The
crystallin form what you experience as
your physical reality. If you think of
yourself as a gate, then on one side is
the physical reality, the crystallized
experience, and on the other side is the
liquid reality out of which the
crystallin realities are formed and back
into which the crystallin realities are
dissolved before you experience any
change at all. You follow me? Mhm. So
far? So far? Yeah. Now thinking of
yourself as a gate. Therefore the way
you interact with the crystal in reality
is as a liquid. The way you interact
with the liquid reality is as a crystal.
You always show the opposite face of
whatever it is you are facing. So that
you can always understand the polarity
viewpoint and have the blended balanced
idea both sides of the issue on either
side of the gate that you are so that
you can function as a gate that
functions in two directions.
You follow me? Mhm. That is all we
meant. Okay. Does that clarify anything
for you? Yeah. I when I was thinking of
the idea, I was thinking of
um another aspect of it which was like
taking a glove and and the outer rim of
the glove like sewing it around a circle
and you can turn the glove either way.
Yes. Although when you turn it we call
wrong side out it's facing in an
opposite direction. Yes. But then it can
go back and face the other direction. So
it's like the same thing with this idea
to some degree. Yes. Although what you
are also including by your example is
the idea of alternate universes.
Yeah. Which are in that sense mirror
images in many ways of the ones you
consider to be facing the quote unquote
right way. Mhm. Okay. But and you said
also the way that the materials are set
up. Is that like the atoms? Is that what
you're talking about? The material to
some degree. But it was also a reference
to the idea of the material you are
interacting with itself. In other words,
liquid interacting upon crystal and
crystal interacting with liquid, the
material itself, the raw material. Okay.
All right. I have one more question. All
right. Um, last year at one of the
channelings, there was an interaction
you had with Jackie, which which I've
thought about off and on for a number of
months. Uh, she wanted you to give her
some information, and you didn't want
to. You felt like it was something you
should do. Yes. And we talked about the
idea of making an exception, right? And
we talked about the idea of absorbing
the responsibility. Right. Okay. Now,
you mentioned that as a result of that
there was a karmic situation of a
blindness in a lifetime, a disease in
one of my past lives. Right. Okay. Now
the curiosity I have about that is that
is like from the the nowness that you
were speaking of at that time did you
create in a past lifetime that
experience from your present? Yes.
Why did you feel it was necessary to do
that? Because we agreed very briefly to do
Because we agreed very briefly to do
something we never do. take
responsibility for another individual
and thus in accepting that
responsibility we thus had to balance it
out somewhere we balanced it out in a time
somewhere we balanced it out in a time
frame that would make sense relative to
when in our time frame we were capable
of experiencing that balance only in our
past are we capable of experiencing the
idea you call disease and so that is
where the life manifested but to the
life. It is still as if it progressed
linearly and was a natural aspect of
that life. Okay. It was not perceived by
that life as having been created from
the future. But it was created from the
future in a sense. Yes. That's very
interesting. Thank you very much.
Recognize in this way we are always in
your terms
cautious of what we interact with you.
For many times the revelation of certain
things to you will be interfering with
the path you chose to be will be acting
outside of our integrity. You can in
that sense even though you may be
thinking that you are being of
assistance to an individual actually
hurting them more than you know. Oh
yeah. Many times individuals say well I
really wish to help this individual and
so I will reveal all this information I
know about them and that will be
something that actually removes from
their life the spontaneity and the
surprise they needed to learn it in the
way they needed to learn it right and so
you will be taking upon yourself
therefore the self-imposed karmic idea
of having upset the balance of their
life in that way okay I I do understand
that and I appreciate your
responsibility there. Thank you. Thank
you. Sharing.
Good evening, Bashar. Good evening. Or I
will say from my perspective, good day.
I think we just had an introduction to
my whole question. All right. More
synchronicity. Yes.
Um my question is basically what else am
I to learn about the relationship?
And I told him exactly what was going to
happen to him if he did X. And sure
enough, it's happened to him to the
point where he's paralyzed. And that's
exactly what I told him what would
happen to him when it would happen to
him. And now I'm afraid after hearing
what you just said that I screwed up.
No. Okay. In your case, you were simply
reflecting to that individual the idea
for which you have attracted each other
to learn about personal power to learn
that ultimately in that sense really
fundamentally no one can really do
anything to you. Even in our situation
it had to be and always is a
cocreation. You follow me? Yes. You
attract yourselves to each other to
learn what you need to learn. In this
case, it's the idea of learning how not
to give power away and at the same time
learning that apparent control over
another individual by attempting to take
responsibility for them will actually in
many ways paralyze you more than it
paralyzes them. You follow me? Um, not quite. If
them. You follow me? Um, not quite. If
you attempt in this way to take
responsibility for the actions of
another, then the idea is that you
rigidly affix yourself to the scenario
they may then reflect back to you as a
so-called reaction to your attempt at rigidizing
reaction to your attempt at rigidizing
or
controlling that particular scenario. We
are not speaking necessarily
specifically of you. We are speaking in
general terms and also to some degree we
are speaking in terms of the opposite
point of view in that
relationship. The idea of attempting to
exercise control in a rigid way over
another individual many times will
paralyze the original individual. Let me
put it in a very simple term
colloquially. A jailer is also a
prisoner because he must remain with the
prisoner at all times.
You follow me? Yes. So I did not do bad
by being a warning label in effect by
saying if you take this much bad stuff
you will get this sick. If you continue
to take this bad stuff you will get that
sick. Now you were simply reflecting
that individual's already existent
belief system.
However you do not have to support that
particular belief system either. How can
I help him at this point? by allowing
that individual to understand that the
situation they are in is the product
only of their belief system not anything
inherent in the actual act but only that
they believe that it is inherent in the
act. This is an opportunity for them to
realize that the power is within them
not in the symbols not in the tools
around you that they think they
need. It is within them and any
experience they are having comes from
them not from anything they have
literally taken.
Thank you Bashar. This individual simply
has chosen a ladder to
climb. Climb it. They have now begun to
do. They do not need to exert effort if
they are willing to learn right now that
the latter being contained entirely
within them can be compressed into one
rung. That the beginning is the
ending. That the means is the end and
the end is the means and they are not
separate ideas. You follow me? Yes. and I thank
ideas. You follow me? Yes. and I thank
you because I was feeling sort of guilty
and I thank you because it makes me feel
a lot better. Recognize again that the
idea of choosing to experience guilt
will only add to the overall negativity
of the scenario that is already there.
You can be of best assistance by
reflecting to that individual your
undying trust, faith and belief in them
that no matter what it is they have
chosen to do, they always have the
strength to change it. Always. Do not
forget you are all
indestructible. You are all eternal and
you are all
infinite. So no matter what any
individual is going through now that may
seem to be extremely limiting, it is
always temporary. You follow me? Yes. Thank you
temporary. You follow me? Yes. Thank you
again and good. We thank you.
Shy. Good day to you. Good day. I want
to say first um how exciting it's been
sharing with you. Still is exciting
sharing with you. Thank you.
Um I when I go to sleep at night, it's
for me it's usually going to sleep and
waking up and uh I don't consciously
remember my dreams often and would like
to know how to do that more often. All
right, there are many different ways.
But before we begin to share this with
you, allow us to remind you also that
not quote unquote remembering your
dreams in the colloquial manner is not
always necessarily a negative thing.
There are many positive reasons for why
you may not. One of which is that as you
now blend the dream reality and the
physical reality into one reality, you
are not actually ever waking up from one
reality into another one. So there is no
dream to remember because you're still
dreaming it. It becomes one fluid
reality. The only reason many of you
dream is because you think there is a
difference between the dream reality and
the physical reality. So you create a
link to bridge the two. You follow me?
That is one reason. Another reason may
be that you do play out in many
different ways all the scenarios in your
dreams that you do ultimately experience
in physical reality. And many times you
do not want to know what that's going to
be until after you have lived through
it. So you will not remember what you
planned until the spontaneity of the
experience has already
occurred. You follow me? Many times the
effect the experience that you call deja
vu is when you actually have a memory of
having planned what you just
experienced. You all of a sudden realize
that you did have the dream. You did
plan it out and play it out. And now
that you have gotten to the point where
it is after the experience, now you can
remember and it comes with that double
reinforcement that it is both in the
dream and the physical
reality. However, of course, there are
also many different ideas that are
created in your society that you call
tension or lack of willingness to
examine or experience different portions
of yourself. And much of this tension
from time to time is also responsible
for not allowing you to be cognizant of
what it is you are doing in your dream
reality. Now allow me to ask you this
question. Why
specifically would you like to have more
recollection?
I feel like I'm
missing communication. All right.
Communication with what? Myself.
Which self?
I don't know. Oh, but you do.
Subconscious self. Oh, subconscious. All
right. But that's just a label.
Unconsciousness. Just a label. Yes, they
seem to be real in your society, but
that's only because they are labeled as
distinct and separate. The same goes for
what you colloquially call your higher
consciousness. Yes, it is real, but it
is also you. It is also what you are.
Your subconscious, your unconscious,
your higher conscious, your collective
conscious, your physical aware
consciousness. It is all the same stuff.
All the same consciousness.
Now if you feel that on this level, the
level you think you are familiar with
the physical level, if you feel you can
create a scenario in your imagination
that allows you to know that you
communicate clearly with yourself on
this level, then you will know you are
quite capable of communicating clearly
from any level to any other level.
Now, all this entails is your
willingness to be clear with yourself in
your definitions, in your beliefs, and
to communicate consciously the ideas you
prefer to experience in life and to be
willing to live those ideas to the
fullest. clear absolute understanding,
willingness, faith and trust to simply
make the decisions you prefer to make
and then realize that the decisions you
have made as a conscious being are
therefore going to be indicative of the
life you will live and therefore
everything in that life will be
conducive and follow in step fall into
line with the decision you make
consciously. You see many times you
think, well, I'm out of touch. I have
this unconsciousness. I have this
subconsciousness. I have this higher
consciousness. It must be in one of
those levels that the controls exist for
me to have the experiences I desire to
have in life. Can't possibly exist in
this level. Everyone knows that in this
level, you're almost always out of
control.
But you see, it is that understanding
that creates the remoteness of
control. The
idea is that you on this level are just
as powerful and just as valid. You are
different, perhaps even more expanded on
other levels. But you are no less valid.
You are no less powerful in your own
way. You are just as powerful as you need to
You are just as powerful as you need to
be on this level to simply
decide truly
decide that you will be in touch with
whatever you need to be in touch with.
You have the commandment on this level
to decide that that will be so and then
it will be so. Your higher self, your
subconscious self and your unconscious
self will listen.
All you need to do is believe that you
have the ability to create that decision
in this life and you will see the
effect. The only reason you're not
seeing the effect is because you don't
believe that the ability to make that
decision exists on the level you
perceive yourself to be on. But it
does. You follow me? Yes, I do. Pleasant
dreams. Thank you. You have opened many
doors. They will begin to be far more
active. do not necessarily expect that
you will be able to interpret them in
the way you think of things in physical
reality. And if nothing else, you will
at least retain the
essence of the experience, which in many
cases is all you
need. You following? Yes.
Thank you very much. At this time, you
may all enjoy a short break.
How's everything going?
All right. I'll say continue.
Thank you. Hello, Bashar. Hello.
I appreciate this opportunity to uh
communicate again and we with you. Thank
you. I have one question on two
subjects. All right. The first is
Nostradamus, the 16th century French
uh physicist, astrologer. I uh made many
predictions. I uh I understand one of
which was that this part of the country
will slide under in May
1988. Uh in May 1988, will you be
challen channeling in a different
location, say Arizona?
There may be many opportunities for the
expansion of the channeling in many
different loces upon your planet. But do
you understand our perspective on what
you call prediction? No. Will you allow
us to share this with you at this time?
Yes, please do. Thank
you. There is no such thing as a
prediction of the future. There is only
a sensing of the energy that is most
prominent and probable to manifest at
the time the prediction is made. There
is no absolute future. It is only a
probability. When a prediction is sensed, the
When a prediction is sensed, the
individual making the prediction is
sensing the energy as it lies at that
moment behind what ideas is the most
momentum and has the most likelihood of
manifesting if important if the energy
doesn't change. You always have the opportunity
change. You always have the opportunity
to change that energy. And in very many
ways, the reason that predictions exist
is to let you know where the energy is
and if you don't prefer it being there,
to change it. So predictions when they
are understood for what they are rather
than the rigidized unmovable structures
many of you have been taught to believe
they are when they are understood for
what they are. Then you will realize
that a prediction when it is made and
therefore when it is known in your
consciousness renders itself many times
obsolete just by being known. Because
when a prediction is known you are now
aware of where the energy is. That
changes the energy. Your awareness of
where it lies changes the energy because
then if you don't prefer it to be there,
you can do something about it now that
your consciousness is focused upon it.
If you hear a prediction and you do not
think you have the ability to change the
energy, if you generate more fear, then
you reinforce the energy that the
prediction first picked up on and make
it more likely that the prediction will
come to pass. But if you simply are
willing to realize that a prediction in
no way, shape or form determines that
this is the absolute thing which must
happen then you can understand you have
a great deal of flexibility with regard
to so-called prediction. Now also
anytime a prediction is made it is made
within the context of the time frame
that it occurs in. and many what you
call ancient predictions, many ancient
sensings of the way the energy of the
entire culture in which you exist was to
be
experienced followed from a certain
belief that existed in your culture at
that time. And the belief generally
summed up is as follows.
The great transformations that were
sensed that were going to
occur could not be
understood as being able to occur
without everything that already existed
coming apart first.
So when those predictions were made,
they were made with the understanding
and the belief that in order to
experience the transformation, things
had to absolutely be destroyed to make
way for that transformation. Now things
do have to change. Things do have to in
a sense break down for another reality
to take its place. But that breaking
down in no way, shape or form must be
destructive. It can be creative. A
breaking down can simply be the
willingness to allow something to change
rather than holding on to the way you
believe it must stay. Then the
situation, then the culture, then that
structure will quote unquote break down.
It will change. it will transform into
the type of structure that is capable of
representing the transformation in a
less catastrophic way. Are you following
along so far? Yes, I believe so.
Therefore, anytime you hear of these
so-called predictions put in that
manner, it is your opportunity to simply
realize that what you are being told is
look, this is where your society is
stacking all of its beliefs. It is still
running off the idea that you cannot
deserve ecstasy without first going
through a trial by fire. But this is an
old perspective. You now are awakening to
perspective. You now are awakening to
the understanding that you do deserve
happiness without having to suffer for
it. And that awareness in and of itself
has already changed much of the original
energy that was sensed back then by that
individual. Now that you know you are
made of love and made of light and made
of ecstasy and that ecstasy and
happiness is your birthright, you now
know that you don't have to shake
yourselves awake. You are waking up
without that violent action. You are now
the funnels, the channels, the valves
through which that energy can be
released and transformed in a positive
way. You can put that energy that was
going to go towards the idea of breaking
you down in a catastrophic way, shaking
you up in a violent way, you can now put
that energy towards constructive ideas.
Manifest the energy of the
transformation in a constructive way.
Doesn't have to be a destructive way.
Now, any individual that simply knows
beyond a shadow of a doubt that they are
waking up, that they do not have to
shake themselves awake will know that
that experience is not something that
they need in their reality. And
therefore, even though there may be
isolated pockets around your world that
does believe it must experience it in
that way. Anyone who does not believe
that they must experience it in that way
will no longer be in those areas
automatically. They will not have to
plan to move. Their life will contain
whatever scenarios they need to contain
and they will move. They will simply not
be where those things are going to
occur. If they are going to occur, if
enough individuals in that area all
realize collectively that they do not
have to experience the transformation in
a catastrophic way, then the energy of
the entire area can change and that
manifestation does not have to occur in
that area at all. It is up to you. So
anytime you hear those predictions, take
it not as an absolute law of the
universe. This is chiseled in steel. No,
take it as an offering, as an
opportunity to examine where you are
being told the energy lies. And if you
don't prefer it to be there, take it as
an opportunity to change it by doing the
things that excite you in life. being of
service and acting as if you know you
deserve ecstasy without having to
struggle and suffer in order to believe
that you follow me. Yes. Does that
assist you? Yes. Very much. Thank you.
Thank you very much. My other question
is this. Last week I asked you at this
meeting I said that I wanted to contact
a great great grandfather of mine. Yes.
And we said you were the extension of
that idea. Yes, that's true. And uh it
um that um discovery blew all the
questions out of my head that I had
because you have connected with more of
a totality. Yes. I perceive now from
that that um the all the experiences of
my great great-grandfather are within my
own memory box.
Um how may I tap that? Can you? By
living the life you are living now, you
will draw upon anything you need from
there as well. You do not have to
differentiate where the knowledge comes
from. The idea is to live the life you
are living now. You will instinctively
know what you need to know when you need
to know it, but not before because there
is no reason to know something before
you need it to use it. You follow me?
You will discover that all the knowledge
you require will be there at hand when
you are willing to simply live the life
you are living now. Because this is the
life now, not that one. This one now.
And there's no way that I can just um u
go back and uh and relive that time in a
sense. Yes. But do remember you are
still living it
now. It is going on now. And the light
you are here cannot occupy the space
already occupied by that life.
Now that is that life. This is this
life. This life contains all it needs to
live this life. There is always some
bleedth through from one life to
another. And there is just as much bleed
through to that life from this one as
there is from that one to this one.
So you are crosssharing with all of your
cells all the things that all of your
selves need to know when they need to
know it. If at some point in any life
there is something you need to know from
the future self, you will know it. If
the past self, you will know it. You
follow me? You can explore this idea in
any way, shape, or form your imagination
so desires. But you will be doing all of
that exploration in the present. You
will be doing it as the present you. And
you will not literally be reliving that
life. That and anything you experience
of any notion of any past life will be a
part of the life you are living
now. You follow it? Yes, I believe so.
Use your imagination. Go into your
relaxed meditative states and simply
think of the consciousness you were in
that life and still are in that life.
Then simply open up to ideas, attitudes,
feelings, experiences. At first it may
come as
sensations. It may not come
analytically. It will come. You are
receiving communication. You simply may
not always think so because you are
thinking you have to receive it in a way
you are used to thinking of
communication. Now it may come more as
sensations at first. If you act upon the
sensations, you will then generate the
thoughts that go with those sensations
and you will know what you thought then
and what you experienced in that life.
The idea in wishing to understand the
thoughts of any other individual whether
it is at any other time or not is to
identify as that individual as closely
as you can. And what that simply means
is love that individual as much as you
can unconditionally and love yourself.
Then you will form an identification
pattern in your consciousness that will
mimic the consciousness patterns in that
life. And then you will share the same
thoughts so to speak. But it may first
come as sensations because the
perspectives in that life were quite
different than the perspectives in this
one. And it may not translate into the
terminology you are used to thinking in
at
first. Go with the flow. Thank you.
Thank you very much. Sure. Could you
clear a title for tonight,
friends and neighbors?
Hello, Bashar. Hello. I have a question.
It's in two parts. The first part is
about a situation that a friend of mine
is in. That is the friend part.
The second part is my reaction to the
friend. Um my friend Ellen has in the past year
Um my friend Ellen has in the past year
and a half or so um gotten a job, held
it for six months and then lost it. Went
through the same situation. Lost it.
Yes. Got another job. We liked it very
much. That's about the way she looks at it
That's about the way she looks at it
too. Nice. And lost it. Um you do know
that you lose nothing.
There is nowhere to lose anything to.
Things may change their appearance, but
they are never out of your reality. The
energy is the same. It is there. It has
changed into another aspect. Nothing is
ever lost ever.
That is an
assumption from a
belief. But nothing is ever lost. It
changes in the way it needs to change to
represent the life you believe you are.
And the idea once again is to realize
that no situation has builtin meaning.
Therefore, when situations occur in your
life, just because you have been taught
to think that it's a negative situation
doesn't mean that it is. If you give it
that meaning, then that's the effect you
will continue to get out of it. But at
the same time, if you recognize it as a
neutral set of props, if you give it a
positive meaning, then you will get a
positive effect out of it.
Okay? That's good. And I'm glad you reminded
That's good. And I'm glad you reminded
me of that. Thank you. I can see her
doing that though. Taking the very scene
of this very negative situation. Yes.
I'll ask her why she chooses to believe
that it must be.
Okay. Can you give me any insight as to
what's going on with her as to why she
keeps turning over jobs?
First of all, she is learning what we
have been discussing. idea that she does
not necessarily have to look at it as a
negative situation and that one thing
changing makes room for another thing
and that all things are equal. She
doesn't have to worry about the idea of
whether she will be supported in life.
It is also an opportunity to examine her
opportunity, her ability to do what
excites her the most and trust that she
will be supported in that and she
doesn't have to struggle and suffer to
make a living.
She can live in ecstasy and she will
generate the support she requires.
You follow? Yes, I do. Okay. The second
part is in being around her, she
sometimes goes on and on and on and on
about the situation. I find myself
getting depressed one and angry too.
That's your choice.
She has nothing to do with it. It is
your choice. Okay. How can I um
by loving her as she is by knowing that
she is learning what she needs to learn.
Anger is only you aligning with what you
know to be true as compared to what you
are seeing in her. But it does not have
to last any longer than your knowledge
of that being what it is. Anger is only
alignment. You see something, you align.
This is what is true for me as compared
to what I am seeing. All right, no big
deal. You don't have to invalidate
someone else just because you are now in
touch with what's true for
you. That's what allows anger to turn
into frustration, guilt, rage, and
hatred. Invalidation, judgment of
Invalidation, judgment of
others. You follow me? Yeah. And the
only way
you will feel the idea of depression is
to believe that her
reality does have something to do with
yours. You follow me? If you simply find
that what she is doing is not the
vibration you are, then why
accept to share that
belief? You follow? Yes.
Shine for that individual as an example
of what a reality can be in harmony and
you will be being of best service to
them. If important if once again if they
decide to choose to share the reality
you are showing them which they do not
have to
do. Everything is equal. Everything is
valid. What anyone is learning is what
they need to learn at the rate they are
learning it in the way they are learning
it. Again, everyone is
eternal. What's your rush?
Okay. Thank you. Thank you very much.
Sharing. Hi. Hi. Um for almost a year now, I've
Hi. Hi. Um for almost a year now, I've
been trying to make sense of my
childhood. Trying. Yes. I haven't
succeeded. Oh yes, you have in many
ways. But that is because you do not
have to try so hard. When you stop
trying so hard, the things you need to
understand will make sense to you. Now,
may I ask you a question first of all?
Sure. Are you sure I may ask you a
question? Yes. Oh, thank you very much.
Do you think it is absolutely necessary
for you to have that understanding
before you will be able to function as
the person you are now? Yes. Why?
Because um because that is what you have
been taught to think. Well, I think I'm
there are too many patterns that are in
my life that if I'm trying to figure out
why these patterns have
happened, I can trace it way back. So, I
figured I would start there. No, because
I don't I want to break these little
patterns. All right, but if you are
paying close attention to what you just
said, you will realize you did not
answer my question at all.
Now, I asked you if you believed that
understanding these patterns of the past
had something to do with you being who
you are now. You said yes. And I said,
why do you
believe that they are connected?
Why do you believe there is a continuity
between what you did and what you
are? This may seem like an absurd
question in your society but it is not.
For you have been taught to think in
linear terms in continuity. This leads
to that. If you are experiencing this
now, that must mean that somewhere back
here there was a cause. Effect, there
must have been a cause. Cause there must
be an
effect. No, it is an illusion. Utterly an
No, it is an illusion. Utterly an
illusion. Cause and effect are the same
event. Now many individuals will always assume
Now many individuals will always assume
that a cause must come first and that if
there is an effect a cause must have
come first. No, you can create an effect
and then create the cause
after in this analogy that we have used
many times. Use this as an
example. Many individuals and to some
degree this is relevant for you believe
that if only they could find a reason a
cause to be happy then they could be
happy. They could have the effect of
being happy in their life. But first
they have to find the cause for
happiness. But if you stop and think about it from
But if you stop and think about it from
the opposite point of view, even for a
moment, you can come to the
realization that there really is no
reason why you cannot simply be happy.
And if you are willing to know that you
can create happiness in your life now,
then nature not allowing there to be a
vacuum in creation will automatically
supply you with all of the cause and the
reasons for the happiness you have
created as an
effect. You can work it backwards as you
are used to thinking it. You do not have
to find the cause in order to have the
effect. You can create the effect and
then create and quote unquote discover
the cause. Now in any way, shape or form
that you care to relate to it doesn't
matter. In other words, you can create
the effect and then it may seem as if
aha now I have discovered the
cause and that cause can now be seen to
be this that occurred in my past. Now
that I understand my past, now I know
why I can be happy now. But being happy
now is what created the cause. And in
many ways, when you decided to be happy
now, that is when you created the cause,
even if the cause for the happiness
appears in the
past. Because time is an
illusion. Linear time. There is no real
before and after. It is all
simultaneous, all parallel.
Many causes for what you are going through in
causes for what you are going through in
life now that you even have a memory of
experiencing in the past were not there
necessarily until you in this present
time created an effect that gave rise to
the need for a cause in the past that
would have made linear sense out of why
you're experiencing the effect you're
experiencing now. Is this making sense?
Yes. Therefore, anything you need to know
Therefore, anything you need to know
about any patterns in your life are all
coming from you.
Now, let me remind you of something that
we have reminded a few individuals
recently of.
You are
constantly creating your entire universe every
creating your entire universe every
single moment of time over and over and
over again. All change, all movement that you
again. All change, all movement that you
experience in your reality is the
product of a series of slightly
differently positioned whole universal
creations. Much like the process you
refer to as the single cells of a film
or an animated
sequence, motion is an illusion created
by the rapidity with which the different
scenes are
changing. You follow me? At any given
moment, each frame of the film of your
life is absolutely complete and not
necessarily connected to any other
frame. At any given moment, you know, by
analogy in a film, even though you may
have a sequence of
images, any one of those frames, you can
at any time remove and replace with an
image that has nothing at all to do with
any of the other images in the sequence.
You follow me? Mhm. Life also is
structured that way. At any given
moment, you can replace a frame in the
so-called sequence of frames you have
been generating. And that one frame will
change everything.
everything.
Everything. Any idea of you as a being
that contains habitual patterns from the
past. That is the whole idea you are
being now.
idea of a person who has habitual
patterns from the past. And now you are
training yourself to be the idea of a
person that has habitual patterns from
the past. And now the same thing over
and over and over again. You do not have
to have that definition of yourself. And
when you are willing to know you can
change that definition and changing that
definition will change the physical
reality in the way you experience it.
Then you will understand that your past
has nothing at all to do in a
controlling way with what you are
experiencing now. The present is not a
result of the past. The present is the
result of what you think it is the
result of now. If you think your present
is the result of your past, that's the
effect you are creating, but you're
creating that effect now in the
present. So, you create all the apparent
linear continuity manifestations that
seem to fall into place to make sense
out of the theory you have of who you
think you are at this moment.
Change that theory and you will no
longer experience anything that has to
do in supporting the old theory. You
will now only experience the
manifestations in your life, the
feelings in your life and the belief
systems in your life that go towards
supporting the new theory you are being
at this
moment. Is any of this making some sense
to you? It is very much so.
It is sinking in on many different
levels. We realize that some of these
concepts in your terms may be new to
you. But also allow us to remind you of
one very important
thing. Never is it possible for you to
hear something you are not ready to
hear. So if you are now in this
conversation with us, that is an
indication that on whatever level you
need to, it's sinking in and making
sense. And bit by bit at whatever rate
you are comfortable in changing those
frames your outer reality will also
change. But simply understand you create
the past from the present not the other
way around. Because the present is the
only experiential time in which you ever
exist. Anytime you look at yourself, it
is always now and it always will be now.
It may be a different manifestation of
now, but it will always be now.
Therefore, any idea of the so-called
past you are creating from now. Any idea
of the so-called future you are creating
from now. It can be anything you desire
it to be. When you change the you you
are now, you will then focus
now, you will then focus
on the particular ideas of the
past that will represent the you you are
being now because the so-called idea of the
now because the so-called idea of the
past has many probable ways of
manifesting just as many as there are
the future. So whatever idea you are
being now will determine the way you
relate and what it is you perceive to be
real about your past and about your
future and I understand that. But what
about the idea that you choose your
parents to learn certain lessons? Yes. I
think that's what trips me up. I mean
all right
but do remember that even though you
have made that choice the idea in no way
shape or form means that you are
incapable of expressing what it is you
are learning in a positive way right you
always have the opportunity to recognize
also that fundamentally many of the
reasons for why you choose those
scenarios is to realize what you are
realizing now that at any given moment
you are absolutely self-contained and
quite is capable of determining what
your reality is going to be like.
Regardless of what agreements you have
made, many of those agreements you have
made are for the purpose of getting you
to the point of realizing that you can
create your reality the way you wish it
to be.
You follow me. Uhhuh. Thank you. So
relax and lighten up on yourself. Thank
you. You are an empowered being.
You are at this moment a reflection,
your unique chosen reflection of the
infinite creation. Act like it. Thank you. Thank
creation. Act like it. Thank you. Thank
you very
much. Sharing.
Thank you so much for coming, Bashar.
And you?
Um, my question was going to be um I've
had this mucus problem for six, seven
years. after hearing what you just said
if I change my belief system um I don't
have to worry about disciplining and not
eating this food just changing my whole
thinking that it doesn't have to be now
you may find that when you change the
idea of yourself you may actually lose
if food has anything at all to do with
your belief system lose the urge to eat
certain foods that may be reflections of
the belief system that causes what you
are experiencing you follow me yes But
the idea is to begin to think of
yourself as a homogeneous whole idea,
not a collection of
parts. If you think of yourself as a
collection of
parts, then there can be the idea, well,
this part doing just
smashing, this
part doing okay, this part needs a
little work, this part I don't want to
think about.
When you allow yourself to realize that
those are not actually representative of
different parts within you, but are
representative of different whole ways
you can
be totally then you can choose the one
you prefer to be and you will act like
that whole idea.
Okay. You follow it? Yes. Yes. So think
of yourself as a clear open
individual. Think of yourself as
connected to all that you need. So that
all will come through you. So that
everything will move,
flow, and release as it needs. Because
that's the whole idea that you are not a
collection of parts.
energy to you,
electromagnetic blue white energy. Allow
yourself to imagine that you are a whole
energy idea.
Breathe deeply and
heartfeltly. Breath is the energizer. It
will energize and crystallize every cell
in your body. Breathe more openly
knowing that you generate the atmosphere
around you that will sustain you and you
do not have to consider that the
atmosphere in which you exist is foreign
to you and will create an allergic
reaction. You follow me? Yes.
You follow me? Yes.
You are not truly a stranger in a
strange land. You are quite at home.
Thank you. Thank you so much. Sharon.
Hello, Bashar. Hello. Last week, you
greatly assisted me in some questions
that I had on my channeling. Thank you
for greatly assisting yourself. Thank
you. Um, I'm going to need some insight,
I think, this week on something that's
been happening. Um, well, then you'd
better go and pick some up down at the
corner store.
[Music] Some months back when I agreed to start
Some months back when I agreed to start
to work um and to use the energies that
were coming through, right?
I totally gave away my my job, my
profession. And I was told that this was
okay, that this would be right now what
would be happening. Now that um I have
worked on this and understand and feel
comfortable with my my channeling um and
I'm starting to work with people and
looking forward to networking with other
channels. Two major film projects are
offered to me. Yay. And needless to say,
I'm rather confused. Why? Because I'm
afraid that it would take Do they excite
you or not?
One part does and the other part
doesn't. All right. But do you not
understand that when you allow changes
to occur in your life, then what comes
into your life that is exciting to you
is a part of the change, not an
interruption in
it. You follow me many times. When you
think you want something, it's when you
let go that it comes to
you. And when it comes to you, it comes
to you in perfect timing to represent a
part of the idea you have now been
willing to be. This is not an
interruption. It is simply that you
needed to do certain things so that if
you do decide that one of these things
excite you, you will have now gained in
what you have been doing insights that
you require to now truly do that thing
to the fullest.
Everything interfits, intermeshes.
Everything is
interconnected. Things do not interrupt
each other. They are all part of a
whole. It is all one whole
idea. Follow your excitement. It is the
thread that lets you know it is all one
whole idea. You follow me? Yes. Thank
you very much. Enjoy.
Thank you. Um, I wanted to say that I do
understand that because of my
profession, why I'm a casting director,
that I guess it would sort of help me in
in working with the individuals more
closely and more humanely. Um cuz that's
what I wanted to do was is that um well
do you not know that what you have been
experiencing for yourself in getting in
touch with all of the different ideas
and aspects personality fragments within
you will now allow you to identify that
much more easily the same type of energy
in someone else. Yes I understand. All
right. Thank you. I also wanted to ask
you, you had been speaking a little bit
earlier about predictions, right? And um
there have been others that I have heard
predict or or I don't like to use the
word predict but say that during the
August 16th and 17th of our year of 87
yes
it is brought the exact idea we have
already shared apply to that as well. I
think again what is being perceived is
that there is a strong energy gate
through which you will step because
that's where your momentum is taking
you. But how you step through that gate
and how you wind up on the other side of
that gate is up to you. Right? What you
wind up with on the other side of that
gate depends upon what you carry through
the gate with you. Is it follow me? Yes,
I do. Is it if a spirit is of the light
and is giving these fears out to
individuals would that be I mean my I I
certainly would never channel something
like that because I don't feel that to
some degree what you are saying is
contradictory but recognize this all
consciousness in forming connection with
your world will
world will
still need to come through the belief
systems of the individuals they are
connected with and cannot necessarily
always override the fears that are
ingrained within the
channel. So the information will come
through but it may be colored by the
channel's unconscious belief. I see.
Thank you. I understand that very well.
Thank you. Thank you. Shouting
Shouting
Bashar. Yes. How are you? Perfect. And
you? I'm fine.
Uh this last week I was uh in the new
home that I've moved to uh rushing
around while the cleaning lady was there
and I slipped in the bathroom freshly
waxed and really came down on my
tailbone. All right. And what a jolt.
Yes, it was a jolt. And um how is your
head? My head seems to feel all right. I
more suffering in the bottom chakra
terribly. All right. Will you now do me
a favor? Yes.
Will you allow yourself to close your
eyes and take three deep
breaths with your eyes remaining closed
at this point? Simply define in a very
simple way how you feel. How do you feel
right now? A little bit lightheaded. All
right. Very good. Now, just breathe
easily. Allow yourself now in your
mind's eyes to imagine the brain in your head.
eyes to imagine the brain in your head.
Mhm. You have a picture.
Yeah. All right. What is the point of
view
where I am? Is it from the top? Is it
from the side? Is it from the back? Is
it from within? What is the point of
view from the back? Very good. All
right. Is it that you are seeing the
brain at a downward angle? Flatten. Very
good. Then continue now to observe from
that point of view that downward angle
your brain. Now see in your imagination.
See where the spinal cord connects into
the base of the brain. Can you see that?
Mhm. All
right. Now, very, very, very slowly,
softly, and
gently, allow yourself to see the brain
and the spinal cord glowing with a blue
light. Can you do this? Mhm. All right.
Now track your vision down slowly down
the spinal
cord. See the blue
light everywhere you look. Look at the
entire spinal
cord. All the way down to the
base. Do you see a different color at
the base? Yes, I do. Just about an inch
up from the base, I see what looks like
a black egg laying sideways. Very
good. Now, the blue
Now, the blue
energy. See the blue
energy flowing like water over the
egg, around the egg, and dripping off
and forming a pool down at the very
bottom of your spine. A
blue
P. See the
A starting to
shrink, starting to melt, starting to
drip into that pool, mixing with the
blue. See the blue
dissolveing the
air, letting it shrink. Letting it
shrink. letting
it feel a cool and a
tingling and then an alternate warmth in
that area as it is now waking up much in
the same way that when you say your foot
falls asleep you feel the pinch
sensation of the returning blood of the
returning life
force and you feel this in your
imagination
let The egg dissolve at whatever rate is
appropriate. At whatever rate represents
to you the absolute certainty that it is
in your mind's eye dissolve. Now
dissolve. Now
see that blue
light filling the
area where the egg used to
be. If there is a gap, see it filled now
with blue transparent
light. See that blue transparent light
connecting the bottom and the upper
portion of the spinal column.
See the blue light coalescing into a
continuation of the spinal
column turning into an extension of it
and connecting the two
sides. See that blue light. Then as you
see that blue light, see within the blue
light the spinal column
crystallizing, regenerating, forming and
regenerating, forming and
solidifying, now bridging the gap once
occupied by the black
age until you see a healthy and vibrant
spinal column once again all the way
down. Now look at the pool at the bottom. See
Now look at the pool at the bottom. See
it swirling and you recognize that there
may still be some remnants, some smears
of the blackness in there that once was
the egg swirling
around. Now see with your mind's eye your
Now see with your mind's eye your
finger, an energy
finger come down.
Dip your
forefinger up to the mid knuckle into
the pool. Swirl it
pool. Swirl it
around until the blackness becomes
utterly dissolved in the blue and is
lost in the blue until it is all
smooth. It may not be exactly the same
type of blue it used to be, but you will
notice it is a deeper and a richer blue.
richer for the
experience. And now that you allow that
experience to have added depth to the
pool, it can once again sparkle
brilliantly with its former translucent
blue light, electric blue light. It
sparkles with potential. It sparkles
with promise. And
promise. And
now you
allow the very tip, the very tail of
your spine to uncurl and relax and dip into
spine to uncurl and relax and dip into
that to relax and
sigh. Let the whole spine
sigh. Let it now drink deeply of that
energy and let it rise like liquid in a
straw all the way up your
spine, all the way up between your
shoulder blades. And as it does so, it
spreads its warmth like the branches of
a tree throughout your entire body
through every organ. Let it rise to the
base of your brain and create a tingling
sensation. Let it
seep throughout your brain. Much in the
same way that a sponge would absorb blue
liquid, blue ink that will write a new
idea, a new definition, and completely
rewire the entire idea of your
brain and your awareness of
self. Feel the blue
Feel the blue
fluid refreshing refreshing
lubricating, invigorating
you in a
cool and crystal and clear
way. Breathe
deeply and feel the vapors from this
fluid going in and out through your
sinuses. Feel the cool vapors enveloping your
Feel the cool vapors enveloping your
eyes and leaking into your ear canal and
imbuing every cell in your body with a
vibrant tingling
sensation. Much like the idea you would
call eucalyptus,
eucalyptus,
feel the breath, the atmosphere around
you to be cool and vibrant and pink.
Feel yourself standing straight and
smooth, whole and
pure, and at once and the same
time soft and supple.
firm but
supple. Flexible, Flexible,
pliable,
malleable, bending to and
fro like a sapling in the
wind. So that any idea in your reality
from this point forward that you perhaps
in the past might have treated as a
shock to the
system will now be
absorbed
gently. You will send not break. How
break. How
wonderful. We thank you for
cocreating
alignment. Allow yourself to breathe and
energize yourself into whatever
crystallized form you wish to be out of
the primal liquid from which you create
your reality. Thank you very much. We
thank you.
Sherry. Hi Rash. Hi. Um, just want to
let you to elaborate on my feelings of
feeling like a vibe sponge. Hey. And
also, uh, lately I've been feeling
disillusioned with physical reality.
Disillusion. Very good. And why the
phrase howdy duty time keeps coming to
mind. It simply is a symbol for you from
your childhood of what you would call a
carefree idea. You follow me? Yes.
idea. You follow me? Yes.
Thank you.
Anything else you wish to explore? Yes.
Um the idea of channeling my music. What
about it? Uh any way I can make it
clearer faster? Make it clearer. Speed
it up. Speed it up. The way to speed
anything up is to live completely in the
present because then you don't create as
much time. Thank us.
Thank us.
We thank you.
chatting. Hello. Hello. I'd like some information
Hello. Hello. I'd like some information
concerning my interest in UFOs and is
there any relationship to a possible
career direction?
No. None. Okay. Thank you. Just kidding.
I know. Thank you. What do you wish to
do with it? You can be quite
instrumental in researching the
information that already exists upon
your planet and correlating this
information in a way that is digestible
to many readers that are interested in
many of the same scenarios. You can do
that. You can communicate with many
other individuals upon your planet that
are already doing this kind of research
around and allow yourself to become
connected with them to in this way
release this information to individuals
who are interested in discovering this
information. You can do that. You can
communicate with many levels of your
government in this way. Many levels of
the government in this way that already
know many of the things that are going
on with regard to the different
civilizations that are visiting your
world. And you can communicate with them
your desire to allow them to work with
you to release this information in a way
they feel will be safe for them as well
as informative for all the other
individuals upon your planet that are
interested in discovering this kind of
information. You can do that.
Thank you. Beating it up.
Thank you very much.
What do you wish to do? I wish to know
if there has been any contact in this
physical life that I am right now
unaware of.
Okay. When
seven times years old. Seven years old.
This was a physical contact. Yes. And
no. Many of the things many of you think
are actually physical contact are
actually telepathic experiences because
on that level the idea is the
same. Physical is the same as that
particular level of contact. So it was
both physical and non-physical at the
same time. You were in a sense in
another dimension of experience which is
not your literal physical dimension you
are in now
anyway. Okay. You follow me? Yeah. But
there was an identification. There was a
communication and much of what you are
experiencing now as your desire is the
result of that momentum and that
impetus. A
so this is continuing of course. Okay.
Or you would not be where you are with
the desire you have. All right. Again
the desire you have is the indication of
what you are all about and what you can
do in life most
effortlessly. It is your desires and
excitement that let you know the things
you can do in life most
effortlessly. You follow me? Yes. Thank
you. One
moment. Are you going to Arizona?
I was planning to. When? In uh
April around Easter. All right. Have a
good time.
I will. Thank you. Thank you.
Chatting for sure. Hello again. After a
while, it's good to see you again. I
have uh just come back from um about 5
months on the east coast of uh the kind
of focus clearing that you and I talked
about before I left and uh a lot of work
has been done. Uh and I am very tired.
Is it just a question of a vacation or
is something one of our what we call
illnesses settled in somehow sicknesses?
To some degree there is a little bit of
that idea but mostly it is simply that
there are many things that you have been
exploring that you have been learning
how to no longer fight and it is all the
fighting that has made you tired. The
energy of that area in that way is the
energy of fighting and that is simply
what has made you tired. Now you are
back in a homogeneous energy that you
are familiar with and you will
re-energize yourself because you are no
longer fighting. Right? It's not just
the place. It's uh the next question
about um it's letting the will go in a
sense with regard to what I'm doing now
and expanding into. Yeah. Although will
is not something you will dissolve again
is the facility that allows you to make
the conscious decisions that you can
create in your life to determine what
your life can be but will in the sense
of fighting yourself. Yes, that you can
dissolve or conceptualizing rather than
doing them just seeing them apart from
me. Hey okay. Uh the one thing I'm doing
now if you could channel some uh
information would be terrifically
helpful. I'm looking for a house to move
into having just come back. Uh sharing
uh who has a house? Who has a house?
Any ideas? Any information? Well,
[Music] there you go.
there you go.
That's uh subleting uh taking over uh
housesitting. Someone's got to leave.
Helpful to both sides. Or a big house
that some roommates are moving out of.
Take a hike. And it's driving me crazy.
That's why I'm asking you. I hate Take a
hike. Take a hike. Take a hike. Walk.
Take a walk. Take a walk.
Anything to do with trus.
Hey, I'm fighting that, but I shouldn't.
Why are you fighting? Too far out. From
what? from uh where I want to be, where I'm
from uh where I want to be, where I'm
telling myself. Oh, really? Mhm. It's
actually quite close to where you
actually need to be. Okay. And where you
really do want to be. Okay. Take a hike
in the country. Thank you very much. We
thank you. When you do so, you will
begin to realize how close to home you
actually are. Thank you. Thank you.
chatting. Hi Vishore. Hi. Um well I wanted to ask
Hi Vishore. Hi. Um well I wanted to ask
you um why is there a fear in things
that are
new? Because you have an ingrained in
general in your society belief
system that anything that occurs in your
life can be something that will
overwhelm you. that if it is an
unknown factor, it can overwhelm you in
this way that you are not in control of
it. You think that familiarity is the
only thing that breeds control. That is
not so. And again recognize that nothing
can occur in your life that you are
truly unfamiliar
with. You follow me? Yes. The fear is
simply a reaction to the belief that
what comes into your
life perhaps can be believed to not have
anything to do with what you think your
life should contain. It is a fear
reaction in being out of control. Oh,
how did that get there? That's new. I
don't understand it. How does this fit
in my life? What's this doing here? What
purpose does this serve? How can this
possibly fit into my life if I don't
understand it? Why is this here now? I
was having such a good time doing this.
Why did this come now?
I must have lost it. I must be out of
control. Things are not going according
to plan. Not as I expected it to be.
What's wrong with
me? Why can I get a handle on my life?
Why do these things keep occurring in my
life? I'm out of control. Help. Help.
Help. Help. Help.
Help. That's what the fear reaction
usually is saying. all of these
different beliefs about the idea that
something can occur in your life that
for some reason you think has no
business being there. That can't
happen. Can't
happen. You have a belief that you think
there is something that you will
discover within that unknown that could
do you harm because you're not in
control. Only your belief will create
the illusion of harm.
You follow me? Yes. Does this assist
you? Mhm. Anything else? No, thank you.
Thank you very much. Oh, one
moment. One
moment. Something just came up.
Something very
important. Something that will change
your whole life in a way you did not
imagine it would even be possible.
You want to know what it is? Yeah.
Are you sure you want to know what it
is? Yes. Are you in the least bit
Yes. Are you in the least bit
apprehensive to know what it might be?
Well,
yes. Tell me, please.
Lee. All
right. I love you.
Thank you. Will
you love yourself?
Yes, I will. Thank you.
Thank you, Shanny. Hello.
Um, I've become uh aware that my
painting has been a tool for me for
transformation and I'm beginning to
share that with other people. Oh, I
uh is there um
anything that um perhaps I'm I'm not
being in touch with with that experience
that would be helpful if I were to say
no, would you believe me? Yes. Why?
Did you just want to hear from me what
you already knew?
Sure. You know you are being of service.
You know you are enjoying doing
it. Are you simply creating one of the
syndromes we have discovered in your
society that if there's nothing to worry
about you worry about not having
anything to worry about?
Perhaps.
Perhaps. Is there another way in which
you would find pleasure in expanding the
expressiveness of your creativity?
Um, maybe. Not now. No. Why not? Um,
because I'm doing everything the way
that I want to do it right now. Well,
then our original answer sticks.
No, there is nothing I could possibly
tell you that you are not already doing
just perfectly. Thank you. Enjoy. I
will. We thank you. May I ask you one
other thing? You just did.
You wish to ask another one? Yeah. All
right. Um uh I know that there's uh something
Um uh I know that there's uh something
going on with my husband and I. Um
something going on.
uh that we cannot
uh do a job together.
So
um we would like to why?
Um it would
uh it would be nicer. Nicer than what?
Nicer than not being able to Why?
Um, it's an unpleasant experience. Why?
Uh, why? Um, yes. Why?
I don't like it. Why?
It feels um feeling is a reaction to a
belief. Just to say you feel is not a
Just to say you feel is not a
reason. What do you believe that creates
the feeling? Why is it unpleasant?
I guess because I want it to work. Why
do you think it is not working the way
it is?
Well, it obviously is because it's going
on and on the same way.
So
um just accept that what are you
learning from it the way it is unfolding
I I feel that there is something to
learn I don't know what it is what are you
I don't know what it is what are you
learning now what have you already
learned
all right let's work it from another
direction. All right.
If you were to in your terms work
together in the way you say you desire
to, what would be the difference?
The task would be accomplished. The
what? Um the task, the job, the the the
what um why is it a
task? Well, it's
always uh Are you saying that you are
not enjoying it at all?
I don't enjoy the experience of not
being able to
perform the job at hand. The if it's
something like moving a chair Yes. from
this side of the room to that side of
the room. Yes. It doesn't happen. Why
not? because we can't seem to be able to
move it together and it's too heavy to
be
moved by one person. Oh, really? So, it
just doesn't happen. Why is it too heavy
to be moved by one person?
Um,
in other words, why do you fill your
life with things that cannot be
accomplished by each individual in that
relationship?
And on another level, where's your
ingenuity?
Well, I use it to find someone else to
help me. I see. I just thought it would
be nice if I could use
um that we could work together to do it
rather than to have to seek someone
else. Yes. But you are in a sense
working together. But you are working
together to also lighten your
load. In many ways at this time much of
what you say you desire will be the
result of when you remove some of the
dead weight from the idea you are
sharing. Then you will be able to move rapidly
Then you will be able to move rapidly
together. Yeah. when you no longer have
to carry the idea of things that you
think of as burdens.
Perhaps this is your opportunity to
empty your suitcase a little bit. Oh, I
I totally believe that. All right. But I
don't seem to be able to unload my
suitcase. But you are if you are willing
to recognize that if something cannot be
moved then why keep trying to.
Okay. So in other words be patience. No
no no you do not need patience. Patience
is what creates
impatience. If you are living in the
moment and enjoying the life as it is
then you are too busy having fun to be
waiting for anything better to come
along. Therefore, you don't need to be
patient.
Okay, this is not about patience.
Patience may be one of those
chairs that you no longer need to sit in
and wait. You follow me? No.
wait. You follow me? No.
Patience is like the
chair. When you sit in it, you don't go
anywhere either.
Yes, I am. And you don't need to take it
with you.
Now, you said you were an
artist. Then only paint in the picture
of your
reality the things that will move most
easily with you.
Do not fill your picture with things
that weigh the canvas down to the point
where you alone cannot move it.
This is an opportunity to recognize that
many of the physical objects in your
life are symbols of ideas that weigh you
down and do not allow you to proceed in
a light and creative and expressive and
spontaneous big word
spontaneous manner.
spontaneity. That the idea that you are
not allowing spontaneity, that you are not
allowing spontaneity, that you are not
allowing yourself to live in an
environment which engenders spontaneity
is
what keeps the appearance of separation
existing in your
relationship. You follow it
abstractly. All right, then let it sink in. Okay?
All right, then let it sink in. Okay?
And you may take it more literally if
you wish. Perhaps you do not think I
mean it literally. May I ask you a
question in a literal way? Yeah. What
would happen if that
happen if that
chair no longer existed in your house?
I guess there would be nothing to move.
Correct. You would be doing the moving. And when
You would be doing the moving. And when
you move, all things that you need move
with you. If when you move something doesn't
you. If when you move something doesn't
move with you, it is a sign that you may
not need
it. So why attempt to drag it
along? Many times individuals will
actually create a physicalized scenario
to very literally represent this
idea. If you are desiring to work
together, then allow yourself to
recognize that the generation of
flexibility and
spontaneity is what will allow you to
intermix and
intertwine more often on many different
levels than you do now.
You follow it? Yes.
Sleep on it?
Yes. I will. We thank you. Thank you.
There will also be someone who has been
close to you many times who will explain
some of this to you in another way in
symbols you are more familiar with
sweet dream thank you at this
at this
timing allow us once again to express to
you our unconditional love and remind
you your physical
reality always is and can ever only be
the product of what you most strongly
believe to be true.
Let your physical reality and the
situations that occur in it reflect to
you not the idea that you are stuck. Not
the idea that you are a failure, but the
idea that if something appears in your
physical reality that you don't prefer,
it is an indication of a belief that you
have that you can change the definition
of. Do not fight yourself.
flow with
yourself. If something seems stubborn as
a situation in your reality, then it is
a reflection of your own stubbornness.
In many
ways, there is no need for
insistence. When there is spontaneity,
all things inter mesh and interplay perfectly. Interplay
perfectly.
Enjoy. To all of you exciting dream life
and life dreams. We thank you for this
opportunity to experience once again the
crystallin gift of your consciousness.
We are always eager to unwrap that gift
and experience and
explore the more that you always are.
Besides a bond and loving good [Music]
Let everything go.
Thank you all for being here tonight.
Thank you all for coming. Anyone