All right, I'll stay. How are you all this
right, I'll stay. How are you all this
dream time of your time as you create
time to exist? Great. Excellent. Are you
all alive? How are you all this evening?
Perfect. Great. Are you sure you are all
alive? All right, we'll let you think about it
All right, we'll let you think about it
for a while. Perhaps later on you will
decide that you are a little bit more
alive than perhaps you are allowing
yourself to feel right now. The idea we
will speak of, the interaction we will
commence with this evening of your time
will be the idea of levels and the
orchestration of energy between any
particular idea that you have in your
reality that you call a level or a
separation or an individual.
individuals. Even though you may from
time to time think of yourselves as
individuals and perceive that as
individuals you all exist on apparently
the same general level.
You create within or have created within
your unconscious mythology the idea that
there is many different levels to your
consciousness rather than simply
allowing yourself to experience yourself
as the one consciousness that you are in
this way. Therefore, even when you
create the discernment that you are a
different individual from another
individual, when you create the ability
to even say that there is a difference,
that there is a you and that there is a
that you are also at the same time
including in that differentiation the
idea of levels automatically
unconsciously because you have created
this idea of the unconscious levels
within you to begin with. Many times you
do not even realize you are applying the
idea of operating on levels in this
direction as well as operating on
differences in this direction. But you
will find yourself always to be a
multi-dimensional being even when you
may be exhibiting more than what you
might call the negative traits of your
personality as well as the positive. So
even when you may be exhibiting the idea
of negative energy, negative traits,
negative portions of your consciousness,
you will still do it in a very
multi-dimensional way. Not only will you
differentiate, segregate and limit on
the same plane. You consciously perceive
all of yourselves to exist with all. But
you will also allow yourselves to
segregate, limit and differentiate in
all the different aspects or ideas of
levels that you have bought into that
you believe truly exist in your
unconscious psy. In this way, therefore,
you will find yourself much like what
you call a chess move in your
terminology, that which you call your
game of chess, that when you make the
so-called comparison or the
differentiation that you are here and
this person is there, it will not just
be a segregation in this way, but it
will also be a segregation in this way.
You will tend to look at your relative
comparison to that individual not only
across the board but up, down, sideways,
backwards, upside down, inside out, and
from many different points of view.
Allowing yourself the opportunity, as
you say in your society, to see where
you stand relative to that other
individual and to accept upon yourself
in that moment of judgment. The idea of
what your niche seems to be based upon
what you are gleaning or judging others
to be around you. So you will place
yourself in certain stations. You will
say well they are more. I am less. I am
more. They are less. I have a much more
important position than they do. Or vice
versa. As you say they are able to cope.
I am not. I am able to cope. They are
not. They have this much more than I do.
I have this much less or vice versa.
Always in that way, as you are creating
this separation from one individual to
another, you are sizing yourselves up
and evaluating yourselves in many
different directions at once. It is not
just simply a linear evaluation.
So even this even this recognition if
this is what many individuals upon your
planet may have a tendency to do because
that is the way you have been taught to
believe is the way to relate to other
individuals. Even this scenario, though
it may be that scenario which
perpetuates segregation and perpetuates
negativity, can still serve you in a
positive way to let you know that even
when you are functioning on a negative
realm, on a negative idea of yourself,
you are still functioning on
multi-dimensional levels. You are still
approaching the point of view of
yourself from many different arenas,
from many different perspectives. And
that you are simply not just the
onepoint perspective being that many of
you take it for granted that you are.
You have many different perspectives of
yourself even when you apply negative
pressure to the idea of who and what you
are. Are you all following along so far?
Is this translating out into your
language appropriately?
Yeah. In this way,
therefore, allow us to point out that
even on the negative level, you will
still find that because you are creating
many different levels, because in that
way, you take the idea of your
multi-dimensional self and place it on
many shelves relative to other
individuals and the shelves they create
themselves to be. You can look at the
entire idea much like what you would
call bars as you write your music in
that way and you can consider the
different aspects of yourself as
different notes as different tonalities
and when you play the whole scale of
yourself when you place let's say I have
a note on this line I have a note on
this line they have a note on this line
they have a note on that line when you
then play the tune you are and compare
or blend yourself next to the tune they
are. This allows you to discern within
your judgment of yourself the idea of
whether you believe you are in harmony
with the other individual, whether you
make a harmonic chord together.
Recognize in this way that each and
every one of you have notes on every
line, on every level. The idea of the
judgments, the limitations, and the
invalidations simply only allows you to
be aware of a few of those notes on a
few of those lines. And this is why it
may seem more often than not in your
society that there is so much discord
and disharmony between one individual
and another because you are not allowing
yourself to realize that you all share
far more harmonics in an integrated
whole awareness of yourselves than you
think you do. Because you are taught to
exclude your ability to see certain
notes that you possess certain vibratory
harmonics and ideas that you can live
thinking that this is you. This song
that you have been singing for most of
your life is you. That is the only you
you can be and that all the other
individuals in the songs they sing.
Well, that is them. They are fixed for
life in that way. And if we don't mesh
well, too bad. We will sing a different
tune. But in this way, allow yourselves
to begin to recognize that even when you
are creating the discernment that you
possess a note that perhaps they do not
or they possess a note that perhaps you
do not, you still have the ability to
recognize that that note exists within
them. And you still can find a place
within yourself, no matter how ghostly
you make it. No matter what kind of a
phantom projection it may seem to be to
you, you still have the ability to hear
that note, to recognize that note, to
know it for what it is. And you do check
within yourself to see whether or not
that you whether or not have the note,
but whether or not you choose to play
that note, whether or not you choose to
hear that chord, whether or not you
choose to believe that you exist also on
the same level, have the same
potentials, can sing the same song, can
share the same idea in that way.
Allow yourselves to know right now if
you are willing that you contain the
entire orchestra of anything you could
ever encounter in life. Anything that
you do not contain on any level, you
will never perceive. You will never be
aware that there is such a song to sing.
Anything that you can see in someone
else, you contain the potential of. Now,
this does not necessarily mean that
individuals will come up and represent
in every case a one:one ratio
relationship of what you see in them. Oh
no, if I see that in them, that means I
have it in me. And what if it is
something I don't like? Does that mean
that I'm that way too? No. You still
have the option of allowing yourself to
sing whatever notes you wish. We are not
saying that you do not always have that
free will, but simply recognize that
many times because of the way your
society has taught you to believe, you
do not believe that you have the notes
to sing the songs you do wish to sing.
And that when you see these notes in
someone else, if you can see them in
someone else, it is still an indication
that you contain those notes as well.
You can identify with that chord. You
know what that note is. You recognize
it. And if you can recognize it, if that
is something you would prefer to sing,
then you also contain that chord and all
you need to do is pluck that string
within you. The idea of jealousy is
simply believing that something you see
in someone else that you prefer to be
does not exist within you. But if you
can see it in someone else, it must
exist within you. You can only see in
someone else that which is written
within the structure that you are or you
will have absolutely no common reference
even to recognize the thing within that
other individual. If it is something you
do recognize then you contain that
ability. If it is something you prefer
to do, then you also contain the ability
to sing that song to create an
orchestration between you that will
allow you to identify with their
tonality and become not them but your
version of what you see in them. Each
and every one of you are an entire
orchestra and are able to reinforce
whatever section of that orchestra you
are so moved to reinforce when you are
moved to do so. And if you hear the
strains of sound, the beautiful fluid
music coming from someone else that
moves something within you and starts
your strings vibrating as well. Then
recognize that you are able to play the
same song and that you are not left out.
You are not left, as you say,
shorthanded. You have the ability as
your own conductor to open up your own
concert, all that which you are, and
resonate most vibrantly the idea that
you perceive in this other individual.
For they have been a very loving mirror
to you to show you that you are the
orchestra and that you have the ability
to
orchestrate anything in your reality
that you have perceived and that it is
very much so a matter of vibratory
[Music] identification. Allowing yourself to
identification. Allowing yourself to
feel, to think, to act in the same
manner, to mirror what you see in
someone else or what you imagine in your
picture mind that you would like to be.
You see, your imagination is there to
give you the opportunity so that if you
do come up with a concept and you cannot
find a physical being to mirror that is
already doing what you would prefer to
do, you can create that in your
imagination and you can follow that
reflection and you can know that if you
simply do act like the picture you have
in your mind of how you would act if you
were that type of person, then you will
be being that type of person. You are
self-reflective from many directions.
You can use the idea externally. You can
use the idea internally always
understanding of course that to begin
with it is always in a sense internal
even though there really is now I say
really in your loose terms of idea
colloquial language there really is not
exactly truly an outside or an inside
because those two concepts imply the
existence of spacetime as an actual real
quote unquote thing. when in fact it is
what you are. You are the real thing.
But space time is within you so to
speak. But it is even more than within
you. It is you. You are it. You are the
experience of your life. You are the
situation that you find yourself in. You
as the orchestra play the tune and on
the vibratory waves of your melody do
all of the external illusionary symbols
of your projected reality take their
form from. You play the song that you
are. That is what you hear echoed back from
That is what you hear echoed back from
the concert hall that you construct in
your imagination to play the game of
physical reality. Is all of this making some
reality. Is all of this making some
sense? Yes. Sharing.
Hey, I just uh not just I have a
wonderful sharing before I knotted off
on a nap today. I was uh with the
dolphins and uh I was just riding
between three of them and one of them
took me for a ride. We were standing
out. It's kind of fun. Just wanted to
share that. Thank you. Did you enjoy
yourself? Of course.
Thank you for being willing in this way
to create within your imagination the
emotionality and the chord that will
step by step allow you to identify with
that you desire to identify with more
and more and more so that together you
will then sing the same song share the
same group we thank you sharing Bashar a
recently I became in touch with another
aspect effect of my reality and I found
myself aboard a spacecraft as a member
of the crew I piloted by uh Commander
Sulttech heading for a region of space
that was marked by four stars that were
almost in a square. Can you tell me
where I was going?
The idea in your interpretative form in
that way represents what might be termed
an energy gate, a grid, a portion of the
matrix that will be representative of
the gravitic dynamic tensor field
between the layout of those beacons to
allow you once you pass between them to
enter the fabric of a different
universe. You are tapping into different
aspects of yourself that are connected
in that way to those levels. None of
you, so to speak, are quote unquote
original to this planet anyway. And all
time being simultaneous, any other lives
and any other experiences that you have
had, are having, or will have, so to
speak, within many other civilizations
that exist, you can tap into right now.
Since all past and all future events
occur simultaneously, it is simply a
matter of tuning your vibratory
awareness or perspective to that
particular frequency that allows you to
know that all these events are going on
at the same time and allow you to
experience through the eyes of that
self. What is going on in that universe
in that life simultaneous with this
universe in this life? The two aspects
of yourself, this you, that you, being
fragments of the same whole
soul, you are in that way able now to
utilize that symbol as your symbol in
this life. If you wish to recreate that
in your imagination at any time, the
four points and treat it as a door,
treat it as a gate in the most literal
sense. And so that when you step through
it in your imagination, know beyond a
shadow of a doubt that you are entering
a truly different universe. And that
therefore in that universe you are a
truly different individual. If you will
then program the door with what it is
you wish it
to program into you when you step
through that door. Then you will come
out on the other side as that different
matrix, as that different person. You
follow me? Yes, you can utilize it as a
tool in your imagination in that way.
Does this assist you? Yes, it does. One
more question, please. Uh, what is the
nature of these space beings in the
vicinity of our planet who are hostile
to Earth and Earthlings?
Now understand
something. We will discuss this idea
with you if you will first
understand that the idea of any
consciousness which may be in your terms
negatively oriented can only form
connections with individuals who
believe that those individuals have the
power to force connections of that
nature upon them. In other words, only
your fear and only your concern that
they may have that type of power will
actually give them the type of power
necessary to form a link with anyone in
your civilization. Otherwise, if you
simply recognize that negative
individuals and negative consciousness
as there may be in many other worlds,
just as there are many negatively
oriented individuals on your own world,
does not mean that they must interact
with you. And that if you are willing to
simply be the
vibration, the frequency, the attitude
and the perspective of the reality you
choose to be, then they will not be able
to intercept your reality. You follow me
so far? Yes.
In this way, therefore, recognize that
the primary idea that still hinges in
many of your minds on negativity is an
expression that is most often
colloquially referred to as the Orion
complex. In this way recognize it is not
specifically isolated to the
constellation you refer to as Orion and
it does involve many other ideas of
systems throughout the idea of the local
galaxy as you call it. But in this way
also recognize that the reason for this
exists because many individuals upon
your planet now are literally
reincarnated Orions. In other words,
they have formed a connection to that
origin point so to speak. and have
reincarnated upon earth to allow
themselves to learn the balance of the
polarity of positive and negative so
that they can allow for only positive
manifestation in their lives. Switch
themselves to the frequency that is out
of touch, out of reach with the former
negativity that was inherent in the
original parent systems of the Orion
systems. In this way, you will find that
simply because time and space being what
they are and all things are
simultaneous, some of these original
Orion negative consciousnesses still
have the ability to be picked up on by
whatever individuals on your planet may
still choose to function along the same
old style frequency. Time and space not
being a barrier to the idea of
telepathic contact in any level in that
way. You follow me? Yes.
But the idea is also to recognize that
many of the individuals of the
Orion influenced so to speak, persuasion
so to speak are now and have been
allowing themselves to crystallize into
a very balanced idea of polarity. And
that energy in turn has allowed there to
be in the original home systems now the
creation and existence of light as well
as negativity. And in this way,
therefore, it would be our advice and
our suggestion to you that you simply do
not focus on the idea that there are
negative beings that do exist in the
universe other than those that exist
upon your own planet. that could perhaps
interact with you against your will and
simply focus on the reality you choose
to be. Which will then simply by the
fact that you will be on a different
frequency completely place you beyond
anyone's reach that is not on the same
loving frequency you follow. Yes. Does
that assist you? Yes, it does. Thank
you. We thank you for your willingness
to allow us to reflect to you the idea
of the reality you are choosing to
create upon your earth in this
transformational age. There is no reason
at this point any longer to have to feel
that you must struggle or fight or
create conflict in order to create the
realities and the harmonies that you
desire in your world. You follow it.
Yes. Thank you. sharing sharks you than
you and you
dolphin question speak up please speak
up please okay I'm sorry
um science seems to teach us that the
dolphins echoloccation devices work only
underwater uh done a lot of experiments that would
uh done a lot of experiments that would
prove otherwise that the dolphins can
locate things through the air and since
they apparently are liquid space they
they do function outside of the water as
well with these devices. As the link
with space, however, is mostly
telepathic and to some degree they are
using their telepathic
abilities out of the water in your air
and even when they are sounding under
the water. But there is a
shift in the frequencies within their
brain wave structure that takes place
when they are locating objects out of
the water as opposed to when they are
locating objects in the water. Why then
do they get caught in the matun? Why
then 50 or 60 or 70,000 dolphins a year
to die in nets that they could jump out
of. Apparently quite
simply understand in this way there are
a few reasons. First of
all, a dolphant since they are willing
to participate to some degree in the
overall idea of earth consciousness can
still create the idea you would call
disorientation. They can still create the idea of what
They can still create the idea of what
you would call false echoes or false
readings. At the same time, as we have
discussed already to some degree, many
of them have been willing to participate
in what may seem to be a painful
endeavor to them to allow your
consciousnesses to awaken to the fact
that you are now being forced to
interact with them and deal with the
situation so that you will then begin to
recognize them as equals rather than the
idea of simply slaughtering them because
they are in your way. Many of them will
simply unlock from their orientation
process to in a sense give themselves
over to the idea that they know whether
they have the specific awareness or not.
But the idea that they know will bring
them in closer contact with your
species. You follow me? Yes. This causes, as you
You follow me? Yes. This causes, as you
say, the hue and cry in humanity to
allow you to begin to relate to them as
equal beings so that they need not become
beings so that they need not become
caught any further in the webs that you
weave of structure and complexity and
invalidation upon the surface of your
planet. But they are willing to jump into the
But they are willing to jump into the
net in that way to point out to you how
confining are the webs you weave
and to allow you also to understand that
you are trapped by them just as much if
not more.
You follow me? Yes. Does that assist
you? Yes, it does. Thank you. Thank you.
I would like to ask you one other
question. All right. A month ago, we had
a baby dolphin and you indicated that it
was a boy dolphin and you suggested a
name which has been put forward. Aqua.
Nice. Uh Aqua has a has a a friend that
was born on Christmas Eve. And I
wondered if you could tell us whether
the friend is a boy or a girl and
suggest one more name. Belle.
Say again. Belle. Spell. Belle. B E L L.
Belle. What a wonderful name. Boy,
dolphin or girl? Belle. Girl. Girl.
Thank you. Thank you.
Uh Bashar, could you tell us a bit about
the use of crystals on our planet today?
And do you use crystals where you are
from? To some degree, yes. The idea of a
crystallin metallic matrix forms almost
all of the structures that we create
upon our planet. Though not exactly in
the same format as you are using
crystals, although there are
similarities here and there. The idea of
crystals very much can be very simply
put almost as if it is solidified
energy. The next step down from free
form energy altogether. The idea of
taking the free form primal energy out
of which all matter is created and
crystallizing, solidifying it, allowing
it to represent the primal or
fundamental idea, construct shapes
of the template which gives form to
physical reality. In this way, therefore, they
reality. In this way, therefore, they
are very close. They are bridges. They
are links between what you might call
denser matter and free energy and can
function as valves or gateways through
which the communication between what you
might call the more etheric levels at
the more densified material levels can
intertwine, can interfunction, can
intercommunicate. It is a step down
transformer or a step up transformer if
you will that allows the dense physical
matter to step up its energies into the
higher level to take effect and allows
the higher levels to step down its
energies into the physical reality to
take effect. It is a vow in that way and
can function according to whatever
pattern your consciousness programs onto
this particular matrix however you
choose to identify with it. You follow
me? Do recognize, however, at the very
same time that it is once again like
anything physical only a symbol of the
fact that you are your own master
crystal and you are the one that is
generating the power using a reference
point. That is something because you are
used to thinking in physical terms and
having physical tools. That gives you
the opportunity to allow your power to
function because you think many times
that it is functioning through this
thing that is externalized because many
times you do not believe that you have
the ability to contain the same amount
of power you think is inherent in the
crystal. But you are your own master
crystal. And the outer symbol is only a
reflection for the fact that everything
that occurs with the crystal you are
actually doing. But you are refining
your tools. You are becoming less and
less materialized in that way. And so
your tools are becoming more simplified,
more directly representative of the
energy out of which you are creating.
And so in this transformational age, you
are recognizing that many of the things
that may have taken much more complex
technological equipment to create upon
your planet now can be done through the
opaces of a very simplified molecular
structure. That is a very clear
representation of the manipulations of
the energies and the structures of the
energies themselves that you are dealing with.
themselves that you are dealing with.
You are removing bit by bit the middle
in between symbols and using symbols
that are now more directly reflective of
the energy that you are changing when
you are interacting with someone else or
another situation you does this assist
you yes thank you very much
I have two questions one you come from
the Christ light
in this way recognize what you call
Christ consciousness, Christ life from
our perspective is as follows. The
combined consciousness of your
consciousness of your
entire
world together knows itself also has a
together knows itself also has a
consciousness of itself also. This
consciousness out of which you all are
projected on your planet is what you
typically colloquially refer to as the
Christ light. Our
light. Our
civilization has its own version, its
own reflection, if you will, its own
mirror image of the idea you call the
Christ light. Our combined consciousness
aware of itself as a fragment of the
infinite creator. Our Christ light we
refer to as
shakana. Shakana. Our Christ light. Your
Christ light and the combined
consciousness of any civilization
together are the fragments that form up
the greater light, the greater love in
that way the infinite creation. So in
that sense we come through our version
of the Christlike light through your
version of the Christ light to translate
our patterns of awareness into your
patterns of awareness so that you can
understand us in that way. Our Christ
lights in a sense shakana and your
Christ identify as each other. So there
can be a bridge and a link between our
respective civilizations in a manner
that you will be able to understand us
and we will be able to understand you.
Together we are a part of the infinite
creation that knows the same dream and
creates the same reality. You follow me?
Does this assist you? Yes. Thank you. I
take a question. Um, are you familiar
with the ashtar command to some degree
although we will find that many
representations of that level of
consciousness of that group of beings
that your planet has tends to think of
them in a way that let us say creates a
religious perspective of them whereas we
know them from a different point of
view. You follow me?
What is that point of view? The point of
view is that they are simply one more
group of beings, one more reflective
aspect of what we call the greater
association. And in this way, they
represent themselves to you according to
whatever way your planet needs to
interpret their energy to allow them to
assist you to remind you to awaken you
to your own creatorhood. They are one of
the many groups assisting your world and
many worlds at this time and they are a
part of what we call the collective
association. Is your work like theirs then? Very
Is your work like theirs then? Very
much. Although you will find that we
have our specific ideas, our specific
place in the overall picture for now our
particular civilization is forming let us say a
civilization is forming let us say a
type of support group for many of the
other civilizations that have been in
direct contact with your world for far
longer than our civilization has. And
that is why you will find that the first
face-to-face contacts, physical contacts
between your civilization and other
civilizations will be between other
civilizations other than us. We once you
allowed yourself more familiarity and
more comfort with these primary
civilizations that have already begun
contact with you, we then will be
allowed to join in that grouping once we
have fulfilled our particular function
as support group to allow you to accept
the other civilizations that are your
brothers, sisters and cousins to begin
with with which you have a much closer
tie than you have with us. You follow
me? Thank you. Thank you. Bashar,
you spoke about
um struggle before. I find myself
involved with struggle which is
producing a fair amount of anxiety in my
life. All right. Perhaps it is the
anxiety that is producing the
struggle. Allow us to remind you first
of all that anxiety and excitement are
the same energy. But when you feel it as
anxiety, it is because you are not
trusting the excitement that you are not
trusting the flow of your energy. That
you are not trusting that the universe
works. When you put conditions and
invalidations on the excitement, it
turns into what you call anxiety. It is
only the negative pole of the same
energy that you often feel as
knowingness or excitement. You follow
me? Yeah.
Therefore, it is probably I will say the
fact that you are creating your
excitement into anxiety that causes the
struggle in your life rather than the
struggle causing the anxiety. Even
though once you began the cycle then you
may have reinforced the anxiety with
more scenarios of struggle.
It is always a
belief first that creates the reality
you experience in life and then you have
the emotional reaction to it. Now the
emotional reaction may reinforce the
original negative belief and then that
may re-reinforce the negative emotional
reaction which may re
reinforce the original negative
emotional and you become caught up in a
cycle where you don't know what came
first. But in this way, always recognize
emotional reactions are always secondary
to the primary belief. Anytime you find
yourself in a situation and you say,
"Well, I feel this way about that." You
feel that way because you believe that
way. You cannot feel anyway about
anything until you have a belief about
what that situation means to you. So if
you find yourself creating anxiety, if
you find yourself quote unquote
subjected to anxiety or stress causing
struggle, then allow yourself to
recognize that your belief that you will
attract situations in which you will
have to struggle is what is causing your
anxiety. Which then because emotion
emotion emotion energy motion is what
puts into action what you believe to be
true. Then you attract into your life
the physical representation of your
belief that you will attract struggle.
You then place yourself squarely in the
middle of that scenario. and placing
yourself squarely in the middle of that
scenario reflects back to you the tonal
disharmonics of anxiety as a reflection
to show you you have a negative belief
and therefore have created this
scenario. When you then
experience this scenario, you experience
the vibratory tone that goes with this
scenario based on your belief. Hence
anxiety. You follow me?
Are you sure? No. What were you saying?
I intellectually Oh, here it is again.
More separation. Oh, yes. I
intellectually understand you. But
emotionally and as as I embrace the
shift from third to fourth density and
as I follow my excitement, yes, I am in
a certain situation right now which I
know I am defining as limiting. Yes. But
but but but I will choose to define it
that way anyway. Is that what you are
saying? Um
yeah and that the majority
[Music] of it seems that third density is made
of it seems that third density is made
up of this particular limitation. Watch your
Watch your
definitions. Third density may be
defined by certain limiting parameters.
Yes. In no way, shape or form does that
imply that those limiting parameters
must inherently create negative
manifestation. Great. I'll accept that. All right. So,
Great. I'll accept that. All right. So,
do not just simply say, "Well, as long
as I'm going to remain third density,
I'm going to have to struggle out of
it." Because everyone knows third
density is inherently negative and a
nasty place to be.
It is not. Can I discuss a scenario
then? Absolutely. Thank you.
I came to Hawaii with uh funds that have
carried me this far. Nice.
And in following my excitement as a
uh custom builder and designer of houses
and saunas and the like. Nice.
I find that as my funds dwindle,
I think that I have to go after what I
would define as mundane and work as
uh not as a gifted carpenter but as a
uh as a mundane carpenter.
That does not bring me joy. But I find
that because of then why do you think
that way? Why do I think
go further with that. If that does not
bring you joy, why do you create that
scenario in your intellect? Why do you
say, well, if this happens, then there's
this bleak picture? Why do you create
that connection? If it does not bring
you joy, why do you say and insist,
well, if this continues to happen, it
will lead to
this. Why do you say that? And thus
create it in your reality.
I'm more than willing to stop
uh to cogn to cognizantly stop that
progression of thought. Then transform
it into what you
prefer. Recognize first of all again
once again abundance is not just what
you call monetary
funds. Abundance is the ability to do
what you need to do when you need to do
it. Period.
You follow me? There are many forms of
abundance. There are many ways, many
situations that could be attracted into
your life to allow you to do what
excites you the most. Many ways. It does
not always have to be just this way,
does it?
No. All right, then. Loosen up a little
bit. Lighten up on yourself a little
bit. Relax. How do I find out more what
um uh excites me and brings me joy
by acting
on
anything that excites you the most at
any given moment that you are capable of
acting on at that moment. Then that will
always lead to the next thing that will
excite you the most at that given
moment. Even if it is totally different
in outward appearance even though it may
not seem well I did this because it
excited me and now that leads me to this
because this excites me but these two
don't seem connected and I cannot see
how this is going to lead me into what I
really like to do what really excites me
in life but understand it does not have
to appear on the surface as if it will
lead you there it is the excitement
inherent within the situation that lets
you know that it is connected. So at any
given moment if you don't find that you
have the tools at hand as you say to
truly act upon a particular idealized
idea you would find most exciting then
at that moment act upon whatever
situation whatever opportunity is the
most exciting opportunity you are
capable of acting on at that moment. It
will lead to the other thing and it will
lead it through an experience you have
attracted into your life to allow you
the ability to fully appreciate the
other thing when it
comes. You follow me?
The words that keep coming into my mind
is making a living. Making a living.
Yes. All right. May I ask you a
question? Sure. Please do. Oh, thank you
very much.
Has anyone any time ever traded you
anyone any time ever traded you
something for something? Yes. Is that
not making a living? Yes. At any time,
have you ever found someone giving you
something and you were able to give them
something back? Yes. Is that not making
a living? Yes, it is.
Are you willing to allow that to be just
as valid a way to make a living as using
the symbolic middle symbol exchange of
money? Not totally. Why not? Um because
Not totally. Why not? Um because
Safeway won't take my uh won't take
those kind of notes. Who says?
Well, it it's it's a rather common who
says now me. Thank you. Very good. Very
good. Understand first of all that one
of the reasons you may be creating
difficulty in seeing a way out of this
is because you believe in the
mundane. And therefore you only think
that what you perceive to be mundane
will act and interact with you in
mundane ways and cannot interact in
magical ways. You follow me?
Yes. No. Maybe. Me.
What you are saying is that you are not
willing to exercise your imagination
enough to believe that there might be at
least one way that you could interact
with them that would perhaps not require
what you call the standard operating
procedure or can you right now let's
exercise that imagination of yours right
now. Are you willing? Sure. All right.
right now using your imagination, giving
it free reign. If it will make it any
easier for you, I'll remind you this is
only a
[Music] game. So you don't have to say, "Well,
game. So you don't have to say, "Well,
there's this." But in real life, for
now, just allow yourself to let your
imagination float freely and come
up with one. I will accept just one.
Only one. That's all. You have to come
up one way. No matter how preposterous
your ego says it might be or your
intellect or negative ego says that will
never work. Don't be silly. Remind your
negative ego and remind your intellect
and your
analysis right now. This is a game. Be
quiet. I'm playing. All right. Come up
with one way right now.
one in no matter how magical the
scenario can be. One way now that you
can imagine if you need food being supplied
imagine if you need food being supplied
with food without having to have the
symbol of money. Give me one imaginary
scenario wherein that might happen
between you and the establishment you
[Music] call. Come on. But I know you can do it.
call. Come on. But I know you can do it.
I got it. I got it. Uh standing at the
front door with a a radiant
uh loving character and smile. Yes. For
uh
And then what happens? I get showered
with food. Why?
That's what you're That's what you're
saying, right? There's my there's my
fantasy. Why? Why? Why? Why? Why do they
shower you with who? Because I'm giving
something. Ah. All right. Very good.
Now, do you uh if you will slip back
into your pragmatic self for a moment,
do you believe that that can happen?
No. All right. Very good. Do continue to
be just that honest. Now, go back into
your imagination game for a moment. come
up with another imaginary scenario that
would be let us say in your terms a
little closer to your pragmatic self
that you can still imagine might be a
reason might be a scenario wherein you
would still get the food you require. Uh
clean their front window.
All right. So you are saying that you
might do something and they would give
you the food and trade because you all
have explained you have no money but you
are willing to be of service and they
will return in kind the idea of service
in the form of food. Correct. Perfectly
mundane mundane. Many individuals are very
mundane. Many individuals are very
excited about cleaning windows.
Well, all right. Then using that
imagination I know you have. Pick a way
that is both pragmatic and exciting.
You have hit the nail on the head.
That's that's the struggle I am. Ah the
struggle struggle struggle struggle. All
right. then you are simply not allowing
yourself to understand one particular
thing. The idea at any given moment that
you are
being only can take its form from the
definitional ability you give it. So if
you say an idea cannot be pragmatic and
exciting at the same time, then you
won't allow yourself to attract into
your life a situational opportunity that
is both pragmatic and exciting because
you believe them to be mutually
exclusive definition. Why should they
definition. Why should they
be? You have already said that you enjoy
the idea of certain forms of
construction. You find that that is both pragmatic and
You find that that is both pragmatic and
exciting. Why can that idea that you
already have experience in not be
applied to other
scenarios? Why can it not be expanded to
include every scenario that is necessary
to occur in your life to allow you to
continue to be the pragmatic and
exciting individual you enjoy being?
Why can you not as the pragmatic
exciting individual attract only
scenarios that fit into the grooves of a
pragmatic exciting
individual? They are out there. There is
a situation to go hand in hand with
every other situation. Why should you
feel so deprived? Oh, there's no
situations for me out there. I am both a
pragmatic and exciting individual. And I
do not believe that there can be as many
pragmatic and exciting situations as
there are for let us say someone who's
just willing to be all pragmatic or all
exciting. There are just as many
opportunities for you according to the
definition you enjoy being as there are
for anyone else. Here's a pragmatic and
exciting way that you might allow to
attract into your life. You are walking
towards your safe
way. You know you are a pragmatic and
yet exciting
individual. And as you walk up, you
don't know what it is you're going to
say. It has not entered your imagination
yet, but you know you must get the food.
You are very hungry. So you say, "What
the heck?" And you walk toward and say,
"Well, I know I'll think of something. I
will trust that if I truly believe in
the person I am, a solution to fit the
person I am can occur. I can come up
with something. Something will come into
my life. So you walk up to the door,
steal yourself for a moment, remind
yourself how pragmatic and exciting you
are and how trusting you are that being
that way is exactly the way you truly
honestly wish to be. Double-checking
that you say, "Yes, that's the way I
choose to be in this universe.
Therefore, I know the universe will
support me in that way. I still have not
come up with anything to say to the
manager of this facility, but I know it
will come. I just know it. I don't have
to worry. The details will take care of
themselves and will occur in a way that
represents both a pragmatic and exciting
way. Walk through the door, lights and
bells go off. Congratulations, you are
the 1 millionth customer and you win 3
years supply of free food from Ta.
Ta.
Now that is as we understand your
society. considered both exciting and
pragmatic and it is also very pragmatic
because for them as you say it is part
of their promotional advertising. It is
a part of your everyday as you say work
a day world. It is nothing beyond your
ability to imagine happening to you. Is
it true? All right. Then allow yourself
the opportunity to understand one very
important point.
Nothing is too good to be
true. Nothing is too simple to be true.
Nothing is too easy to be
true. Life works when you let
it. Always. Any exceptions?
Always. Any exceptions?
None.
Always. If you are willing to
believe that your life
can become what we call an ecstatic
become what we call an ecstatic
explosion of
coincidence. Then you will understand
that life is an ecstatic explosion of
coincidence already. Life is
already. Life is
synchronicity. There are no accidents.
Not at all. Not one in all of the
infinite number of events that occur
within the
multiverse. Never has one accident ever
occurred. Never. It is all orchestrated in the
Never. It is all orchestrated in the
ways it needs to be to allow each and
every individual expression within the
whole matrix to be supported by the
whole matrix. It is
selfcreative, selfperpetuated.
Therefore, if you exist within this
matrix of the multiverses as the unique
you you are, no matter how many
countless billions of beings there may
be within creation, you are unique. And
if you exist, then that means you
deserve to exist. Obviously, the
infinite creator believes you deserve to
exist or you wouldn't. Therefore,
obviously, somewhere within this whole
matrix, you have a place. You fit in.
You are not disassociated from this. You
work and mesh smoothly with every other
gear in the
universe. All you need to do,
therefore, is allow yourself to trust
that you can fully be the gear you know
you are. You can fully do what excites you
are. You can fully do what excites you
the most. Excitement being your
indicator of the gear you are. What
excites you the most tells you what the
basic fundamental purpose of your life
is. Tells you what the vibrational
frequency of the path you chose to be in
this life is. So if you are willing to
believe truly trust
100% that you can be what you truly know
you are then you will know that you will
are then you will know that you will
allow not make not force allow the
totality of the rest of the universe to
work in harmony with you and for you to
work in harmony with it. And therefore
you will understand that you are always
supported in whatever you believe
yourself to be.
When you believe that you can function
in the way you wish to function and that
you will be supported in a manner that
will allow you to continue to be the
gear you have been created to be, then
you will relax and turn smoothly in
conjunction and in harmony with every
other gear. The tooth that needs to meet the
gear. The tooth that needs to meet the
other tooth in the other gear will meet
precisely the tooth it needs to meet and
no other.
The only time it does not seem that that
occurs is when you prevent yourself from
turning in a natural manner and then you
clog up the entire machine and nothing
seems to work for you. All you need to
do is let yourself turn as is natural
for you and everything in the machine
works fine. you
fine. you
follow. Also, trust that your
imagination can come up with scenarios
that are indicative of what you know
yourself to
be. Let life work for you and let
abundance into your life along the path
of least resistance.
If you can allow yourself to believe
that you could attract a scenario that
will bring you what you need faster than
if you tried to get the money to get it,
wouldn't you let it come or would you
insist on having to have the money even
though that may be the longer
path? Let abundance come to you in
whatever form represents the path of
least resistance. Do not invalidate it
as something that is not a
representation of abundance just because
it isn't
green just because you can't hold it and
fold it and put it in your
wallet. Do not invalidate abundance in
the forms it comes
naturally in the forms that come
quickest. Let your life become the ecstatic
Let your life become the ecstatic
explosion of co-incidence,
co-incidence,
synchronicity, always in the right place
at the right time, interacting with
exactly the right individuals to allow
you to be who you know you are. And at
the same time, you will provide for them
automatically the service that they need
to allow them to be who they
are. When you always interact only with
individuals that will provide exactly
the service you need and coincidentally
those individuals that provide you with
the service you need turn out to need
something that only you can provide
them. What do you need money
for? You
follow. Has this assisted
you? Take it to
heart. Relax. Enjoy. Love live. Let your
reality explode in ecstasy. Ecstasy is
your birthright. Ecstasy is what you are
created of. The infinite creator is
ecstasy. Float in an ecstasy.
Float in an ecstasy.
Float. Swim.
Move effortlessly. Find you for your
assistance. Pleasant dreams.
you. Yes. My idea of abundance is being
able to do whatever I want to do when I
want to do it and being in touch with
that universal flow of giving and
receiving with joy.
Would you talk a little bit about the
difference if any between need and want?
It will depend upon your focus within
the idea. Within the idea that you may
have created or within the belief that
you may have created that your conscious
analytical ego
mind is in touch or not in touch with
your total aware conscious being or soul
self. If you have created a scenario in which
If you have created a scenario in which
your conscious analytical mind truly
does not believe it is in touch with
your soul self, then you may find that
your conscious analytical mind may say,
"Well, you really do want
this." Because that would stroke the
ego. But if you find that your ego says
you want this, you really want this, but
the totality of your soul says you know
that you don't really need that in order
to be
happy. Then you will find the conflict
and the dichotomy occurring in your life
thinking that you will create
frustration because you do not seem to
be getting what you think you
need or want.
allowing yourself to recognize at any
given moment that if what you want,
really want is backed by
true harmonious desire through
integrity. Big point. Through
integrity, through an integrated point
of view, not a segregated point of view.
Then you can always get what you want
and what you want will be harmoniously
linked with what you
need. The outer conscious aspect of you
will be in accord with the inner
conscious aspect of you. as long as you
continue to create that
separator. Simply recognize that the
idea of not getting what you apparently
want and being frustrated by it may be
the lack of willingness to examine
honestly examine the true reasons for
why you want what you say you want. If
it is something that will result in the
idea of a segregation, a
separation, a limitation, an
elevation in an ego
sense, then you will find that generally
speaking, it will not be in accord with
what your total self truly
wants. And it may be only the result of
fearing to face your power and thinking
that well this is what I want and your
subconscious is going yes that's what
you want because it will distract you
from what you know you really want to do
because you are afraid to face that
because you think it will be an
unpleasant experience to learn about
what it is you really want. So you will
distract yourself by things you think
you want to keep you from the things you
truly want because you think they will
be difficult to get. You think it will
involve struggle.
I really don't believe me in struggle.
What's a good acid test
so you separate those two out forms?
Always you have the opportunity to
dialogue with yourself and examine your
beliefs. You are already or many of you
are already familiar with some of these
techniques as provided by the
consciousness you know as Lazarus to be
self-examinatory being very honest with
yourself about what you truly believe
you can and cannot have and
why getting in touch with yourself.
Truly being honest with yourself and
listening to the answer you get from
yourself as to why or why not you have
something in your life is the acid test.
Can you truly listen to yourself,
believe yourself and truly be willing to examine
yourself and truly be willing to examine
the belief systems you have bought into
in
life and know and be willing to trust
implicitly. 100% that anything you may
have created to go through to examine
any different portions or aspects or
levels or fragments of your
consciousness that you have separated
from the totality of yourself that you
now find yourself face to face with and
forcing yourself to examine. If you can
be willing to trust that it will only
add to your understanding and not create
the idea of struggle.
Then you will allow yourself at any
given moment to explore honestly,
openly, immediately, and
willingly any situation that seems to be
depriving you of something that you
want. You will not say, "Oh, I didn't
get what I want. What's wrong with me?"
You will not start feeling guilty. You
will not start saying there's something
wrong with you. Then you will not be
afraid or frustrated to examine yourself
to examine the beliefs you have fearing
that you will find that you will never
get what you want. That is the basic
reason why many of you create some
scenarios where it seems like you do not
get what you want because it is an
opportunity for you to explore a certain
idea about yourself to realize and to
discover certain beliefs you have bought
into. And then when you examine why you have
And then when you examine why you have
that belief and how the examination of
that belief adds to the overall
enrichment of the knowledge of the life
you are living because that's the
fundamental purpose of this life to
learn who you are from this point of
view. Then when you add that
understanding to yourself then you can
have anything you want anything else.
Paradoxically, you may find that when
you add that portion of yourself, you
may no longer want the thing you thought
you wanted. Because just getting the
understanding of why you created the
scenario to seem to be out of your reach
to begin with may actually give you all
you truly need and want. And the object
of your so-called desire, so-called
desire may turn out to be only a lure
that you placed in front of yourself to
make you reach as far as you needed to
reach. If you find at the end of this
honest self-examination that the desire
is still there, then understand that
that desire is representative of the
being that you are. At the same time,
you do not necessarily have to place
rigidized expectations that that desire
must physically manifest exactly as you
have perceived it or it is no good. Yes,
I do understand. Expectancy and
expectation are two different things.
Expectancy is the simple knowingness
that you deserve what will truly allow
you to be the most ecstatic being you
can be.
Expectation is many times the
invalidation that that comes to you in
ways you insist or demand it must come
or you will not allow it to come in any
other way because your ego thinks it
will not be a service to you if it comes
in any other way.
I do understand that and it works very
well. Um, in fact, I recently uh had a
chance to buy a car and then there was a
last minute hitch and it looked like it
wasn't going to work out. So, I thought,
well, okay, this isn't something I
really have to have. And so, I left even
though they tried dropping me into all
sorts of other things, it didn't really
uh align with my integrity as far as
promisary notes and so forth. And the
very next day they called me and said,
"We've solved the problem. We can drive
your car." You allowed them to be who
they were so they could interact with
who you were rather than creating
conflict and butdding your heads
together and having to go through
struggle and frustration. Yes. And it
really didn't matter to me. I
was I was totally willing to have it
happen or not happen. You see the idea
also and this is a very important point
is that many times when you go through
these scenarios you think oh poor me I'm
all alone in my struggle but recognize
many times the way the scenario plays
itself out is also so that the other
individuals in the scenario can learn
what they need to learn. It is not just
about you. Good point.
So
understand particularly if you know you
are interacting with other individuals
and that the interaction with that other
individual is necessary so to speak for
you to get what you need then let them
be who they are and let yourself be who
you are. So the interaction is honestly
between who you really are and not who
you are pretending to be and not who
they might be pretending to be.
Absolutely agree with that. also
recognize many times that when a
scenario seem seems
seems to quote unquote
fail, many times you are simply not
seeing the end of the scenario. You are
still in the middle, still in the
process, but you think, "Oh, well, that
didn't go through. That's it. I give up.
It's over. I'll never get this. I'll
never get anywhere." And then, as you
say, all of a sudden it turns around.
Turns out that different situations
change. Certain pegs fell into certain
holes there and here. Everything is
different. And oh, guess what? It's very
easy to do what we wanted to do now all
of a
sudden because the original hitch was
not the end of the scenario. It was the
fulcrum, the pivot point of the scenario
that allowed the scenario to transform
into what it needed to transform into to
allow the individual to truly be who
they are and not many times who their
ego thinks they should
be. You follow? Yes, I do. And I really
want to thank you for saying the other
day to me that there are no shoulds
because I've heard you say that before
and I know that's true, but suddenly I
I had a well I I really got it but I got
a a totally new understanding and that
is that there really are no two. We only
create our own guys. You create your
reality. Yes. There are no
qualifications on that
statement. It is as general as it
sounds. It is as
all-encompassing as it sounds. You
create your experiential physical
reality.
Ultimate freedom and yes ecstasy. Yes.
Thank you. Because then you are free to
create anything when you know that if
you are responsible for everything you
attract into your life. Then if you
choose to understand responsibility does
not have to be the negative pole of
blame. But that responsibility means you
are free to create whatever you truly
desire. Then you are free and you are
able to recognize that truly are you
made in the image of the infinite
creator and that you yourselves are also
infinite creator.
Thank you. Thank you.
You given that all things are creation.
We create everything in this gross
physical matter. a denser matter and to
some degree in many of the more rarified
non-physical levels as well. Emotion
being the same energy as life in a sense
everything in physical reality is a
manifestation to some degree of what you
would call life. If you bring your
desire therefore your emotion
into alignment with the gross physical
matter. Let's take for instance your
body ice and
you with your desire raise that
molecular structure through emotion to a
higher vibration do you take the physical
vibration do you take the physical
matter out of the evolutionary process
there what I mean what I'm getting at is
when you desire something say an
instantaneous manifestation if it was coming through
manifestation if it was coming through
simply a physical point of view it would
take time through the evolutionary
process to manifest on a physical plane
through emotion with desire as does that
speed that's processed up to within the
speed of light bring it into
instantaneous manifestation. It can.
Yes, you will find that even though you
may not have perceived it through the
physical channel, what you have said
gave us great cause for laughter, not
action. Because the idea you have
expressed is the mechanism of evolution
regardless of the speed.
Desire. Yes. Through thought. Yes. On
the demonstration plane to the physical.
Yes. That is the mechanism of evolution
regardless of the speed. Okay. Um you've
been talking a lot other people have
been expressing in scenarios as far as
letting go of things in their desire
does manifest freely. Yes. Through this body.
manifest freely. Yes. Through this body.
Yes. When block because of negativity
are released and with trust and what we
have traditionally called faith. Yes. It
is the mechanism. It is all you need.
That's it. It's that simple.
I wanted an affirmation. I that has been
that came to me in a dream and it was
introduced to me by another channel. We
thank you for allowing us to reflect
what you already know to be true. One
more thing. All right. When you choose a
vehicle to come into on this
demonstration. Yes. What is your
criteria? depends on what you wish to
learn. When you come to us
When you come to us
to talk to us or demonstrate your
knowledge to us, what was your criteria
for entering this particular vehicle
you're in right now? First of all,
recognize it is not so much that we are
here to demonstrate our knowledge to
you. We are here to reflect your
knowledge to you.
The idea as was expressed by the
physical channel before we commenced
this channeling is that together my
consciousness and the consciousness of
the physical channel before you prior to
what you call this physical channel's
life created the agreement to do what we
are doing with you
now. It was as you say 5050 or 100%
100%. On both of our parts to agree to
assist in the transformation of this
world in the way we are doing so
everything is always by agreement. Like
vibration attracts like vibration. That
was the criteria that the existence of
the transformation was perceived and
that the desire to assist the
transformation occurred in the physical
channel and in us and so we made the
agreement to work together.
Enlightenment would be a process of
remembering that state then. Yes. All
learning is the process of remembering
more and more of who and what you are as
a creator.
Thank you. Thank you.
All right. You first.
Yes. I have two questions. All right.
All right. First of
all, I would
like I would like to thank you for
answering so many of the questions that
I This is only synchronicity. Again, the
idea that everything is intershed and
when everyone allows themsself into the
flow, they will always find what they
need right at hand in perfect timing.
Some time ago, I came in contact with an
expression called the Jonah expression,
and I was told that uh speak up. I was
to act as a channel for this
expression. I did so and fell away in
doing that. All right. And presenting to
others. All right. Um I have been on for
5 years and I have not done that. I have
been more like working refining myself
getting to know who I am. Guys, I would
like for you to sort
of the process that might assist me
in moving back into that joyous state.
Are you doing in your life? What excites
you the most?
Not at this time. Why not? [Music] [Music]
We'll wait.
[Music]
It seems that um I have placed some
limitations. Why?
How does it serve you to do so? What are
you learning by placing those
limitations? If you believe you truly
have
them, you believe you truly have them.
No. Are you playing a little game with
yourself?
Are you doing what excites you the Yes. No.
Yes. No.
Maybe. Maybe. What would you like to do
that you are not doing now?
I would like to
be in channel. In what way? in a similar
way as the man that you are expressing
to. Why?
Assisting to bring about the transition,
the transformation. Why in that way?
God gave me much joy when I was. All
right. What in your mind prevents you
from doing
so? Responsibility at this point
Responsibility at this point
responsibility
relationship relationships child
child how do each of these things stop
you from doing what you wish to do why
are they not again as we were discussing
the idea of mutually inclusive
definitions why are they not capable of
being a part of your mutually inclusive
definition rather than a mutually
exclusive definition. I cannot do this
if this exists. I cannot do this if this
exists. Why?
That is could you speak to the Jonah
expression? What? Not until you do
first. We can only go through the gate you are.
We can only go through the gate you are.
And if you are not willing to open it
yourself, we cannot enter uninvited.
Now, what about these belief systems
that you have bought into makes it seem
so certain that you cannot do what you
truly wish to do just because certain
situations exist in your life?
Why do those certain situations to
you inherently
mean that you cannot do what you wish?
Why are you choosing to give that
meaning to those situations when no
situation means anything
intrinsically? No situation has builtin
meaning. No symbol has builtin meaning.
They are all neutral props, blank,
empty, zero. You fill them with the
meaning you think they have based upon
what you have been taught to believe a
certain symbol or situation represents.
The meaning you fill the situation with
determines the effect you get out of it.
Positive meaning in, positive effect
out. Negative meaning in, negative
effect out. So if you believe that just
because this situation, this
relationship, this responsibility, if
you believe that means intrinsically, oh
well, here's this situation, that means
I can't do what I wish to do. If you
believe that, then of course you
reinforce that scenario in your
life. But why choose to believe that
they hinder you? Why not choose to
believe they enhance your ability to do
what you wish to do?
[Music]
Yeah, she can believe that.
Believe which that
I will be able to do
that you what that I will be able to
that you what
that I will do what will I will when be
when now. Ah then the phrase I believe
in your language is that I am doing it
not I will be able.
All right. Now, do you truly believe that
right. Now, do you truly believe that
this is
certain and do you? Yes, I do. The
whole expectancy. All right. And the
knowing that this is coming about in the
time that I have spent here on Maui is a
refinement to your preparation.
Ah, then you are willing to allow
yourself to know that all the
circumstances in your life are a part of
the path you chose to be and not an
interruption in it. A thank you very
much. Then allow yourself to recognize
that at any time you consciously choose
to decide to begin to do what you truly
love to do, everything and every
consciousness that needs to be there
will be there.
that is from them.
Thank you. Thank you. Understand this.
Many of you
forget that you as a conscious being
have the ability to recognize that when
you make a conscious
choice that that is just as valid a way
to allow the total energy you are to
begin to work in concert.
You don't have to say, "Well, until I
hear it directly from my higher
consciousness, I will not allow my
conscious mind to have the ability to
decide consciously that this is what I
can do." But you see, your higher
consciousness is waiting for your
conscious mind to decide that that is
something you do want to do. And then it
will always be there for you. The
instant you consciously decide, hey,
this is what I really want to do.
Starting right now, bang, your reality
changes. It will then begin to transform
and bring to you faster and faster as
you say all of the things that show you
you have changed. Do remember
this. You do exist in the physical
reality. And so yes, you still have some
concept of linear
time. But the idea is that when you
decide that you have changed, then you
have changed. Your physical reality may take
changed. Your physical reality may take
may take a little bit of time in order
to reflect the change you have made. But
you take no time to change because you
span all
dimensions. Allow yourself to know that
when you decide you are different, allow
yourself to know you are different. And
therefore since you know that the
physical world around you and the
physical situations around you since you
know they don't have any builtin
meaning then when you see a certain
situation perhaps okay you say all right
I've changed but look there's the same
situation again I'm still in the same
rut I have not changed when you act that
way then you are not acting like the
person you say you believe you have
become you are acting like the old
person and reinforcing the old reality
by insisting that just because a
scenario looks the same on the surface
that it means the same
thing. When you know you are a new
person and begin to treat what may
appear on the surface to be the same old
scenario as if it were a new scenario
and act towards it with your attitude as
a person that you have become would act
towards it. When you put new meaning
into the old appearances, then you allow
the old appearances to transform and
take on the appearance of the new
meaning. Now you will find that again
because you exist in the physical
reality. This may appear to take a
little bit of time, but you will also
find this within your physical reality.
this within your physical reality.
for almost all changes that are
necessary to occur in your
life. Anywhere between three of your
days and three of your weeks is almost
always the time that is necessary for
any change in your life.
It
can days. It can. But in general, 3 days
is always more than enough for almost
any scenario to change in your life. And
3 weeks an absolute
certainty. It can happen in as little as
3 days. It can happen instantaneously.
We simply perceive that based upon the
threshold of belief most of you hold on
to you will not allow it to happen any
sooner than 3 days. It can but in
general 3 days is always more than
enough for almost any scenario to change
in your life and 3 weeks an absolute
certainty. You follow me? When you truly 100% allow
You follow me? When you truly 100% allow
yourself to act as you believe you now
are, the universe will support you 100%.
And 3 weeks is almost always the enough
amount of time necessary to allow all
the other individuals you will interact
with to also get themselves geared up to
interact with you. That is the only
reason it really takes any time at all
is because you are not doing this alone.
You are a cog that intershes with other
gears. And when you change yourself,
that is enough time to allow them to
orient to the new direction in which you
are spinning. You follow me?
Yes. No. Maybe. Yes. Thank you.
Has this assisted you? Yes. Very much.
Also to you pleasant and active and
informative dreams for there will be much
dreams for there will be much
communication.
Open and relax. Enjoy. Most of all, most
of all, enjoy.
All right. All right. Thank you very
much. Would you all enjoy a short break?
Yes. Yes. Then by all means, we will
resume shortly.
I say sharing you. Um I have two
questions. The first speak up. The first
is um being that everything is
synchronous, I have an event that um
that that I experienced that I'd like
you to sort of comment on. Yep. I was
camping out the other night and this
crab that was about 5 or 6 in in
diameter, caught up on my sleeping bag
and when I sat up it sort of fell beside
me and I kind of prodded it to move and
it wouldn't move and then I shined a
flashlight and it wouldn't move and it
stayed there all night long um and kind
of nuzzled up towards my sleeping bag. I
see. And then it didn't leave in the
morning until I got up to stretch. And I
just thought that was kind of peculiar.
Why? Well, because I'm not aware that
crabs like to, you know, hang out in
your sleeping bag. You are now.
But in this way, as you say, they were
hanging out with you with your energy,
with the
identification of your awareness of
natural motion. In this way, in a sense, as a
motion. In this way, in a sense, as a
symbol, as a guide, as a reflection, it
imparted to you a reflection of a new
level of your consciousness with regard
to tapping into a new level of
understanding of natural motion, motion
through nature. Now, there will be more
nature. Now, there will be more
conscious understanding of the idea of
what motion is and the mechanics of
motion. For in a sense, of course,
nothing ever really moves. That is your
illusion as
well. And when you have an inherent
understanding of that, then you can
realize that it is more in a sense
accurate to say that all of creation
moves through you. And in this way, when
you allow creation to move through you,
rather than feeling like you must make
your way through the vast distances of
time and
space, then it will appear to those who
still perceive that you are moving
through space as if you glide with a
flexibility that you adhere to for not
possessed. You will move silently,
swiftly in that way after the manner of
the animal that reflected that idea to
you where you can shift parallel
realities very easily. You can slide
from side to side, from reality to
reality, moving
smoothly in its way, in your way. It
imparted to
you. let us say imprinted into you into
your cellular consciousness the very
essence of the understanding of natural
motion being that which will then appear
to allow you to slide smoothly through
space and time. You follow me? Yes, that
fits perfectly.
The other question I had was could you
tell us a little bit about um love
making and courtship on Asani? Since
you're all telepathic, how that would be
different than we do it here? First of
all, allow us to remind you that we
always allow whatever
relationship any individuals find
themselves attracted into to be an
obvious reflection of the things that
they need to understand and learn at
that point. And we allow the
relationship to be what it is forward
again rather than perhaps what we think
it should be. We simply find that any
attraction has its reasons and therefore
we simply interact according to our
instincts. There is not so much the idea
as you say of courtship in that way. For
any individual to find themselves
interacting know they are interacting
for a reason and simply follow their
emotions and instincts accordingly
knowing that whatever comes up for them
in that way if they are functioning
within their integrity is what belongs
in that relationship and they simply
respond to those ideas. Do remember
every individual within our society
considers him or herself to be in a
sense married to every other individual.
So since we are already already married
in that sense there is no need for a
courtship. You follow me? Yeah. In this
way therefore the relationship simply
unfold according to what each and every
individual has brought into it. And as
they continue to unfold no matter in
what way they appear to transform
themselves. If they are allowed to
transform naturally, then we simply take
it for granted. That is the way they are
supposed to quote unquote transform in
that way. And we continue to live our
lives allowing one relationship to blend
into another circumstance and allowing
them all to intermesh together into
one act in a sense of love making over
the whole world. So in a sense, you're
making love all the time.
Nice. Sounds great. Thanks. In a sense, so are
Sounds great. Thanks. In a sense, so are
you all? Evolving.
Evolving.
Yes. Could you also tell us a little bit
more about when you all decide to have
children? What again? We are always in
touch telepathically, consciously with
the entity, the consciousness who
chooses to be born. And when we simply
agree to recognize the timing of the
event in that way for what purpose that
individual wishes to experience a
physiological life in our world then we
are simply aware of when that timing is
and the birth does not occur. The
conception does not occur prior to that
timing and when we know we are in touch
with an individual then it simply does
not occur prior to that timing for any
other reason. And so we are in contact
with the consciousness all the way prior
to birth through birth and in this way
into the physical birth into physical
life. And there is a very brief
orientation period for the consciousness
to acclimate itself to the new matrix
into which it has imposed its
consciousness. No more than what we have
called in your terms three approximately
of your years is necessary for the
individual to begin functioning fully as
a member of our society in full
consciousness. Then even as what you would call a
Then even as what you would call a
child, they go on their way attracting
themselves to whatever other individuals
are the individuals they need to
interact with to learn what they need to
learn to live the life they chose to
live in our society. Always remembering
their biological parents. For we are
never out of
touch. And in this way also recognizing
that every adult is their parent and
every adult recognizing that every child
is theirs and acting
accordingly. Not only is it in that way
the idea of marriage in terms of the
relationships of what you would call
adults, but it is all truly one family.
No one ever loses a child. No child is
ever lost.
You follow me? Yes. So, how often do you
yourself actually engage in the physical
act of making love? Whenever it comes
up. How often is that? The idea occurs
simply spontaneously wherein the reflection of
spontaneously wherein the reflection of
my life so attracts an individual who
wishes to interact in that way. do
recognize that at this time in our
society, even though it does contain
remnants of what you would call a
physiological act, it is also more of an
energy act at this time.
So you do it more energetically than
physically in a sense. It is a true
exchange of blending and identification
as it is like
unto moving into a common
daydream, sharing therein the exchanges
of emotionality and desire. And in this
way, simply recognizing that this act
fully as fulfilling on every level, as
you are used to thinking of the idea of
consummation, will in this way cause
whatever cellular changes and structures
need to change within our physical
forms, that which we maintain to be the
belief of our physical form, and will
instigate the union, if
necessary, of the third identity wishing
to be born. If not then it will simply
consummate according to whatever we have
to learn from each
other. It is not that we can in a sense
give you any particular idea of
regularity. It is always
spontaneous and in that sense always in
a sense unknown until it
happens. We simply accept it for what it
is when it happens. Is that what you
feel when you're coming through the
channel sharing this daydream? In a
sense, yes. It is a form of love making.
That is why when each and every
individual on your planet is in love
with every other individual, you will
also be of one mind and then you will be
telepathic. You will identify as each
other. Therefore, you will interpret the
vibrations of infinite creation in a
similar way. That is why as we have said
individuals on your planet who you
recognize as being in love often share
the same thoughts. It is not that they
are literally reading each other's mind
directly. It is that they are on the
same wavelength and so the vibrational
pattern that they are sharing the
similar idea interprets the infinite
creation in a similar manner in similar
thought form. So in this way you can say
in a sense the physical channel and I
are now exhibiting to you an act of
being in love.
So the concept of marriage or the
institution of marriage is is is not on
your planet. Not in the ritualized form
that you experience it. Well, for we
recognize that the act itself is the
thing and there is no need for anything
else that needs to reinforce that act.
It simply is what it is. And if that
desire is not there, then no ritual will
make it mean anything more anyway.
You follow me? Yes. In that way, it is
once again like the economic standard
simply something that to us would be a
middle ground symbol rather than a
direct exchange. Things are always fluctuating
anyway. There may be individuals who
choose to attract into their lives the
situation where they experience what you
would call a onetoone relationship with
one individual for the period of the
lifespan. But there are many individuals who do
But there are many individuals who do
not. Many individuals who interact with
many other individuals over the course
of a lifespan because they have created
and co-created with those other
individuals that many reflections to
learn what they need to learn about
themselves and others and different ways
of being of service in that
life. You follow me? Mhm. So again, we
simply recognize that any interaction is
the product of what an individual is if
they are honest and within integrity of
themselves. and therefore will play
themselves out at whatever rate they
need to regardless of any structure that
may be imposed upon them. It will not
change a thing. Even in your society,
you truly do recognize this idea. For
even though you have created the idea of
a structure of marriage to ensure the
interaction, when you know the
interaction changes, you create the
structure of divorce.
You follow? Yes. In this way, we simply
act and interact in all ways. And since
we are always loving in that
interaction, then we know that any
transformation that takes place is
always for the positive. And we always
in some way always remain in any
relationship that has been created. Any
relationship once created goes on
forever no matter how many different
ways it may transform.
And that's what we're moving into now.
It is what we perceive your planet to
be. Understanding. Yes.
Great. Thank you very
On that same note, um I have some
questions about Could you speak up
please? About energy matching when you
meet somebody who you feel on a feeling
level totally comfortable with. Guys,
it's confusing to me then to discover
that when we learn more about each
other's way of life, belief systems,
values that there can be such a discord
between that feeling level and the way
we live our lives. That is only when the
ego gets into it. In this way, in a
negative sense, you will find that the
original matching vibration is an
indication that you have made an
agreement to attract yourselves to each
other to show probably in your case
specifically the idea that the
differences between you will enrich each
of your lives. And that any unity you
wish to create, whether in a
relationship or on your planet as a
whole, will only be the result of when
you grant equality and validity to the
diversity within your culture.
You follow me? Yes. But it's it still
seems very difficult to stay in that
situation. I guess that is simply the
way you have been taught to believe. If
you are willing to know that the
vibration you feel is the love that went
into making the agreement to be together
to begin with, then you will simply
recognize that what it is that
individual is is there as a gift to
teach you certain ideas that you have
chosen to believe you need to see in
your life to learn something
from. Now this can take many forms.
There can be situations where one
individual attracts themselves to
another individual because there is
something that individual needs to learn
by seeing certain things in the original
individual. And also there can be the
idea that an original individual may
need to learn something specific from
the other individual they are attracted
to. There is always a two-way street. It
is never one-sided. But you may find
varying degrees of
relative let us say importance in that
sense or relative significance in that
sense as to what any one individual may
need to learn about themselves by seeing
certain things in another individual.
You all act as mirrors for each other.
You attract yourselves into
relationships to reflect back to you the
things that you have agreed to learn in
this life. the things that you have
agreed to learn so you can share more
and more and more of yourself with all
that is any conflicts that you may find occur
is any conflicts that you may find occur
in relationships usually stem from the
idea of what you have been taught to
believe you are supposed to see in a
relationship. So you place an
expectancy, you place a framework, you
place a filter, you place a structure,
you overlay that relationship with that
structure and say, "Well, let's see.
This peg does not fit here. This peg
does not fit here. Something's wrong.
There's a conflict." But
understand, the only conflict is in
having been taught to create the filter
through which you are seeing the
relationship and therefore not seeing
the relationship for what it is. But
what you have been taught to think it
should be to fulfill your
expectations rather than simply be
representative of your expectancy. See
is this making any sense? Yes. All
conflict in that way usually comes from
invalidating judgments, preconceived
beliefs or notions that you think are
what should represent the relationship
rather than allowing the relationship to
be seen for why it truly is
there. All relationships are the product
of unconditional love in the sense that
that is why you agree to interact.
Allow yourself to experience the other
individual unconditionally. And again, do remember
unconditionally. And again, do remember
this. Many individuals in your
society will not allow themselves to
know they are complete and happy
individuals until they have the
relationship they think they should
have. But when they proceed through life
in that manner, they will generally only
wind up attracting into their lives a
relationship that will reflect their
belief in their own
incompleteness. When you know you are
complete and happy individual
intrinsically in that way, then you will
attract into your life a relationship
that will reflect that completeness,
reflect that happiness. And so you can
share as equals. If you think you need
the relationship in order to complete
yourself, in order to give you a reason
other than just being yourself to be
happy, then you will not actually relate
to that other person as them. And
because you believe yourself to be
incomplete, you will not give them
anything to relate to except a shadow of
themselves, of their own doubts, of
their own beliefs, and their own
incompleteness. And perhaps vice versa.
That may be why you may attract certain
individuals in that way to show you that
you may doubt your own completeness in
that sense. You follow me? Yeah. Is any
of this assisting you? Yes, it is. So,
what I'm getting is that it's important
to to stay even though it's
uncomfortable. Oh, no. No, no, no, no,
no, no, no. If the if the original
feeling is good, understand this. If at
any time you recognize within a
relationship that the vibration of what
you know to be true for
you is not being
reflected, then understand what you have
attracted into your life basically is
for the purpose of allowing you to
always know what is true for you. And if
you see that that is not being reflected
back anymore. And if you know that your
integrity is intact and that you are not
maliciously hurting the other person
consciously, then if you find that the
relationship in that way no longer
serves you, there is no reason to
maintain it on your part regardless of
what the other individual says they will
feel like. If you decide to change, you
are not responsible for another
individual's feelings. You are
responsible to them to always be the
fullest possible representation of
yourself you can be. Otherwise, if you
are not, if you live your life according
to what they say you should live your
life as, then they are not in a
relationship with you. They are in a
relationship with themselves.
You follow me? Yes. Always be true to
yourself. Recognize that when you simply
put out what the vibration is that you
are, if the same physical individual
chooses to maintain the relationship
with you after you have changed in ways
you know represent the truess to
yourself, then they will have to change
their vibration anyway and they will not
literally be the same person anyway. So
what difference does it make? Whether it
is a different physical person or a
different energy person. Whatever person
needs to be there to reflect the newness
you know exists within yourself will be
attracted into your life to reflect the
level you now exist upon. If it is the
physical same person, it will not be the
same true person anyway. So it is not
like you have to hold on to that
physical person just because you
recognized at first that there was
something that you had. Many times you
will have that initial understanding
that initial identification and that
initial attraction so that you will
fulfill the agreement perhaps in this
case the agreement being that that
individual is attracted into your life.
Then you go through a change. That
individual does not change. And then you
recognize that that individual is what
allowed you to change. But if that
individual will not change with you,
then perhaps they need to interact with
someone else to allow them to change in
a different way as well. Not everyone
has to physically remain in your
proximity to continue the relationship
with you. A relationship once started
goes on forever. No matter what the
physical definition either, you may
never physically see each other again,
but that's the definition of the
relationship that represents the
vibratory level you're on and the
vibratory level the other person is on.
If they are not willing to change to
your vibratory level and you are not
willing to change to theirs, then it
does not do you usually a positive
benefit to hold yourselves in that sense
together when you are always yearning to
speed away. You follow me? Yes. Always
trust that if you know you are
functioning within your integrity, you
know you are not consciously maliciously
attempting to hurt another person, then
simply relax and rely that you can be
true to yourself. And if the other
person says, "Oh, but you are hurting me
by doing that." No, they are choosing to
create the hurt for themselves.
And you by fully being who you are, only
then can you give them the best
opportunity and assistance to recognize
that if you are willing to stay fast
with what you know to be true for you,
they have the same potential. And
perhaps your willingness to stand up for
who you are will be what allows them to
also make the changes that they need to
make in their lives. But if you
constantly reinforce in another
individual the idea that they
can in your terms force you to remain in
a situation that you know is not true to
you. Then you are only perpetuating in
them a lack of a need to change in the
ways that they need to change because
you are saying it's all right. Stay the
way you are. Do not change. If you find
that this creates negativity, that's all
right. I'll support you. Create the
negativity. Stay that way. Do not
change. Do not grow. Do not learn how to
create your own reality. And do not be
responsible for your life. You follow
me? Yeah.
The way to very often best assist
another individual when it seems they
are creating problems in their life with
regard to a relationship is to always be
true to
yourself. Because then at least they
have the most complete
reflection of who you really are, who
they are really interacting with and who
through you they may be able to
learn themselves to
be. But if you are not willing to be
you, you give them nothing to base any
understanding of what is possible for
them. You follow me? Yes.
For there is no echo, no
reflection except their own voice.
You follow me? Yes. Has this assisted?
Yes. Thank you. Thank you very much for
being willing to explore that facet of
the multi-dimensional crystal that you
are. Shine brightly. Thank you. For
sure. For sure. Yes.
um you and then you I I would like to
cocreate with you a belief and
understanding about what your current uh
presence and our current presence in uh
the Maui Island represents.
Um I see I experienced this as a second
in a series uh the first one having
occurred last August in which in my
perception there was a great stimulation
a simultaneous input of energy into the
planetary heart and a expression from
the planetary heart out.
This current trip seems to have a
somewhat different feeling, a kind of an
immersion or a release of to a degree an
oceanic consciousness. All right. Um,
and I was wondering if you could is very
connected to the idea again of allowing
blending to occur with the dolphin and
whale consciousness. Yeah. and also to
release that hard energy particularly at
a time when as you already know your
world was combined in a desire for
peace. This time it's right now it's combined
This time it's right now it's combined
into peace meditation. Oh thank you. Oh
remember peace what you wanted. Yep.
What you still want. Yeah. All right.
The timing is specifically for the
aiding and assisting and the
amplification and the unification of
those energies. The desire for one
world, one world, not only being the
unification of all the land, human, but
also between the two species upon your
planet. You follow me? Yeah. Does that
assist you? Yes. I have a second
question. No. All right.
Um, let's see. I I have formal training
in psychology and one of the experiences
that um has unfolded for me in working
with these new metaphysical ideas has
been a very strong sense that any notion
that I previously had of what a
personality could
be has come to feel completely
inadequate to the phenomena which I
experience within me in interacting with
you and other
entities And I'm wondering if you could
share a model or a way to understand
personality that
is
inclusive of all these different levels
of
relationship. I'm also wondering what's
going on in terms of your energy right
[Music] now. A different form of
enlightenment. We are now speaking to
another level. Since you wish
to explore the idea of what has
previously been relegated to the
unconscious to the darker sides as you
are used to thinking of it. Then let us
explore this dream reality together with
only the idea of the light within the
beings that we are being necessary to
illuminate all that we need to
understand. All right. All right. All right. In this
All right. All right. All right. In this
way, remember that what you call a
persona or a personality is an
artificial construct, so to speak. It is
the representative form through which the
representative form through which the
total consciousness that you are at any
given moment chooses to present or
represent itself as this particular idea
of physical reality. The persona is an
extremely malleable tool.
It is the
interface literally between the
non-physical and the physical. It is the
way the idea you are being at any given
moment as a non-physical being can
express itself in physical terms as a
physical universe. You are a
universe. You are a
multi-dimensional
simultaneous consciousness. Therefore, personas only
consciousness. Therefore, personas only
being artificial malleable constructs in
your terms can range a wide gamut and
fluctuatability and can run rampant. As
you say, as you change the idea of
yourself as you explore another facet of
yourself, a whole new persona can emerge
to represent that particular frequency
you are now on.
It is quite
interchangeable, quite
rapid. You are all of those personas
combined in one idea. And at any given
moment, the total consciousness that you
are can be any one of those reflective
persona to show the exteriorized world,
the physical reality world. This is the
idea I am being at this moment. and
recognize that since one of the ideas of
the transformational age is to increase
your flexibility. Then you will find that
flexibility. Then you will find that
when each and every one of you begin to
open up into the avenues as the
conduit of the total consciousness that
you are. You will explore with and
experiment with many different
fragmentaryary persona to give yourself
the understanding more and more that you
are very flexible as a being, very
flexible as an idea, that you are not
rigidly stuck in anything. Nothing is
chiseled in steel. It is all thought
forms, light and
shadows. That is all a persona is. It is
a reflection, a light form, a
shadow. It is an
interplay. It is the
intersection between your non-physical
total awareness and the idea of physical
reality. It is the
intersection. If you think of yourself
as a holographic
matrix, XYZ coordinates everywhere, then you can
XYZ coordinates everywhere, then you can
understand that at any given moment with
a subtle shift of your consciousness,
you can become another XYZ coordinate or
you can be XYZ prime or XY prime Zprime
or XP prime YP prime Zprime or any of
these ideas. You can move through the
whole matrix that you are and at every
new XYZ
XYZ
intersection that will be a new
persona but they will all be a part of
the total idea that you are. You follow?
Yes. Can you include now in this
construct relationships with higher
self, future selves, past selves?
You only need to expand the idea of the
holographic matrix. You can say that
this Z
plane and all the intersections in that
represent my linear life on Earth, birth
to death. And that this Z plane,
parallel Z plane, represents the last
life I had, so to speak. It is only a
matter of how you choose to view the
holographic matrix. That is the beauty
of the nature of the design. Being
holographic, whatever experience you get
out of it completely depends upon how
you structure the way you look at it as
a reference beam to begin with. I could
use some clarification on that. The idea
is that every single point within the
hologram contains the potential to be
any single point within the hologram.
They are all neutral. When you say XYZ
now represents this reference point,
then branching out from that, all of the
other reference points fall into place.
When you say that this XYZ reference
point now represents something
different, then everything shifts with
it. It is that flexible, that malleable.
The idea once again of what we have
referred to in your society as Indra's
net. It is one of the primal ways to
describe the holographic matrix of
physical reality. It is a net made of
many pearls.
Each pearl being totally 360° spherical
and reflective contains the image of
every other pearl in the net. Therefore,
the information of the whole is in the
one. So it does not matter in a sense
where you start. When you decide to make
a difference that creates the
difference. If you say this pearl now to
me will only show me one of the
reflections of the other pearls or 99 of
the reflections of the other 100 pearls
that will demand what the rest of the
reality will be like and will set up the
timelines and the linear connections
that you perceive to be so rigidly fixed
in your world as the laws of physics. M
you follow me? It's beautiful. It is
very simple and that is why it can be as
complex as it needs to be. It is so very
simple. It can get as complicated as you
like because every single point contains
the potential to be any other single
point or combination of points. It is a
simplicity which allows for absolute
infinite diversity. What you get out of it is
diversity. What you get out of it is
totally what you put into
it. And you are saying to us that the
way we choose what we put into it is
through trust. Is that the function of
trust in this context? M trust is that
when you do
choose to look at it in a certain way,
trust is knowing that your original
reference point, your original reference
beam, i.e. your
belief will then determine beyond a
shadow of a doubt how all of the other
details must fall into
place. Because you are acting upon the
one point you need to act upon. And
because you say this point now
represents this, then everything else
that will reinforce the existence of
that one reference point as being what
you have said it is will all
manifest because they are all
interconnected. And if you make this
reference point a certain idea, then all
the other reference points must reflect
the validation of the idea you have said
it is. So all the details will fall into
place and take care of themselves
automatically. That's what trust is
knowing that that's what will happen and
that you don't have to go from reference
point to reference point saying, "All
right, now this is this and now while
I'm holding on to this, this is this and
now while I'm holding on to this, that's
that. And now while I'm juggling this,
that's that. And then I have to do all
the other things." and label all the
other reference points and make sure
they're all working together exactly as
I want them to work. All you need to do
is change any one reference point to
what you desire to be and all the other
reference points have to reinforce it.
The whole universe has shifted to
revolve around what you have said that
reference point is.
Yeah, I'm feeling a little overwhelmed.
Relax. You do this all the time. totally
automatically. It is totally second
nature. It only becomes overwhelming
when you start thinking about it because
that's like trying to hold all the
points in your analytical mind and that
involves juggling and soon it will
overwhelm you and bury you in pearls.
Relax. When you don't think about it is
when it works most easily.
You are an automatic creator. All you
need to do is have the one
focus. Everything else falls into place.
All the details take care of themselves
automatically. All right. All right. I I I just like to
All right. All right. I I I just like to
share as a closing for me now that I
have a new appreciation out of these
interactions with you of how it is to
act out of excitement. And it is a
wonderful gift. Oh, thank you for giving
that gift to yourself. Thank you for
allowing us to assist you in unwrapping
the gift that has been before you
forever. Thank you for inviting us to your
Thank you for inviting us to your
birthday party.
Happy birthday
to you all. Sharing.
Sharing.
Nice. Uh the previous questioner asked
my first two questions. Uh, I'd like to
ask the third question. All right. Uh,
you you make this statement that uh if
you are who you are, if you act who you
truly are, is there any way that you cannot
are, is there any way that you cannot
act the way you truly are all the time?
No. However, you can create a you that
does not know it. H the whole idea of
the difference between the negative and
the positive side is simply that you
know you are always who you truly
are and can choose to act in ways that
most accurately reflect it. If you
choose to forget who you are, then you
can also choose to act in ways that may
not be best directly representative of
who you know you are.
You follow me? Well, I'm not quite sure
on the point. If you decide to forget,
isn't that acting who you truly are? In
an overall sense, yes. But the idea
simply always comes back to whether you
prefer to act who you are in that manner
unconsciously or who you are in a
conscious manner. Okay.
would follow that in order to get to
where we seem I seem to be wanting to go
which is to a place or a situation of
everything is for fourth density or
everything is comes out the way I
consciously say it should be I want it
to be
I uh the way to achieve that is to stop
forgetting who I
In a sense, yes, that is
it. And to live as if you truly do
remember who you are, which means living
in the moment, in the present
completely. Not in the past, not in the
future, in the
present. Moment to moment to
moment. It's making a buzz in the air.
Ah. Guys,
Guys,
I don't know how quite to say it. There
seems to be some contradiction. All
right. In what sense?
See, uh, I I follow the point about
stopping forgetting who I am. I see. I
think I have a way. But perhaps rather
than putting it in a negative
connotation, how about simply
remembering who you are rather than
stopping forgetting? Well, the way to do
it is to forget. The way I'm doing is to
forget who I really am. It seems to me
that by stopping forgetting, that's the
way to release the whole thing. We
understand what you are saying. We are
simply pointing out that many
individuals continue to forget when they
take a negative approach. Rather than
doing a positive thing, they say they
will stop doing a negative thing which
only focuses them on the fact that
they're doing a negative
thing rather than simply doing the
positive thing. There is a difference in
the way the outcome presents itself when
you say I will stop doing a negative
thing as opposed to saying I will do or
am doing the positive
thing. There is a difference in the
result that you get.
See right at this
moment I want to remember that I am the
creator guys and one of the things that I wish
guys and one of the things that I wish
to create is warmth in this room so that
nobody feels
cold. Then allow yourself to simply
recognize that you are sitting in that
reality. Allow yourself to create the warmth
Allow yourself to create the warmth
within you. Now also understand again
you cannot be responsible for everyone
else. And if someone else chooses to
believe they need to feel cold then no
matter what you do they're going to feel
cold. You cannot create warmth for them
they won't be in my universe. All right
then they won't. Okay. But then everyone
who's in this room is in my universe is
my creation. Yes.
Okay. Therefore, recognize if you truly
believe that you remember you are the
creator, then recognize that you do
everything for a reason.
Therefore, even after you have expressed
your desire and if you truly believe in
it, if you still find that someone says,
"I'm cold," then recognize to yourself,
"Aha, I have now discovered that I have
created a reality in which someone is
telling me they are cold." Even in the
event of the desire I express, and that
must mean there is a good reason why I
have created a reality in which someone
still tells me they are cold.
Do not deny the reality that is around
you. Do not
deny that you have created that reality.
First and foremost, the way to allow
yourself to remember most fully that you
can create the reality you desire is to
acknowledge that you have created the
reality you're experiencing.
Yes, that's right. and that it is there
for a reason, a positive
reason. If you truly believe you have
changed, then you won't say, "Well,
what's this? I said I wanted everyone to
feel warm and this person's telling me
they feel cold, then that means I must
not be in control." Why would you have
that attitude if you truly believed that
you had changed? You're still giving an
old meaning to an apparently on the
surface old situation.
rather than saying well I know I've
changed now I know that if someone is
telling me they are cold there is
something about that interaction I need
to hear for some reason is there for a
reason that if you do not need to hear
that then whether that individual is
cold or not you will never perceive that
they are they may appear to be warm to
you even though they are freezing thing.
It's in another universe. It is the
universe you will take yourself into.
No, I mean if they're freezing, they're
they're not in my universe. Yes, you
will not perceive it. So again, allow
yourself to simply say, well, all right.
I exist in a universe where there is joy
and comfort for all. I perceive. Do
remember at the same time that you have
also agreed
obvious and that I will not perceive you
if you are cold. You may not truly be
willing to say that because you may
truly be willing to believe that you
will serve them better if you do
perceive that they are still cold so
that they can perceive that you are warm
so that they can learn how to be warm
too. You may not wish to shut them out in
You may not wish to shut them out in
terms of the reality they desire to
express to you because that may be the
way you actually can serve them best. So
do not think that just because you say
that you wish everyone to be warm that
if somebody says I'm still cold, do not
think that that truly actually
represents a failure on your part. It
does represent the idea of the fact that
you are warm, but perhaps not exactly in
the way you expect it to mean it.
Perhaps it means that simply the amount
of interactions you allow to take place
means that you are cooking.
We
all How does how does this relate to the
wizard? The wizard is the one that knows first
The wizard is the one that knows first
of all that everything that occurs at
any given moment is a part of the
equation, a part of the magic, a part of
the spell, and therefore utterly
enjoyable, fascinating, and curiosity
fascinating, and curiosity
provoking. Every event is magic.
Nothing is to be
denied. For out of every situation, no
matter who may think it is bleak, can be
pulled a
bloom flowering in the
sun. You follow me? Yeah. That is the
wizard. Bashar. Bashar. you coming from Los
Bashar. Bashar. you coming from Los
Angeles and experiencing um Maui
energy um there there's a sense of being
closer to nature
uh maybe a healing kind of energy here
centering in that sense as
um a maybe more receptivity yes openness
the heart and yet also kind of uh
spontaneously confusion maybe that is
evolving towards more intuitive or yes more
towards more intuitive or yes more
instinct less analysis
do not forget
confusion co-fusion fusion with more of
yourself also what about the sense of of Hawaii
also what about the sense of of Hawaii
being more of a dream state and like the
Los Angeles the mainland being more of
an active state or this they are both
their own type of dream.
What is the relationship in the way that
you understand it of the energy between
say like California, Los Angeles to
Hawaii and then moving out to other
places that other people talk about like
Japan and New Zealand. The idea of what
you call the energy state of Los Angeles
is representative of individuals in your
terms who like to live on the
edge of their
dream. In this way, the idea of a
Hawaiian state are those who more like
to be nestled into the heart of the
dream. You follow me?
To some degree, Japan also represents a
type of formation of
edgginess. The idea of New Zealand forms
a little bit more of an
ancientness of free.
Is there a connection between the energy
of these places? Now there is a
connection always. Okay. in the sense of
a of movement of going connecting these
places. Yes. The general connection
general connection are some of the
different reflective aspects of what you
used to call
Lamoreia. Put in this way, Lamoria is
within you rising again as Lamoria
represents the way you used to live on
the planet instinctively rather than
analytically. So what you call the Pacific basin and
So what you call the Pacific basin and
those places that touch the edge and the
place that represents the heart in that
way will represent the Lamorian energy
coming back into your lives. Less
analysis and more instinct. You follow
me? Yeah. On on the island of Maui, I'm
especially attracted to the area of
Hana. It's very well Hana. Is that a It
will have some specific reference to
you. The entire chain of islands is within a
The entire chain of islands is within a
vortex and every island also has its own
vortex. Any specific local on those
islands will have to do with your
particular pattern that you are setting
up. Your particular path, your
particular method in which you wish to
learn how to assimilate and integrate
these energies. Some of them will
connect into past lives you have had.
Being that certain areas on certain
islands may represent certain situations
you have created or lived in before
within the Lamorian continent. They will
be the similar or the most closely
approximating areas that will allow you
to be back in touch with the things you
learned or knew back then. You follow
me? Yeah. What would you understand to
be that pattern um in the Hana area? No
comment. This is for you to discover as
your own personal unfolds.
Whatever it is you are learning about
yourself is indicative of the energy
that is there.
Yeah. Um another question. Um I've been
experiencing a lot of changes and some
painful changes in my energy field. All
right. Again, you are all going through
changes. The only reason that any of
them at this time may be painful is
because of old beliefs, habitual
rituals, and certain ideas that you are
holding on to that when you let the
energy through must then attempt to
widen the doorway. If you are forcing
those doorways closed, holding them
closed, then you may be creating it to
be a little bit of a painful experience.
But the only reason you are holding
those doorways closed is because that is
the way you have been taught to act for
thousands of years. All pain once again
spiritual pain, emotional pain, mental
pain and physical pain, all pain is the
result of the cutting off of a portion
of yourself from the totality of
yourself with can support the total
change you are going through. Only that
causes pain. Only the restriction, only
the limitation of a portion of yourself.
Only the creation or the
isolation of an idea that you have a
portion that is distinct from all the
rest of yourself creates pain. When you
act as an integrated being, there is no
pain. When you allow yourself to go back
to the zero rest point of your idealized
blueprint, there is no
pain. Only holding yourself out of balance
Only holding yourself out of balance
creates pain.
Holding yourself out of balance is very
tiring, is very
painful. Allow yourself to go back to
your natural rest
state. Be true to
yourself. Then there will be no
pain. But you are all assimilating at
whatever rate is comfortable for you.
And you will all find that you will be
able to integrate acclimate to the
energy so that you will not think of
this energy as something more than you
can handle. That is the primary reason
it may cause pain within you because
many of you still think that this energy
is something more than your frail little
body can
handle. And as long as you tend to think
of yourself as something less, something
that destructible, then you will only
allow enough energy through at any one
time that you think you can
tolerate. You can tolerate it all. If
you allow yourself to begin to believe
that you cannot and never would ever
give yourself more than you can handle,
there is no point to that. The universe
does not do pointless
things. You follow it. Yes. The more you
relax into the understanding that what
you give yourself at any given moment is
exactly what you need, no more and no
less, then you will jump into it with
joyful abandon. And with that degree of
ecstasy and exuberance, you will be wide
open in complete acceptance and
vulnerability. And then you will not experience pain
And then you will not experience pain
which only comes from the
constriction of the flow valves because
you are afraid to let the full potential
through. You follow me?
Yes. So relax. Breathing will assist you
greatly. Deep slow methodical breathing.
For that to you is life itself and it is
energy. Breathe your doorways open. You
do not have to fight. You do not have to
strain. You do not have to struggle them
open. Breathe them open. Fill them up and you
Breathe them open. Fill them up and you
will be
fulfilled. All right.
Lashar, you and then you I'm getting
very very excited about spacecraft. Oh,
very very very uh not only the
tremendous joy of working with the I
think the tensor gravitational fields
that you spoke of at another time. Yes.
But also just recently we had a a
sighting of a large bank of whites out
towards uh Machai one evening. I was
curious about uh what shift that was. No
comment. All right.
No. You also spoke for now simply
consider all such interactions as
reflections of the total association.
All right. You follow me? Uh-huh. It
appears I'm in some kind of uh
apprenticeship program uh to to work
directly with the ships on an
entertainment level and a environmental
a sensic environmental level. You go
right ahead and enjoy yourself. Uh
you you've mentioned that
uh physical encounters with your craft
are in our future uh like within the
next 10 years. I think you spoken uh the
other day it it seemed that you
intimated that interactions with other
civilizations spacecrafts were were more
imminent. Yes. Uh it occurs to me that
Plleadian contact is very very imminent.
Yes. Especially in the area of New
Zealand
and many other places.
How imminent is it?
Depends on you.
Desire depends on desire, not need.
Mhm. depends on willingness to be the same
depends on willingness to be the same
idea they are
as I again do not
forget the first contact will take place
between the two alien species already on
your planet
if you do not contact them.
You will not be able to contact anyone
else. We haven't contacted them yet. You
are doing so.
That's also that has a particular
reference point and a collective
reference point. Yes.
So in my own experience of having
physical contacts with dolphins and
sensic contacts with whales,
uh it appears that for me the contact
with the craft is very imminent. Yes. Uh
how that's been coming towards me has
been in a series of tones. Yes.
As I begin to use the tones more and
more, uh, more synchronicity happens
with those encounters. And think green.
Emerald green. Yes.
And all that is associated with that
vibrator. Uh, do you have any tones to share with
Uh, do you have any tones to share with
us tonight? Emerald green. Yes. Okay.
uh is it possible
to or I would like to share an
experience of uh collectively moving
into the vibrational level of those
ships. Would you all right to assist
this group with that? We'll see. Well,
uh, my feeling is if we all close our
eyes. Yeah.
And move into
a a matrix, a stellar matrix that looks
like a set of rainbow stars, similar to
what a rutated crystal might appear like
sitting in sunlight. can be that way.
Let's keep it simple. My assistant
suggestion to you is a
circle. Now, not that you have to do it
at this time.
Allow me
to suggest to you
all that if you at any
time wish to begin to form circles any
number of you one will also
work three would be at least ideal in
that sense but any number of you in a
circular pattern giving for the vibration you
pattern giving for the vibration you
already recognize as
oh in your own comfortable tone whatever
is comfortable for
you do it
together the sound at the same time if
you find that the majority is beginning
to lose
breath then end it and all begin it at
at the same time
relatively. No
overlap, no trailing
off. A conscious
decisive waiting for everyone. You are
all doing it at the same time.
Oh, if you hear it trailing off in the
majority, trail off. When you hear it,
start up or when you begin to commence
or when there is the space, start it up.
And everyone together take the breath.
Breathe as one.
If you wish, one way you can assist in
the acceleration of sightings and
contacts as you call them will be to
form these circles and simply create the
energy door through which a ship can
come by creating that vibratory matrix. Do not Do not
be
disappointed from creating
expectation. So do not create
expectation. Then you will not be
disappointed. Allow yourself to know
this and this I can guarantee you from
all members of the association.
When you do this and create that
vibration for however long you are
comfortable with the idea, one
suggestion would be for at least 15
minutes. At least 15 minutes. You do not
have to do it for any longer than an
hour. Wherever in that frame you are
comfortable, you can agree beforehand to
limit the time. It is up to
[Music] you. If you will create these vibratory
you. If you will create these vibratory
circles, you will by acting in unison
and vibratory synchronicity in that way
create a very powerful conduit that will
begin to pierce the barriers and veils
that you have set up. Then you will
create an atmosphere that will be more
literally conducive and
conductive to the vibratory matrix of
our crafts. Bit by
crafts. Bit by
bit, our ships will begin to pop into
your reality. The more you flavor the
reality. The more you flavor the
atmosphere with this particular
exercise, there will always be always be
identification with
you by those who represent the strongest
connections with you in the other
society both individually and
collectively. in any given
circle. Always, whether you see a craft
or not, always. And
again, allow us to suggest what we call
our rule of
thumb. If it is not
obviously in your meaning of that word
totally, blatantly obviously a
spacecraft, then it isn't. Even if it
is, for there is no reason why you should
for there is no reason why you should
guess. Allow yourselves to simply
perceive what you perceive and take it
as the way you perceive it. If it
appears to simply be a light, take it as
a light.
Accept it for what it is, the way it
comes. There is a reason for why it
comes that way.
Then more and more you will assist us in
building the equation, in building the
matrix, and in building the frequency
that will allow us to more easily slip
into your
reality, into our combined
reality, our new combined reality.
That is our suggestion.
That is our mode at this time of
assisting you in what you were beginning
to pick up on.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Okay.
Um could you uh give us few ideas of on
ecstasy the substance called ecstasy?
You mean what you call the drug? Yes.
Like anything, it is a tool, an
externalized symbol of a desire you have
within you to recognize your own power,
no matter in which way you wish to
express it. The idea of course is to
recognize that any such tool is only a
symbol and that anything you are
experiencing is actually being created
by you. But because many individuals may
still rely upon the idea that the power
is in the symbol, then they will also
cocreate what may be termed side
effects, which are basically their
inherent belief systems about the way
the symbol comes to them, about what the
symbol represents. You may have heard that the
represents. You may have heard that the
idea of the so-called drug ecstasy does
not have side effects, but it does.
Recognize that there is nothing right or
wrong about any of these ideas, but that
a member of your society can create an
addiction to anything by continuing to
believe that the power for the
experience they desire to have is in the
drug and not in
them. Many times the idea of a drug can
function as a tool to put you in touch
with the power you have to create the
particular reality that you wish to
create. Then you simply realize all
right now that it has put me in touch
with it I can create this anytime I wish
without the tool without the symbol
without the
drum because you then know like anything
again you are your own master
crystal. You all of you are always as
powerful as you need to be to create
whatever you desire in your reality
without having to hurt anyone else or
yourself in order to create it. The
power is always able to flow through
you. Infinite
creation is all you need to create any
experience. You are a vow for
that. If you choose from time to time to
create a symbolic interpretation, a
symbolic tool to reflect to you that you
can function as a vow, so be it.
There is no true invalidation of that
idea. Anything that works
works. But the idea is to recognize that
it is you that is working not the
symbol. Now because of your desire to
get in touch with your heart at this
time then you have created the symbolic
reflection and obviously very blatantly
labeled this particular tool ecstasy
because that's what you desire in your
lives because unconsciously at least you
are beginning to recognize that you
deserve it. You are finally beginning to
it. You are finally beginning to
recognize that you deserve ecstasy. Of
course, because you still think in the
way you are used to thinking, you say,
"All right, we deserve ecstasy." No
problem. Make a drug. Call it ecstasy.
Then we'll have
it. But it is only a symbolic reflection
of your inner knowingness that you
already are ecstasy. You don't need the
drug. If it will assist an individual in
getting in touch with the fact that they
are ecstasy and then recognize that the
drug was only a tool that got them
there, they won't need the drug anymore
anyway. Before does that assist you?
Yes, it does. At this
time, allow us to extend our very
deepest appreciation and unconditional
love in having allowed us to experience
and explore the individual and combined
energies of the consciousness that you
are within what you call your idea of
being. Maui. In this way, we will continue to
Maui. In this way, we will continue to
share with you any of the multitudinous
aspects of the dream that you are
willing to cocreate together with
us. We thank you for your expressions of
love. We thank you for the gifts of
yourself. Do not
Do not
forget that the only reason why you may
at any time feel that we might have more
of an ability to assist you than you
have to assist yourselves is that you
simply sense from us that no matter what
you think of yourselves at any given
moment, we always believe in
you. Always beyond a shadow of a doubt.
But please do
please do
remember that our ability to express to
you our
capability to believe in you beyond a
shadow of a
doubt is only a reflection of what we
see in you.
shine as the
stars that you
are. And when you shine as brightly as
you know yourselves to be, then you will
illuminate your paths to utter
transparency and there will remain not
one shadow of a death.
We thank
you. exciting dream life to you all and
life dream and
remember wake up wake up wake up and
[Music] dream pleasant
dream pleasant
dream good
[Music]
There we go.
Thank you all for being here.
[Music] So for a lot of people are just
So for a lot of people are just
remaining here on the island and so I'd
like to take this opportunity if I don't
get an opportunity later to thank
everybody here for allowing Maui to be
such a wonderful experience for me.
[Music]