Welcome to more bound. Thank you. You
know, a couple weeks ago, of course, the
audience wouldn't know this, but uh I
had the opportunity of previewing Daryl
Anka Bashar and um I think very briefly
Bashar and um I think very briefly
before we actually get into what Bashar
is all about, I was wondering if you
might tell us just a little bit about
your background because what people are
about to see this trans channeling for
some I think will probably be a very
shocking sort of thing. But I I want
people to know that you are an average
normal type of I walk the streets just
like everyone, right? Um well, basically
most of my life I've been uh a designer,
an illustrator. I've been drawing since
I was two and got into the business
relatively early. I've become involved
in also the miniature end of uh special
effects or motion pictures within the
last several years as well. That's
basically what I have done for a living.
So I mean you you've cranked out graphic
arts and these miniatures and that's how
you you earn your keep. And then how did
you shift into getting involved with all
this extraterrestrial other dimensional
activity? Well, like a lot of people had
been somewhat interested because that
subject matter does run through our
society. You hear about it. Some people,
you know, may choose to just discount it
and some people are attracted to it. I
just figured that I was hearing so much
about it, there must be something to it,
even though I knew there might be a lot
of peripheral information that wasn't
necessarily accurate. I just decided to
begin researching, reading books on it,
just seeing if there were kernels of
information that would piece together.
And that's basically what started me off
in that direction. And then at some
point, uh, how many years ago was it you
actually had a sighting where you
physically saw a spacecraft over Los
Angeles? 13 years ago. Um, two times in
the same week. Uh, four friends with me
the first time, two friends with me the
second time. So I had witnesses, thank
goodness. This was not a figment of your
imagination. They all saw it. So if it
was a figment, it was a mass fment and
it was very close broad daylight
physical sightings. The first time not
more than about 150 ft away. Second time
not more than about 60 ft away. And um
good long solid sightings. And what I
didn't understand then and what I
understand now is that sighting was
Bashar's way of sort of tapping my
subconscious memory to get me to start
accelerating the things I was learning
to fulfill an agreement that I had made
to do the channeling as I have now
discovered. So really it was it if you
will was a triggering a soul memory.
Yes. So that that image inside you would
would latch and say okay this is
something I want to pursue even though
you didn't necessarily know about the
shark conscious. Oh, most of my my
understanding of most mediumships is
that they are usually the product of an
arrangement or an agreement that is made
prior to the physical life. So, you come
into this life doing whatever you're
doing and that memory is of the
agreement is buried in there somewhere.
So, some event in the life will usually
trigger that and that was the one that
triggered it for me. And then when did
you finally actually start practicing if
you will trans mediumship or or channel
about four years ago now I in in
accelerating my research ultimately I
came across what mediumship was. I was
eventually introduced to several
practicing mediums at the time and one
of those mediums, one of the entities
coming through one of those mediums
offered to teach mediumship for whoever
was interested because there were
several people that were I took him up
on it not even then thinking this is
something I'm going to do. I just wanted
to learn more about it. I had read every
book. You had no idea what was going to
happen. I had no idea whatsoever. Um,
and in the process of being tutored by
that entity, when I was in a receptive
state is when Bashar, their people made
the mental connection with me, as soon
as they did, the memory came back. Who
they were, who I was to them, what the
ship sighting had been for, dream
conversations I had had up to that point
that I had totally blocked, all came
back in that one memory. And along with
it came the message, okay, now is the
time for you to start doing this if you
still want to. So, obviously, I said
yes. That was about four years ago. You
had the chance. And at what point, I
mean, did it start out in a little way
and then you all of a sudden there's
been more channels going on? You know,
it it took a while to get used to. I
mean, I'm not something that I
automatically acclimated to. It it was
difficult at first. The energy was very
different. There were physical changes,
emotional changes. I went through a lot
of the same skepticism that a lot of
people go through, like, is this really
happening to me? Am I making this all
up? Am I going nuts? But I had a lot of
validation from a lot of unsought
sources that kept pointing in
directions. And I just got to a point
where if I was going to do it, I had to
start going with it because if I was
going to continue to fight the idea,
then it would really start driving me
crazy. So I figured if I'm going to do
it, I might as well trust it. As soon as
I began to really trust it, it became
clearer what was happening. Pieces began
to fall into a pattern and it became
obvious that there was a particular
direction to it. Now, these spacecraft
are still circling our Earth. I mean,
and there's several different types.
Some are several different civilizations
as far as I know. Um, the one that
appeared to us, as far as I understand
now, was Bashar's scout craft, which was
triangular in shape, an equilateral
triangle about 40 ft on a side and um
was dark dark gray in color. And how
many lights flashing? There were there
was one light on each point. So, a total
of three lights. No flashing, just
solidly on. And uh there they have many
different styles of craft, but that is
the one that I've seen and several
people have seen it since and reported
it separately. So this craft leaves the
mother ship if you will and can get
closer to Earth and doesn't have as many
gravitational problems to do. I
understand that that sort of stay a
distance and then let the small craft
come and go much, you know, like a
scout. Okay. And then in in the course
of your working with Bashar and I
understand what his is is it his lady
friend or his consort is Anima. He calls
her his counterpart. I assume they're
just basically associates.
Who knows right at that point. Uh maybe
you can ask him. Um but they they are
representatives from their civilization.
They have chosen to do this kind of work
as many members in their civilization
have and they do function through many
individuals on this planet and other
planets helping them elevate themselves
through whatever transformational
processes they happen to be going
through and we know what they look like.
I think you brought a sketch and yes
they have described themselves. I have
seen them in the trans state and in
dream communications and they are
roughly 5t tall on the average. They
have a very white whitish gray skin
coloration. Their eyes are very large
and upturned. Uh they have said that if
we're going to make any kind of a
comparison to something we're familiar
with at all, it would be maybe Mongolian
Eurasian. Not quite. They're much more
slender. The females seem to have hair.
The males don't. And the the hair
usually tends to white even when it
exists. So they're they're pretty
monotone in that sense, but their eyes
stand out as the largest feature. And
then what about the actual process of
the channeling? Very briefly, what is
what is the the telepathic communication
mode that takes place between you and
Bashar? What I've what I've learned from
Bashar and what I've learned now to do
is to relax what typically passes from
my focused consciousness and let it
become more diffused or plastic if you
will so that his consciousness can sort
of impress itself upon mine so that mine
can start picking up the pattern of his
vibration. That interlinking allows my
consciousness, my energy to become a a
model of his thought patterns. So you
get a translation through my body and
he's not actually speaking English. It
just pops out of my subconscious.
Whatever words in our language need to
the concepts that are coming, right? So
it's almost like tuning forks getting in
resonance very much so. He says
everything is the product of different
frequencies of vibrations in the
universe. So, it's a matter of matching
vibrational patterns to allow an
identification to take place so that I
can function like a translation device,
for lack of a better term. Well, is
there anything we should know about what
you're about to do just before you go
in? Uh um just that uh when he makes the
link, it'll be relatively
conversational. It's it's a very
ordinary thing in in that sense. It it's
very easy to communicate with him. He's
very outfront. He's not shy at all. So
just a an open friendly discussion.
Anything anyone wants to really ask or
say doesn't have to be a question is
really the mode of operation for it.
Well, let's meet Bashar. All right.
Thank you. It'll just take me a second.
Sure. I think we have an extra cushion
there. Hey, thank you. So,
this is just more the help me put my
body in the position that I'm used to
for the channeling. [Music] [Music]
Nobody.
All right, I'll say how are you this day
of your time as you create time to
exist. Welcome.
Welcome.
And to you, we extend our deepest
appreciation for your willingness to
cocreate as individuals and a
collectivity of consciousness. This
interaction, this day of your time, to
facilitate the merger and the blending
not only of all the members of your
society, but of your society with other
societies at this time in your
transformational age. You may simply
proceed in whatever manner you have
co-created this interaction to take
place. Thank you very much, Bashar, and welcome
Thank you very much, Bashar, and welcome
to Inwardbound and welcome to TV.
Although I'm sure you have probably much
more advanced methods of communication,
but this is the best thing we've got
right now here on planet Earth. I was
wondering if you might elaborate a
little bit on the idea that you had in
mind when we picked the title two weeks
ago for the theme of the show, Live Your
Dreams. I have some I have some
questions in mind, but I thought you
might like to um have something to say
first. Thank you. The idea is simply to
lay down a foundation and a format as
you call it to let you know that what
you typically refer to as physical
reality is in a very real and literal
way simply a projection a dream. Now
when we say an illusion as many of you
have already recognize that physical
reality is an illusion. We do not use
that term to discount reality. But
simply all we are saying is that your
perceptions in and of themselves
in and of themselves
are what create the reality you
experience. That you are manifestations.
You are expressions. You each and every
one of you are facets of the
multi-dimensional crystal of infinite
creation. You are all the thoughts of
the infinite creator. all the different
ways that the infinite creation has of
thinking itself into beingness, thinking
itself into creation. And so physical
reality is but the dream of the infinite
creator. And each and every being within
creation are the active co-dreamers,
co-creators. So as you dream, as you
believe, as you perceive, as you think,
so you experience. So when you learn
that your physical reality is simply the
product of what you dream it, what you
imagine it, what you believe most
strongly, your reality to be, then you
will recognize that you are in control
of the eb and the flow of that
experience of energy in your life and
you can create it to be whatever you
desire, whatever you prefer it to be if
it is not. So at this timing when we
when we look at our lives I'm now
speaking obviously for myself and I
think for some people in the audience
for many of us there seems to be a
discrepancy between the dreams that we
hold the visions that we hold for
ourselves of what we would really like
to accomplish and and what we see
happening around us. say, but this is
primarily because of the habitual ritual
that your society has created, of not
believing that your imagination, that
your thoughts and that your desires do
in fact have an effect upon your
physical reality. Not only an effect,
but they are responsible for creating it
to begin with. When your society
continues to believe that physical
reality happens outside of you and that
you really have absolutely no power over
what is going on, that you are simply a
random cog, as you say, in a large
machine that operates without you or
with you, then you do not know that you
are in touch with that creative ability.
You do not know that the reality that
you see around you will also be the
product of your unconscious and
subconscious fears and belief systems.
The idea is to bring this awareness to
conscious level so that you can know
that what you see around you may be the
product of what you have been taught to
fear might be true. What you have been
taught to believe might be true against
your desires, against your preferences.
And to be in control of knowing that
once you acknowledge that you are
creating what is around you anyway, you
know you are in control of it and you
can change in the directions you prefer
to. We talk about belief, emotion,
thought. These being I believe as you
put it the keystones or the cornerstones
of the prism. We are a crystal in
structure. Our body has obviously an
energy field and those three things
belief, emotion and thought is what
creates the reflection is what creates
what you call your persona. Your
personality you see your persona your
personality the person that you believe
yourself to be you consider yourself to
be in this life in this focus is not
exactly the totality of who and what
each and every one of you is. It is an
artificial construct. It is one of your
many faces. As a total being, a total
energy being, you span all time, all
space, and you project many aspects, if
you will, of yourself into many
different dimensions of reality and
experience and expression. So each and
every one of those faces, each and every
one of those persona being an artificial
construct is like a prism and like a
glass prism. It will take the white
light, the homogeneous light of the
total consciousness that you are. And
passing that light through the prism of
belief, emotion, and thought, it will
break that light down into the
diversified spectrum of the immediate
specific physical reality you hold at
any given moment to be true and real for
you. So when you adjust
the ideas, the beliefs, the emotions,
and the thoughts within you, you create
a different type of prism. And the white
light then passes through that prism in
a different way and therefore projects a
different type of reality upon the
imaginary screen 360° all the way around
you that you think is exterior to
yourself but which is actually within.
So it's fair to say if we are
experiencing a reality that is less than
pleasant for us in no small part we are
responsible for that. Yes. But we do not
mean to imply that that means blame.
Responsibility, total responsibility for
the creation of your reality means
ultimate freedom in that way. And it
takes acknowledging that you have
created it. Perhaps acknowledging that
you may have unconscious or subconscious
beliefs or fears within you that can
attract these realities, negative though
they may be, to you. And in recognizing
that you have those beliefs, in
acknowledging that you have those fears,
then you own them. And simply remember,
if you wish to change anything, you
cannot transform something you do not
own. So first you must own the idea that
what you do experience in your life is
your creation. That puts you squarely,
as you say, in control, as you say, in
the driver's seat. And then you can
steer your vehicle through life along
the path you desire. Once you know you
are firmly in control, but the easiest
way to do that is to recognize that the
reality you experience is your creation
to begin with, even though it may be a
subconscious creation. And that element
of fear,
it would seem that what you're saying
would back up what is commonly held in
in psychology and I think religion and
certainly philosophy and that is fear is
our biggest enemy. In a sense, it was
truly stated in your world that the only
thing that you do in fact have to fear
is the fear itself. Because there is
nothing nothing
inherent about any circumstance or
situation that needs to create a
negative result. Only the fear, the
doubt, the belief in lack of
self-empowerment generates the negative
effect out of the circumstances that you
then become fearful of. And in becoming
fearful of the effects you generated
with your belief to begin with, you may
then reinforce that fear through the
experiences you create. But the
experiences you have in life, they do
not create the belief to begin with. The
belief within you creates the experience
which may then reinforce the belief and
then recreate the experience and catch
you up in that cycle that you call your
catch 22. So simply it takes an
understanding that if belief creates the
experience once you change the belief
you will change the experience and we
guarantee 100% that is the effect that
will occur. You can do it for yourselves
and create the proof you need for
yourselves to see that it will occur.
What would be something any one of the
viewers could do at home right now
watching the show to really get in touch
with perhaps what their highest mission
is, their purpose, their destiny, what
will make them happy. I am convinced
that everyone has an optimal even though
we may not experience it, we have an
optimal path in a sense. Yes. Now this
is a very simple idea and a very simple
answer for recognize what excites you
with integrity the most in life itself
is the sign and the signal that lets you
know what it is in life you can do most
easily and can most effortlessly support
you in the doing of that thing. What you
call excitement, strong desire, that
frequency, that energy, that vibration
in and of itself is your physical
translation, your bodily translation of
the vibratory energy that represents the
path in life you chose to be. So when
you follow what excites you the most,
you are most harmoniously,
synchronistically aligned with all
levels of your consciousness. All you
need to do to see the effect of
following what excites you the most is
to trust it implicitly 100% and follow
through and act upon whatever
opportunities present themselves
automatically to you in life that do
excite you the most with integrity at
any given moment. And that action, that
doingness will lead to every other
circumstance, every other situation,
every other relationship that you need
to experience in your life to allow the
path you chose to be to unfold in an
automatic and natural and effortless and
ecstatic way. It is your birthright to
experience ecstasy. No one needs to
suffer or struggle in order to believe
they deserve happiness. You deserve it
because you exist.
Yes. And in that creating what we want,
what is it that blocks us from achieving
that? I mean, there's a whole room full
of dreams here. And but again, the idea,
you have been taught it isn't that easy.
You have been taught that if there is
anything worth having in life, you must
struggle. You must suffer in order to
earn it in that way. As you have a
saying upon your world, I believe it
goes no pain, no gain. If you believe in
that, then you will not allow yourself
to experience gain without the pain. You
simply have not been taught to believe
that you are the effortless creations of
the infinite creator. And since you are
made in the image of the infinite
creator, all of your creations can be
effortless, too, because you are just as
much a multi-dimensional creator as the
infinite creator is. What about quote
the American dream? We've heard a lot
about that and I think my opinion now is
a personal opinion that perhaps we've
lost our focus. But if you think about
what we've accomplished relative to
other countries in the world and
relative to other economies using
certainly uh material output as one
measure, what is it that has happened that has
what is it that has happened that has
diffused our focus? And is there in fact
an American dream? Is there a collective
dream as well as an individual dream?
Yes, there is. And there are specific
dreams within the collective dream. And
all the individuals within any
particular nation's dream are also truly
valid dreams unto themselves even though
they may be let us say synchronized with
a collective dream. But the diffusion
that you may feel that you may be
experiencing is simply in a sense a
blending a time of unlocking from past
conceptions and a refocusing into new
points of view, new attitudes, new
directions, new approaches. In this way,
this diffusing broadens your scope,
broadens your horizon, broadens your
perspectives, and gives you more
opportunities to determine for
yourselves that there may be more ways
to get somewhere than you previously
thought. You see, there is no one way to
do anything. If there was only one way,
there would only be one person. Look
around. Your world is populated by
billions of individuals. And each
individual is a different way, a
different idea, a different expression,
a different path of the infinite
creation and the overall collective
dream if you will. Now each and every
nation upon your world shares and holds
an aspect of the collective dream and
different nations will represent certain
ideas that other nations are not willing
to play out or simply have not chosen to
play out. That is why you now find your
world growing and blending together.
Becoming, as you say, smaller and
smaller every day. Because now you are
becoming one dream each and every
individual in every nation and each and
every nation are gathering together and
bringing with them the pieces of the
collective total dream so that you can
all live the one dream of the total
collective consciousness that all of you
together on your world are. That is what
will now begin to allow you to function
as one world and that functioning will
allow you to function with other whole
worlds and allow you to join what you
may loosely term our association of
worlds. It would almost seem that this
particular technology that we're using
right now television is a very good way
to achieve that. There are many valuable
tools of communication. Whatever works
best for each and every one of you will
be the tool you'll be attracted to and
can be of best service in utilizing upon
your planet. But there are many forms.
They will become much more rapid and you
will begin to understand that you are
linked mentally, emotionally and that
you can begin to exercise that level of
communication as well as what you might
typify to be your electronic media. How
how dependent is living one's dreams on
if you will being in the moment? We
always hear be in the now, be here, be
now, don't be yesterday, don't be
tomorrow. How important is it to be here
right now? In a sense, it is critical to
the operation of the mechanism. For if
you are let us say living in the past if
you will living in the future if you
will not living in the present then all
the things you could be attracting to
you will not be able to find you because
the present is the only experiential
time in which you actually exist. So if
you are not focused in the present then
you will not be aware of all the
opportunities that are in the present
for you to act upon. You'll be looking
elsewhere for everything else outside
yourself in the past in the future and
all the time right as you say under your
nose are all the things you need right
within you right here right now when we
look at the concept of time some people
say time is sequential and linear and
then of course there's the argument
which I think is now becoming very
popular is that actually all time
already exists all events have already
taken place so rather than being in in
linear sequence they've already all
happened it's just our percept ceptive
understanding of them. Well, yes, in a
sense, although your nomenclature that
they have already happened is also a
linear frame of reference because they
are all happening all the time right now
simultaneously forever. But the idea is
that both are true. Linear time is from
within the perspective of the
physicalized universe as you understand
it to be and that is the way you see it.
It helps you focus upon the particular
aspect of yourself that you are dealing
with at any given moment, shall we say.
Whereas on different levels where that
time constraint is not so critical then
you have a broad overview that allows
you to know that much of what you may
have thought in physical reality took
place one after the other in terms of
events are actually not sequential but
actually are all simultaneously
existent. Let us use the analogy if you
will of the communication form that you
are dealing with today perhaps what you
might call your video or your film
analogy. You know that each and every
idea of the frame by frame by frame upon
the film are all separate moments,
separate instance and you perceive them
sequentially one after another in order
to make sense or continuity out of the
flow of motion. But you in living in the
frame perhaps are not aware of the frame
about to come up. Do not have a real
strong perception of the frame that has
already passed by. You are only
immediately aware of the frame you are
in. However, when you as the let us say
film maker which is what you are the
creator of your reality step back and
look at all the frames laid out below
you well you know that even though each
and every experience in every frame is
the discrete experience in sequential
order as a filmmaker you know that the
whole film exists all at once all the
frames are there right now. Another
analogy is what you call your radio. You
know all the programs are there all at
once. All the frequencies are there all
at once, but you only hear the one you
are tuned to at any given moment. But
we're going to have to pause for just a
moment, but I want to thank you and
we're going to be be right back here.
So, you can see living your dreams.
We've we've really had uh quite an
information expressed by Bashar and I
think it's going to take some analysis
but the most important thing the most
important thing as I see it is being
here right now and following that
excitement with integrity. So stay with
us. We're going to be right back here at
Inwardbound with Bashar and some
audience participation.
[Applause] [Music]
Welcome back to Inwardbound. I'm Sam
Kart and if you're just tuning in, we're
in mid channeling, if you will, with
Daryl Anka who is channeling Bashar, who
is an entity from the planet Essani and
we're talking about live your dreams.
And I think Bashar, now with your
permission, we'd like to have some
audience participation. So if I could
have hands right here. Okay.
Yes. Bashar, you talk a lot about dreams
and the subconscious. Could you give us
a better explanation of what the
subconscious really is in human terms or
how we can understand it better? Is it
like a tape recorder where we're born
with a blank recording or is it
something that that's been programmed
before we've been sent here on the
planet? To some degree it is a product
of the combined mentality you have
created your civilization to be. It is
in a sense a filter if you will because
you come into this society not believing
that you can be completely conscious
about all that you need to be conscious
about. So you create levels compartments
if you will into which you can place the
things you are not yet in your terms
ready to deal with at any particular
moment. One thing at a time as you say
it is the product of living in linear
time. It is the compartmentalization of
the consciousness that you are so that
you can in your terms sort things out in
a more highly focused methodology. You
can allow yourself to begin now to know
in this transformational age that you
are one consciousness. And as you begin
to know you are one consciousness, the
ideas that you experience that you call
the subconscious and the unconscious
will in a sense begin to dissolve and
allow you to experience yourself in the
now moment as one operational
consciousness. simply knowing what you
need to know when you need to know it.
Anybody else?
Gentlemen behind. Yes, Bashar. Um I was
curious uh keeping in mind that that our
physical self is basically a
personification of our spiritual self.
Um, are we able actually to physically
as we know it change or restructure
ourselves physically based on on a on a
spiritual restructuring? And is the
change actually
physically noticeable as we know it? It
can be. Again, as you have said, the
body is simply the spirit in physical
terms. The physical world is simply the
shadow of the soul. When you wish to
change the shape of your body's shadow,
you do not pull and tug at the shadow.
You change the shape of your body and
the shadow follows suit. When you wish
to change the shape of your body or any
idea or aspect in the physical world,
you change the shape of your soul which
is the idea that you are at any given
moment. The physical reality has
absolutely no choice but to follow suit
and it can be noticeable to the other
individuals in that physical reality. If
your communicative telepathic skills in
that sense are strong enough, is there
any way that we can develop that type of
concentration? And and if we are able to
develop that concent that type of
concentration, is it possible that for
for example people who would have for
example di a disorder such as diabetes
or down syndrome would actually be able
to restructure themselves to live what
we would consider to be you are now
beginning to explore in your
civilization many of the understandings
that you are made of energy. You are a
fo and electromagnetic energy in a
particular crystallin pattern. You can
learn to reidentify,
restructure that pattern. And in so
restructuring that pattern, your body
will recristallize in whatever format is
indicative of that pattern. And as a new
blueprint, a new definition. If it does
not contain the definition of disease,
then it will not be able to express the
idea of disease. Yes, it is very
possible because everything is a matter
of vibrational frequency. As you
believe, so you shall experience. Now
there may be individuals who cannot
bring themselves to believe that that is
possible. And so they may wish to work
through some of the belief systems
within your society that your society
already considers valid. But even though
you may avail yourself of what may be in
your terms a mundane belief system, a
mundane cure in that way, it is you that
have still in a sense cured yourself by
simply extending a belief into a
particular type of method that you think
will work.
Michelle, I think I have a follow on
question to that. So, it would be fair
to say that the multi-billion dollar
healing industry that we have for
instance in this country is essentially
based on the doctor doing certain things
which lead the patient to believe
they're cured regardless of what the the
technology or the methodology is. Yes.
Because there are individuals in your
terminology who may exhibit the simplest
of symptoms that no medical practitioner
will be able to cure. And there are
individuals who in your medical
practitioner's eyes have absolutely no
chance of living. Who in your
terminology will become cured through
methodologies that your doctors do not
believe in. It is all up to the belief
system of the individual and what they
attract themselves to that determines
how they transform themselves into
whatever new idea they desire to be. Is
it fair to say that using light spectrum
is one method of healing? It's something
we really haven't done much with. You
are beginning to and you have actually
done it as a society many times many
times before. Though you have forgotten,
it is something you are now recognizing
because your tools now that you are
changing are becoming simpler, more
transformational in concept. Less moving
parts, less diversified materials are
necessary. You are now working with the
energies of creation itself. light.
Everything is made of light. In our
ancient language, Esasani, how we refer
to our own home world, literally
translates into your language as place
of living light. All beings are
literally living light. Okay. Any other
questions? We have a question over here.
Um, a lot of wonderful acceleration
happened to me since coming to the
channeling about the last nine months
with you. um a lot of acceleration, but
I'm still plagued with when in the
middle of something exciting, a
left-sided sore throat erupts. And I've
been recently using crystal rose quartz
kunzite to place there. But I noticed
that it's always more severe in the
springtime, Easter time. I always
remember as a kid coming down with these
sore throats around Easter vacation. I'm
just wondering if you can uh shed some
light. Some of it is your susceptibility
to the environment that you believe you
exist within. Some of it you will also
work out in the process you are going
through now that it will involve you in
the idea of the acceleration of your
energy, the acceleration of your
momentum and the lack of waiting that
will clear some of the systems in your
body so they will not be as sensitized
to those changes taking place in your
planetary atmosphere at this time. I
have a question. Is there anything more
I can do with the crystals while I'm for
now? Trust your own instincts and
imagination and follow whatever belief
systems you think are strongest within
you. We will speak more with you later.
Thank you. Over here, the gentleman in
the gray sweater.
Uh you refer to you make references to
terminology that's indigenous to our
culture, our society. And I wonder if
you get this through uh you get this
empathically uh through whom you're
channeling. In a sense, we use the
channel as a repository of your
vocabulary. We are not speaking your
language but only activating from the
channel those words that are necessary
to make the best sense in your terms out
of the concepts we are sending. And does
that equate to or with uh what we might
call the universal storehouse of uh
knowledge or information that is
accessible to everyone? Yes. Thank you.
Thank you lady Penny in the back.
So in other words, everything you are
physically and mentally is a matter of
visual visualization. In a sense, that
is one approach. We are as we imagine
and believe ourselves to be. You are as
you imagine and believe yourselves to be
as you see yourself, your self-image. In
that way, that is the effect and the
result and the experience that you
generate. So yes, visualization,
one of the strongest senses you have
within your inner eye, your inner sight,
your inner mind, is highly responsible
for the effects you experience
physically that structure themselves in
your material world. Yes. And mentally
also. I mean, as far as your health and
everything else, it is all literally a
matter of belief and attitude.
Thank you. Any other questions? Yes,
here in front.
Erica, I wondered if you would talk a
little bit on a national scale about our
conflict with Russia and our fear and
misunderstanding of them and about
nuclear possibilities.
The idea simply put once again is that
as the representative polarity powers
upon your world or what you call power
upon your world, you are for each other
the thing that each other fears the most
within itself. You are the polarized
reflections of those things that each
side fears to contain. This is why the
blending together from your hearts, from
your desires, from your mind will allow
you to become the one society that will
contain all of what you might call the
best aspects of all the nations, all the
cultures within your world. Recognize
that it is only the fear about facing
the things within yourself that allows
you to project that fear upon each other
and then generate circumstances and
scenarios that lead you to think you are
going to wipe each other out. Now this
may be true on certain levels but the
idea now that we can and are allowed to
share with your world is that your world
will not destroy itself by nuclear
annihilation. You as a society, even if
it is a collective unconscious
recognition, have already decided that
you are not going to destroy yourselves
by nuclear annihilation. You may still
be posturing. You may still meet many
accelerations of violence upon the
surface of your world. But in a sense,
you are now bringing all these things
and getting them out of your system up
to the surface, letting them be open so
that each and every one of you at this
time can decide, is this how we want our
world to be or do we prefer it to be
another way? Recognize also at this time
and we can tell you this now only
because you have already as a society
decided that you will not destroy
yourselves through nuclear means. It is
your world. You may do with it as you
wish. We cannot interfere. That would be
contrary to our belief systems. However,
you are therefore allowed to do what you
will with your world. You may even
utterly destroy it if you wish, but not
through a methodology that will affect
more than your own world. Nuclear
annihilation would tear through the
dimensional fabrics of space and time
and affect many of the alternate
parallel universes to which you are
attached. And therefore, as your
government is actually already well
aware of, your world would never have
been allowed to wage nuclear war. and
your government has been given many
demonstrations over the course of
various years that the different
societies in the Association of Worlds
of which we are a part would in this way
simply create an ineffective operation
of your war machinery should it have
come down to the point where you decided
to activate that idea. These
demonstrations have been given and your
governments are very well aware of our
existence and know beyond a shadow of a
doubt that nuclear war is not now in
your future. We can tell you this now
because you have already yourselves
decided not to wage that war. It would
not be in anyone's interest at this
point. Thank you. Thank you. We have a
question here on the end. Yes, sir.
Thank you. Bashar, you've spoken of
parallel dimensions. Nice. And it
appears that uh you've you've talked
about also being in a different
dimension and I'm wondering if that's a
dimension that you could be in the same
space with us and be in a different
dimension and we would not be aware of
your presence. In a sense, that is true
for every parallel reality. No matter
how far away it is in time or space, all
of the idea of time and space being the
type of illusion that it is means that
every idea, every civilization, every
time, every place exists quote unquote,
as you say, here and now simply on
different frequencies. Once again, your
radio analogy works best. All the
programs overlap. All the frequencies,
all the signals are there. You get the
one your dial is tuned to. All the
others tuned to other dials will not
experience your program. You will not
experience theirs until the dial is
shifted to accommodate the translation.
So in your society, you're able to tune
to different programs or stations. Y and
as you are learning to do as well. You
see the modality of our space travel is
not really travel in that sense. It is
reidentification of ourselves within the
universal holographic matrix. When we
reidentify the ID of our time space
coordinate vibrational signature, then
by definition, our spaceships must
appear at the new coordinate that has
been programmed into the identity of the
vibrational field of the ship. We do not
travel in a sense. We relocate,
redefine, reidentify ourselves within
the universal matrix. You follow me?
Yes. And I'm wondering about the
direction that we're going to go through
um uh to be able to travel efficiently
at greater distances uh or relocate our
positions. Um our technology has to be
upgraded. We have to have the clarity of
the light crystallization. Come to know
this. I presume uh much of this
technology does already exist upon your
world, but because of what you have
created and structured your society to
be, much of it has been suppressed.
How soon do you see us within what you
call the next three decades of your
time? As we perceive your energy, an
entire foundation for your society will
have been laid to allow each and every
one of you to know beyond a shadow of a
doubt that you create your own reality
that there are other civilizations
desirous of interaction with you. And
you will begin to formulate the ideas of
what you call harmonious existence upon
your entire planetary sphere. So will we
uh have an uh a revolution in travel
then uh the vehicles that we use? Yes.
And are we also able to travel just
spiritually? Oh yes. Understand this is
all quote unquote spiritual travel
anyway. The idea of spaceship or your
own automobiles or trains or planes are
all simply extensions of the level of
awareness your consciousness has created
for itself to exist within. We utilize
the idea of spacecraft still because it
allows us to facilitate interaction with
many societies such as yours more easily
with things you can identify with more
strongly. Although our society is going
through its own transformation and we
are moving from the idea of physicality
into non-physicality even as you are
going from the type of physicality you
exist within now to a more rarified and
more accelerated type of physicality
yourselves. Ashar, I I have a follow- on question if
Ashar, I I have a follow- on question if
I may. Hey, to um the point that was
made earlier about not destroying the
planet. When we're talking about living
your dreams, I'm sure every single
individual regardless of the political
system that they're in really deep down
inside feels that they want peace, they
want harmony, they want some sense of
grounded belongingness. Nice. And I'm
wondering what we can do as individuals
to jointly and individually create that
dream of of peace and harmony. Not in
some airy fairy sense because you know
the people say ah it's a bunch of
baloney. We have to have our weapons. We
have to have this. We have to have that.
Yet on the other hand, I think if we
were to place the same assets, shall we
say, the same resources that are going
into weapons research and things of this
nature into upgrading our ability to get
along with each other and sharing
positive technologies, it would it would
work better. What can we do if you were
advising us? What can we do? First of
all, you can begin to teach the
following idea to every being upon your
world. Each and every individual truly is as
Each and every individual truly is as
powerful as he or she needs to be to
create whatever reality they desire
without having to hurt anyone else or
themselves in order to create it. By
beginning to understand that if anyone
believes they have to force a point of
view on someone else, they obviously do
not believe in the power of that point
of view themselves. The idea of forcing
your point of view on someone else is an
expression of powerlessness, not an
expression of self-containment, power,
not an expression of being a facet of
the universal energy. Belief that you
are already an aspect of universal
energy means you know you are in
control. Forcing an idea upon someone
else means you believe you are out of
control. And then you have a tendency to
believe you are going as you say down
the tubes and wish to take as many
individuals with you as you can because
you do not want to be alone which the
belief in lack of power allows you to
feel as if you are alone. You are not
alone. None of you are alone. You are
upon your own world together as a
family. Literally you are connected to
every other world every other
dimensional plane within creation. Now,
in your terminology, pragmatically
speaking, if you will, but allow
yourselves to know that you can do the
things in your life that attract you,
that you desire, that excite you the
most with integrity, knowing you do not
have to hurt anyone else or yourself in
order to create that reality. You will,
I guarantee it 100%
see the differences occurring. You will
know. You do not have to fear anyone
else because the vibration you are will
be the reality you experience. Remember
this. It is simple physics, simple
mechanics. No circumstance and no
situation has builtin meaning. They are
neutral, blank, empty scenarios in that
way. They are a set of relationship
props. You give them meaning by having
been taught to believe that they mean
this or that or something else. So any
neutral situation that you give a
positive meaning to, you will get a
positive effect out of. Any neutral
circumstance you give a negative meaning
to, you will get a negative effect out
of. It is simple physics, simple
mechanics. And it does work. I guarantee
it. As soon as you know beyond a shadow
of a doubt with ultimate trust and
simplicity that if you are willing to
know what you prefer in life, willing to
believe that your ability to desire it
is your ability to manifest it, then you
will act accordingly physically. You
will act upon the opportunities that
present themselves to you in positive
directions and you will see and reap
positive benefits always. There are no
exceptions. Thank you for I think we
have time maybe for one more question.
Gentleman in the back Kurt, one second.
Let's get back there.
Just this uh in a spiritual sense there
seems to be no contradiction between the
the the idea of predestination
and free will. We do have free will. Oh
yes. in in a spiritual sense, but in a
physical sense. There are two types of
free will. The free will of the physical
you, the physical consciousness you know
yourself to be. The free will of what
you might call the higher consciousness,
the total being. Now, the free will of
the higher consciousness usually will
express itself in your terminology as
what you perceive as predestination or
fate. But it only expresses its free
will in that sense in the most
generalized of terms. All of the
specifics of how you experience the free
will of the higher consciousness is up
to the free will of the physical being
you are in this world at this time.
Another analogy, in other words, let us
say before you chose this physical life,
as you were more blended with your
higher self, you determined that through
and down a specific hallway in this
life, you would walk. That is your
general theme, your general destiny. How
you walk down that hallway is up to the
free will of your physical being. You
can walk, you can run, you can go in the
light, you can go in the dark, you can
go alone, you can go with friends, you
can swim, you can fly, you can go
backwards, you can go upside down, you
can look at all the doorways down the
way, you can go right to the end. It is
up to you how you walk down that
hallway. But walk down that hallway, you
will because that is the basic
experience that the total soul, the free
will of the total being you are desires
to have. You follow me? Yes. But we'll
still be subject to certain physical
laws. uh if for example it is
predestined that California uh where we
are now uh will someday experience a a
disastrous earthquake or it is not
predestined there may be gradual change but
there may be gradual change but
recognize this about what you call
prediction. The idea is that there is no
such thing as a prediction of the future
for all probable futures are just as
real. When you hear a prediction, as you
call it, recognize that it is simply
this. It is a sensing made at the time
the sensing is made of the energy that
exists at the time the sensing is made.
That is the most likely energy to
manifest if it doesn't change.
Therefore, you are being told by the
sensitive individual, this is the
blueprint. This is where the energy is.
This is where the momentum is. If you
don't like it, change it. When you are
made aware of the prediction, if you
realize that you are simply being told,
look, this is the direction you're
moving in. If you don't like it, now
that you are aware of it, render the
prediction obsolete. You are always in
control. You can function as a safety
valve if you wish. And you can channel
that energy through you so that it does
not have to build up to the point where
you have to shake yourselves awake. If
you are willing to wake up now, you can
aid and assist in the transformation and
allow it to change your world in
beneficial rather than disastrous ways.
You can destructurize
your society to reform a new society
without having to cause destruction in
the negative sense. So that is not
predestined. There may be a great deal
of momentum behind it, but much of that
momentum since the first time it was
predicted has changed. And you will find
that many of the catastrophes that have
been predicted for your entire world are
now far more remote, far more isolated,
not as generally widespread. You have
already woken up to a great degree and
done much to transform this energy in
positive ways.
You are always in control. What you may
recognize as the basic laws of the
universe, you may agree to believe in on
math to a certain extent. None of those
laws in any way, shape, or form means
that you must suffer. If a certain area
is going to experience the idea of a
catastrophe in that way, if you are
simply not of the vibration of that
idea, if you do not need that idea,
whether you plan to consciously or not,
you will simply not be in that area when
it occurs. Bashar, I want to want to
thank you for just a moment here. We're
going to have to pause
a little bit speechless as I'm sure many
of you are. But the important thing to
remember here is that we are having
access right now to a reflection of
someone who right from from an outside
environment that's simply reflecting
back to us what we already know. I think
think deep inside we know that this is
what it's all about and we be
responsible for the reality to create.
So stay with us. We're going to be right
back here at Inwardbound with Live Your
Dreams. [Applause] [Applause]
[Music]
Stroke is the nation's third leading
cause of death, but it can be prevented
if you watch for these important
signals. Sudden temporary weakness or
loss of feeling in your face or body.
temporary loss of vision in one or both
eyes, difficulty with speaking, or loss
of power in your legs that causes you to
fall. Today, with your help, stroke can
be a preventable disease. This is a
message from the Will Rogers Institute,
White Plains, New York.
Welcome back to Inwardbound. I'm Sam
Kart and we've been visiting with
Bashar, channeling through Daryl Anka.
Bashar just very briefly I would like to
thank you very much for sharing your
ideas your philosophies and giving us a
good mirror upon ourselves. We thank you
for functioning as ambassadors of your
world and allowing us to function as
ambassadors of our respective worlds. We
extend our unconditional love to you
all. When we talk about inward bound, the
When we talk about inward bound, the
whole theme of the show is about going
within. And I think when we listen and
absorb what Bashar has said, that whole
key thing that we are prisms of light,
all is vibration and belief, emotion and
thought, those are the cornerstones of
the prism. This physical reality that we
create, our persona. And if we want to
really change what our outer expression
is, what we're feeling and experiencing
and seeing reflected back to us and our
creation, then we have to be willing to
change. and hold a different belief of
how we conceive of ourselves and our
relationships to others. And in doing
that and in getting that harmony for
ourselves, we'll bring harmony and peace
to the planet and we'll all have an
awful lot more fun. Thank you. And
please be with us again.
Thank you, Bashar. Great.
Enjoy it.
[Applause] [Music]