all right Al sir how are you all this
evening of your time as you create time
to
exist allow us to begin with the
understanding all
connections linkages and
linkages and
control if you wish that is your
entitlement in recently speaking with a
member of your
Society we did
pull forth out of our interaction the
recognition that we can now find a great
perhaps benefit in Sharing at this time
with you of the idea of the
degree to which you have control over
the linkages and
connections of every circumstance and
situation in your life to every other
circumstance and situation in life
itself and by drawing what you may call
a mean mecal
analogy it may
assist in forming a picture in your
mentality that is most conducive to a
complete and simple fundamental
understanding of the way in which the
mechanism works that allows you to know
you are in
control and that all
circumstances are linked and connected
to all other C circumstances an idea I
have discussed many times with you but
perhaps the Simplicity of this
mechanical analogy will further
illuminate the
idea imagine if you will that each and
every circumstance situation
circumstance situation
relationship an event in your life is
like what you call a wheel before you a
gear if you
wish and and let us say you have many
such gears poking into your particular
sphere of influence your particular
immediate reality these gears can be seen to be
reality these gears can be seen to be
opportunities or circumstances that are
going on in your life ideas that you are
aware of that exist in your
reality that you can act upon can do
something about if you wish if you
prefer to now in vision
to now in vision
that while you may have your own bubble
of reality and these gears may be poking
through the skin of that bubble to you
that they are connected to a rod a shaft
if you will and that these rods these
shafts in proceeding through the skin of
your bubble to the outside of your
bubble into other reality bubbles all
the potential circumstances and
situations that there can be in all
levels of dimensional reality they also
on the other end
of that shaft have a gear a
corresponding gear like the one that is
in your
Bible now recognize that these gears are
connected to other gears which are
connected to shafts which are connected
to other gears in many in fact all
different directions and planes of
existence so simply
recognize that when you turn any of the
gears in your bubble all the gears are
turning now even though this may not be
literal in terms of a mechanical
structure it is literal in terms of the
effect being the same as if it were a
literal mechanical structure when you
turn any gear any situation any
opportunity in any direction that exists
within your bubble you move all other
gears now some of those gears in your
terms may be bigger some may be smaller
so some may move more infinitesimally
than others some may move greatly but
you move them all
nonetheless so recognize what this means
to
you you do not have to go far and wide
searching for the way to control those
outside gears searching and searching
for years to gain
control over gears in that sense which
you believe are so very far removed from
your immediate
reality you do not have to go searching
because you are already in control of
them all the gears all the situations
that poke into your sphere already
connects you to all those other gears
turn them any way you wish it will turn
all the other gears
now many of you may then find that by
this analogy what will allow you to
understand that as you move polarity is
balanced always throughout the Universe
by everything that you do is once again
to understand this as a mechanical
analogy for if you have a gear on your
end of the shaft and a gear on the other
end of the shaft if you to your
perception in facing the gear turn it
let us say one quarter turn to the right
recognize that the other hypothetical
individual on the other end will see
that gear turn a quarter turn to their
left you understand the perspective
as
such they are moving the same way but
from one perspective they are turning to
your right and from the other
perspective they are turning to your
left this is a mechanical analogy of why
balance is maintained in the universe
because everything is connected
literally so as you make any change in
the format that is indicative of your
immediate reality then must be changes
in the formats of all other reality all
other reality to maintain the balance of
the changes you have made it must be
so even though as we have said this is
not necessarily a literal blueprint of
the structure of the physical Universe
in effect it is literal because you get
the same effect as if it were truly
literally a mechanical structure in that
analogy so simply recog
their F that you have all the control
right there within your bubble the
circumstances that make themselves
obvious to you are your gears to move
around and you can then know that by
simply turning those gears because of
the linkages and the connections to all
other gears you from being just right
where you are affect the entire universe
you have an impact on all the way the
rest of the universe shapes itself to be
that is also why you have the best
control I shall use your term best for
now the best control when you remain in
the present where all of your control
gears are when you go outside that
sphere looking in the past looking in
the future looking hither fither as you
say and
yawn then you are ignoring the fact that
within your own bubble I shall say of
reality all the control mechanisms are present
all the control mechanisms are present
and at hand literally and they are
simply the opportunities themselves that
present themselves to you in that
reality the ones that represent the
things that excite you the most as we
have discussed with you many times those
are the control gives and when you act
upon them when you turn them in the
direction you prefer positive negative
right left if you wish that determines
utterly the balance that is created in
the remainder so to speak of the
universe in the reflection of the
universe for the reflection that is out
there are all the other gears that must
by definition respond to the turn of
your gear so what you do determines the
feedback you create the circumstances
you create the environment you create in
the reality around you because you are
turning the gear it is that simple keep
it that
simple this simple mechanical analogy
will allow you to understand that you
have infinite
control from right where you are to what
you perceive to be the infinite reaches
of the
universe for none of that is really in
your terms truly out there it is all
right here you have pushed the illusion
out there to make it seem as if you are
operating within space a volume of space
but that is simply the illusion of this
particular physical
Universe it is all right here and in a
sense truly it is all one Gear with two
signs though you can recognize the
analogy is exactly the same if you
remove the linkage and simply allow that
far gear to Simply Be the other other
side of the gear you have your hand on
you get the same effect turn to the
right somebody standing on the other
side still sees it turning to the
left it is the same gear truly it is the
same gear allow yourselves to know you are in
gear allow yourselves to know you are in
the driver's seat you have all the
control right at home here now in the
presence we thank
briefly and for a moment
specifically wizard yes strawberry
no this is a specific connotation even
though you are all
wizards here the
stars during that
convocation will be sending specific
crystallin vibrations Cal and patterns
of
energy that can be interpreted and
channeled through those beings in that
place at that timing for the laying down
of a crystallin sheath a crystallin
cover a crystallin pattern a crystallin
blanket if you will it will be the
taking of the heaven template the laying
upon it upon the pliable land of your
Earth in that area to allow the pliable
land of that Earth in your area to form
and match
the crystallin template of the stars of
the heavens you follow me yes transmit that
heavens you follow me yes transmit that
idea for now that will be sufficient
thank you thank you at this time
a we extend our appreciation once again
always and forever most deeply to each
and every one of you individually and
collectively for allowing us to
experience this gift of your willingness
and your your interaction this gift of
your Consciousness for being willing to
Consciousness for being willing to
function as the ambassadors of your
society and allowing us to function as
the ambassadors of ours and we simply
ask you now how may I serve
you good evening bishar and to you uh
about two weeks ago I had a dream that I
awoke from feeling like it had a
profound meaning for me but uh the the
symbols and the images drifted away and
I can only remember a little bit of it
um in the dream in the beginning of it I
remember being in a place where I was watching
being in a place where I was watching
the night sky and saw space Vehicles
doing like a demonstration for me I and
I had a wonderful feeling at that time
and then further on in the dream under
the same Sky there was an Indian now I I
think in in my mind it was a hopy Indian
but I'm not sure if I'm just reading
that into it or not will be close enough
it will have been in a sense an
interpretation there will be some
literal connection to it but it will be
representative of energy that they are
very very very familiar with mhm and
they were doing a ceremony and in that
ceremony the name m was given to me it
has some relationship to my husband and
that name just stuck with me and I
wondered if you have any comment on what
that's about what has changed in your
life in these last two of your weeks
most drastically
physically well my Health's getting a
little better all right then that is
some of the conversation and some of the
information some of the recognition of
very ancient connections for you for now
you are in your terms in the middle of a
process which we cannot really interrupt
and besides which that energy that you
perceived is the one in your terms
handling this interaction for you in
your dream state let us for now say to
some degree it carries some cacina
lineage some Kachina energy though there
are many other connections many other
dimensions of connections to ancient
times even preceding what you may call
your recognizable world history mhm
allow yourself to Simply continue to
feel the depth the thickness of the flow
of that energy of communication between
you there are many more things which
have yet in your terms to be revealed to
you before it will begin to truly make
itself an obvious pattern in your
physical reality which is what we
perceive will be the typical way it will
tend to come out rather than maintaining
conscious recollection of any so-called
conversation the patterns in your
physical reality your attitude the way
you do things your habits will change
and begin to alter most drastically and
it is those changes that will allow you
to see physically feel and experience
the results of the conversations you are
having for you are in many ways
beginning to identify with a very old
self in a very new way and you are going
to begin to be that old self in a new
way completing a circle that was begun
in your terms begun a long time ago
for now that is what we can share with
you otherwise we would be interrupting a
flow that is still ongoing thank you in
this particular case I have another
question uh what is the origin of mulite
techtite and how can it best be used to
increase multi-dimensional awareness
well have to some degree indicated that
since it is in your terms Green in
coloration it to some degree represents
the dimensional Gateway of your fourth
density transformation since Emerald is
the crystallin format represent ative of
the fourth density Earth in that way but
this has in your terms obviously
extraterrestrial connections some of it
in your terms is an Orion connection but
not directly much of it is actually what
you would term a mdec connection the
planet that was in your solar system
destroyed the planet that served as a
temporary base between the ancient Oran
incarnations and what you now call your
present Earth incarnations prior to what
you call atalan in times you follow me
mhm yeah so it is now in raining to your
planet and being discovered upon your
planet as having rained it is elements
of the transformation perhaps with some
specific frequencies that are conducive
to certain individuals who are very
strongly connected to that particular
flow or reincarnational path all the way
back to Orion but Orion Energy is not
the only thing connected to it there are
many other Pathways in general it is
repres presentational of the Gate of
transformation specifically with regard
to the doorways that are opening between
your world and extraterrestrial
community and is there something you can
do with it in terms of meditation or
techniques or size or shape of it use
your imagination for your energy will
steer you uniring in the way that it
will work best for
you trust me okay thank you thank you
very much Pleasant green thanks sh good
much Pleasant green thanks sh good
evening Michelle and to you um my first
question has to do with my daughter
Jennifer who is three and a half years
old since the time of her birth she's
been very sensitive and re is always
getting sick is every has a cycle of
every six to three months of getting
very sick and then having to be on
antibiotics getting well and then
reoccurring constantly reoccurring so I
was wondering what if there's any
agreement between all of us the family
with her or always always there is we
assume you mean what is the agreement
yeah and if I can I don't know how can I
help her with this or how can we just
how can it sit peacefully with me I need
to know all right one
moment the original agreement that we
perceived was for this in your terms
condition to exist approximately up to
the age of
seven perhaps between seven years of age
in your accounting and 10 years of age
in you're accounting there would be a
type of assimilation in this being in
this child that will allow them to
balance and blend some of the energy
they have brought with them from other
lives that they are still working
through you'll kind be of assistance in
accelerating this energy to some degree
if you will by laying the child
down by envisioning a blue energy field
around the child and envisioning in that
field a doorway and a connection back
through outside what you would call your
physical reality to the non-physical
realm back where and when the agreement
was made and in that sense allow your
unconditionally loving energy to be
added to that field added to that
agreement add your awareness to that
agreement and
accelerate the time frame of that
agreement within that energy
field project from your imagination that
that child now exists even though in
your your terms they are but three and
1/2 of your years of age that child now
exists in that energy field as seven
years of age 10 years of age and do it
that way seven first then 10 you follow
me yeah take it linearly otherwise it
may be too confusing for the mentality
okay project the child up simply by
sending the essence of the energy of the
idea that will be Blended by the time
the child is physically seven allow the
child to feel that energy
now and allow the child more recognition
that they can remember they have been
born into a world that does not have to
insist any longer that things take as
long as they used to because time is not
what it used to be you can learn now
with that child to redefine
time redefine it completely utterly in
the moment in the now experience the
idea of the blending at
7 experience the idea of the
understanding at
10 and in that way you may if you wish
briefly take it a little bit further and
project very
gently just a general essence of all the
patterns that will have been laid by the
time the child is 30 to
33 so that the child will understand
that in that time period they have laid
the foundation for the activities they
are going to experience from 33
on gently you are going to be reminding
the child that they knew what they are
doing they are working things through
they are actually very strong but you
can Aid and assist in accelerating that
process a little bit by allowing time to
not be what it used to be so that it
does not have to take as much time for
the child to process you understand
yeah this will allow the releasing to
occur in a very accelerated
manner follow me yeah I think
so what do you think you need
clarification of um I
just I'll just need to hear it again
moment if you wish
as was suggested call upon the
assistance of both through that doorway
not only your guide the child's guide
but also the
dolphins all right okay call upon their
assistant imagine that all the Blended
energy of all those beings is in that
energy bubble and then think the idea of
the blending of seven the blending of 10
and the understanding in that way of all
those ages up to 33 and the momentum
generated clear the channel in that
sense you will have all the help you
need all right okay thanks for that can
I ask one more question about um a dream
I had about three weeks ago um anyway I
was dreaming this dream and then in a
point of it I stopped and said I don't
want to dream this anymore and suddenly
I appeared at the footsteps at the of an
escalator and there was my husband and
myself and a woman there that was like a
tour guide or something yes yes
yes and very good very good you are
taking yourself to a new level entirely
lucid dreaming being aware that you are
dreaming when you are dreaming allows
you to know you are creating your
reality on all levels and that being now
that you had opened yourself up to that
recognition was capable of being seen
and perceived by you and there to guide
you to the next level for you were in
the astral realm and that was one of
your guys yeah because um after she led
me through a maze of different
escalators and I could never remember
the Dream from the point of stepping on
the escalator to the end I just remember
being at the base of an escalator and
then getting off of it and going on to a
next one but I woke from then suddenly
less analysis more trust
okay confusion in that fence is being
used to relax your analytical mind since
you have no hope of figuring out where
you are then you stop trying to and let
yourself get to where you're going right
at the I when I woke up from the dream I
after you have those escalators do
you I um suddenly I I was put back into
where I left off in the dream but it was
I controlled the the scenario a little
differently and and it worked out really
great and but I woke up um like singing
or vibrating having these like tones and
I could feel myself waking up but my
body wasn't completely awake and I I
could consciously recall having to like
or do the these tones or something to to
like pull out or something very good
because then you now have been allowed
the opportunity to be very aware of the
fact that all physical reality is the
product of vibration and now you are
very aware that with that vibration you
create the physical reality you had to
exercise your conscious control over
that reality to create it you are
becoming aware of the fact that the
creation of reality is now a conscious
act not an unconscious
one thank you well thank you for waking
up into a new world all together I mean
that literally yeah I know thank you
very much thanks good day to you good
morning Sher
hello my friend done to you how is
everything perfect and you perfect oh
thank you it's been a while since I've
spoken with you here but um a friend and
myself have been transmitting
telepathically to you over the past week
empathically T empathically I was
wondering if uh if are we are we coming
through it
[Music] all in a sense you are feeding into the
all in a sense you are feeding into the
mainstream energy of which our
civilization is entirely involved in
that sense I do not have to have
specific always recognition of the ideas
of specific communication if and when
such recognition is necessary on a
specific level usually it will occur
when and where it needs to but we do
feel the addition of the energy always
the addition of the general energy and
the involvement and intermesh if I may
of your Society without
we are not focusing on the specifics of
the individual Persona we are focusing
upon the general addition of energy I
understand completely what you mean that
experience happens I think all the time
yes thank you for that like you I um
last week we took a trip uh to your
spacecraft and in that journey I noticed
a couple of things that I wanted to ask
about all right uh first of all I
noticed that there was a some sort of a
hand salutation of some sort could you I
uh was that just a greeting I mean is
that what it was it was in a sense
simply welcome opening of
Hearts it was very
nice and um there was also a star-shaped
Crystal formation now I'm I'm just this
is what I envisioned and right ahead
trying to align that or anything almost
every single individual that has taken
that Journey with us through the aspects
of their mentality has arrived in what
will be extremely colloquially called
the chapel now this contains a crystalline
chapel now this contains a crystalline
structure that each of you will
interpret in your own way and that
crystalline structure in communing with
it will put you in touch directly with
all that is we refer to it as a chapel
simply because of that connotation that
analogy it is not literally a chapel as
you understand the idea but it is a
chamber it contains that Crystal and in
communing through that Crystal you open
up to all of all that
is oh boy that fits in so perfectly the
next question I was going to ask you or
the next item was I envisioned some kind
of Rejuvenation
chamber and I saw your
companions walking in and they would
just stand there and it I don't know why
I just got the idea that they were
rejuvenating themselves somehow in a
sense for communing with all that is
always keeps us in the now and in a
sense that is rejuvenating it forms what
you might call an active stasis lack of
Aging oh
oh
oo that would be handy
huh anytime you live in the now you
become ageless for you do not create as much
ageless for you do not create as much
time yes and you know that's it's also
interesting too because you've you've
said many times as well you've tried to
tell me and I've tried to apply it uh
the lack of finite the finite quality in
life the No Beginning No End and if you
really truly can remove yourself from
the time scale schedules and the time
framework and and think of your and not
be waiting for things to always happen
waiting for results you know then I
really I feel like that is really one of
the keys to approaching fourth
density and that is what allows it to
accelerate most quickly for when you're
not looking for it it turns up
sooner that's really true because you
are not creating as much time in between
where you think you are and where you
imagine it is
is it is only the creation of that time
that places it out there right instead
of right here yes oh boy again it is the
analogy of having the two gears you
decide how much of a Links of a
connector Rod there is between the two
because there doesn't have to be any
it can be two sides of the same coin the
same
gear I see that would help
greatly I'm learn I'm I'm learning how
to apply that yes you are and you are
doing brilliantly thank
brilliantly thank
you that goes for all of
you this is a great group too I I have
one more question all right um since we
are accustomed to a certain set of
problems and or challenges as third
density beings speak for
yourself can I I'll call them
challenges all right is that better okay
if um as third density beings
approaching fourth density you are
neither third nor precisely fourth yet
but you are more fourth than
third oh all
all
right you are in the transition
state you are limbo
beings so we we are in the midst of the
transformation we are neither
specifically one nor the other very good
you are the idea of the transformation
itself therefore not precisely either
one or the other yet
interesting okay does that assist you
yes it does I have one more quick
question I know everybody wants to ask
questions it's regarding the seminar and
I wanted to thank you I haven't had a
chance to thank you for the seminar that
I participated in yes you have by doing
what excites you in life that is our
thanks ah
the the one thing I need to clarify were
the specific or the relatively specific
effects of the different colored
energies that we experienced I believe
they were red blue gold white and
green um and specific the the reason I'm
asking is because after the seminar I I
got a little ill um yes sometimes many
of you will in processing what you may
call the toxins out of you
ah so it's emerging or old problems that
are coming up with something that is all
it gets a bit headyy for a while but it
clears out okay that is all there is to it now
out okay that is all there is to it now
which now the blue energy that we we
will leave that up to you for now trust
your imagination whatever you seem drawn
to work with it in whatever way it seems
to come most naturally okay thank you
thank you very much Bashar
good night and to
you sharing greetings Bashar and to you
sharing greetings Bashar and to you
we're very excited to be here and I was
wondering if you
could give me an explanation of the
words ad vasu barakus their origin their
meaning ad in that way shall be a
general representation
of a certain level of non-physical
energy non-physical
Consciousness sometimes
attributed to what you might call the
overall Collective Christ
Consciousness sometimes to one of the
levels of consciousness that filters
through or as the Christ Consciousness
that you may call Angelic Consciousness
all of these are very colloquial
nomenclatures however the
the
secondary has to do with filtering some
of that particular style of
Consciousness through a particular
format a cultural format upon your
planet that is very ancient centered
around the areas you would call the
Himalayas and therefore
perhaps reflective
of very ancient interpretations very
ancient relationships and very ancient
understandings of the world Spirit the
Collective Soul if you
will repeat the third baracus ad vasu
baracus references in our perception are
scattered on the third there seem to be
many connections many plugins to many
different cultures at many different
times some of which may even be in your
terms extraterrestrial in origin it is a
very ancient terminology in that sense
but it has become extremely mixed
throughout the different cultures and
Evolutions upon your
world it was used as a closing
salutation by on many tapes that I heard done by a
by on many tapes that I heard done by a
channel 15 years ago of from a space
being space Brothers the boys upstairs
as they call them and I
never there are girls here
too good now yes that is some of the
Extraterrestrial energy we are
connecting into but it is not
exclusive to the upstairs in that sense
I see it has been utilized many times in
many different cultures many different
sects of understanding upon your
planet it has to do to some degree with
mirrors and reflectivity of
Consciousness it has to do also with
ancient intertwinings some of them actually
intertwinings some of them actually
genetic between your civilization and
others and the mirroring represented in
that connotation as
well some of it will reach deeply
down into your ancient Beginnings as
physical beings upon your
world and let us say
briefly those that have been
watching since
then to some degree it is a symbol it is
a salutation of a gathering of
Consciousness extraterrestrial in nature
which may generally be referred to
Simply as Watchers
observers for now that is our perception
for now has that served you that has
thank you very much thank
you sharing hello Bashar hello hello um
sharing hello Bashar hello hello um
you it's really good to talk to you I uh
well because I have a project in mind
and I thought I'd uh Broach it to you a
co-creator all right um and a little background on
all right um and a little background on
it was that last year uh not this last
winter but the winter before when it
rained so so much there was a
manifestation on the Hills above a
little town named Gorman on the Ridge
Route of your two favorite colors that
you've given us in many meditations the
orange and the
blue and um I Came Upon them Easter
Sunday upon those Hills uh the year
before last last Easter year ago Easter
and it for 3 miles it was Brilliant
Orange and in all the cracks of the
hills down through the little gullies
there was this beautiful blue of the
loopin well last year there was not very
much rain and when I went up on Easter
Sunday this year hoping to see the same
thing again there was just a few flowers
scattered on the Hills so I got this
idea because it was your two favorite
colors I thought I did not say they were
my two favorite not your two favorite
but two that you work with quite yet and
uh I thought maybe if uh I could um uh
use a a little visualization and
meditation and you could SE a few clouds
maybe we could get a lot of rain
going and come up next year with the
same kind of manifestation that we came
up with last Easter of three miles of
Brilliant Orange Hills with blue loopin
in them how about if we seed a few
hearts a few Souls of Minds that sounds
fabulous then in that sense go and be
that Bountiful Bountiful
Garden be there and radiate your energy
be the crystal through which the white
light of your higher Consciousness will
be broken down into the Rays of blue and
orange and fed into that field be the
seed yourself okay the energy of the
universe is yours to flow through you as
you wish and you can create the
necessary energy rain for those flowers
they will will respond to you perhaps
within a certain perimeter you may have
to stand in a few places to get them all
to
feel you mean uh actually go up to the
mountains and and stand actually go up
to the mountains yeah okay I'll take a
few people up there and we'll seat it
this year we can all go up on a trip
next year and maybe your spaceship can
come over and say hello maybe maybe not
mine okay well maybe another uh
okay and my other question was um about
lucid dreaming I um I'm very interested in
dreaming I um I'm very interested in
lucid dreaming from the time I was a
little girl I was taught that it was one
of the ways one of the most efficient
ways to change your reality was to
become a lucid dreamer and then to
control your dream and have it come over
into your is very efficient yes okay so
it deep inside of me is that training
from when I was a very small child and
um how far inside of you deep deep way
down there yes
right well uh I'd like to call on that
and know if there's anything that um you
could add to the techniques that I've
been reading about and um yes stop
picturing it as being so deep it is
right on the
surface otherwise the most powerful
light you could ever imagine will never
reach it will never illuminate it for
you oh why keep it so deep mhm I think
that's probably what I have been doing
all right saying that it was back in my
child bring it up to the surface the
child is with you now you are the child
right now right
now okay I feel that all right then it
is with you right
now is there uh anything you don't
believe it do you no I guess I
don't I want why not just simply believe
it and then go and dream
okay all right I will thank you very
much forar well thank you very much
little
girl little flower
Shing hi Bashar Hi how are you perfect
oh good and how are you I'm very excited
to be here same thing uh um
I have a couple questions the first one
has to do up the first one has to do
with um the animals on our planet yes um
lovely aren't they they are they're
wonderful and uh I am wondering if um
are they conscious beings are they
different from us how are they different
from us they are not
self-analytical that is the prime
difference mhm um I guess what I want to know is
mhm um I guess what I want to know is
how I can get in contct with them better
how I can communicate with your emotion
with your heart with your understanding
with your love with your sharing with
your joy with your playing with them
with your entering their realm of Nature
and getting in touch with the fact that
they are also simply projections and
aspects of your own Consciousness
getting in touch with those aspects of
your Consciousness will bring up within
in your imagination your emotionality
and your physicality all the
identificational vibrations you need to
begin to relate to them as one of them
and allow them to relate to you as you
for you are extensions in that thing
that sort of gets into my second
question which is
um I understand that I create my reality
right I also understand that there are
other beings that exist apart from me
all right in a sense yes well that's
where I get confused where you know
where does that line lie how it lies
within you and it isn't really truly a lie in
you and it isn't really truly a lie in
that sense the idea simply is to
understand that whatever it is you
experience regardless of whether it is
an interaction with another being or not
you must create in your reality your
version of that being in order to
perceive that you are interacting with
them anyway so what you are actually
physically directly interacting with is
still an extension of your energy even
if it is a representational extension
that represents someone else you follow
me not exactly all right let us say that
you have surrounded yourself with a wall
of rubber all right okay now it is plain
and smooth perhaps if you wish a
360° sphere of smooth thin rubber yeah
now you know that other beings out there
somewhere beyond the wall of
rubber when another being comes up and
says hello anyone there who say yes in
here well they may press their face into
the Rubber and that may be an
interaction with another being but what
you see is the rubber made of your own
world that is what allows you to
perceive them the rubber comes from you
you follow me yes that is the analogy
you can draw and animals are the same
way in a sense yes although
more precisely the animals are the
rubber you lost me there animal
Consciousness though it is its own
Consciousness as the rubber is its own
recognizably different material from you
is an extension of you is an extension
of creational
energy manifesting in the
format conducive to reflect in the most
efficient possible way your particular
connections to all that is through that
particular scope that particular aspect
that particular idea animal
Consciousness is the rubber it is not
really beyond the rubber now in a sense
everything is the rubber but animals are
more just the rubber itself because they
are not
self-reflexively analytically aware
they are aware but only as pure
Consciousness they are knowing
Consciousness not thinking Consciousness
they do not remove themselves from the
essence the fabric the rubber of
creation whereas what you call
intellectualized Sapient beings can
create the illusion that they are
something separate from the Rubber and
then use the rubber to create a
representational format in which they
can reconnect in order to be able to
reconnect in order to be able to
interact in an apparently remote
way you follow me a little bit all right
it has sunk in it yes let it play itself
out in your
imagination dream and drift about it
Muse about it contemplate about it do so
in nature and the animals will reflect
as the loving guides and Reflections
that they are all that you need to
understand about your relationship to
each other
it does not have to be an analytical
understanding yes that's true um just in
response to that I usually have very
clear dreams that I remember very well
but I have not been for the last week or
so you are simply not yet used to the
fact that you are beginning to blend the
dream and the physical reality together
as one there is some confusion on your
part because it is not as clearcut a
separation anymore that's very
true I have one more quick question and
this is um
in response to I I heard you about a
month ago talk
about uh the fact that there are a lot
of people in our government that know
about you and have interacted with you
not me specifically you but the various
civilizations and the association yes
yes um I uh where I work we had a
presentation not too long ago by a man
from the Air Force about our role in
space exploration our Earth role named
Joseph Angelo and I wondered if he was
one of those
people not
directly okay but there are in your terms orders
okay but there are in your terms orders
being passed down filtered down to
certain individuals to get them to
function within an overall plan of
timing that is conducive to the
Revelation by your government of the
information that they are aware of even
though many of the individuals in that
plan do not know there is a plan okay I
just wondered because he uh he seemed to
be expressing a lot of the ideas and
philosophies that I'm hearing here he
has his own understanding of this as
well quite apart and aside ah from the
intimate knowledge that certain other
individuals may have he is generally
aware of what is going on and that is
why you are picking up that General
representation but it is not a direct
understanding it is what you would call
speculation that is mostly
accurate okay thank you thank you very
much rainbows to
you sheding hi Bashar
hi um a couple of months ago I was um
sick and was in the hospital and I came
to see you after that after that little
bout and you had told me to to do what
excited me most and that things would
come through in my dreaming State and um
after that
about oh a couple of weeks after that
cuz I didn't remember anything for a
couple of weeks but after that about um
every 3 days I dream about swimming with
whales um and it's very real I me it's
like I I am swimming with them and um
they are swimming with you yeah it's
wonderful yes um and I um a couple of
nights ago um I had a dream where I was
with um a friend of mine who is a little
fearful I think of you know the
possibility of actually doing it in the
physical reality um and we were in this
near this tank and there were
three large whales and they were
swimming around and around and we were
petting them and touching them and
talking with them and a man came in the
back and I don't know who the man was it
there was no face attached
but he had said something and all of a
sudden I for the first time got fearful
of their size and immediately the three
whales disappeared along with my friend
and my husband was there all of a sudden
and there was a baby whale and I was
touching it and everything was okay
again um my question is
is now I'm confused why well now I don't
know what to do I'm like do I go try and
find a job where I swim with whales or
if
you I don't well it does I well then
then go do that you don't have to try to
find it yeah allow yourself to attract
the obvious Opportunity by placing
yourself in whatever environment is
conducive to being asked I
see okay and simply remember that that
individual was a part of your timing to
allow you to examine at that moment
whether the reflection of the infinite
power from on that whale that reflects
back to you your own infinite power is
something you believe you can handle at
this point right well I remember asking you
point right well I remember asking you
if I could swim with the whales because
everybody had been talking about
swimming with dolphins and everything
and that was okay and you said yes why
not you know and um and I got very
excited about that possibility and I
went home and told um my husband and a
friend about it and both of them got
very fearful about the size of the whale
and I said that the whale knows this
their size and they know my size and
they would never hurt me it would be
okay correct um but the idea is that
individuals who fear them for that
reason usually are not in touch with the
size of their own power and fear it I
see okay all right okay and that is what
you were given an opportunity in that
moment to decide for yourself whether it
is truly something you know regardless
of its size is a gentle loving energy or
whether you will simply let that the
idea of the size be something that will
invoke your excitement into fear could
that have been what that male voice was
in the dream behind me was my fear
coming through it was in a sense some
assistance to give you an opportunity to
hear and feel the fear come through so
you could decide whether it really had
anything at all to do with your reality
or not oh and you immediately allowed
yourself to bring it down to size oh
okay same concept but a baby right okay
good it will always conform to whatever
parameters allow you to continue to
participate in a comfortable and loving
manner okay always good okay thank you
very much say hello I will thanks
morning
you B do you do you experience
fluctuations in mood and emotion
personally you mean from happy to
ecstatic and back to happy
again like that
forever a wise
guy let us simply say there may be
moments within what you would perceive
to be our
demeanor where we would seem to be
perhaps intent upon
intent upon
something but there is always
contentment with that so you're simply
focused more in certain directions at
times okay that may create an apparency
of
fluctuation and it is fluctuation but
not within what you would call a wide
range of emotional fluctuation gotcha
some reflection on um personal
experiences occurred recently actually
been going on for some time we've
addressed this I think most of the
answers are there but it has to do with
shall we now undress it yes let I like
that concept pretty much right
um it has to do with the fact that uh um
on a number of occasions I have got
excited about things had them go
extremely well and then apparent for no
apparent reason have them go wrong wrong wrong
reason have them go wrong wrong wrong
meaning heavy fluctuations in Emotion
appear to be able to not sustain the
excitement or to have the specific
materialization I know that this you
know you know you speak of the subject
of expectancy and one comes back to
Simply allowing what occurs to occur yes
and recognizing what is occurring to be
a part of the change you have made and
ceasing to assume that it is an
indication of an interruption in that
idea that that's part of what I need
some or would like some reflection on
because it seemed to fall into the old
pattern of why do you continue to assume let me
of why do you continue to assume let me
put it this way sure the old pattern if
it is anything is your continuance to
assume that you are falling back back
into an old pattern no I'm simply trying
to look at it this is not true I don't
expect these things to occur that's not
the point okay what I are saying is that
when they do you are saying that you
continue to evoke the old pattern of
assuming that these things that have
occurred are the wrong
things rather than knowing you have
change and therefore what is occurring
is the thing that is indicative of the
change and not an interruption in the
change understood intellectually
emotionally you've got uh I have an
excitement going something is flowing in
a particular direction and then there is
the feeling I know this is possibly not
you're not too familiar with feeling
like crap but
uh I know I can get an exterior view I
can take the exterior point of view that
you have but I'm not sure whether you
are familiar with the um with that kind
of VI of vibration being stuck in that
sort of a heavy condensed emotional type
of we can recall from the experience of
the physical Channel's life in terms of
our past experience in that way to some
degree mhm but I'm not sure that the exterior
mhm but I'm not sure that the exterior
view Viewpoint always has a degree of
workability yes why doesn't
yours because it gets introverted
instead of why does it get introverted
because of my judgments on on the energy
that materializes do you Jud was
unexpected why do you judge
them habit I suppose why do you have
that
habit good question
well um if you continue I shall say to bring
um if you continue I shall say to bring
yourself back to the level of looking at
the Habit you believe you have then work
with that idea while you're on that
level perhaps as a suggestion and
speaking in your colloquial terms the
reason you keep bringing yourself back
to that point perhaps it's because you
haven't dealt with that point yet
Perhaps there is something you are not
looking at not dealing with before you
go on perhaps you are attempting to
circumvent something you really know
deep down inside of you you need to look
at first obviously all right so how does
having the habit if you believe you have
it how does that serve
you what is there within the idea of
having that
habit that you need to look at I sticks
your nose back into the situation that
you haven't been looking at I suppose
all right that may be one idea there may
be things about yourself that you are
avoiding looking at let me give you a
specific example because I seem to be
getting a little bit off of this um I
have I have someone that I love very
much and we've been having experience of
abundance and then there materializes an
apparency of going having to go back to struggle
of going having to go back to struggle
resulting in
grief to have
um Financial Freedom to move around the
person fig feels that you know we were
flowing creating a certain abundance an
abundance of some specific idea money
why just that Focus I didn't have just
that Focus but I found that
uh that she fell into the concept of
having to go back to struggle in order
to survive and I felt empathy for that
so wasn't certain how to handle it um
all right empathy a does not have to
mean sympathy nor does it have to mean
sharing the idea in your reality there
wasn't sympathy all right there was
there was a bit of sadness well then
okay tou now the
idea of watching another individual go
through the fluctuations of their
understanding of abundance if that be
the thing they are working
through does not in your terminology
even though you are quote unquote
bonding with them have to necessarily
create fluctuations in your life
that you must experience in the same way
if you agree to go through
fluctuation because the other individual
is going through
fluctuation then your solid trust and
faith and belief in what your
fluctuations represent as a positive
idea can allow you in translating them
in a positive way and seeing positive
manifestation in your life occur from
treating it that way can allow you to
function as a reflective positive mirror
for another individual going through
what may on the surface appear to be
similar fluctuations but which they may
be choosing to interpret as negative so
you can act as a polarity again the idea
of the gear the two sides of the gear
just because another individual sees the
fluctuations as representing a left hand
if you wish or a negative turn doesn't
mean you have to even in experiencing
the same surface manifestations doesn't
mean you have to interpret them in the
same way you can reflect your
interpretation in a positive direction
of the same fluctuations again remember
no circumstance has buil-in meaning just
because they look the same just because
you are going through the same scenario
doesn't mean it will affect you in the
same way if you don't have a similar
attitude to someone who is going through
it and choosing to look at it as a
negative experience yeah I think I T I
tend to fight the experience that they
have you might just be assuming that
simply because you are in the same boat
you have to be seeing the same ocean
and that is not true yeah no no I don't
m i what what tends to happen is now one
moment go ahead one more nothing tends
to happen agreed okay poor choice of
words which reflect I
understand um go ahead and defy I will be almost
um go ahead and defy I will be almost
projecting a uh a mental bolt that's too
strong that says no no no you don't have
to think of of it this way all right now
there's a very strong and important clue
for you as well for you may be focusing
on the fact that you fear you will fall
into it so strongly that you
automatically do you don't not have to fight that all
do you don't not have to fight that all
you hit a cord there just know that you
don't prefer it that way and if for a
moment because of the empathy because
you wish to identify because you wish to
understand what someone else is going
through if for a moment you identify to
the point where you experience the same
idea you empathize doesn't mean it has
to continue for longer than the moment
it takes to understand what they are
going through so you can help
them right so do not fear that just
because you do perceive the
identification of what they are going
through that it becomes a scenario you
have to fight back for that attitude in
and of itself will plop you squarely in
their ocean lovely that's very helpful
thank you for opening that door it was
well oiled thank
you you're a good friend Bashar what was
the question you wanted to ask about
material best material for
meditation pyramid perhaps
copper in the idea that it is a very
strong electromagnetic conductor in that
way lovely one side facing magnetic
north all right you're as clever as we
are B Sure
clever you have I just been insulted you
no only if you choose to assign that
meaning to
it I will take it as a com oh well good
that is the way it was
meant but you know how how much fun we
love to have with you I know together y
byebye than you hello
sharings hi Bashar hi good to see you
and um I'm really sharing this evening
by all means oh great and share okay I
will take
take
oh all right enjoy your show thank you
okay um well ask week I I learned to
follow the excitement so I thought well
I I'll do it so I uh well I needed a job
at the time so I uh one of the things I
did was uh call up a company I used to
work for and I wanted uh couldn't have
just an ordinary job I had to have the
best secret EXA secretary job there so I
used to work there and the the executive
I called said how did you know I said no
what and he said uh my secretary's
leaving and I need someone how could you
possibly know we haven't told anyone or
posted it or put an ad in the paper and
I went
well what can I say this is the truth of
what's happening and he says well get
over here so I went over there and um
and went had a nice reunion with them
and uh then I was in Waiting okay and I
didn't really know if I had it but I was
pretty sure I did so um I had some
considerations on it so I thought gez
I'm going to get stuck in this job it's
going to take up so much of my time I'm
um I'm a singer also so I need a lot of
other time and uh and I had these
considerations like oh God it's going to
be fulltime I'm not going to have enough
time right so it just kind of floated
along for two weeks while I was
listening to Bashar tapes and everything
and then there's another excitement in
my life to follow and I thought well
well that's cooking on the back burner
I'll go off and follow this other one
and so I made a reunion with a very dear
friend of mine who was appearing at the
Anaheim Convention Center last Saturday
and I went I was so excited to to see
him again and it was packed there and I
went with two of my friends here tonight
and we were sitting there waiting for
the show to start and my one friend L
said why not to go down backstage before
uh the show start and I went oh no he's
busy I haven't seen him in three years
and all that kind of just go I went all
right so I went back downstairs and
there was this gate and right at this
gate was a man and he had a little
uniform on and a name tag that said
Marty and I said hello I'm a friend of
Jose's and I'm here to see him and he
goes I'm sure you are and he just opened
the gate and uh yeah I just walked right on
gate and uh yeah I just walked right on
through and I went backstage and and I
just had this most incredible reunion
with him and he asked me please stand
beside the band stand while I do the
concert I said I'd love to so I just
stood there and in the when his opening
number it was just so incredible the excitement
it was just so incredible the excitement
and Ecstasy of that moment with the
crowd and everything in the orchestra
and I just stood there and realize I am
living my
dream yes yes that's what I wanted to do
and there I was and I went this is where
I belong all right so I had two really G
great tremendous things happen and then
I started having a
dream and I r that I was going into I
thought it was a car wash right and I
thought it was in my car but I liked my
little car and it's kind of like a
little spaceship you know and I drove
into this place and it was all white and
Misty and I went well it's not really a
car wash
so so I got out of my car and it was
more like a bay like a big Bay you know
like a Docking Bay or something and I
got out of my car and I stepped back and
I took some things out of the car to
throw in the garbage garbage that I
didn't want and my car immediately
transformed into what I thought was this
beautiful white motor
home and I I went this is beautiful
right and I went wow so I went inside
and everything looked familiar to me and
I went yeah that's mine okay and then I
went outside oh I was about to go
outside and this man came in and he
resembled a man who had threatened me
once in my life and I had a tickle of
fear for a second then I went uh-uh
right and the guy came towards me and he
just looked at me and I just put it out
there hey no
negativity so so instead of harming me he just went
so so instead of harming me he just went
around he picked up some of my
belongings and he just started putting
him in an order that I didn't approve of
okay and I went uhhuh okay and I just
walked out I didn't get all caught up in
it right so I walked out and I'm
standing there and I turn around and to
my left is this guy and he's like 8 feet
tall seven or eight feet tall I mean I
had to go like that you know I'm short
but I looked at him and I went see
that's weird I haven't seen you before
right and he goes well I've seen
everything that's happened I went really
and as I kept perceiving him I could
perceive him even more and here was this
gorgeous man he was blonde he had giant blue eyes
man he was blonde he had giant blue eyes
beautiful light tan golden skin he
flashing perfect white teeth he was
gorgeous right and I went
wow and he had white on he was just wow
right and he came
around and he came around behind me and
I went whoa and he put
it and I was so like wow and he put his
arms around me from behind and I felt as
though I was being enveloped in wings or
something it was so wonderful and he put
forth to me the most love I have ever
experience and I melded with this person
and he you did for it is
you it is your own future
beingness welcome
home thank you to that space to that
ship and to yourself which has beckoned
you from across the ages more more
Communications will
ensue more connection more acceleration
more ecstasy Believe It or Not can't
harly take
anymore yes you can perhaps not the you
you are now but the you you are becoming
will always be able to let more in and
give more out
oh at this
timing we will extend our
appreciation for your sharing thank you
and will suggest that each and every one
of you
live your
break we will resume contact momentarily
thank you
how's everything going [Applause]
all right El say
continue good evening Bashar and to you
a pleasure to be here again with
you um I have been experiencing more and
more connectedness to more aspects of
myself um I sort of feel like that that
energy globe or sphere that you've
described with connections extending into all
with connections extending into all
Dimensions all right and other
civilizations as well also last week
when I was driving down the freeway I
was listening to some very
moving very emotional Scottish songs and
I found myself channeling
that sort of vibration through my own
experiences to
essani and feeling
that it would be a way for all of you to
maybe understand more about how we've
experienced our lives in separateness
and um all the aspects
of eons of judgment and so forth that
we're now transforming out of thank you
we have our particular civilization
along with many other civilizations but
with our particular
civilization very strong strong
connection to the energy vortex in that
area you call the aisle of man
aha well that's very synchronous because
I was experiencing reexperiencing for
myself all those lifetimes of you
marching into battle behind the bag
pipes and feeling feeling all those
emotions and thinking this is like the
last bit of that the third density
manner of experiencing those ideas but
Underneath It All was always that
Spirit we're kind at this time now
because this gate has opened and passed
reveal in this way some information
which may in your terms seem innocuous
enough on the surface but which will
open many gates within many of you this
night of your time and allow you to
explore what has been held to be the
Subterranean areas of much of your
Consciousness well how have been
told that we are not so much speaking
your language but it is our thoughts in
a sense that are activating within the
channel subconscious whatever vocabulary
is inherently been programmed within him
and translates your Concepts your language
translates your Concepts your language
our Concepts into your language
utilizing the physical Channel as a
translation Divine now the idea of the channel
Divine now the idea of the channel
subconscious in Pursuit receiving us to
be as you would say foreign is what is
the mechanism as you say responsible
for time to time adding what you would
perceive to be an accent to the words
that come through the physical Channel
I've always loved your action but now
specifically well recognize it is not my
accent but now specifically the idea
also of the accent that automatically is
supplied by the channel subconscious to
the words that are utilized in
interpreting the concepts of our thought
has to do specifically with the very
strong gate on the aisle of
man for it is deep within the channel
subconscious of a very strong connection
there and it has to do with the opening
of many doorways and the exploration of
the Subterranean aspects of the group
Consciousness that your world is it is
our particular flavor or entry point
into your world in many ways for many
reasons Aon
gbra we thank you for your sharing and
your synchronicity in allowing us to
open that particular doorway and aspect
of the collective Consciousness that we
are with you this night of your time
thank you so much Bashar you're always
full of surprises so are you all this is
true you keep us hopping I'll tell you
that one more thing um yes is it
possible to ask for a message from the
dreamers tonight Daryl's wearing his
dolphin t-shirt and I think that would
be then for now recognize that the
symbology is message enough if you focus
upon it you will find that from time to
time as you catch yourself unawares
there will be messages coming in if you
utilize the symbol itself you will click
into that frequency and messages will be
received by you which will be played out
later perhaps in your dream ities or
physical lives this is true it's
happening all the time thank you very
much we thank you
sharing good evening B and to you one
moment as we have also shared the idea
that our thoughts are translating not
only what you perceive to be vocally but
also some of the communication we are
having with you let us say the spillover
is translated in the physical motions
you see undertaken by the Channel's body
many times with what you call the hand
movements to reinforce not only what has
been communicated auditorily to you but
also to let you know there are other
levels of communication taking place
from us to you the third methodology
unspoken of as of yet and no accident
involved in this many times are the
actual graphic symbols upon the
Channel's body for the visual clues in this way
body for the visual clues in this way
and the individuals that may from time
to time provide some of the visual clues
that are worn from time to time also are
conducive to the opening up of
communication with you on yet other
levels that you have not even
suspected thank you thank you a trary
method of communication as befits the
Triads in which we
function sure I've been very interested
in painting for since I was two years
old no right is there any information
that you could give me that might help
me to remove whatever barriers I have
what barriers do you have creating in
that way have you painted some not as
much as I would like to how much would
you like to I'd like to do it every day
why don't you that's the question what's
the answer I don't
know that's why I'm asking you well in
your estimation what prevents you from
painting every day I have not the
foggiest notion let's put it this
notion let's put it this
way are you now going to paint every
day I doubt
it what would you like to
paint mostly Landscapes all
right any particular
type no just Landscapes and SE Scapes
all right Land And
seascapes now when you pain what do you
do where do you go how do you set up how
do you begin how long do you paint when
you paint how often do you
paint well it's usually from 3 to 5
hours at a time no right
and an ordinary eel and paint set up
oh how many times in what you would call
your average week or month if you put H
used to be once a week it's not anymore
what is it now once a month right
whatever six months all
right now when you are painting how do
you feel magnificent
magnificent and when you are
not somewhat less than that all right
may I suggest
something yes no maybe oh absolutely oh
thank
you begin if you
wish to understand everything in life as
a painting for you have literally
painted everything you
experience the astral U the dream U is a
magnificent painting look at what you
have done look at your canvas all around
you shining with bright iridescent color
light but light look at the
painting now one of the reasons that you
may be holding back from the expression
in your typical terms paint upon easel
upon canvas in that
way maybe because
you are placing a little bit of
invalidation upon the painting of life
itself because you do not believe that
there are in that sense inherent within
life the beautiful things that are a
painting in and of
itself you may be creating a little bit
of apathy within you about the painting
in which you already exist and so you
perhaps find your
inspiration to paint not necessarily
thinking that your paintings can capture
what you believe is missing in the
painting of your
life what would it take to inspire
you what does it take to inspire you now
what inspires
you beauty in any form Beauty in any
form do you recognize that life itself
even when you are not physically
painting is Beauty in every form oh
absolutely all right then why is it less
magnificent when you are not physically
painting than when you
are I think maybe that sometimes my
representation isn't
as true as what I perceive in my own
Universe do you mean your representation
on the canvas that's right so you feel
that you come up short mhm so you feel
you cannot express it as magnificently
as you think you should mhm that's right
all right
however in putting upon that conas at
any given moment the best that you know
how to do you are expressing an absolute
perfect manifestation a full
manifestation remember anything you do
at any given moment is perfect for what
it is and has no business being compared
to anything else for relative Merit
you understand yes it is a part of the
landscape your painting is a part of the
present landscape it belongs there if you have
landscape it belongs there if you have
the urge to do it don't judge it let it
fit in and do
remember no matter what you tend to
think about it you are painting as many
painters do windows for other
individuals as well well to see through
and other individuals will get many
services many enjoyments out of your
painting you know you will always change
you know you will always expand and you
know that another painting that you do
may be in your terms a more expanded
expression of the magnificence of life
that you feel in no way shape or form
does that mean you have to discount the
paintings you have already done or
similar to discounting the things you
have done in the past that you no longer
prefer to do if you discount them you do
not allow them to form the base upon
which the next painting can
occur each painting that you do forms
the very canvas for the next painting
you are able to do in all aspects of
your life do not invalidate them for the
way they come out them to come up short
they are perfect for what they are at
that moment okay do you
moment okay do you
think as your sun
sets that even though a particular
object May reflect different degrees and
colors of light at different times that
any one of those Reflections at any
given moment is anything less than any
other reflection no then allow all angles of
reflection no then allow all angles of
light to elude illuminate all aspects of
your life enjoy what you do for the moment
life enjoy what you do for the moment
then do something else that you enjoy a
it's Marvels thank you thank you very
much
sharing good evening Bashar to you this
is my first time here do say yes no um I
always remember I got
uh I uh always remember my or usually I
should say remember my
dreams lately um my dreams have been
more glorious and I've been happier in
my dreams than I have been in my real
life ah now is the time for you to
recognize that your dream and physical
reality are the same reality you have
created a separation in those two
realities because your Society is in the
habit of thinking they are two separate
ideas and that they think the dream
reality is not even real now you know
that you create once again the painting
The Blueprint in your dream reality for
what your physical life can be all you
need to do is remember that you are now
blending your physical reality your
dream reality they are one reality as
you begin to live your dreams all of
that happiness will transfer into your
physical dream as well because your
physical reality is a dream is a dream
is a dream
I I thought that might be
um I have had psychic
dreams and I it didn't frighten me at
the beginning but it does frighten me
now and I don't know
why again to some degree it is because
of the separation that you have created
and now that you know you are connected
into everything you are simply recoiling
at the degree of power you are because
you are beginning you consciously
awaken into the force density dream of
being aware that you are the creator of
your reality and for now many of you are
still a little jittery with that
concept so that is shall we say normal
yes it is natural natural okay for now
it will change allow yourself to do
something with the energy with the
Ecstasy do the things in your physical
life that excite you the most that are
more representational of what you perceive
representational of what you perceive
the Ecstasy of the dream reality to be
Live Your Dreams in physical terms and
then you will blend the Two Worlds you
will know that everyone is psychic
because being psychic is only
consciously knowing that you are
connected to
everything oh that's wonder that is all
it is some of you still feel that that
because you don't think you can contain
that without
exploding that's true that is all that's
very good you are learning to hold your
ecstasy you are learning that you are
big enough to contain it all of it oh
that's it is a passing symptom what you
are going through little bit of the
fourth density
flu I I do have one question more to ask
um
my dreams may have something to do with
I'm sure they
do I have to move I have two poodles and
a cat do you see me finding something
soon please do you have to move or do
you want to move I have to move I do not
want to move why don't you want to move
because I'm very happy where I am do you
think that you could be happy where you
are moving
to if I could find a place if answer the
question okay you lost me would I be
happy let's back up okay you have
poodles and
cats do you enjoy having poodles and
cats oh yes oh yes oh yes no doubt about
it no doubt about it no D then what you
are implying is that having poodles and
cats a thing that represents what
excites you the most creates and
attracts into your life the circumstance
that you now must move
yes um well I don't have to move because
of them
why well I have to move because the
people that have the property want to
move where I am so so they want me out
so they can move in all right but I'm
having difficulty finding a place that
would take
two you have and Cat Cat
yeah back you you you you you since you
know that is representative what excites
you the most you are the
idea of being with poodles and cats you
do not come any other way
way
therefore whatever idea at any given
moment you are that is representative of
what you know know you are all about
must have a niche in the universe to fit
into must therefore relax and allow the niche
must therefore relax and allow the niche
to present itself to you because as soon
as you relax and know that you have to
fit in somewhere otherwise you would not
exist in the frame of reference that you
do because nothing that doesn't fit in
the universe can exist in a frame of
reference that doesn't have a place to
be so as soon as you know you fit you
will attract the obvious automatic
coincidental opportunity to show you
that you know you fit you don't believe
you fit so you can't see the obvious
path let yourself know you fit and the
fit will find
you yes yes absolutely all right I
understand in my heart I understand too
yes you
do so allow yourself to also know again
that everything happens within perfect
timing perfect
timing it is in your sense timing for
you to move or they would never have
told you they wanted to live where you
are you understand yes everything fits
perfectly there are no
extraneous Creations in the universe no
sloppy leftovers
everything whether your analytical mind
thinks it can make sense of it or not
everything has a reason for being a part
of any event down to the smallest
tiniest most infinitesimal
detail nothing is an accident nothing no
exception zero you follow me yes yes I do all you
zero you follow me yes yes I do all you
need to do is trust it I guarantee
100% that if you trust that you know who
you are and you trust that you fit the
universe will then be able to show you
that you fit because you will allow it
to show you which it is always doing if
you let
it that's wonderful because everybody
said to me get rid of the dogs get rid
of the
cat and I did I guess I didn't realize
that I do fit with them in the universe
if you realize that they are a part of
what you prefer then that's how you fit
thank you thank you
them chatting good
evening uh I block my dreams I can't
remember my dreams at all there is not
necessarily anything negative about that
again remember that a dream what you
call a dream upon Awakening is your
ability to remember that you have been
doing something while you are asleep but
the idea is that as you separate the
physical and the non-physical reality
into two segregative separate reties you
then create the idea that you need that
dream to remember that they are
connected when you begin to live your
dreams generally you may find that you
will not remember as many dreams
typically as you used to because you in
the process of blending them into one
idea so in a sense you are never really
waking up out of the dream you are still
living it and so nothing has to come to
an end so you can wake up in another
reality where you remember that you were
doing something somewhere
else because you're still doing the
original Dream and it flows into your
physical life and you are alert and
awake in both realities and you never
wake up out of the dream that is common
to both reality now that is one reason
why individuals may not have
recollection now in this
transformational age of what you
typically call a dream which is only a
symbolic interpretation of an experience
generally there can be other
reasons sometimes individuals may block
certain Avenues of information to
themselves so they will not have to face
certain things they do not think they
wish to face they are afraid to face
sometimes you will block information
because you don't want to know what it
is in your physical life because to know
it would not allow you to live your
physical life
spontaneously because in your dream
state you plan out everything you do day
by day by
day that is what Deja Vu generally is
all about when you finally get to the
end of an experience you have purposely
blocked and then you remember allow
yourself to remember that you planned
all this out of course it feels like you
did it all over again you have done it
before you remembered that you planned
it all out and now that you're at the
end of the experience you're allowed to
remember that and that's your Deja Vu
experience thank you now let me simply
ask you
are you doing in your life what excites
you the most yes all right what do you
imagine you would get out of remembering
your dreams that you are not getting
now being able to control them control
learn how to control them I'm trying to
do that you know trying all right yes
why do you think you need to control
them and in what way do you think you
need to control them if you don't even
remember them how do you know there is
something there that needs
controling you're right thank you and if
you are living your dreams living them
in your physical reality and you're
doing what excites you then they are
under control because your physical reality
control because your physical reality
and your dream reality is
one it is under your control beautiful
thank you so very much keep it simple
yes sir Pleasant dream thank
you Shing
Bashar my name is Karen Chow do you are
you familiar with me not yet not yet as
you share you open doors that we then
have access
to what do you wish to share um R has uh
cleared me for channeling and I pick up
people and they like overlap me and I
feel if it's a man I feel beard and
mustache all right and when they talk to
me my mouth uh speaks their words yes so
okay but it's not my uh thinking we
understand you are forming Junctions
with their emotional bodies and you are
acting as Reflections in that sense
psychically attuning and channeling by
identifying with them in that way you
are matching their vibrational frequency
so that you become a mirror reflection
of who and what they are in that way and
even though you may have had assistance
from what you call another Consciousness
you are the one that must always clear
yourself for
channeling um there's one particular
person that I'm channeling as a male and
I feel very attached to him and yet I
can't reach him or connect with him on a
physical level all right why in your
terms do you think you need
to I don't know I just feel attached to
him all right attached you are now you
are in a sense using that to some degree
as a lure you are using that as a lure
to draw you through a series of
circumstances that you are about to go
through to allow you to learn certain
things you need to learn so that by the
time you draw yourself perhaps to that
individual you will then be the person
you need to be who will then be capable
of appreciating and interacting with
that individual in the way you agreed to
you are not quite yet the person who
would be able to truly in a relaxed and
loving way receive that interaction on
the level you agree to in terms of a
face to face but you are using that
energy as a beacon to draw yourself
there and it will draw you as you draw
it to each other through a series of
circumstances and life events that will
allow you to grow nourish yourself
expand trust relax love create and
experience ecstasy so that by the time
you face Toof face
meet you will then be the individual
that originally made the agreement
before this physical life follow all
right um I was thinking um the person who he
um I was thinking um the person who he
says he is is he necessarily who he says
he is or right now that may be mostly an
interpretation that is necessary in the
moment we would simply suggest that you
trust the
essence rather than the label the label
is a convenience it assists with the
guidance but it is not necessarily
something to absolutely lock on to it is
simply a l or to allow you at any given
moment to decide whether what is being
offered is the direction you prefer or
not and to learn to trust your own
instincts about your own Integrity with
regard to what you prefer to be true for
you in your
reality there are going to be many
polarities that you will explore at
various stages of this interaction to
allow you to Center balance and
strengthen yourself within the absolute
Assurance of what life style and ideas
you believe are most reflective of the
individual the Blended balance of male
and female energy within yourself that
you perceive yourself to be regardless
of what anyone else says you follow
okay uh thank you very much does that
assist you yes thank you allow yourself
to know that as you relax this evening
of your time as well and Center in a
meditative State we will suggest that you simply
State we will suggest that you simply
Envision a Rosy golden sphere of life
and allow your guides to assist in
sharing with you the degree of their
love for you so that you can learn from
their example that you deserve that
degree of love from you to yourself as
well and that will assist you
greatly thank you thank you very much
for your
share there will
be a short amount of time remaining
continue good evening M and thank you um
is there a Planet by the name of Leila
and if there is where is it we are not
focusing on that
nomenclature understand that when you
say is there a Planet by the name of uhh
generally you will have created an
interpretation into your your own
symbols that will not necessarily
translate back to us perhaps as the
energy by which we may or may not know
it Now understand that we are in contact
with hundreds thousands of
civilizations many of them in
conjunction or separately may be some of
the energy that individuals in your
world will perceive and then attach an
interpretive name
to so in that way it may take many
tracings back along those lines to
discover what in your terminologies the
origin of that energy is and how it
represents itself to us which may be
vastly different than how it represents
itself to youh you follow
me not exactly some um another Channel
had told me an entity that is being
channeled that I was from a planet by
the name of Leila and I had never heard
of it and so there was no way for me to
trace it or will you do us a favor now
yes will you close your eyes
relax open your
imagination and allow yourself now to
Simply begin to think of that energy
think of it by whatever name it feels
correct to you if you wish to use the
term Lea simply to focus upon it that is
all right if that term changes in your
mind during this imagination exercise
let it change and most importantly if a
pictorial symbol presents itself let it
do so and describe it whichever comes to
you first and quickest describe it now
do not think about it a musical note all
right very
good can you approximate it with your
voice is there a color you can associate
with it violet one moment
the closest Association we can scan at
this moment will be what you would call
a water world that would translate
through our nomenclature and our
understanding not so much distinctly as
Leila but as
period this does not mean that Lea is
incorrect for it is also also simply an
interpretation of the similar energy
that we perceive in our own
understanding this watery World contains
the idea of
Consciousness which is not unlike the
idea of the dolphin Consciousness in
your own world but is different in many
ways it is also very musical in that
sense in that being the primary focus of
their communication from one to another
the of tonality although this is quite
different as well from the way in which
your dolin conscious translates the same
idea let us say for
now that their energy has been
represented in your world many times as
the energy that comes out of your
Collective archetypal conscious
substream as water
Sprites even though they are a
Consciousness projection from what you
might call elsewhere
it
evokes much of the energy that was
communicated with through what you would
also call your Medieval Times upon your
planet's history and will invoke some of the idea
history and will invoke some of the idea
of the flowers of the
field which can in a sense be somewhat
deceiving in thinking that the planet
itself may look like that there are
patches which do but it is mostly in our
perception a watery idea perhaps of best
assistance to you is to recognize the
essence of the fluidity of the energy
the ever constant change and shifts of
the weather patterns which take place
and which in and of themselves are an
orchestration of the mentality of the
beings that exist within the sea on that
world they are flowing and pulsing and
as more and more gateways and doorways
open up upon your planet to the
association of Worlds more and more
energy of various sorts will be allowed
in through those various windows and
doorways that you are now opening within
the house in which you
live let it come in as bright beautiful
light through the windows but let it
carry the warmth of the flow of the
oceans of its world for it is very much
as you would interpret it not that it is
physically so but like unto the Golden
Honey the flow of the energy in that
ocean is a very thickening and tangible
loving and warm idea for now this is how
we can best interpret this idea for you
this will open some Avenues in your
dream Consciousness which may also
clarify it inter terminology you can
utilize in your Physical
Realm it is not completely up to us to
interpret this energy at this time for
you for there are many others hovering
around you that you have made agreements
with that perhaps will function best as
your intern interpreters rather than
us a golden Bell and the tone it evokes
in your imagination will call them
anytime when you are at
rest wonderful thank you briefly I'll
sharing good evening Bashar and to you I
wanted to share something that has been
happening since March the 15th I and
that is that the excitement that has
been brought into my life is something
that I don't believe I almost defy a
playwright or a novelist to create in a
scenario it is just it was in
comprehensible to me that such things
could occur the circumstances the events
and things that have presented to me as
challenges um I'm happy about it I'm
excited about it every morning when I
get up because I think what's going to
happen today because it's a challenge
and I can handle it and I know it and
I'm going to grow from it and it is just
like the domino effect just one thing is
happening right after the other and I
feel like a racehorse is just waiting to
get out of that gate and go you are off
and running I am off and running and I
love it I love it and the