All right. Say, how are you all this
evening of your time as you create time
to exist?
Allow us to begin this interaction, this
evening of your time by remarking first
of all on our enjoyment of the gathering
of such a cozy little
group. As we have always indicated in
all our interactions with each and every
one of you individually and
collectively, the timing for everything
and every gathering and every
interaction we have with all of you is
always perfect and all the individuals
within any particular gathering anywhere
for any reason. The amount is always
flawless flawlessly representative of
the collective of the energy of the
energy that is represented by any
particular interaction that is about to
take place.
Therefore, allow yourselves this evening
of your time to, I shall say,
snuggle into the ideas that we will be
into the ideas that we will be
discussing, which will be, if you wish,
entitled this evening, autumn.
We have perceived at least with the
group we are dealing with right now
through this channel that the season as
you call it in your particular area of
your planet is what you call autumn your
October month.
Now our planet in that way does not
really have widespread seasonal changes.
Our axis tilt is not as strong as your
own. Our overall environment in your
terminology is relatively similar from
moment to moment. Not usually ranging
beyond what you would call approximate
span of about 13 to 15 of your degrees
one way or another.
The idea, however, on your world, of your
idea, however, on your world, of your
season, your times of
change, your
autumn represents, as many of you
already instinctively understand, a
gathering together, a going within, a
nurturing energy of introspection.
The idea of harboring new
understandings, new discoveries of
yourself within
yourself, surrounding the inner hearth
of your being with all the ideas that
you have discovered yourself to be
during the active months of your year.
And now coming into an
assessment, a type of early hibernation
which in no way, shape or form implies
that you become inactive, but simply
that your mentality, your consciousness
collectively and sometimes even
individually can begin to recognize that
this particular timing in your world
represents the idea of the
opening the
opening and the
exploration of many of the things you
have gathered. gathered many of the
packages you have picked up along the
way to this
point to
review and allow yourself to perceive
what within those experiences, within
those packages represents the things
that you prefer to carry through into
your new year and those things that you
prefer to allow to assimilate within an
old idea. And in that sense to remain
within the concept of the past. It is
now timing in your society in general
for the opening of many spirit doors
within you, many levels of
consciousness. Now, not so much directly
connected with physiological reality,
but now the exploration of many states
of dream reality, dream awareness to
begin to be able to allow more blending
between the non-physical and the
physical to
occur. So that upon your birthing in a
new year, you are stepping through that gate
year, you are stepping through that gate
as a completely whole description of
yourself, both physical and non-physical
aspects of your consciousness in tandem,
connected side by side, stepping through
into that event of a new year with all
the unfoldment of new growth, new
perspectives, new discovery.
But now your autumn time as you
all have created mythologically is
recognized as the time of communion with
spirit. In that sense, the spirit of
yourself within yourself and all aspects
in whatever way your consciousness, the
spirit you are can present itself to
you, both positive and negative mirrors
for you to gaze into to discover those
things you desire within yourself to
discover those things you can integrate
into the being you prefer to be.
Now in your civilization has been
discussed many times a time past that
you call the civilization of
Adalantis. And we have reminded you from
time to time, those that are familiar
with this, that what you
call the
destruction of the civilization on your
world of Atlantis actually does have a
commemoration time in your reality.
Though many of you no longer realize
what these commemoration times
represent. The commemoration time is the
3-day span. you call All Hollows
Eve. And the idea in some of your
religious vernacular, you call the All
Saints and All Souls Day of your
November first two
days, the All Hollows Eve and November
1st, November 2nd of your timing
represents symbolically the night before, the day
symbolically the night before, the day
of, and the day after the destruction,
the sinking of Atlantis.
That is why the idea of All Hollow's Eve
represents many aspects of facing that
which you fear most within you. The
opening of the dimensions between the
physical and the
non-physical. the seeing of the spirit
realm, the expansion of the
awareness of being in touch with all
levels of reality and the creation of
the reality you most strongly define
with your strongest beliefs and/or
fears. That is generally what it
commemorates in that
sense. But in this way now, not in
destructive ways, not in destructive
terms. Now it can represent the opening of a
Now it can represent the opening of a
doorway to allow you to
assimilate to gather in all the
understandings, all the definitions you
have created yourself to be and to
become that introspective meditative
self that allows you to
review and to choose the ideas that you
prefer to be. The ideas and the
realities you prefer to act upon the
ideas, realities and perspectives you
prefer to manifest in your lives as the
physical experiences you have in a
daytoday nomenclature. your
your
autumn, the falling of many of your
leaves pages in your books of life that
you have written. The
written. The
allowance of the
strengthening, the feeling of the
strength within you that burns bright in
the hearth that you are, the hearth of
spirit, the hearth of
consciousness, the home. Each and every
one of you have created yourselves to be
both on an individual basis and as a
world as a world
home. Many new
accelerations are beginning to take
place within your society. Many new
recognitions of consciousness.
Now, our ability to have this
conversation with you at all in this way
indicates that much has changed on your
planet within the last century of your
accounting. Do remember, however, in all
of these
interactions that we are simply here as
a mirror to reflect the brightness of
the flame. you
are. Do not believe anything that I
share with you just because I share it.
That is not what any of this is about.
It is about
you kindling and rekindling and fanning
the flame of your
own integrity, your
own inspiration, your own ecstasy and
imagination, your own action. the flames
of your own
conviction to live the lives you prefer
to live because you can. Because we know
you can. For as we have said more often than
can. For as we have said more often than
not, no matter what any of you choose to
think of yourselves, we believe in you
utterly. And we know beyond a shadow of
a doubt what you are capable of
creating. If you truly desire it and act
upon that conviction, act upon that
desire. Nothing is beyond you.
Nothing. And this is not
talk. We are not handing you
philosophies. We are not handing you
sugarcoated dreams.
We are talking mechanics of creation,
physics of reality of the physical world
in which you
live because we know you have always
created the reality you experience
because you are facets of the
multi-dimensional creator. It is what
you are. You must create. You can't help
yourself. But whether you choose to
create negative or positive is utterly
up to you.
But you will always
create, you might as well create what
you prefer. And so in our interactions with
prefer. And so in our interactions with
you, we discuss the methodologies of how
you have chosen to create, how you can
use your own selfmpowered reflection of
the infinite to create the reality you
desire. You are all awakening now.
Paradoxically enough, in this your
enough, in this your
month of
hibernation is when you go within and
awaken in the strongest sense of the
word. We thank you for allowing us to
experience with joy the awakening that
you have created upon your planet which
allows us to interact with you now.
We thank you for functioning as
ambassadors of your
world. That is what you are right
now. We thank you for allowing us to
function as an ambassador of our
respective collective worlds that we
refer to as the association.
These interactions bit by bit and day by
day make it more conducive for us our
worlds your world to be able in very
short order to interact face to face
when you know you are equal to any other
consciousness in creation.
That will then
be the timing, the day, the
season. At this time, in return for the
gift of your willingness to share with
us, I ask you now, how may I serve you?
For sure. I would first uh like to ask
any comments that you have about the
timeliness of today's uh moderate
earthquake. Well, many of you love
living on the edge.
That's why you are where you are because
there is a great deal of energy and you
are learning to use it not fear it. You
are now learning to direct it so that
you can begin to realize that your
reality utterly is the product of your
beliefs of your directions of yourself
attractions of yourself to particular
places that represent different degrees
of energy. And in attracting yourself to
such a highly energetic area upon your
planet, you give yourself the creative
opportunity to know that you can flow
that energy through you, that you can
begin to identify with the power that
actually is within
you. For no magnitude of any quake that
has ever occurred on your planet matches
even infinitesimly the amount of power
you have to create your reality.
So you are learning to direct your
energy by feeling it to some degree
externally in ways that show you how
much power you are. You have so that you
can get as comfortably as you wish to at
whatever rate is comfortable for you.
more and more used to the idea of living
with that much power and of
understanding what that much power is
capable of doing and in choosing to flow
that power in a positive way rather than
a negative way in allowing that power to
destructurize but not
destroy. Understand? Yes. Well, thank
you for all being so bold.
Thank you, Basher. Well, thank you. It
is simply a little bit of the part of
the process of allowing yourselves to be
shaken awake to stir things up a little bit so
awake to stir things up a little bit so
it does not become quite so
sedentary or sedimentary. shooting
Bashar. Um, hey, good day to you.
I'd like to say I'm glad to meet you.
I'm from New York. Uh, this is my first
channeling, so I'm uh All right. Was a
little surprised to be the first
questioner. No. All right. There are no
accidents. However, I I understand it.
That's why I came up. All right. Um the
specific subject I wanted to ask you to
to talk about um is very narrowly uh
binge eating
really more broadly compulsive
addictions and that sort of thing and
and and trying to understand it uh why
why I have it and what what will happen
and now I'm sure you understand. May I
ask you a question? Yes, please. All
right. Are you sure? Yes. Yes,
absolutely. Thank you.
Now, honestly
examine within yourself the
idea of believing or let me simply ask
you, do you
believe that you might run
out of things in life that there might
not be quite enough for everyone?
Yes, probably. No. All right.
Maybe, maybe not. The idea in general
for any sort of what you call a
compulsive addiction first of all is the
belief that has been ingrained in most
of you since
birth that the power is not within you
but is in the things around you.
Therefore, when you think that the power
is in the things around you in order to
feel more powerful, you have to have
more more more of what is around you
because you feel
empty, devoid of that power, of that
foundation, of that stability.
The idea first and
foremost is to some degree an attempt
exteriorly to replace what you have been
taught to believe interiorly you don't
possess. But if you start allowing
yourself to recognize that the placement
of the power in the symbol
outside is in a sense the removal of
your own power from you. that you are
still using your own power to do that.
And you take that power back and cease
to believe in all the belief systems
that deny you your power as an aspect of
the infinite. When you then bring your
self-empowerment back to you and start
taking responsibility for all the
creations in your life, that does not
mean blame. That means freedom of
choice. By the way, when you take
responsibility for all the creations in
your life, you will then begin to feel
that energy within you. You will start
to
feel full of that energy. And in feeling
full of that energy. And in feeling
fulfilled, you will not necessarily then
assume that you have some sort of a void
that is constantly empty that you are
constantly attempting to fill endlessly,
endlessly endlessly. Now the idea to
some degree sometimes when it connects
itself to an immediate
rejection what you call then a purging
of the
idea will simply
represent your overall consciousness as
awareness that the exterior is not what
has the power. It is you bring it back
to you by allowing you to understand you
must always rely on yourself not on the
exterior ideas but that relying on
yourself is not a matter of effort is
not a matter of stamina. This is one of
the great misconceptions if I may call
it that in your society that the idea of
being able to maintain a view of
yourself that you desire to maintain
somehow requires stamina. It doesn't. It
doesn't. All it requires is a
definition, a clear definition of what
it is you really believe yourself to be
or what you really believe you desire to
be and then a decision to be that
person, to act like that person that you
desire to be. That's all it takes. Your
decisions stick. Addiction is simply the lack of
stick. Addiction is simply the lack of
belief that you have that
power. And therefore any power it is
assumed must be in your life from that
viewpoint must come from exterior
ideas to fulfill the emptiness that you
have been left with because of how your
society has taught you to think of
yourself as not being in control.
Understand so far?
Uh some most of it. Yes. All right. Is
this assisting you at all? Yeah, you're
really speaking about creating your own
reality in in everyone does. We are
answering your question on a very
foundational fundamental level so that
all individuals may apply their
particular perspective to what you have
shared to be your specific
situation. But it applies nonetheless.
The idea of any type of what you may
call an
overindulgence in anything exterior is
usually based on the assumption that you
don't have what you need to begin with
and that you have to do that you have to
binge because you do not believe there
will be
enough. Understand?
Yes. No. Maybe. Yeah. I I understand. I
I guess the only other part I mean
that's that's that's um on an
intellectual level I can understand that
one moment one
moment when you say that's on an
intellectual level you are making a
distinction that does not inherently
exist. If you understand it, you can
learn to assume that you actually do
understand it on all levels rather than
just assuming that you only understand
it on one. Just because you don't
necessarily feel it in a certain way
doesn't mean you don't have the
understanding you
need. The idea that you can understand
something just intellectually or just
emotionally is one of the definitions
your society has taught you to buy into.
to make that segregation, that
separation that allows you now to have
the experience you're having right now
with this
information. You understand it on far
more levels than you think. However, the
first step in transforming it is to
first of all acknowledge the reason for
why you would be doing it to begin with.
Once you own that you are choosing to do
it out of your freedom of choice, you
place it squarely under your control.
It is not something that's happening to
you. It's happening through you because
nothing does happen to you. Nothing
comes from the
outside. Nothing is an
uncontrollable addiction. Nothing is
really a habit once you know you have
it. If you know you have a habit, you
don't have it anymore by definition.
Because a habit is something you do that
you don't know you're doing.
If you know you have it, you have to be
outside of it, quote unquote, in order
to see that you had it to begin with. So
once you are aware of the fact of what
you're doing, that is really no longer
you. And it is only an
assumption, a belief, a definition that
for some reason it is difficult to stop
doing it, that you keep doing it. It
isn't anything inherent in the
circumstance itself from that point
forward that makes it difficult to stop.
It is only your assumption, the
definition you have been fed in your
reality that makes it seem difficult to
stop because your definition of that
idea is that it is difficult to stop and
it is only the definition that gives it
that power. Nothing inherent within the
circumstance itself. Understand?
Yes. Is this assisting you? Yes, very
much. Is there some specific idea that
you feel is not being touched that we
might be able to clear up?
I'm still groping a little bit for for
technique. Uh
well, all right. You are missing the
point. Now, we can give you a thousand
and one a million and one
techniques. Your imagination can supply
you with whatever technique will work
best for you. That's what your
imagination is for.
That's how it works best. So you are
quite capable of creating whatever
technique you desire. And even if we
gave you a technique, your imagination
would alter it to fit you anyway.
However, you are also under the
assumption that you need a technique to
make a change.
The idea we have just outlined it if you
are willing to understand the concept we
are discussing is in and of itself all
the technique that really is
fundamentally necessary. In other
words, the
realization of what your circumstance is
in and of itself is the transition of
that circumstance. As we have said in
simpler terms, if you're aware of the
habit, you don't really have it anymore.
All you have to do is understand you
don't have it and stop acting or
pretending like you do. Now we do not
mean pretending in the sense
that we are calling out that you are
doing something false in that sense.
That is not what we mean. But the idea
is that if you know you have a
habit, you don't have it anymore. All
you have to do is see the you you would
prefer to be. Do you see the you you
would prefer to be? Do you have a
picture of what that you would be like?
I I can't create that in my mind. Yes.
Go right ahead. Create it. Now,
have you got it? Yes. All right.
Now that you however it
looks now do you really believe that
what you have in your visualization in
your imagination is representative
sufficiently of the you you really
prefer to be? Yes or no? Yes. All right.
Does it excite you when you then
consider that that you in your
imagination could be you? Yes. Does it
really excite you? Yes. Can you feel
what it would be like to be that you?
Yes. Are you sure? Use all your senses.
Get into it. Put it on. Wear it. Be that
you in your imagination. Feel what it
would be like to be that
you. How does it feel? Describe it to
me. What would it be like to be that
you?
It feels very adult. Very adult. All
right. Very adult. What
else? Get excited about it and describe
it to me. Representative of the level of
excitement you are about
it. Use all your senses. How does it
feel? How does your body feel? What
things attract you? What things do you
notice? What kind of things do you hear,
smell, taste, see, feel?
What is this body like? What is that new
you like?
Well, well, well, well, well.
Um, there's an absence of u of of of of
uh the battle. All right. All right. All
right. Fair enough. However, I did not
ask you what it is not.
I asked you what it is.
It It feels free. Free in what way? What
does that mean? Does it mean it feels
like that body could get up and just run
as far and fast as it really wanted to
and it would feel absolute ecstasy in
doing so?
Yes. All right. Are you sure? Now, I
don't want to push you into
this. Is it a body that laughs
easily, that experiences great joy and
depth of
breath? Is it an expansive reality?
Yes. Yes. All right. Yes. Can you feel
it? Yes. Then you are it right now.
Believe it or not, you are it right now.
Now in the very next moment, you can
decide. You can choose. You can define.
Oh, that's not me yet.
couldn't be me
yet. Everyone knows it will take some
time before I could ever be
that. Why is my question to you
Why is my question to you
why? This is an illustration of what we
were saying. If you know what you
prefer, if you can really feel it and
use your imagination to see it, you are
it right now.
Now, does that
seem to indicate to you a little
stronger understanding than just what
you formally call the intellectual? Yes,
I I I do understand. All right, then. It
is up to you. However you define
yourself at any given moment is what you
will be. Plain and simple.
If you have any situation or
circumstance in your life and you are
not sure as the you you are now how to
handle it, this is what your imagination
is for. Create the you you prefer to be.
Invest it with life. Use all your
senses. Get into it as you say. Take the
situation, hand it to the you you prefer
to be, and watch what that you does with
it. Do the same thing, and you'll get
the same result. That's what your
imagination is for. It is the template,
the blueprint. Follow it, mirror it, be it.
blueprint. Follow it, mirror it, be it.
Be that person. You will have the same
kind of
life. Exactly. Understand? Yes, I do. Does
Exactly. Understand? Yes, I do. Does
that work for you? I I think so. Your
enthusiasm is um infectious. Infectious.
Yes. Now remember one other thing. What you
Now remember one other thing. What you
see in me is a reflection of what I know
you are. You are seeing
are. You are seeing
you. Be that you if you prefer to be. I
reflect what you can choose to be. It is
up to you
utterly. Thank you. Thank you very much.
Sharing, thank you for applauding
yourselves, guys.
Uh, the question I have is on Oh, one
moment. One moment. Good day. Good day.
Oh, thank you very much. Proceed.
Earlier you had mentioned or I took it
being a a consciousness or a world
you're part of. Yes. And separate of a
world we're part of here in a sense on
one level. Yes. Okay. Question I have is
individual consciousness and an entire
or full civilization as you will
consciousness. I get the feeling that
you're out individually per se
channeling to we as individuals in order
for our world to touch your world as a
collective what do you feel will have to
take place you must consider yourselves
to be absolutely equal to us
then we can interact on all levels you
desire to any level at all in any way
shape or format
Once you know you are equals and cease
to consider yourselves as less or more
among yourselves. Now the idea that sometimes
yourselves. Now the idea that sometimes
makes the idea of equality seem aberrant
to many of you is that you have created
a mythology I shall say an assumption
that equality unity on your planet means
loss of individuality and it couldn't be
more opposite the strengthening of the
opposite the strengthening of the
individuals you are and the granting of
equality to all other diversity as
individuals in your society is what will
create you to be a unified world, a
collective. Many individuals, each
unique, each with their own expression
and yet at the same time of a single
mind, of a single heart, of a single
thought, it is both. So while I am an
individual, by all means an individual,
I am also the
collective at the same time. At any time
I choose to see myself that way. At any
time it serves our interaction simply
for the purpose of reflecting to each
and every one of you individually and
collectively. That at any time you sense
my energy to be that of an individual
and that of a collective. You will
simply know as a reflection back to you
that nothing that we have created
ourselves to be is at the expense of
either side. Understand? Yes. Does that answer
side. Understand? Yes. Does that answer
the question? No. All right.
The feeling I get is that you're waiting
then for a collective. Not me. I'm not
waiting. Fine. I am doing I recognize
that your world is moving into the idea
of a collective. But I'm not waiting for
it. I understand.
But we do perceive that the world you
call your earth, its energy
approximately within what you call the
next 30 to 50 of your years at the
outside will be functioning very
similarly to our civilization. Now you
just answered my question. Thank you.
Sharing.
Good evening, Bashar. And to you, good
day. Good day. I have a question on
creation and excitement. Creation and
excitement. Then by all means be bold,
speak up and share so that all may
participate.
Well, I know that uh your policy is to
My policy um
I write a new policy every second. Okay.
that we should um do things that excite
us the most. Not that you should, but
that if you do, you will have a life of
ecstasy. Right. Okay. And I was
wondering I was wondering about a
uh how that fits in with uh choosing and
creating your own lifestyle.
Specifically, an example that has come
up for me recently when I had uh a
choice of I was I wanted to find a new
job. Yes. I had a choice of one job that
excited me greatly. Yes. And I had
another choice of a job that excited me
but not as much. All right. And I ended
up with the job that excited me not as
much. All right.
So I thought about by your own choosing
or by what you call circumstance.
That's what I was wondering about. Um,
oh, all right. My first my first thought
was, well, it was by circumstance. And
then I thought about it, which can be
unconscious choice.
What you call circumstance can be
unconscious choice. Well, couldn't have
I at the same time chosen the thing that
excited me the most. May I ask you a
question? Sure. Thank you. Do you
absolutely believe beyond a shadow of a
doubt that you were capable of doing
that job?
Um, why is there hesitation? Well,
because if I believed it, then it would
have happened.
All right. But that does not mean you
have to play 20 questions with
yourself. Do you believe right now that
you are actually truly capable of doing
that job that you say excited you more?
Yes, I do. All right. Do you believe you
deserve it? Yes. Absolutely. Yes. All
right. Now, is there anything else that
actually excites you more than having
gotten that
job? Would have
um not not in terms of of career
positions. Oh, and um we're making a
distinction. Yeah. Let's let go of the distinction
Yeah. Let's let go of the distinction
for just a moment if we may.
What is the most exciting thing you can
think of to do in your life regardless
of whether you call it a career or not?
Well, I like to write.
Is that more exciting than the job? It
is, but I'm writing at the I'm still
writing now. I'm writing at the same
time. Yes. Now, so it it is exciting
when I do it. And but you don't believe
you can be a writer now? No, I am a
writer now. Oh, all right. You are a
writer. Is that how you would prefer to
make your living?
That is what I expect to do eventually
for a living.
When May I ask you another question? You
know what's coming up now?
[Applause] Let's drag out the little machine with
Let's drag out the little machine with
the little
dial, the threshold of believability
meter.
All right. Are you enjoying this? Sure.
All right. It's fun. All right.
Now, let's explore together.
let's explore together.
Just without thinking about it in all
the honesty you simply are aware of that
you are
using answer rapidly without
thinking all of the following questions.
Now you are a writer. Yes. Yes. All
right. Now you have created a little bit
of a differentiation in the sense that
you now recognize you are a writer but
we are assuming because of how you have
defined yourself that you do not
necessarily think of yourself as a
successful writer correct
well I haven't sold a book yet is that
how you would define the success for now
will that do as a sufficient
representation of success the fact that
you would be making your living at being
a writer
I is that what you want.
Well, that's how I look at uh Is that
what you want to be? Is that what
excites you the most? To be a writer and
make a living at being a writer? Sure.
Yes. All right. You're clear on that?
Yes. All right. Now,
we set up the
machine, test it out. All
right. It's working
perfectly. Oh boy. Probably because we
use it so
[Laughter] often. No dust on this
machine. Answer the following series of
questions quickly, directly, honestly.
Yes or no? Okay. within what you
call a 10year time span. Do you believe
a 10year time span. Do you believe
beyond a shadow of a doubt that within
10 years you will be a successful
writer? Yes. Five
Yes. Five
years? Yes. Three
years? More and more hesitation
maybe. All right.
Now, not that that will not change. In
fact, it probably already has changed
just because we have examined it. But if
you use this technique, you always give
yourself the opportunity to
understand whatever amount of time the
beliefs you have within you will
probably allow it to take. When you
start to hesitate, wherever that time
frame is that you start to fluctuate,
that is probably a good idea of exactly
how long you will allow it to take right
now to be the idea you say really
excites you. Now once you know how long
you have created it to take, then you
can examine and explore. Now you have
some material to work with. Now you can
say, why would I need to believe it
would take that long? What belief and
definition do I have or would I have to
have within me to allow me to believe it
would have to take three? Do I want it
to take 3 years? Yes or no? Uh, no I
don't. Oh, all right. Then allow
yourself the
selfexploratory journey of openness and
honesty with yourself. Discover within
yourself in your meditations all the
definitions you would have for why you
would believe it would have to take 3
years. Get in touch with those
definitions. Rewrite the ones you no
longer prefer, the ones you believe
absolutely are easy to change, the ones
you really recognize you no longer
prefer. Replace them with definitions
you do prefer. Then hook yourself up to
the meter
again and go through it again. Do I
believe beyond a shadow of a doubt, and
I mean beyond a shadow of a doubt, that
I will be this writer that I prefer to
be in 10 years? 10 years? A snap? No
problem. 5 years? Absolutely. How could
it ever take that long? 3 years? No
problem. Two years? Absolutely. One
year. Oh well, one year. One year. Oh, I see.
Oh well, one year. One year. Oh, I see.
All right. Now, I have brought the
three-year threshold down to
one. Go back and examine the definitions
over again. Do
this and be honest about what you
discover. Be clear about your
definitions as to what these things you
say you want represent to you. For many
times, the only thing that seems to stop
something from manifesting
faster is because of your definition of
what you think it is or what you think
you will have to take along with it that
you don't necessarily want as a part of
your definition of the thing you say you
prefer. Be clear about your definition
of the thing you desire. You can use
this technique to clarify that and bit
by bit you can allow that timing to
become very very
forhortened. Then you will begin to feel
it be more imminent. The more imminent
you feel it. The more excited you will
be. The more excited you will be. The
more accelerated your energy, the more
accelerated your energy, the more
imminent it will be. And on and on and
on and pop. There it is.
Now, let me just oh, drop a little
hint for almost any type of
endeavor that you would consider in this
light that you might want to be.
Rarely rarely does it ever require more
than three of your months for full
manifestation. Usually most things can
at least start to fall into place within
3 weeks and almost every endeavor will
at least give you a sign it is starting
to move in that direction within three
of your days. If you trust beyond a
shadow of a doubt that the thing you say
excites you the most is really the thing
that can support you by definition. The
thing you can really do effortlessly and
again watch the definition. You may
believe you're a writer. Yes, I define
myself as a writer. But why don't you
define yourself now as a successful
one? That is a definition in and of
itself. and you don't have to wait
for do anymore about it when in fact
there might be many things you could be
acting on that represent the thing you
really want to do. You might be settling
for less by acting on some of the other
circumstances rather than truly having
I'll say exhausted all of the prime
opportunities first before you then
allow yourself to start acting on the
secondary level opportunities. Yes, as
always, if you truly have no capability
on any other way, shape or form of
acting upon the thing that really
excites you the most, then do by all
means act upon the thing that is the
next most exciting thing.
However, allow yourself to be very clear
about what those prime opportunities are
because very often many of you will not
realize nor recognize a prime
opportunity because it's right in front
of your face. Well, aren't we creating
these opportunities? Yes. What I am
saying is you may be creating more
opportunities than you think and not
recognizing them as opportunities simply
because you have always created them and
simply take them for granted and don't
recognize them as opportunities. In
other words, as an example, I'm not
saying this is specifically the case
with you, although some of this may be
applicable in your situation. Some of
you will say, "All right, all right. I'm
waiting for an opportunity." Well, where
is it? Well, I'm waiting. Where's the
horns and the trumpets and the bugles
and the lightning, the banners and where
is it?
However, not stopping to
realize that you have always
known for years of your life that right
down the block is someone who works in a
certain capacity that if you were to
simply go to them and share your idea
could actually assist you in getting
what you want. But oh no, no, no, no.
That's too mundane.
But yet it could be an opportunity. That
is the opportunity that represents the
path of least resistance. You see,
that's the key. The opportunities will
always be there, but they will be the
ones that represent the path of least
resistance. And sometimes you surround
yourself with so many opportunities and
take them for granted that you may not
simply recognize them simply because
they have always been there all your
life. And even though now maybe the
first time you could really use it, you
simply don't pay attention because you
have always seen it. You just treat it
like part of the landscape and it
doesn't stand out anymore to you. So the
idea is to act on whatever you really
are capable of acting on. And many of
you have been brought up to believe that
certain things you are not capable of
doing. And so because you have been
brought up to believe you cannot do
them, you can't approach them. What's
wrong with you? there and
your you can't go talk to them. Are you
crazy? And so when you hear enough of
that, you walk right by the building
every day. Where's that opportunity I'm
day. Where's that opportunity I'm
waiting for? And all you have to do is
walk through those doors, go up and talk
to those people as an
equal and let them respond to you as an
equal. Because the whole idea is that
you exist in a physical reality with
many other physical beings and you're
all here to help each other. So all we
are saying is that many times these
opportunities are not going to be
delivered by flying
horses. Sometimes they can be very
obvious in that fashion. But more often
than not, the opportunities will always
be right under your nose. But you have
been taught out of seeing them. Well,
why would someone create something that
doesn't excite them the most?
That is not what we are literally
discussing. Well, the idea, however, one
moment. The idea, however, is that as we
have just been saying, there are many,
many things you might be very excited
about if it weren't for the fact that
your society teaches you to not be
excited about them. You might not
understand that you really could
innately be far more excited about far
more things than you are allowing
yourself to be excited
about. The idea is to face your world
with a childlike
fascination. Then you will begin to
discover that many more things you take
for granted as being mundane are
actually quite a bit more exciting than
you thought. And you will then be able
to act on them because you now see them
for the excitement they are. Many of you
have very thick skins by this time. And
so things that could be exciting to you
don't have much of an effect on you. You
may not even be able to recognize your
own excitement because of the thickness
of that
shell. Understand? Yes, I do. So start
walking through it. Allow yourself to
break through it by simply breaking
through the conventions of your society.
And that will allow the skin to become
much thinner and allow the excitement to
penetrate much more easily. Then it will
be obvious in what
direction it lies.
Okay. Thank you. Thank you. Sharing.
Good day Bashar and good day to you.
I have some very wonderful friends who
recently have shown their love for me in
various ways. All right. And I would
like to be able to show mine for them a
little bit better than I feel like I've
been able to up. In what way would you
care to express your
love? in a way that that they would
appreciate their own lives better, that
I might be able to help them. Then be
the fullest living example of
unconditional love and ecstasy of living
that you can
be. And they can then see reflected in
you a way they can choose to be if they
want to, but they don't have to choose
it. That is how you serve anyone and it is
That is how you serve anyone and it is
the only way you can serve anyone. Be
the fullest example of the idea that
gives you the most
joy. Reflect it to them. Share it with
them but not because they have to take
it. Simply because you are an
opportunity they can choose if they want
to. That is really all you can
do. Be of service in whatever way it
moves you to be of service. And by
example, it can, as you say, rub off,
but not for the purpose of getting them
to change just because that's the way it
gives you joy to
be. Then they will see that joy. Look at
him. Look how happy he
is. How do you do it? I do it because I
choose to be of service, to be of joy,
because I know I choose my reality.
Therefore, I choose what I prefer.
That's how I do it. You can if you wish.
You don't have to, but you can if you
wish. Now remember that one of the
easiest things to do is that if you do
find someone in your reality that is
living the way you want to live, copy
them. Do what they do and you'll live
that way
too. So if you are the fullest living
example you can be, then you give them
the best opportunity to have something
to copy.
Understand? Oh yes. Does that answer the
question sufficiently for you? Very
well. Well, thank you very much for your
chatting. chatting.
Hello, Mr. Diplo Matt. Hello. Hello, Mr.
Ambassador. [Laughter]
Thank you, Bashar.
Howdy. you know, um I don't really have
a lot to say. I just wanted to say hi.
Hi. And I I didn't want Thank you. Next.
Almost. Almost. All right. Um you'll
come up with something more. Well, yeah.
Uh in the last few sharings, I have
addressed you as Mr. Ambassador and you
have addressed me as Mr. Diplo Matt.
Yes. And I I had the feeling that there
was a specific reason that you used
Diplo Matt. Yes. Since there is a
distinction, a subtle distinction
between ambassador and diplomat. Yes.
Care to share why you chose that? Thank
you. Diplo. Welcome Matt. Understand?
Understand?
I understand what that means, but uh I
don't think that's the the the real
meaning behind your choice of that term.
Oh, all right. Then you invent one.
It's the meaning I mean right now.
Okay. Well, let's create a past here for
a moment. No. All right. And tell me the
meaning that you meant when you've used
it in the
past since you chose to use it. Oh,
thank you. Diplo
Diplo
Matt, the idea many times of what you
perceive to be, the fluctuations and
inflections of how our thoughts
translate into your language are not
necessarily indicative of any particular
meaning we wish to ascribe to the word
but are indicative of the way we are
playing the energy so that it will reach
you on other levels. The fluctuations
that you hear audibly many times are
simply an overlaying as you would say on
a surface of some of the fluctuations
that are going on in the depths. The
energy that is going on in the depths
much the same way that the waves on top
of an ocean up and down fluctuations and
patterns that you see on the surface to
some degree reveal the actions of what
is going on below but do not necessarily
tell the whole story. So when you hear
such fluctuations many times it is
simply an indicator on the surface that
there are other levels of communication
going on below the surface and that is
simply how the surface the word responds
to what is going on below it. I
understand I I have understood that
before. Now why don't you share with me
some of those
underlying uh interactions? What do you
feel them to have been?
Well, regardless of the way you chose to
or the way the energy translated in the
in the tonalities. Yes. I felt that you
chose that because you perceived
something about me past or future as I'm creating
about me past or future as I'm creating
it from present time. All right. Perhaps
which related to diplomacy. Oh, you see,
an ambassador can be a lousy diplomat,
quote unquote. Nice. And a diplomat
doesn't necessarily have to be an
ambassador. Nice. So, you chose the word diplomat,
Nice. So, you chose the word diplomat,
and I thought perhaps I felt that you
were perceiving something. Well, the
word diplomat to some degree is far more
representative of the older terminology
we used for you, which is simply
switcher. Since it is an exchange of energy
Since it is an exchange of energy
through a central medium. Ah, I see that
connection. Thanks.
Okay. Anything else you'd like to share
about that? Thank you. One other thing,
simply the recognition that even though
we may have quote unquote chosen that
particular modulation at that time with
a particular
intent, it was on your behalf the choice
to make a mystery out of it. Well,
Well,
but we blind you. No, not to contradict
you. I really didn't make a mystery out
of it. No, I understand on that level.
All we are saying is that you were the
one with the question. What did you mean
by that, Bashar? I
didn't it really didn't it really didn't
come across as mystery. Yes, I I do not
mean it in the fullest sense of the
word. Okay, good. I am once again
playing with you. Okay, I will accept
that. Thank you very much. Thank you
very much, Mr. Ambassador Door. You may
open it and
leave. And of course, as always, enter a
new experience. Thank you very much,
Sharing. Good day, Bashar. And to you,
good day. I recently was invited to
somebody's home and they had a great
deal of crystal crystals in their room.
A great deal of crystals. Yes. Yes. A
lot of crystal power. All right. And I
picked up a small piece of rutated
quartz crystal and I started to pass out
and um I had to leave the room and for
the rest of the evening when we did some
group meditations, I felt very close to
fainting. Oh. All right. So about a week
later, I bought a small piece of rutated
quartz and um I find whenever I hold it
directly that I start to get nauseous.
All right. And I'm wondering why the
titanium has this effect on me and what
it means. To some degree, it is simply
indicative of the highly sensitized
conductor, directional conductor that
you are now allowing yourself to become.
You are now tapping into a live current.
You simply have some remnant beliefs
within you that allow you to feel a
little bit overloaded by what you are
now beginning to understand to be a very
large flow of energy that you have
access to always have had actually and
always have used but now you're becoming
aware of it. So there is less
resistance, less resistors to block the
overall effect from you. Understand? The
quartz simply reflects that the
rutilation reflects your hyper
sensitivity as an antenna.
Now understand does that mean that I
should work with the stone or should I
avoid it because it's too powerful or
Oh, you can work with it if you wish. It
can aid and assist you. Remember any
crystals in that sense even though they
are representative of energy and power
in that way on their own right are only
triggers and catalysts for the power you
are. They are reflective facets of what
it is you are creating yourself to be at
any given moment. So by all means you
can work with it. Start small if you
wish. Enlarge it when you believe your
capacity to flow that energy through you
is enlarged if you wish. But remember,
you are your own crystal and you have
your own conductive
filaments in that
sense and you are simply now becoming
more sensitized to the antenna of
directive energy that you are my little flashlight. Understand?
flashlight. Understand?
Uh yeah. Are there are there any other
stones that would be as conducive to
this? Perhaps what can assist you to some
Perhaps what can assist you to some
degree since you are dealing with these
symbols to begin with might be a small
quantity small quantity of what you call
hematite to magnetically flatten or
ground you to some
degree. And also in and of itself now
and then you might wish to simply handle
the pure quartz form without the
rutilation to create what you simply
might call a bit of a blank for a moment
to allow what you choose to perceive as
the energy to be able to sort of diffuse
without being so highly directed in a
laser-like fashion. Understand? Yeah.
But trust your own imagination and trust
what you attract to you. All of these
things are simply reflective symbols of
the idea you are awakening to find
yourself to
be. So enjoy. Can I ask you one quick
thing related to it? I asked you a few
weeks ago about alternate energy that
would be uh non-polluting. Yes. Uh would
the titanium relate to this? Yes, to
some degree it does.
Thank you very much. Oh, thank you very
much for opening up your treasure chest.
sharing. Good day, Bashar. Until you
good day. Um, you had discussed a
connection that I have with another
individual and how our interaction may
best progress to serve uh ourselves and
humanity. Thanks. Now, I know that I
have the ability to choose the path I'm
going to take and to uh go ahead with
agreements I've made or change them.
Yes. I also know that
um well what I want to ask you is how
can you see the future in a sense? I
know time is an illusion but if you can
kind of pick up on connections that two
people have um some things now and then
will flow into formation and be
representative of a highly
momentum fulfilled state. Those stand
out. So, it's vibration of energy you're
picking up on. overlapping vibrations
that reinforce each other are sometimes
easier to perceive. But the idea of any
sort of prediction is always a
fluctuating idea at best because there
is no solid future. And the ones that
are perceived are simply the ideas, the
probable realities that have the highest
degree of momentum, the highest degree
of reinforced energy behind them at any
given moment, but only at the time the
prediction is made. Because the
prediction is simply a sensing of the
energy that is the most likely to
manifest at the time the prediction is
made. That can change in the very next
second. You can perceive things that
seem unlikely to divert and those are
the ones that usually come to pass.
Uhhuh. Understand? Yes, I knew that
then. No. All right. Um I have one other
quick question. Yes. The last two weeks
I've been dreaming and remembering my
dreams and um a lot of simultaneous
lives that I've been dreaming about.
Guys, last week I went to sleep and I
literally don't remember the entire
evening. All right. Other than I woke up
and the night gown I usually sleep in
was tossed across the room and my bed
looked like a war zone. All right. And I
had a sensing of extraterrestrial
presence to some degree. Yes. Would you
like to add anything? No. Okay. It will
come out in the fullness of time. Many
times, this can be a general clue for
all of you.
Many times when you awaken from your
typical sleep
state, truly feeling like you have been
out and not really carrying back with
you any particular memory at all is
usually an indication of simply a very
strong and direct and straight
communication with another level of
consciousness. that your mentality
simply at this time hasn't yet
assimilated in terms it can understand
to be able to present to you symbols
that make sense but it will play out in
the things you do. The information and
the energy is there and is
representative of the agreements you are
making in doing the things that excite
you the most. This information will come
out in the actions you perform in life
and bit by bit through many different
methodologies. Some of which you may
call deja
vu. Some of which may simply be
instantaneous revelation of
awareness. Some of it simply the
synchronicity of the interactions that
go on the coincidences in your life. All
of these and many more are different
ways that this information plays itself
out to bring back to you through your
reality and awareness of all that you
have created and agreed to.
So bit by bit it will come out. Now you
can begin even in your dream realities
to ask for more assistance in unfolding
it and in remembering it. But do not
insist upon it. Continue with your life.
It will all flow out if you keep
flowing. Don't stop and try to analyze
it. You block the flow. Keep flowing.
Keep doing. Keep being and it will come
out because that's what it's for to be
put into active
service. Understand? Yes. Uh my
remembering all these other dreams, what
is I know that I'm blending more and
integrating. Yes, remembering these
dreams is what is the service of them?
You know that I much it can be
absolutely individual from dream to
dream. They can be representative of
many different types of interactions or
self-aware revelations. Get in touch
with each and every one and
examine every idea that you remember in
the dream and remember that it's a part
of you. So talk to it, dialogue with it,
ask yourself this is me. I am this
portion of the dream. I am this thing in
my dream. I am this emotion in my dream.
What I want to say to me
is listen. You'll get an answer. Okay.
Just relax and let it flow. All right.
All right. Thank you very much. Pleasant
dreams. Shutting.
Hello Bashar. And you good night. Um I
read in a book this afternoon that uh
there's an impending axis shift of All
right. All right. All right. All right.
Did you notice the reaction? Yeah, I
did. It's the first time I've heard of
this. Yes. The energy wave hit long
before your mouth opened.
Obviously. All
right. Changes of electromagnetic energy
there are. But again, the idea, the
overall fundamental idea is that any
transformation can be experienced in a
positive or a negative way. It's up to
you. Whatever vibration you buy into
most strongly will be the way you
experience the shifts going on in your
electromagnetic field. Individuals that
have a great deal of fear about the
shift will lure themselves into places
of destruction. Individuals that simply
understand they can use the energy to
enlighten themselves and elevate and
accelerate themselves in a positive way
will simply know beyond a shadow of a
doubt they do not have to give
themselves the idea of a trial by fire.
And they will lure themselves to places
on your planet where they will
experience the energy as a
destructurization rather than
destruction. Understand? Yes. The more
individuals on your planet that
recognize you can use this energy in a
positive way rather than simply fearing
or believing it has to happen in a
negative way then can change the energy
of the entire planet so that the
majority of the planet need not
experience any transformation any shift
in a negative way at all.
So the idea is that yes there are shifts
in your energy taking place both in you
and what you call your planet since in a
sense you are one and the same thing
here and there as you have experienced
this day of your time. You may see
pockets of adjustment in your land mass
but it does not have to be as
devastatingly overwhelming as many of
you used to fear it had to be. You have
already done much to change a lot of
that energy. You have already changed it
in a positive way to a great degree just
by being willing to understand that you
do not really have to truly shake
yourselves completely awake. That if
you're willing to wake up now, you do
not have to suffer and struggle and go
through all sorts of negative trials in
order to simply wind up with the
understanding you could have now that
you deserve
happiness and that you can create your
reality to be whatever you prefer it to
be. A lot of the idea of someone
experiencing a transformation in a
negative way is simply because they are
holding on so tight to an old belief and
will not allow themselves to let it go
and trust their natural flow that it
takes that degree of violence to make
them break their grip. Sometimes
individuals will actually even take
themselves out of physical reality in
order to allow themselves to start a
fresh but they do not really die.
Nothing ever really does. It is all
eternal and infinite. However, you don't
have to struggle and you don't have to
suffer. Anytime you are made aware of an
idea and it is presented in what you may
call a potentially negative format, take
it not as an absolute prediction
chiseled in steel or
neutroneum or whatever you think is most
difficult to change. But the idea is
simply presented as an opportunity.
Look, it says you can vibrate in
synchronous accord with the negative
energy of this idea, the fear, and
attract yourself to it and attract it to
you or vibrate in accord with the
positive energy, the opportunity, the
exploration, the excitement, not the
anxiety and the fear and the limitation
and the segregation. Whatever vibration
you choose will be the reality you get.
Remember no circumstance has builtin
meaning. All situations are
fundamentally neutral, blank, empty,
zero. You give them the meaning because
of what you have been taught to believe
these things mean. The meaning you give
it is the effect you get. Positive
meaning in, positive effect out,
negative meaning in, negative effect
out. Simple physics, simple
mechanics. You experience the reality.
You are the vibration of. You cannot
experience the reality you are not the
vibration of.
Understand? Yes, I do. Thanks. We thank
you very much. And at this timing, you
may all enjoy a short break. We will
resume contact in approximately 10 to 15
of your minutes. [Applause]
How's it going?
Please have a 10 or 15 minute break.
I'll call you when uh when Daryl's
ready. And if you want a copy of
tonight's tape, just see Lynn around the
corner. You can have it tonight. $10 for
the two tapes. [Music]
[Music]
first and foremost that the main purpose
of this
interaction is not for the validation of
my existence. It is for the validation
of yours.
However, no matter what the methodology,
no matter what the reason for what is
taking place, simply the idea is that we
will cocreate and get out of the
interaction whatever either of us put
into it. So proceed in whatever manner
you desire to. I will enjoy the
interaction whether I exist in your mind or not.
whether I exist in your mind or not.
Okay. This is my first time here. Yes.
Well, mine too right now. Every time is
the first time. And
um my uh therapist invited me to one of
these meetings cuz I'd never heard about
these meetings before. Well, I had but
this is my first time that Oh, right.
The question that I have is
um
she has done you know body work and
energy work with me right and I had
this experience
experience
that is still very difficult for me to
comprehend. All right. Can you describe?
Yeah. The experience was one moment. One
moment. Can you all hear this individual
adequately? Can you speak up a little
bit for the sharing of all? Have you
heard what I've said before? Oh, okay.
Okay. The experience was
um I started Okay. I'm a
very I guess you'd say conservative. All
right. Not hysterical person or
All right. Okay. But in this particular
experience, okay, I started shaking,
okay, and screaming. Oh, how exciting.
[Music] And
And
and I had this this vision of um I
thought, "Oh my god, I'm going crazy."
Oh. All right.
This this this vision of an Indian. Yes.
um with his hands coming and reaching
out to me and and kind of um asking me
to come towards him, guys. And what did
you do?
I I just freaked out. Did you go toward
the vision or stand there? Go away? No,
it just it seemed like it was a vision
and it was a lot of sadness. Sadness at
the time. I thought it meant going to a
trip to a you know certain I went to South
to a you know certain I went to South
America. No, it's all right. And it's
you know a very mystical place which a
lot of tourists go to now. Machu Picchu
as I thought that that's what it meant.
Although in a sense it is only your
society that has made it
mystical is quite a natural
representation of the energies of the
transformation going on on your planet
now. Quite natural.
But we understand what you mean.
Continue. Okay. I want I'm scared to
contact I don't know if if contacting
this spirit or whatever. Oh, all right.
Is of benefit now in my life. Oh, all
right. Now, may I ask you a question?
Mhm. Are you sure? Yeah. All right.
Don't want to ask it if you don't want
me to. No. Go ahead. All right. Thank
you very much.
Do you believe in the idea that is
called timing?
timing. Oh, let me put it this way. Do
you believe that everything and every
event has a place in
existence? In other words, I'm not sure.
All right. Do you believe there could be
such a thing as a creation that doesn't
belong in
creation? Could you believe, can you
perceive that there could be such a
thing as an extraneous creation,
something that didn't belong in
existence? Or do you understand that everything
Or do you understand that everything
that exists by definition must fit or it
couldn't exist? Which do you prefer to believe?
I want to I want to believe that there
are other dimensions that Oh, yes, there
other dimensions that Oh, yes, there
are. But that has nothing to do with
being extraneous. When we say extraneous, we
extraneous. When we say extraneous, we
simply mean could there be in your mind
something that you could perceive that
somehow doesn't belong in the universe?
Could something exist that didn't belong
in creation? No. All right, step one.
Very good. Now you can use that understanding
good. Now you can use that understanding
and apply it to some degree at first to
your circumstance. If the circumstance
circumstance. If the circumstance
happened, then on some level somehow it
belongs in creation. You follow me so
far? Yes. All right.
Now everything in creation fits
therefore by definition with everything
else. Perfect placement, perfect timing.
In other words, a thing cannot happen if
it doesn't belong in that moment. It
can't happen in that moment. It can only
happen in the moment in which it
belongs because space and time must both
be considered when you are talking about
the idea of whether something fits into
creation or not. If it fits, it has to
not only just fit in space, it has to
fit in time as well because that's the
definition of your physical universe. So
if a thing did happen, then the where of
it and the when of it must be by
definition representative of the
absolutely perfect timing and need and
reason for that event's existence to
begin with. Understand me so far? Are
you saying
that getting going or contacting this
entity or the spirit
uh is not necessary right now in my
life? Oh, that's not what I'm saying at
all. What I am saying is that because
obviously as you have just suggested
contact has already taken place then by
definition it obviously belongs or it
couldn't have
happened. Now for what reason it belongs
that is up to you to determine now you
can say all right I am cocreating
cocreating this event so that I can
determine whether or not I
choose to continue such events in my
life whether it serves me in one way or
another serve you it does how you wish
it to serve you is up to you how you
wish to use. It is up to you, but it
serves you by presenting you with a
perfect representation of exactly the
type of interaction you agreed to have
at that moment. Nothing can happen in
your life that you haven't agreed to
experience. If you haven't agreed to
experience it, you can't perceive it.
That's what other dimensions are. What
you have colloially referred to as other
realms of reality that you may not
immediately perceive are simply realms
of reality that are no less real but you
simply haven't at this timing got as a
part of your definitional agreement a
reason to perceive it yet. But whatever
you do perceive therefore by definition
must be a part of your agreed upon
timing your agreed upon interaction and
what it is you really want to do want to
see want to have an interaction with or
you wouldn't have had the
interaction. Therefore, are you
following me so far? Yes.
If you can understand it from that point
of view, if you choose to understand it
in that
way, then you can recognize that you
agreed to meet it halfway. You have to
create a similar vibration. You have to
be of the similar vibration of anything
you perceive in order to perceive it.
You can't perceive what you are not the
vibration of. That is simple physics.
Understand the
analogy? Yes. No. baby.
Uh, some some. All right, let's use the
radio analogy. You have on your planet a
device you call a radio. Yes. Yes. Now,
you only hear at any given moment the
program your dial is tuned to. Yes. Yes.
An expression of your intention to pick
up a certain frequency. Yes. Yes. Does
that mean all the other frequencies
aren't there at the same time? No. They
are all there.
Similarly, all realities, all types of
interactions, all levels of
consciousness, all dimensions exist now.
They are all coming to you quote unquote
at the same time. loosely meant.
However, the only things you perceive at
any given moment, the only thing you can
perceive at any given moment out of all
of it are the things that are most
reflective of whatever frequency you're
on at that moment. Understand? Yes.
Therefore, the interaction you had
obviously had to be by
definition representative of the
frequency you were on at the moment. And
therefore, since you were on that
frequency, somewhere within you, whether
it was consciously or unconsciously, you
had to be the one to turn your dial to
that program. So that was your part in
the agreement. In turning your dial, you
could receive a message from that guide,
from that spirit consciousness.
Now the only reason in a sense you
feared it to some degree is simply
because of the habit patterns, the
definitions, the belief systems that
most of your society has been brought up
with that this is the physical world and
there isn't anything else and if you see
anything else you're
crazy. But understand what crazy is.
What you call insane
people are simply people with their
dials tuned to other frequencies. They
are seeing other realities, other
aspects of the total whole that are no
less real than the ones you may
collectively agree to call real. But the
ones that do not know how to communicate
what they are perceiving in a way in
which it allows them to apply it back
into the consensus
reality. Then usually lock themselves
into a self-perpetuating cycle where
they focus on that other world they know
is real and do not allow themselves the
capability of communicating through them
the information that might be able to be
applied into the world they have already
locked themselves into. What you call a
genius, as you all already recognize,
the fine line, as you always say,
between genius and insanity, is for this
reason. A genius is somebody who simply
sees the other reality, knows it is real
in a sense, and knows a way to
communicate it in a way that makes sense
to the rest of your reality, in a way
that allows it to fit, to be applied to
the rest of your consensus reality. The
insane or individuals you call insane or
crazy are simply individuals who have
never been taught that what they're
perceiving A is real, just as real as
anything. And B, they have never been
taught to be able to let the information
come through them in a way that makes it
all right to apply what they're seeing
into the consensus reality. If the
consensus reality says, "No, no, no.
what you are seeing is not real. We
refuse to accept it. You are nuts. Then
they knowing what they are perceiving is
real will lock themselves away in their
own little world and be very difficult
to reach from that point forward. That
is why usually it takes a great deal of
the idea you call therapy to bring them
back out again fully. Now not meaning to
allow this to be an absolute figure for
it is always fluctuating but just to
give you a representational idea as an
analogy roughly what you would call 85%
of all individuals in what you call your
institutions for insane are simply
seeing other realities and don't know
how to communicate that because your
society hasn't taught that art hasn't
taught that all levels of perception are
representative of real realities. ities
that can fit or at least somehow be
accounted for whether it is immediately
applicable to this reality or not. So
back to your issue, the idea is that you
have made many associations in many
lives with many different levels of
consciousness and you have made certain
agreements with yourself to open up and
explore and be of service on your planet
now in certain ways. When those timings,
those signposts, those self-created
destiny points crop up, when you are on
a sufficient level to perceive it,
certain individuals who have agreed with
you to function as reflective guides
will pop into your life to remind you
now is the timing to explore this idea
of yourself. Now is the timing to
realize you have the ability to see
beyond the definitions your society has
taught you up to this point. And this is
one of the things this life is all
about. Knowing I am real. I am here to
reflect to you other aspects of your
consciousness so that you may discover
them and apply them to yourself as you
care to understand. Yes. But it's up to you
to understand. Yes. But it's up to you
to discover those specific ideas, those
specific connections and it's up to you
utterly to decide how you wish to apply
it. There is nothing inherently
fearcausing in this situation.
Only your belief system, only your
definition that you have to fear
something like that is what causes you
to feel the way you're feeling. Because
all feelings, pay attention, definition
coming up. All feelings are reactions to
something you already believe to be
true. You don't just have a feeling for
no reason.
All feelings are reactions to something
you have been taught to believe is true.
When you change the definition of the
belief, automatically you can no longer
have feelings other than those that are
representative of the new belief you
have, the new definition you have of the
reality you have co-created with any
other consciousness. Understand?
consciousness. Understand?
Most of it. Most of it. All right. You
understand it all. You have gotten it
all on every level. More and more and
more of this information, if you are now
willing, can come out in your dream
realities. They can become far more
active and vivid along this line if you
are willing to simply open up and trust
that you made this agreement that you
have attracted this occurrence because
of what it is you need to do, what you
need to discover about yourself to be of
service in the way you want to to live
the life that is really exciting to you.
Then let it in. Trust it. Trust it. And
you will find when you let the
information be delivered from that
guide, you will find that there is
nothing in that information that's
inherently negative. Only your
definition of it would be the idea that
would create it to feel negative at any
point. Trust it and let it in. But it's
up to you. You don't have to. But such
things cannot be an indication of
something outside of your control. And
that guide will only approach you to
whatever point the guide feels you are
ready to handle the information. They're
not going to push you. They're going to
let you be who you are and they're going
to let you determine the absolute
precision of the time. As soon as you
know you're ready, they are ready
because that's their job. Your job was
what you chose in being born on your
planet. Now the discovery of yourself,
the living of the excitement of yourself
and the expression of that excitement
that is the service to everyone else by
being fully who you are. It is simply
that you all have assistance to remind
you from time to time of when you set up
for yourself in this life a timing a
signpost that you wanted to look at to
remember more of who you are. In a sense
that vision is only you looking into a
mirror and seeing another higher aspect
of yourself reflected to you from a
friend. Understand? Yes. Now you don't
have to understand all this empirically
or analytically or terminologically or
semantically. All right. Now your timing
is flawless.
Relax. Everything comes out in perfect
timing. Now does this serve you? Yes.
All right. Now, may I ask you another
question? Yes. This is simply out of curiosity.
Yes. This is simply out of curiosity.
And in no way, shape or form is it meant
to reflect once again that it really
matters one way or another whether you
choose to believe I am who I say I am.
That is not the point. But simply this,
do you believe it is possible to
experience what you call telepathy?
Yes. Do you believe that other forms of
life exist in the universe on other
planets? I don't know. Do you believe it
is highly likely? I think it's very
possible. All right. Then there is
nothing so strange in the putting of
those two things together. And that's
what you're getting here.
Someone like you in many ways, who lives
on a world like yours in many ways, who
believes in telepathy and practices it
and has made an agreement with a certain
individual, the channel sitting before
you, to practice it in the following
way, to be of service in the way we are
being of service. Now, it is really no
more complicated than that in terms of
the idea of at least describing the
mechanism of what is going on. But once
again, our main purpose is for the
sharing of the information
itself. Though we love you all and would
enjoy ecstatically direct interaction in
time with you all, it matters not
whether you really choose in that sense
to prefer to interact with us or not.
What you are doing in your lives now is
the most important thing you need to be
doing. That is all right now we care
about. And do remember one other thing
and this is absolutely not a
chastisement. But simply the definition
of what you call
skepticism is not usually what most
people think in terms of having an open
mind. An open mind is an open mind.
Skepticism even though the original root
may have meant to know usually in your
society now means already having a
preconceived bias towards a particular
idea.
understand. Yes. Mhm. We thank you
lovingly for your sharing. We thank you
for being of service to all these
individuals for allowing them to see
through you different ways they could
apply the information you have
discovered about yourself to their own
lives so they may grow. We thank you.
Thank you. Pleasant
dreams shooting.
Hello Bashar and to you. Goodbye Bashar.
I want to tell you that my interactions
with you and just your being here is a
tremendous contribution to my life and I
thank you. Thank you. Thank you for
contributing to ours.
The question I have tonight has to do
with a series of situations I've had in
my life that are related to each other.
All right. That I'm not excited about
having in my life. Oh. All right. And
I'm uh anxious to learn the lessons I've
created them for and move on. Anxious.
Yes. Excited. Excited to All right.
learn these lessons and move on. Oh, all
right. Go ahead. They uh have to do with
the people that I'm close to in my life
along the path one after another
seemingly um uh inevitably inevitably
um uh inevitably inevitably
inevitably
My my
little piece of neutroneum there. That's
right. Inevitably. Yes. I said seemingly
inevitably. I know it's not inevitable,
but Yes. Just lightening things up a
bit. Thank you. Comes about that.
Um the people that I'm close to come to
a place where they feel they can't make
their own living and want to or do
become dependent on me. Oh, I see. All
right. I don't like the situation. Well,
all right. Then why do you support them?
Well, I stopped doing that. And what I
what I have now is a lot of people I'm
close to that are angry at me. Oh, or
have um maybe they're angry at
themselves. Maybe they are. At any rate,
I don't feel um resolved about handling
this. Not because it keeps coming up.
All right. So, can you express to them
the idea that you will help them all you can
idea that you will help them all you can
as long as it does not represent the
idea of taking responsibility for them
because you can't. You can be
responsible to them. You can give them
assistance as long as it in your
terminology does not violate the
integrity of what you prefer to be.
What I found is that when originally
when I first started having more money
than the people I'm around and they
first started coming to me needing
money, I thought it was a great joy to
be able to give it. I felt it in that
sense now. Yes. But remember
also there are again fine line
definitions especially within your
society connected to the idea of money
where a sharing can be a sharing and
then sometimes because of the shifting
in integrity the shifting in definitions
the shifting in levels of consciousness
it can allow itself to drop over into
the idea of dependency and that seems to
be what I create in these situations
that well all right then perhaps for
you. The lesson is in that sense in
allowing yourself perhaps to teach other
individuals how to match your vibration
to be abundant for themselves.
Yes, that's what I want to do. And
sharing in that sense and allowing them
to learn to be equal in that sense. Now
again there can be or could have been
some assistance given in the way you
have given it. But if you can use the
assistance you give on one level to help
them on many other levels to get them to
equalize your vibration that enabled you
to assist them to begin with rather than
simply allow them to assume that because
you're assisting them they don't have to
match your
vibration. Then you can equalize the
idea out. You can use the idea of giving
them some support to allow them to grow
in their own self support.
understand I do and I don't know how to
do that. That doesn't seem to happen
when I support people. They seem to grow
in dependency. And as so far as I can
see, everybody that I've assisted
financially has continued to not be
competent in that area. Then shift the
definition of how you assist them.
Assist them with knowledge of how to
match your abundance. I think I have a
conflict in myself, Bashar, because I
feel guilty. Guilty. My Yeah, I feel
upset when my best friend tells me she
doesn't have money again to pay her rent
and um horror stories and she really
needs a place to live and would like to
live in my place rentree. Let's use an
analogy that perhaps may put it a little
bit into perspective.
Now, are you telling me that you are
going to feel guilty if instead of
giving your friend a slice of bread,
which you can do and have done, that you
teach them how to bake their own so that
they can always eat whenever they want
to rather than having to come to you for
a slice now and then. You know, these
people are they they really don't ask
for a lesson and and or the way that I
give it is resented. I I But that's
their choice of reaction, not yours. And
it is not cause for the idea of the
guilt you are accepting into your life.
Why am I creating all of these people
that are not to give you the opportunity
to stop feeling guilty about being the
abundant person you are?
Well, yeah. And that's that's I
understand that and what I have left. I
don't understand that. Yes, you do. I
said, well, if you understand it, then
put it into action. Put your
understanding into application. If you
are a
friend, then go with your friend and
say, let us discuss the idea of how you
can match this vibration. I can still be
willing to utilize some of my abundance
and direct it in a way where and when
necessary to assist you in learning how
to be equally abundant.
However, if you find that they generate
within themselves a reaction that is
outside of integrity, that's not your
choice. That's not your reality. That's
their reaction, not yours. You feeling
guilty about their choosing to accuse
you means you are simply willing to buy
into their expression of lack of
abundance rather than standing firm in
your understanding of your own abundance
of who you are. Why would you want to
buy into the idea of their offering of
lack of abundance?
It hurts me. Why? Remember what they
said about reaction. They don't have any
money to eat. It hurts me. I understand
what you are saying. But the idea once
again is that you are not really serving
them unless you teach them how to serve
themselves. Understand? Yes, I do. Could you point
Understand? Yes, I do. Could you point
me in the direction of being a better
teacher other than displaying what I do,
sharing with
them how I have accumulated abundance,
sharing with them the way that I do
that? Can you point you in a better
direction than being a living example of
what you believe in? Well, it's just not
working for my friends. I'm still
creating. What you do may not work for
them, but that in no way, shape, or form
determines the effect it has on your
life. If you know you are being of
service, then derive the joy out of that
that you deserve to derive. If they do
not choose to find joy in it, if they do
not choose to create it to work, that's
not your
responsibility. You cannot do it for
them. So why take the responsibility
when they choose to ignore the
information? Understand? I do. And what is it that I
Understand? I do. And what is it that I
do that um makes people give up their
responsibility around me?
You feel guilty about your
abundance. You buy in too easily to the
idea of guilt. So you attract
individuals who give you a sparkling
opportunity to discover how guilty you
feel for what you have and they reflect
it right back to
you. Understand? Yes. Plain and simple.
That's it. Remember that if you say you
have all this
love, then you won't choose guilt.
Because guilt once again is the true
opposite of love, not hate.
Guilt, the complete lack of belief in
your worthiness. Understand? Yes. Does that
worthiness. Understand? Yes. Does that
assist you? Yes. I have a little more
left. Can I continue briefly? Okay.
Um, what I see you saying is given a
specific situation where my where I've
offered my friend the tools and she um
remains in the same situation and is
angry. Yes.
Um, you get on with your life. I get on with
you get on with your life. I get on with
my life. That's what you do because
again only by a living example can you
give them the opportunity to have
anything to look at that they can mimic
and change into.
And once I start just moving on with my
life I will then attract people that are
abundant and I can share that. In other
words, let me put it this way. If you
know you have been doing your best, if
you know you've been acting out of
integrity, if you know you've been
acting out of love, if you know you've
been being of service, then why would
you believe it when someone tells you
you haven't been?
It just happens a lot. It doesn't just
happen. You choose it. Mhm. So if you
don't prefer it, why choose it? And if
someone tells you, "Oh, you're cold and
uncaring." You say, "I know I am not."
Mhm. Beyond the shadow of a doubt, I
know I am
not. If that is your perception, I love
you unconditionally enough to let you
have that perception. But it doesn't
change that I know my life is full of
joy. Understand? Yes, I do. Thank you
very much. Thank you, Bashar. All my
love to you and
you shooting.
Hello, Bashar. And to you, good day. You
know, back in uh 1970, I went to a
lecture in Scientology and they had a
demonstration where everybody mocked up
a picture of a cat and had it run off.
Speak up. Speak up so that all may hear.
Had it had this group mock up a picture
of a cat and have the cat run off. Yes.
It's demonstrating how the mind worked.
But the thing was out of a group of
about 13 people, there was two in there
that didn't have mental image pictures.
Yes. So, I spent 14 years wanting to get
my mental image picture back. I wonder
why is it that uh I can see pictures in
a dream. Yes. And I can sense what
something looks like impression, but I
have no mental image picture. I can't
make a mental image picture. Well, not
there may be to some degree a slight
clarification necessary in what it is
you think you ought to be doing as
opposed to what you actually are doing.
You may be doing what you need to do,
but you may be carrying with you an
assumption that it quote unquote should
be a certain way when that is not
necessarily so. And let me ask you this
out of curiosity.
If you are not
capable of having the idea you call a
mental image picture, then how do you
know you're not doing it? Well, like
some people is they have very vivid
colors in their pictures and stuff. Like
I can right now now mock up a picture of
a cat in front of me, but it's an
invisible cat. An invisible cat. Yeah.
May I ask you a question? Yeah. What
color is this invisible cat? I can see
right through it. All right. Then it is
a clear cat. Yeah. Is that not color
enough? No, but I can't give it a color
either. Do you want to? Do you need to?
I would like to have good metal image
pictures. But that's not the question.
One moment. One moment. Listen to what
you are
saying. You may be getting the image
that you
need. May I ask you this question?
If the image you are getting serves your
purpose cleanly and clearly, would you
want to complicate it with more detail
that doesn't need to be
there? No.
Why not relax with what you get the way
you get it and allow anything else that
needs to be there to simply
spontaneously occur rather than trying
to get a detail, a complexity, an
additional symbol that you don't
necessarily need to accomplish what you
need to accomplish. If the animal is
already clear, maybe that's the way it
needs to be. Who knows? Maybe one day
you might have a discussion with a group
of people that have been, as you say,
mentally imaging. And you'll sit there
and go, listening to them. Well, I had a
go, listening to them. Well, I had a
cat. It was red. I had a cat. It was
black. I had a cat. It was green with
purple polka dots. And you'll be sitting
there going, "Gee, all I get is a clear
cat." And they all turn to you and look
at You get a clear cat. We've been
trying to get a clear cat for years. All
we get one.
[Applause] All we get are all the cats that are
All we get are all the cats that are
confused in all sorts of different
shades of color. We've been trying to
get the color out so the cat could be
clear. And you can do this
naturally. Well, my my my my. The whole
point simply being let it happen the way
it needs to, knowing that the way it
does happen is the way that will work
best for you. Anything else you need
will automatically spontaneously be
there if you really need it. Do not
necessarily back yourself into a corner
with a definition you think ought to
represent what you should and should not
be doing. Okay, I see that. The more you
relax, the more spontaneous the image
will be able to be. And the way it comes
is the way that serves you best. And
when you let the way it comes be the way
it needs to come, the paradox occurs,
the irony occurs. That's when you start
seeing the entire
spectrum. Because when you allow what is
to be what needs to be, you then allow
all that is to be in any way that it can
be. And you allow it all to be perceived
by you. Don't be too
insistent. Open up your definition and
allow it
in. Understand? I understand. Well,
thank you very much. Okay. Thank you.
Give our regards to your cat. Okay. sharing. sharing.
[Music]
Good evening. And to you, goodbye. Thank
you. Uh can you assist me in
understanding how to allow and flow more
positively with situations presenting
presented to me especially in the last
few months and they are affecting me
physically and emotionally. No. All
right. One moment. One moment. Remember,
remember apply everything we have
discussed this evening and remember that
they don't affect you. You choose to be
affected. Understand? Yes. Now, you
understand that you attract these ideas
in your life. You choose them. Yes. I'm
understanding that more fully especially
when I Very good. The idea is not so
much that you necessarily make a
conscious choice for that specific
circumstance. It's that whatever beliefs
you buy into most strongly attract the
most likely circumstance to represent
those beliefs. So in having attracted
that circumstance by the attraction you
are given the best opportunity to see in
no uncertain terms what strongest
beliefs you have because that's the
reality you're getting so that you can
determine if you want to keep those
beliefs. The circumstances that occur in
your life don't occur to show you you're
stuck or to show you that you're a
failure. They occur to show you that
this is the belief you have and if you
don't like it, change it and the
physical reality will change along with
it. Also remember, don't automatically
assign a negative meaning to a
circumstance just because you have
always been taught that that's what it
means. Understand?
Yes. Now, do you have a particular
specific idea you can
share with regard to one of these
circumstances that you say have affected
you? More understanding on how to maybe
More understanding on how to maybe
change or work with the subconscious
where I feel that maybe conditionings
are affecting me negatively. All right.
All right. All right. But let's start
right at the absolute fundamental belief
which you are obviously already in touch
with. Bravo. The fundamental belief is I
Bravo. The fundamental belief is I
believe I have subconscious conditioning
that may affect me
negatively. Why choose to believe
it? That's your fundamental belief right
there. Why choose to believe that? Do
you prefer to believe you have
subconscious conditioning that might
affect you
negatively? Do you prefer to believe
that? No. Then why believe it?
Because I am not flowing. I'm not
allowing things that are happening. You
are talking about the past. You have not
been. But what's that got to do with
now? What's that got to do with this
point forward now that you recognize
that what happened then was the product
of the fact that you chose to believe
you had these subconscious beliefs cuz
whatever it is is affecting me still
now. So I haven't maybe let go or how
long do you think it will take for your
realization of this belief to allow a
change to occur in your physical
reality? Do you believe it can happen
instantaneously? Yes. Are you being
honest? Yeah. Are you sure?
Yeah. All right. You absolutely believe
beyond a shadow of a doubt that if you
allow yourself to change your
fundamental belief right now that your
physical reality will change.
I just need to understand how
then you don't believe it is
instantaneous because you already
understand how and yet now you have just
denied that you understand it. Knowledge
itself of what you prefer to be if
believed in more strongly than what you
have believed in before will
automatically replace what you have
been. Now at the outside you can give it 72 of
Now at the outside you can give it 72 of
your
hours. That can be for some of you
representative of instantaneousness.
[Music] 3 days
3 days
maximum. Describe what you call the
physical affectation.
There's a tremendous energy within me
that's just
constantly almost like the earthquake
today. All right. Constantly. Are you
saying this is negative? I don't know
what it is. You don't know what it is? I
don't know what it is. Do you prefer
that it is positive?
You don't know? I don't feel wonderful
about it. That's not the question. I
don't know. I really don't know. Do you
prefer it is for a positive reason? Yes.
All right. Then start to believe that it
is. Do you not recognize that all the
transformations that are taking place
upon your planet now all have to do with
the fact that all of you are awakening
into more of the energy that you are as
a being. That what you have thought of
as your limited physical reality is no
longer the border of your definitions
and that all that you are feeling now is
an acceleration of energy within you
that is representative of the higher
accelerated energy you actually are now
discovering yourself to be. Do you not
understand that? I'm trying to
understand that. All right. What do you
imagine prevents you from understanding
it in that format? Are you not familiar
with the idea of the semantics of
consciousness and
energy? Do you know that you are made of
energy? Yes, I know that. All right.
That is an absolute for you then. Yes.
Yes. All right. Then what you are
feeling is more of your own energy. And
by the old definition of yourself,
you're simply not used to that much you
yet. You are used to less you.
Now you are awakening. Now you are
exploring. And as you explore, as you
open up in what you call your spiritual
quest, you allow more of you to be
apparent within you. You begin to feel
more of the energy you are. That's all
you're feeling. You're feeling more of
the actual level of vibratory energy on
which you can be existing. If you are
hesitant about what it is because you
don't have a clear definition of it,
then simply first and foremost
assume that it is positive, that it's
there for a positive reason. Your
assumption, your approach, your
direction in this manner will allow you
in short order to derive a positive
benefit, a positive understanding from
it. It is only your classification of it
that makes it seem any negativity you
are feeling. Understand? It is because of
feeling. Understand? It is because of
your definition of uncertainty. Be
certain. Be certain in the direction you
prefer to be certain in. That's all it
takes. It's called trust and faith. I
don't know what this feeling is, but
because I know I am a positive person,
because I have chosen to know I am a
positive person, it must be a part of
the positive unfolding of who I am. Oh
joy, oh
joy, since I know nothing in my life is
an interruption in my life, but I only
know that everything I experience I have
chosen. Everything I experience, I have
attracted. And therefore everything I
experience is a part of the unfoldment
of the path I chose to be. Then whatever
this is must be a part of it. And that
means that now that I'm experiencing
this, I am now unfolding at a faster
rate. I'm accelerating. Otherwise, I
wouldn't be experiencing what this
energy is. I wouldn't be discovering
something new if I weren't changing in
directions I want to change in. Oh
ecstasy. Oh ecstasy. I am overjoyed. As
soon as you become that happy about
what's happened to you, your level of
energy will rise to match the vibration
you're feeling and it will feel like it
smooths
out. So you don't notice the difference
anymore. The energy is there to show you
what level you can match at any given
moment. When you match it by trusting it
and getting excited and getting into it,
then it will seem to dissipate or
disperse, but it is simply that you have
matched that
level. Understand? That's what it's for. Is
Understand? That's what it's for. Is
this making any sense to you? Yes. Are
you willing to trust
it? Are you willing to trust your own
ecstasy? Are you willing to believe it
is that easy to change? Well,
Well,
still not sure
there seems to be the questioning of of
how to open. I told you
how. I just told you how. Then what is
it within us that blocks that that is
there for us to believe or have faith?
As simple as this. your assumption that
there is some mysterious how that needs
to be known before you will simply act
in the manner you want to. In other
words, laugh, be happy because you want
to. As soon as you do, you'll match that
frequency. There is no mysterious how.
None that has to be
there. And if you really want a bottom
line definition, then live now. That's how.
definition, then live now. That's how.
Anytime you live in the now, utterly in
the moment, any energy that comes along,
any difference that you feel, you will
match instantly because you are living
fully in the now, accepting it all. Open
to it all. Absolute vulnerability, not
weakness. Openness, strength,
self-empowerment. That's how. Live in
the now with it. Assume that what is
happening belongs in your life. Accept
it. Acknowledge it. Integrate it. Live
through it. Get into it. Explore it.
Examine it. Get excited because you know
it's there for your reasons. Whether
you're conscious of them or not, it's
there for your reason. The more you act
like you know it's there for your
reason, whether you're conscious of what
the reason is or not, the sooner you
will become conscious of the reason. And
very often the only reason you will discover
often the only reason you will discover
after you accept the energy and
accelerate is simply that it was there
for you to accept the energy and
accelerate. And by the time you
accelerate, you have used it for the
reason it was there. And there's no
other reason to discover. That's it. It
may come in the disguise of seeming to
be some particular specific reason you
need to discover. But by the time you
actually use it, you discover that
simply the using of it was reason
enough. And that's it. And you go on to
the next thing and the next
forever. Always enjoy and ecstasy. You
follow along? Yes. It's that simple.
It's that easy. It is that easy. Nothing
nothing is too good to be true. Too easy
to be true. Too simple to be true. Cause
and effect are the same event. You don't
have to wait for a reason to be happy in
order to know you prefer to be happy. Be
happy. Create the effect of being happy
and you will attract into your life all
of the causes to support the happiness
you have created. Just because you want
to and just because you say so. There
doesn't need to be any other why or how
because you are the creator of your
reality and that's it. What you say
goes. Understand? Yes. Thank you very Does
Understand? Yes. Thank you very Does
that serve you? Yes. Thank you
at this
time. Allow us to extend to each and
every one of you once again our deepest
unconditional love, our joy, our
excitement at being allowed to feel the
energy of your consciousness put forth
boldly with the conviction of who you
have created yourselves to be.
You are the season of change. You are
the autumn of change. You are the
threshold of manifestation
manifestation
on the night of our
interaction. Though there may be still
in your terms a little bit of time
before we get there. another session or
so in
between on the night of our
interaction just
prior to the time you would call your
Halloween. We will share with
you our version of a ghost story.
[Music] We extend to each and every one of you a
We extend to each and every one of you a
fond, exciting and loving good day. Good
day. [Applause]
How'd it go? Great.
Thank you all for being here tonight.
[Music]
Yes. Thank you very much for coming.
Anyone who wants a copy of tonight's
tape, you can have it tonight. Just see
the gal in the yellow suspenders and
she'll fix you up.