I say how are you all this evening of
your time as you create time to
exist allow us to begin this interaction
this evening of your time with the
entitlement the
neighborhood we are going to speak a
little bit further on the idea of your
immediate Stellar
neighborhood and the type of neighbors
that you have and to some degree where
some of them may be
found now I have discussed with you many
times the idea of focusing upon your
planet especially in this time of change
and transition and in no way shape or
form do we mean by this particular
entitlement tonight to remove your focus
from the earth for that is where it
belongs in that sense we do not mean to
pull you away from the understanding
that the quote unquote most important
job now is the
familiarization with yourselves to
yourselves the neighbors that you have
all around you the neighborhood that you
as a planet are do not forget that that
is your primary focus for that is what
you have chosen to be bor this time of
your time of counting in this
transformational age to be of assistance
to your entire world but we will discuss
a little bit the
idea of how it is to some degree that
your immediate shall we say neighborhood
of solar systems a
structure now in the physiological
formation of any particular idea that
you would call a solar system a star or
many stars and what you would call their
attendant planetary
bodies the materials as you say the
elements that go into making up that
particular physiological
system will be found within the original
shall we say
cloud of matter cloud of elements cloud
of dust that will then congeal collapse
to
form the stars and the planets of that
particular system different areas
throughout the Universe will have clouds
of matter that contain many different
elements depending upon the original
dispersal of those elements within the
universe and also depending upon the
actions in actions of other Stellar
masses that has gone on throughout what
you would call eons of time within the
physiological Universe sometimes collapsing into
Universe sometimes collapsing into
systems sometimes as you say destroying
themselves in what you would call Nova
phenoma and giving up of their elements
into the universe only to be dispersed
into other clouds and shared gathered
together once again to form other
systems at some other time all of these
interactions of the comings and goings
of stellar masses determines the types
of elements that are available for the
formation of new solar systems and what
will be possible or probable to find as
the different types of physiological
life that will be available to be shall
we say expressed as Consciousness in a
particular system different areas different Pockets
system different areas different Pockets
within the universe will be richer in
certain elements than other Pockets so
to
speak Now understand this
sometimes a given area of matter of
cloud dust formation in the universe
will collapse to form many different
systems this is how large some of those
dust clouds can be those Elemental
clouds can be to form many different
systems that are in your terms light
years apart when you find in any particular
apart when you find in any particular
area one system that has what you would
call life indigenous life upon the planet it
life indigenous life upon the planet it
is a as you say likelihood therefore
that many of the surrounding systems
will also have because usually within
any one given area all those systems
have congealed out of one large mass
that contains the richness of the
elements necessary to provide the
foundation for different physiological
life forms through which Consciousness
can express
itself therefore it is one of the most
solid shall we say CL clues that since
you already exist upon your planet in
that way since there is life upon your
world that you can almost guarantee that
there will be at least an average of one
civilization for what you would call
approximately every five to seven like
years of your counting in your radius
around you this is a typical average
cross-section of how civilizations are
scattered through out Galactic
Mass so understand you have quite a few
neighbors simply because you exist in
your area in all likelihoods then you
have ideas of other
civilizations within a relatively near
range of your solar system simply
because your systems were all congealed
out of one original mass that contained
the same richness of elements and could
provide a basis and a foundation for
many different styles of life form
expression in many of those systems
the average as we have said will usually
be one civilization every five to seven
light years now some areas will have a
denser population and some will have a
sparer population but that as we have
found is roughly the average at least
within what you would call this Galactic
Mass therefore in addition to some of the
therefore in addition to some of the
civilizations we have discussed from
time to time
we will once again delineate those
systems which within what you would call
approximately a 12 Lightyear radius are
your closest neighbors star systems that
have other
civilizations upon the planets within
those star
systems now we have discussed Zeta
reticulum we have discussed pleades we
have discussed the idea of many other
civilizations ours include
of course in that sense we are to some
degree a little bit different in the
sense that we occupy another dimensional
plane other than the one you are in but
the idea is as follows your solar system
is most closely bordered by what you
would call the system of alpha centor
you're counting and there is
civilization there then there is Barnard star system
there then there is Barnard star system
and there is civilization
there now the last time we read this
list to you we mentioned a star that you
have called wolf
359 and we said will'll avoid that for a
moment this time we can tell
you there is in a sense life within that
system not on any Planet not like you
understand life and there is more life other life
life and there is more life other life
not indigenous to the system observing
the life that is the life that is is not
in a format you are familiar with that
and those specifics we will discuss
another time but there are two life
forms in that system one indigenous but
nothing like you understand life today
and one observing them more familiar to
you perhaps as a life form but not
indigenous to the
system then we will move on to the star
system you have called serus which we
have discussed many
times then what you would call star
system Epsilon
eridani star system Epsilon
Indie and then within that 12 Lightyear
radius the final star system Close to
You harboring civilization would be star
system TTI so you can see in that sense that
TTI so you can see in that sense that
you are surrounded
by quite a few
neighbors now these distances from what
you would call approximately
43 light years to approximately
11.7 light years may seem to be long
distances to you but within the idea of
the next 50 years of your accounting you
are as a civilization going to be able
to understand more and more the idea of
the type of electromagnetic
transference that is utilized in our
spacecraft that will allow you to
redefine your location within the fabric
of SpaceTime to allow yourself to
dissolve yourself at one location and
reemerge at another location this is not
traveling faster than the speed of light
you are not remaining within your
Universal realm at all when you do this
you are in a sense simply redefining
your existence at another place in time
when your civilization within what you
call the next 50 years of your time
accomplishes this idea you will be able
to be very strongly in touch with many
of these other
civilizations and open up Broad communic
a with them as well as many others that
have already been interacting with your
Society for many years another we have
talked about will be the civilization in
the star system you have called Zeta
reticulum this civilization is the one
that is more often than not responsible
for What on your world you have called
the interactions
abduction which we prefer to call
temporary detainments since they are all made by
detainments since they are all made by
agreement and they all serve a common
purpose of aiding and assisting in the
transformation of Consciousness upon
your world and the dissolving and
transformation of the fear that each and
every one of you have been brought up
with by being in your
civilization more and more and more
civilizations in that sense will be
revealed unto you in that sense more and
more interactions will begin to take
place in time but remember
remember we now reflect this idea to you
of your immediate neighborhood so that
you can begin also to look at your own
planet as in a sense a group of star
systems each and every one of you being
your own Stellar awareness your own
spark of infinite
light each and every one of you then can
begin to form your own Coalition your
own Association of solar systems by
Association of solar systems by
interacting in peaceful and harmonic
ways learning in that sense to express
equality among yourselves and becoming
your own in effect Galaxy Galactic
Consciousness on your own Planet your
own unified whole point of
view so that then in becoming a whole
planetary civilization you can begin to
interact with other civilizations that
operate on a similar frequency a similar
wavelength now this is not to say that
every other civilization you will find
within the Galaxy is going to be
operating on a planetary scale in fact
the idea of the civilization in the
Barnard star system we have discussed
with you many times you will be
interacting with them as we perceive
your energy in much the same way we are
interacting with you now they are in
your terminology approximately 300 of
your years in the past technologically
speaking and as you begin to interact
with them as you achieve true space
flight then you will be their
UFOs and they can make up stories about
all of
you the other idea simply is
now that distances are becoming much
much closer you always have the capacity
of reaching these other civilizations
within the Gateway of your imagination
and in your dream state many of you have
already begun to lay down the lines of
communication to these other systems to
allow yourselves to understand that you
can function as a network of many of
these systems of your immediate
neighbors that you are
all emergent from from a common origin
in that sense in the sense of the
material that was created the material
that was used to construct all of your
solar systems physically speaking you
all share that degree of commonality
that your physical representational
cells are born out of the same Stellar
material the same Stellar cloud in that
way the same bubble of the
Galaxy now you can begin to reflect
these ideas in your own planetary sphere
by aiding and participating in every
Endeavor that promotes the idea of
harmonics and peace upon your planet to
truly function in a way that will allow
you to be one of the neighbors one of
the active participatory Neighbors in
this bubble as these distances are made
smaller and smaller and smaller and
smaller very soon for 50 of your years
is not a very long time at all your
entire civilization will begin to
realize that you you can come and go as
freely between these stars as you now
come and go freely between the different
cities upon the surface of your
world you are truly
moving not into simply another
generation but truly into another
culture on your planet and as we have
said many times the children being born
upon your world now are now being born
into a conducive atmosphere that does
not allow them to forget as much of who
and what they are as an aspect of the
infinite because of this conducive atmosphere you
because of this conducive atmosphere you
are accelerating greatly and many of
these children will be responsible for
the discoveries technologically speaking
that will carry you to the stars in no
time at
all you are truly giving birth to a
different culture upon your
planet a total shall we say
emergence of a truly more mature form of
human being now in this sense we are not being
being now in this sense we are not being
derogatory and not calling you
immature but the idea is that you are
still maturing like every race matures
and changes and
evolves and within the next five of your
decades you will be laying the seeds and
the foundations and the atmospheres and
the interactions to truly allow you to
enter what can be called planetary
adulthood you're having a fine
adolescence now at this
at this
timing we extend to each and every one
of you our deepest appreciation in being
willing to receive us as your neighbors
and in being willing to allow us to
receive you as ours and to interact as
representatives and diplomats of each of
our respective
civilizations so that through these
interactions bit by bit in day by day we
can create a more conducive atmosphere
that will allow us to meet someday face
to face as equals but only when you are
equals to yourselves for only on that
level do we desire to interact with you
when you in that sense recognize the
validity and the deserv ability of
sharing your unconditional love with
each other for then can we play
together as fully mature
children we thank you for this
opportunity of sharing we thank you for
allowing us to Delight in the experience
of your individual and Collective
Consciousness for you are a gift to us
and in return for the gift you are
giving us now I ask you how may I serve
you hi Bashar and good day to you uh my
question is to deal with our natural
resources and the way in which we use
them are they in finite Supply yes and
you know that already Yes and is the way
we're using them damaging our
environment irreparably so certainly
aspects may be in your terminology
irreparable not all of them are some of
them can be
reversed some of the ones that you may
now call irreparable you can find
substitutes for to some degree but as
your Society now and within the next
couple of your decades begins to move
toward the understanding that the
electromagnetic field of your planet can
provide all the power you want you will
then begin to cease delving into as we
perceive your energy the idea of the
exhaustion of these natural resources
and begin to rely on an exhaustible un
exhaustible source of the idea of the
simple infinite power of creation of the
energy out of which all matter is
created that electromagnetic field that
surrounds your planet you can tap into
many ways many individuals in your
Society have done so many times but the
information in your circles has been
suppressed over and over and over again
but now many of you are beginning to
understand this is possible and there is
now shall we say a momentum within your
general public I believe what you call a
Grassroots movement to allow you to
invent and reinvent and ReDiscover the
idea of the natural electromagnetic
pulsations of your planet that can be
tapped and transformed into the
different types of power application
that you need and serve all your needs
in that way this can be done within what
you call the next 10 to 20 of your years
at the outside each and every one of you
that is interested in this idea begin by
exploring and experimenting in this way
now the idea is that the more of you do
this the more other individuals will
catch on that they do not have to use
the resources that would be exhausted in
that way nor the resources that would
create what you would call the pollutive
aspects of your
world you understand mhm it is not in
that sense therefore in the overall
scheme of things too late but certain
attributes have been used up exhausted
and may take quite some time before they
can be in your terms fully repaired the
sooner you allow yourself to Avail
yourself of the Natural Energy that has
always been available to you the easier
it will be upon your entire planetary
system to allow those repairs to begin
what repairs can be
made and the higher your Collective
vibration becomes the more you truly can
literally transform your entire planet
raise and Elevate its vibratory level
so that in a short amount of time you
can then while not necessarily
reclaiming the things you have exhausted
you can in a sense repair the Damage
Done by taking your world into a new
state a new phase of existence
electromagnetically speaking understand yes thank you Does
speaking understand yes thank you Does
this answer the questions sufficiently
yes thank you very much
sharing hello Bashar and good day to you
I have some information that came over
from Australia all right about EarthLink
88 as I wonder if you had any
information on this about the 13th of
February 1988 CLE is going to be an
electric blue crystal transmitter cell
beneath Air's Rock in central Australia
I have discussed the idea of that local
you call Air's rock as being a highly
powerful magnetic Vortex and yes in a
sense there is an ethereal
interdimensional crystallin formation
underneath it that is one of the
balancing centers of your planet one
that can send out electromagnetic pulses
to Aid and assist the idea of the
balancing of your entire Collective
mentality also the idea of what we have
called the peace clock project to some
degree will synchronize with that as 12
midday even though only on one day of
your year has been called out by them to
be the appropriate timing to synchronize
your thoughts for World Peace the idea
is simply representative of a group
Harmony a group harmonic a miniature
Mass Consciousness within your entire
planet that is focused in that direction
in that way any and all that resonate to
its vibration May participate and can
add their impact and momentum to your
entire world's ability to create peace
that much more rapidly understand with
that project this project and any
projects that you care to develop on
your own Freer imagination to promote
the idea of Harmony on your world you
you will accelerate that ability more
and more and more and more it is not
impossible that you could accelerate the
energy of harmonic peace on your planet
sufficiently so that by your year
1990 you could literally declare World
Peace it is possible it seems at this
time more likely that you may go through
transitions through your 19 90s until
you allow certain events of a worldwide
nature and what you would call 1997 to
really shall we say force the issue and
from that point forward within three of
your years and then up to the time frame
you call 2011
2013 those events will have driven your
planet to truly begin to lay down models
ideas foundations for the true drawing
up of what you would call World Charter
in that sense where you'll begin to
reroute a lot of your economic systems
to focus on the idea of shall we say
feeding your people clothing your people
and in that sense truly focusing all the
idea of your energies towards unifying
your entire world it can begin as soon
as your 1990 right now it seems more
likely that it will be kicked off more
in your
1997 but that's up to each and every one
of you this event EV you are mentioning
and any and all events that add their
assistance add their momentum to the
idea of a true desire for World piece
will determine exactly where the timing
will fall and how much impact it shall
have okay thank you well thank you very
much
Shing technical problem here
thanks good day Hi how are you perfect
and you oh a little tired but fine all
right um okay being in this body and in this
um okay being in this body and in this
in this time I kind of have a hard time
getting out of it in I mean you know
meditation yes going out there but on a
day-to-day basis
basis
um I know I should be more succinct um
you are doing just fine
um dealing with the physical life as it
is now yes because I have a body that
has a couple of minor difficulties oh
all right such as such as uh my skeletal
structure skeletal structure all right
and and it uh there will be pain coming
from that from the well actually I don't
know if it's the structure if it's
something that I'm putting on it is the
same thing you are creating your own
stru structure by the ideas by the
definitions that you create yourself to
be this is how any physiological reality
is manifested it is the composite the
combination of all the variable
definitions within the equation you have
written yourself to be as an energy
being that I understand yes um actually
surgery yes the technological things in
surgery now to rearrange IAL yes
structure it is one of the ways you can
exercise your understanding of control
over physical reality isn't the only way
but it is one way and it is valid it
depends upon your strongest belief
system if the strongest belief system
and strongest definition of reality you
have within you says that that's the
easiest way for you to change your
structure if you have a desire to do so
then by all means recognize that system
in all probability will work best for
you if your mentality desires that
another methodology work best then your
imagination will attract you to the
circumstances that will provide you with
the information you need to allow that
methodology to work best for you always
your strongest belief system will
determine what methodology will work
best for you but they're all
valid are you exploring the idea of
making changes in ways that your Society
might find
unorthodox yes such as uh one is uh deep
tissue or just changing it in my mind
seeing it changed and letting it change
by itself s yes uh and you know and
through just realigning them manually
realigning them through the muscles all
right well you can begin with the
understanding of the following
issue even some of your own medical
practitioners are now beginning to
realize the following
idea every single thought you have
literally physically
reorganizes the neurological Pathways in
your physical brain every moment of time
you do not have the same brain literally
physically there are neurological
Pathways right now in your brain that
were not there a minute ago and some
that were there a minute ago are no
longer there and I do not just mean that
some of them are closing and opening and
they were there to begin with New Paths
are actually created Old Paths are
actually dissolved absorbed back into
the mass of the physiological brain some
of your scientists are beginning to
realize this now that with every thought
you have you already literally change
the physical structure of your brain now
your physical brain is responsible in
that sense for shall we say monitoring
the physiological structure of your body
the only thing that would create there
to be a seeming block between your
understanding that your thoughts alter
physical reality would be if you have
been taught to buy into a definition
that says somehow the alteration of your
physical structure is more difficult
than Simply Having a new thought and
allowing your physical body to take that
form this is what many of you have been
taught that physical reality is fixed
and that your thoughts are simply
ethereal ideas that do not really have a
great effect upon physical material but
you are beginning to realize just the
opposite in fact you are beginning to
realize that physical material
absolutely has no structure without the
definitions of your thoughts so one
thing that may be able to begin to
assist you is to really as you say get a
handle on the idea that you're changing
physically every moment anyway literally
physically every single moment once you
can allow that to inspire you perhaps
you can then redirect the idea of that
physical change exactly where you want
it to be but do understand this it is
isn't always just a matter of having the
thought and quote unquote just letting
your body change many times if you
simply have the imagination have the
picture of the way you desire your body
to be you see it in the way you want it
to be many times because you are so
immersed in physical reality and the
habitual rituals that have gone with it
many times what it will take to truly
initiate shall we say ignite that vision
to allow your body to change most easily
will be to act in ways that are
representative of the change to allow a
physical action to lock into your body
habit your body pattern the idea that
you are in fact more truly the vision
you desire to be than the physical
reality Vision you have been that you no
longer prefer so many times
opportunities will come into your life
that will give you a chance to act as if
to act in the direction of the change to
exhibit a trait that is representative
of the change you say you prefer to the
best of your ability when those
opportunities happen act in that
direction as if you were already changed
and that is what starts retraining
reprogramming your body Consciousness to
begin to take its cues from a mind that
thinks of itself as whole rather than a
mind that has been trained in habitual
rituals to think of itself as somehow
unstructured or unaligned you are
retraining yourself in that way is this
sinking in at all is this helping you
yes very much so use that imagination to
really see the you you prefer to be
allow circumstances to be attracted into
your physical Life by that particular
Beacon you will set up in your
imagination and whatever the
opportunities are that come with
excitement that your imagination has
drawn act on them physically to the best
of your ability and you will step by
step retrain your body to align to a new
idea a new definition a new template of
yourself the template you really prefer
to be so have a clear vision of what you
really want know that that is you it is
you and then allow yourself to blend
into it by starting to act like the you
you see in your mind's eye if there are
things that that I know are stopping
that should I just avoid them no no no
no no if you believe there are things in
your terminology that stop you from
doing that then dive into them find out
what beliefs you would have to contain
in order to attract those things that
would seem to stop you for there are no
real blocks what you call in your
Society blocks are actually packets of
information about yourself that you need
to discover that you need to explore and
open up and then in discovering those
things to integrate that knowledge and
that idea within you to absorb it to
become more than you are now in a sense
so if you feel that there is something
stopping you then examine the fear
examine the so-called block find out
what kind of definitions you would have
to contain in order to attract into your
life ideas that would seem to stop you
that's what they're there to show you
they are mirrors mirrors of the ideas
you believe yourself to be most strong L
understand yes does this assist you yes
well thank you very much thank you very
now may I ask you a question why of
course oh thank you do you feel when you
talk about this idea a strong burning
excitement in the pit of your solar
plexus uh it's somewhere between my
solar plexus and my heart all right
close enough allow yourself to feel that
enough allow yourself to feel that
sensation as often as you can in other
words get excited about the idea of the
changes you say you prefer to make feel
it on your physical being in your
physical body feel that Rush of energy
let it spread throughout your entire
body what you call on your planet the
Goosebump effect let it spread through your entire
effect let it spread through your entire
body become inspired become excited when
you allow that energy to spread you are
literally literally changing the
cellular structure of your body
throughout from within you are elevating
your energy accelerating your energy
upwards that's what that sensation is
you're taking yourself to another level
you're operating on higher energy so
when you see things you desire let
yourself get inspired let yourself get
excited feel that in your solar plexus
the chakra of intention feel it feel the
conviction let it spread and then know
that when you feel that energy when you
feel that sensation you are not at the
same energy level you used to be you
have completely changed yourself you are
a completely different person operating
on a completely different level who now
has more access to more energy to create
more change understand yes well thank
you very much thank you very much
sheding
by the way these ideas are not simply
philosophical issues we are talking
physics we are talking mechanics we are
talking the allowance of physiological
change as you understand it sharing hi
hello b a good day to you good day to
you too speak up so that all may share
my name is Rebecca all right if you say
so yes well at least at this time yes um
I had a series of events that I think is
somehow all linked up all right and I'd
like to share describe the synchronicity
to all of us okay uh just before the
conversions I moved into a new apartment
all right and as I at night time just
around dusk until just before the Sun
would rise I would look out and up along
the side of the Hill there was like a
triangular shape um and it had three lights in each
shape um and it had three lights in each
corner and it was like just white pure
light guys and I I would see this no
matter what time of night whether it was
3:00 in the morning or you know five it
would always be in the same position
during the day there was nothing
there I there was no structure there was
no way for any ref understood okay I had
a sense that maybe it was some craft or
something like that continue okay after
the conversions I started to uh which I
went to chichin for all right and was on
the pyramid and I started having a lot
of different uh experiences opening up
to me and a lot of acceleration of my
energy F uh in November just before November I
F uh in November just before November I
was doing a meditation where I saw
myself in like in the
universe in the universe and all of a
sudden I was with a group of other light
beings or yes light beings
like they were at this huge table or
like a a galactic table or something
like that and I came to them and they
all there was a lot of love a lot of uh
beautiful energy and welcoming it was
like welcome home we're glad you're here
and then I was taken over to a seat
where I sat there and they individually
came over and gave and um said hello or
exchanged energy it was like a welcoming
yeah and an identification okay of energy yes
and an identification okay of energy yes
then just in November I went to a
medicine real gathering with the Native
American uh Indians out in Malibu and
just before that experience I saw myself
again at this Galactic type uh table I
was in my Association convergence yes
okay and then what happened was I saw
myself like a light go from that
image an energy go all the way down into
the center of the earth and it was like
just this huge stream of energy from
there and how did you feel I felt great
specifically um well I felt that did you
feel like the Earth could you identify
more strongly with it yes all right
continue and I also felt that it was
some form of healing yes that I'm here
to do as well but as all of you are yes
right correct but there was some other
link still to this this other connection
outside of the all right what do you
want to do with all of these energies
and realizations how will you not act will
realizations how will you not act will
you act differently now after these
realizations and connections than you
did before and if so
how um well I think that I'm acting yes I am
um well I think that I'm acting yes I am
acting different all right and and I'm
acting um more in a state of Truth and
centeredness all right do understand
that all that you are experiencing to
some degree is a telepathic contact that
is becoming more and more and more solid
to many of you because you are beginning
to realize that physical reality in a
sense is only the combined product of
your Collective imagination anyway so
our telepathic contacts with each and
every one of you can begin to take on
more and more what you would call real
qualities and you are seeing into
different dimensions of reality the idea
of the trary formation is not something
that really existed in your dimensional
reality as a physiological object but it
was representative of a gate shall we
say of a relationship shall we say
rather than a spaceship a
relationship in that sense that you were
interpreting an energy form were being
shown as a mirror to activate certain
ideas within you to allow you to release
yourself to form that identification
telepathically astrally as you say with
the association energy so that you could
then identify strongly yourself as
representative of Earth and
representative with Earth to identify
with the very heart of the crystal of
your planet to accelerate your ability
to be of assistance at this time it is
like checking in and saying all right
here is the job I have chosen to do do
as a part of the council as a part of
the association this is who I am you are
saying this is my energy this is how I
want to be of assistance I am checking
in shall we say accelerating my energy
forming an alignment and taking that
alignment back with me you are saying to
the place what I have chosen to be of
assistance and accelerate that
assistance now you are simply
recognizing agreements you have set up
from a long time ago you are recognizing
your timing now unfolding and taking you
to a new level you have accelerated
yourself in that sense uplifted yourself
to another notch shall we say and on
that level you can simply have conscious
awareness of the fact that you are
telepathically linked to many beings as
all of you are it is simply that most of
you don't know that because most of you
have been operating on an unconscious
level walking in your sleep so to speak
now you are waking up as many
individuals on your planet are waking up
and you realize there are many more
conversations going on than you
thought are you having a good time yes
Does this sufficiently answer your
question uh yes but it brought up one
other question all right okay I was told
recently that um that all this process
that I was going through was because of
an agreement that I made yes as we have
said you are remembering your agreements
right and I was also told that I made
another agreement that at during the
time period of the 25th to the 1st of
this um
month that I would be asked again
whether or not I would know what my per
my specific additional purpose was and
that I would be asked again whether or
not I wanted to make that agreement all
right and so so I I guess I'm asking for
confirmation in regards to that
information there is no confirmation I
can give you okay allow yourself simply
to understand there are many other
things that will unfold within your
Consciousness yes there are many other
ideas or levels to the overall agreement
and there will be many more for you to
discover as you unfold not just one
specific one but the more you accelerate
the faster you accelerate the faster
those recognitions and remembrances will
come understand yes now remember once
again these specific purposes these
specific missions in life are not the
purpose of your life they are the
methods by which you can express the
purpose of your life which is the same
for all of you to be the fullest
possible being you can be that's the
purpose of your life any way you choose
to go about it those are the methods
through which you express the purpose of
your life the mission of your life you
understand mhm so your unfoldment will
take place in perfect
timing live spontaneously live in the
moment it will all be revealed in
perfect timing you will not miss
anything you can't miss anything right
relax enjoy thank you very much thank
you very much
sharing hello B and good day to you um I
don't have any difficulty finding things
to get excited about oh thank you very
much neither do
I but I do uh occasionally I get too
many irons in the fire oh and um kind of
tend to lose sight of the ones that I
really get excited about and and uh
sometimes get my attention split up in
too many ways all right now it may
simply be a
matter of having bought into the
idea that in knowing the direction that
really excites you that you have to pay
attention to all the details and make
sure they're all going to fit in order
to get the thing that really excites you
instead of relaxing into the knowledge
that when you focus on your strongest
intention everything else that is less
exciting than that may be still exciting
but less exciting than that is going to
be now represented as one of the details
that falls into place that backs or
shall we say reinforces the most
exciting thing in your life and
therefore you don't really have to watch
all the details as closely as you have
been you don't necessarily have to walk
down every Corridor thinking that if you
don't watch every single step of every
single Corridor that you will somehow
not allow them to come together in
perfect alignment to reinforce the thing
that really does excite you the most is
this making some sense definitely the
idea simply is that many of you can find
yourself juggling many different things
and not having enough hands to do it
because you think that you have to pay
attention to all the details and you
have to control all the details and make
sure that all the details are doing
exactly so and so and such and such at
exactly this and that time or everything
else will fall apart instead of
realizing that if you simply aim for the
strongest intention all the details fall
into place automatically fall into love
automatically reinforce each other
perfectly and all create with them the
appropriate amount of time and timing to
be dealt with by you and can be touched
lightly in that sense and effortlessly
in that sense and will contain all the
momentum necessary to support the things
that are really the strongest intentions
and the strongest levels of excitement
in your life you don't have to watch all
the
methodologies understand got it so
consolidate in that sense into your
definition of what it is that really is
the most exciting thing out of all of
these let the others then become the
details that support it and act at any
given moment upon that which you really
can act upon that is the most exciting
thing everything else will fall into
place sometimes you create these other
avenues thinking that you actually even
need them to support the thing that
excites you the most and you don't at
least not necessarily in that way yes
does this assist you takes a lot of
pressure off oh thank you very much when
you take the pressure off you expand
naturally thank you thank
you
sharting hello fishar and good day to
you um I'm not quite sure what my
question is but I oh that's all right
good um um first of all is there a
difference between telepathy and
channeling depends
what you call telepathy what we have
coined as
tathy is basically the
idea of forming a strong
identification let's say for now in this
example between two
individuals it is not the direct reading
of another's mind as many of you
mythologically think the idea simply is
is that when you form a strong
identification with someone you begin to
match their frequency because everything
is fre quency everything is a vibration
of the Primal energy different
frequencies of the same energy when you
begin to identify strongly with another
individual you begin to vibrate at their
frequency when you vibrate at their
frequency you manifest the same type of
thought patterns through your
Consciousness that they manifest through
theirs and when you do it strongly
enough you manifest these thought
patterns at the same time in the same
way and that makes it seem as if you are
reading each other's thoughts what
you're actually doing is being perfectly
reflective mirrors of each other in
slightly different very similar ways you
have the same thoughts at the same time
now channeling to some degree is much
the same
idea in that you form a
strong Universe you create a model of
that which you identify with and so seem
to be channeling something else when in
a sense what you are doing is forming an
IDE identification with something else
and channeling your own energy as a
mirror image of that idea you are
identifying with so in a sense the
mechanism is very similar it just
depends on whom or what you are
identifying with that determines what
comes through and in what way it comes
through the idea therefore is why we
always say that channeling fundamentally
is simply doing anything you really love
to do and letting it through in a
creative expressed way without doubt
without worry because the idea is that
the strongest vibration of
identification is love that's why
individuals that you say are in love
very often are the ones that more often
are not exhibit the idea of reading each
other's thoughts knowing what another
individual is going to say before they
say it because they are thinking the
same thing at the same time because
they're on the same frequency on the
same wavelength so they're creating the
same patterns
that's telepathy that's channeling
that's psychic functioning it's all of
those things in slightly different
manifestation methods of expression you
follow me yes thank you very much oh
thank you does that clarify the issue to
some degree yes it does so well thank
you okay I had one other thing that went
along with that was um uh I had a dream
the other night and um I had written a
book uh and the thing that was most
exciting to me about it was the idea
that um I could have actually gotten
this story from a dolphin oh yes story
you interact many of you many many many
many of you now interact with Dolphin
Consciousness since they are the other
shall we say sensient species upon your
planet the other alien life form aside
from humans and they are blending with you
humans and they are blending with you
because they are highly tele empathic
and they share many of your dream states
with you and you go on Many Adventures
in your dreams with them you are one
society and in a sense One race in your
dreams it is simply that in physical
terminology you have two different types
of body
expression yes but is it possible to
actually understand uh telepathically a
Dophin absolutely with us because the
idea then is that there are no language
barriers in that sense no real
differences because you are the same
type of Soul
absolutely and many of you do all the
time and have conversations all the
time so if you find yourself inspired by
that energy now realize many of them are
interacting with all of you let the
inspiration through in any way that
serves all concerned in a joyous way
okay and if you wish you can even
physicalize the idea by going down to
your oceans and walking into their
environment and accepting their
invitation to go and play
physically because that is what they
desire now for many of you
to equalize your societies for even
though we have described once again
beforehand the idea of the neighborhood
of all the different you would call
alien civilizations in the Stars around
you the closest alien civilization to
you is on your very own Planet the
Dolphins and the
whales you are a planet with two
different alien species right together
on one
world understand yes this happens from
time to time and you have created it on
your planet as
well it is not that uncommon that there
is more than one species On Any Given
Planet so go and play if you
wish I will thank you very much
sharing hello Bashar and to you good day
um I'm excited this uh Monday Henry and
I are going to be going to Zion all
right then Wyoming and on the way back
through Sedona all right and I'm also
anxious because I anxious I have an
opportunity uh to move to Wyoming if I
choose yes and I wanted to ask you um
since you know the agreement that Henry
and I uh since
I uh since
you there may be aspects of the idea of
the agreements you have made that we can
perceive but it is not up to us to
absolutely unfold all those agreements
in front of your face for you though um
and from the energy that you pick up in
my being yes do you see Wyoming as a
positive place for our interacting
together can be one of the places we see
that there are a few others that may be
equal in scope however are you
any any any any any any are you in any
way shape or form under any amount of
pressure to make a
decision I've chosen to be uh to feel
myself under pressure why what's the
rush well I feel like it's time for me
to make a career uh shift or go back
into being a fashion designer all right
and it doesn't really excite me and yet
at the same time um yes I feel like I'm
in a limbo state to a sense all right
then give yourself a little time to see
in that sense what becomes most obvious
to you you're not under any rush in that
sense mhm the anxiety is only the doubt
so take take the time in the limbo state
to explore the doubt find out what
definitions you have that are creating
the doubt transform the anxiety back
into excitement when it transforms back
into excitement there will be no doubt
and the decision will be obvious so it's
all in the timing of course uhhuh if you
find that you are having anxiety then
obviously there may be a few other
things you need to look at take the time
to look at them transform them back into
excitement and then it will be obvious
which way to move do you see our
stopping through Zion or s know as being
a powerful place for us at this
time now may I ask good question
sure if I said no would you believe me
no cuz I'd still go thank you then why
ask okay you already in other words know
what you're going to do you know in that
sense what the strongest inclination is
within you so why ask okay you are
self-empowered you know what you want to
do do it I have one last question all
right um two weeks ago Henry was in
Wyoming and I was in Los Angeles and it
was a Saturday night we both woke up at
3:00 in the morning very suddenly dingly
awake yes yes yes and something very
powerful seemed to go on and the next
thing we knew it was 7:00 in the morning
and even though we were in different
states that day we he flew to Los
Angeles and we shared that we seemed to
feel we were transported elsewhere well
in a sense yes what you actually
did was create a tunnel between you and
in that tunnel your time sense was
shifted drastically you had created to some
drastically you had created to some
degree what can be called a temporal
Vortex and you moved yourself through
that tunnel let's say jumped through
that tunnel in time
understand yes what was the purpose of
this to connect to connect but that's
not all would you care to share anymore
all would you care to share anymore
no thank you very much just
understand that you now
have this type of shall we say vacuum
say vacuum
conduit between you you have established
an equilibrium of electromagnetic energy
in a particular way between
you you have flipped your switches
on when you pass through the
electromagnetic fields of
Zion and
Sedona there may be some
interesting polarizations of that field
that will accelerate you
greatly you are now in a sense a live
wire
and you are now in a sense passing
through an electric
field that is going to create a
particular type of magnetic momentum
that will now allow you to begin to
really let's say
slip and become very Loosely attached to
the notion of SpaceTime in your physical
reality understand yes I do I am being
in your terminology cautious
about what I am
saying in the sense that I do not want
to create too much anticipation of
particulars and at the same time I want
you to
understand that you know what you're
doing even though it is not all on a
conscious level right
now you're going to be going on a little
bit of a wild
ride but ride with the
wave it'll be all
right this is your true opportunity
to really express the
idea of true magnetic
awareness and
Trust there will be some very strong
increase in dream communication for you
from various shall we say
sources now that your switch is open
you will be receiving many things allow
them to fall into place in the
appropriate pattern in the appropriate
timing as you simply move through the
field according to your imagination your
excitement and your conviction you will
sweep up all the information you
need until you truly take yourself to a
new cycle I cannot speak about that
cycle I cannot speak about that
now you've shared a lot thank you you
very much we thank you and have a
wonderful time discovering all the
surprises thank you mishar I love you
our love to you as
well sharing hi Bashar good day to you how
sharing hi Bashar good day to you how
are you perfect and you I'm very good oh
thank you for those that are in your
terms new the terminology of saying we
are perfect does not mean we do not
change or grow or learn it simply means
that we recognize that at any given
moment any particular being is an
absolutely perfect version of whatever
it's being at that moment and that you
don't in a sense truly become more
perfect you just become perfect in a
different way continue I'm more perfect in a
way continue I'm more perfect in a
different way now thank you I'm real
excited about a project I'm working on
no all right do share with all
excitement excitement and projects speak
up and be bold an Interstellar guide
book Interstellar guide book all right
yeah and I'm assuming because I'm
excited about it that the timing is is
right no all right and it would be
basically the timing is correct for
whatever information you will be able to
receive to put it together yeah do not
forget one of the primary focuses is
upon your own Planet as well right don't
forget to include yourself on the
map yes
continue um I was just wondering if you
had any suggestions I mean I'm happy
enough to just follow my excitement all
right well we to some degree have given
you a little bit of a list this evening
of your time of some of the individuals
that would be in that guide book right
could you give a description of say
epsilon Indie and the other not at this
time in your near future yes not at this
time and it will be given by another not
me I don't suppose you'd give me any
information about the
other the other will be referred to as
simply the
galactic it will not be a physical being
as you know
it
okay it will come through this channel
but it will not be
me okay okay and I had
um the past week and a half or
so I felt as though I woke up one
morning and I felt as though another
excuse me aspect of myself had come into
myself all right that you have expanded
the idea and the definition that you are
an acceler ated yourself into a new
persona yes thank you and I walked down
the street and I was very surprised that
there was only one son as opposed to two
I understand the feeling
sometimes and since then I felt I have
felt that there has been communication
from stop our suggestion to you for now will
stop our suggestion to you for now will
be to go scouting through your Star
Charts if you have not already done so
with the ID in mind of what you call
your Galactic guide book and see what
ideas of Stellar systems really attract
you maybe as a hint the red and the
blue we shall see okay thank you very
much we thank you very much pleasant
dreams
Shing good evening and to you good day
um for for recent years I've been um
having the most Vivid vivid dreams yes
and just recently I sort of get part one
and part two and they sort of tell
stories and I'm not quite sure what I
meant to do with them I mean they're
very very Vivid well are they enjoyable
they're very enjoyable do you feel like
writing them down I asked the question
in the dream should I get up and write
this down or will I remember yes and
usually I will remember and so the next
day I do sometimes write the all right
do you feel like sharing those stories
with other individuals in that written
format um not really no all right what
would it excite you to do with the
information in the stories then well I
don't really know I just write them down
maybe they're going to have some
interests for me in years to come I
don't quite know what I meant to do with
them oh all right sort of information
that I it is information all right may I
ask you what does excite you then it
excites me that I have these dreams I
love them yeah I mean I almost prefer
them to the day ah then that's one very
strong clue for you and the clue is to
allow yourself to begin to transform
your physical reality what you call the
day into more of an understanding that
you are dreaming right now very Vivid is
it not yes this is a dream your physical
reality is a dream literally a dream a
particular type of dream with a
definition of solidity and focus in a
very particular way it is a dream
nonetheless and not really much
different than the other dreams that you
have one of the things you can do is to
allow that information to allow you to
begin to create less of a distinction
between your physical reality and what
you call your non-physical dream
state one
moment you have been many times in other
lives very very instrumental in the
aiding and assisting of the blending of
trans transformation from physical
reality to non-physical reality you have
helped many individuals through the
death process many times you are in that
sense literally a dream Keeper in that
sense you have acted in many lives as
the idea of facilitators from one
dimension to another dimension and you
have done this from both sides aiding
individuals who are physically dying
into the non-physical aiding individuals
in the non-physical who have just died
to acclimate in that way you are in that
sense a Dream Weaver a dream keeper a
dream spinner in that sense you have a
very strong notion of the idea of the
blending of the physical and the
non-physical you can use this in many
different ways it is really up to you in
terms of discovering how it is you
really wish to use this idea you have
used it in many ways you can use it in
many ways again you can tell stories you
can in that sense amuse the children you
can in that sense allow your dreams to
aend individuals that are making
transitions from physicality to non-
physicality you can in a sense by
sharing those stories allow individuals
to change their lives drastically by
hearing the ideas presented in the
dreams you can even Aid and assist other
individuals to allow themselves to
experience dreams in that Vivid manner
that you do you can and have been many
times what you would call A Healer in
that sense very strong at working with
color you have worked with the idea of
crystals many times but I would remind
each and every one of you once again
that of course all these ideas you call
crystals even though they have power and
can funnel power through them are simply
catalysts and triggers for your own
power they are mirrors of who and what
you are you have been very powerful in
many different lives in that way it is
up to you it is up to you as to how to
express these stories you have also in
many different lives experienced the
idea of shamanism especially in what you
call your Native American culture where
the telling of stories was the way of
preserving the heritage of what you
would call the history of the people on
your planet you have been a Storyteller
for quite some time there have been
times when you have been wandering
Minstrel going from town to town as you
say telling of the stories and bringing
of the news in that sense you're very
familiar with the weaving of tales and
now and then in some of the lives you
have woven Tales to your own ends that
were not necessarily in your terms as
true as they could have
been you have used this idea in many
different ways in many different
capacities at many different times it is
completely up to
you now in whatever way really gives you
the most Joy now it is really up to you
was to what to do with those Tales
perhaps the idea of the review we have
shared with you from our perception of
your energy has perhaps sparkk some
inspiration within you and can perhaps
move you in a particular direction but
that's up to you you are the captain of
your ship and you have been at the
tiller many times you have many tales of
far distant land
and you are still visiting them even
though your hand may now be at a tiller
of a different sort on a ship of a
different sort sailing a different sort
of dream
see is any of this being of assistance
to you wonderfully well thank you very
much thank you very much may your sales
always be full of
wind sharing hello B Andre you good day
good day it's absolutely thrilling to be
here with with you and I just want to
thank you for being available we thank
you and are always Overjoyed to share
with each and every one of you I've been
so delighted with the interaction that I
have with you and in most of the cases
my interactions with you are not here on
the as a physical Channel we understand
there is energy always from our
Collective Association civilizations
being beamed to your planet for your
imagination to tap into in whatever way
shape or form you wish to have you been
happy about the interaction with
yourself yes thank you very I wanted to
ask you how how does that work what what
creates that spontaneity we have talked
about the idea already of tath linkages
of forming an identification of becoming
a particular frequency that by
definition will automatically put you on
the same level as something with a
similar frequency so you can
spontaneously interact that is why most
of the idea of telepathy and psychic
functioning happens only spontaneously
and not on command because the idea is
that you are always switching your
channels around you are always scanning
for different ideas that relate to you
at any different moment you are always
having a different degree of intensity
of focus on different subjects at any
particular time so you will simply
spontaneously key into what you really
need to that represents the vibrational
frequency you on at any given moment it
is not something that you necessarily
want to regulate that heavily because
that would remove the spontane and in a
sense remove the basic structure or
methodology for the living of life in
its full emotional awareness you
understand I think so it's the the
excitement that's created in that
interchange yes is is the
structure the excitement is
representative of the vibrational energy
of the structure yes of the level you
are on okay that I I also have another
question you you do all of this so
spontaneously well thank you how is it that you that
well thank you how is it that you that
you arrive here every Thursday night at
8:00 it is not in your terminology quote
unquote Thursday night at 8:00 to me the
idea of what time is for us is not
exactly the same as it is for you simply
we also function so spontaneously and
synchronicity that no matter when in
your terms the session needs to take
place I am always available at exactly
the same timing no matter what the time
is for me in that sense and we do not
really keep track of time and also
sometimes these interactions do not
happen in your terms at the same time
sometimes to put this very colloquially
this interaction can be happening shall
we say last week for me I simply will
project myself to whatever area of time
I know the interaction needs to take
place for
you understand so we are always slipping
understand so we are always slipping
around
always slipping through time in that
sense do understand we have made a
foundational agreement with the channel
to be always linked and connected to the
intentions of the flow that is going on
on your planet so when we simply feel
the flow we will always respond in that
sense it may not in your terminology be
at the same time in a parallel notion
okay yeah the reason I asked you that is
to get an idea of how you do that
because I always seem to be out of sync
in a lot of ways with what I do so what
I need to do from what I'm hearing you
is to
um to be more open to my own flow of
energy well in a sense remember this you
are never any of you really out of sync
right you are always perfectly in
synchronous harmony with the strongest
definitions of reality you buy
into understand yes so as you change the
definitions of what your reality is and
what it's capable of being you then
synchronize with that and begin to have
the experiences that go hand in hand
with the nature of your new
definition our civilization simply has
an extremely shall we say loose
definition of time and space therefore
we can slip here and there in and out
you see we know that physiological
reality is within our imagination
and yet at the same time we know that
our imagination is real so in a sense it
could be said that I am imagining that I
am having this conversation with you but
I know my imagination is real so I also
know this conversation is going on
understand yes yes is this making any
sense it does um do understand that
actually many of you do this with
yourselves all the time sometimes the
quote unquote voices you hear within
your mentality is actually your own
future self Whispering back to you
okay what what I'm doing that I prefer
not to keep creating is that I keep
committing myself to things that when
the moment occurs like if I commit
myself to be here next Thursday at 8:00
then I'm finding that when that time
arrives I would rather spontaneously be
doing something else what is your
definition of
commitment um it's an agreement that's
co-created with a structure of time
space why does it have to contain a
structure of time and
space well an agreement can be an
agreement without it how about an
agreement with an understanding of the
appropriate timing rather than
timing rather than
time I'm not sure I could get away with
that it it seems that it is not something to
it it seems that it is not something to
get away with oh it is an expression of
the trust that if you know that you are
acting to the best of your ability with
the fullest Integrity you can must and
that what you are doing is not the
result of running away from something
you're not willing to face then you can
also trust that everything will fall
into place in perfect timing and that
when you really need to be somewhere you
will be and when you don't you won't and
that the agreement you have made as long
as you are open in your communication
keeping the lines open in that sense and
being the most honest you can be with
your integrity with all other
individuals involved with whom you have
made the agreement you can then begin to
see that all the events will fall into a
synchronous alignment and that when in
keeping with your integrity something
simply does not work out according to
the time frame it also will be exactly
what everyone else in that agreement
needs to experience and it will work out
perfectly in timing rather than
time understand yes I do timing is
simply representative of the definition
of the event no matter when in time that
happens okay is this a little clear
clear it's extremely clear thank you
very much well thank you very much for
the timely
conversation at this timing you may all
enjoy a brief break we will resume
contact in approximately 10 of your
minutes of counting how's everything how's everything
[Applause]
going and it say
[Music] continue good evening Bashar and he good
continue good evening Bashar and he good
day I'd like to thank you for the
sharing you
did uh to with Judy concerning that
conduit that she and I built we thank
you for creating it so that we could
shut it thank
you and the question I have in the
sharing um is one that's uh going to be one
um is one that's uh going to be one
moment each and every one of you
remember that everything you hear this
evening of your time applies to you as
well or you wouldn't be hearing
it apply it in whatever way it works
best for you in your imagination there
will be relative degrees of
applicability and different ways of
applicability but there are no accidents
and remember you are all one single
event and in a sense you are all one
single being talking to itself through
many
mouths continue this is an opportunity
for everyone to uh toh take a look at
where they stand in the idea of judgment
judgment inv validational judgment not
the Judgment of discernment
right we are talking about the idea of
invalidation judgment continue
okay I seem to have co-created a
situation uh in my life through my
interactions with uh an individual that
I chose to uh take into my home and my
place of uh uh business all right uh who
was in in a great need and I felt that
it could be a mutual learning experience
which it which it is you bet all right
can you simply in general terms Now
define the nature of the interaction as
we are assuming you are saying that it
does not match what you would prefer it
to right okay defying the
nature the situation that was created
was one where I felt
um abused slapped in the face and we not
talking about describing the
personal interpretation describe the situation
interpretation describe the situation
physically what is is the idea what is
the idea that was put out what do you
believe is the idea that has not been
met in that sense not the idea of the
personal reactions for the moment simply
describe the nature of the
situation okay um the
circumstances what are the circumstances
and what do you desire to change in the
circumstances well is it simply the idea
of the emotional interaction
the intensity of it when I perceive that
I am at one place and I react in in a
way that I actually didn't imagine that
I could ever react all right but now you
know you can I know so are you telling
me that what you have discovered in this
interaction is that you still have
buttons that can be pushed
you yes all right well now that you have
discovered those buttons do you desire
to have them pushed no all right then
now you can realize where those buttons
are you can redefine what is written on
top of them and now you do not have to
find yourself reacting in the same way
yes no maybe yes all right so you have
learned that that's one thing okay what
else well to experience something on on
an emotional level and a mental level
and then for me to then turn that into a
physical symbol for the other person
okay in a
reaction to me is I mean we're in we a
synthetic being and when that does not
mean you're not
natural just because your persona is a
creation doesn't mean you're not natural
though do not take the meaning that we
have used synthetic in that sense oh I
mean synthesized yes okay integrated
Blended Feud that's what I meant okay um
that in the moment when I reacted
physically I
um I actually was as at least as shocked
as the individual with all right but has
it helped you to realign the definition
of your integrity yes do you wish to
function that way
again no then don't but I hadn't wished
to function that way then all right but
the idea is simply now that obviously
something has been brought to your
conscious attention that you were
relegating to your unconscious
attention now that it is conscious now
you can decide consciously
decide why you used to react that way
and why you now no longer prefer to
react that way and that will make a
difference now that it has been brought
out in the open
understand mhm so all right you have
said it was a
surprise well now that you have
discovered it apply it in whatever way
represents the Integrity you say you
desire to
have understand yes and proceed from
there is not an issue of the idea of
guilt in that sense or regret in that
sense it is the idea of now what do you
do with the information you have
discovered do you in that sense sit
around and berate yourself and other
individuals adding to the negativity or
do you apply it in a positive way now
that you have discovered you had created
Yourself by that definition well I know
that there's a positive way to all right
for this to Now understand remember that
at any given moment you are a different
being so perhaps there have been in your
terms times when you did not contain
that particular idea but then having
attracted a certain situation to
yourself you simply chose to be the
being that did doesn't mean that you're
that being now but now you can examine
why you chose to be that being that
reacted in that way in that given
situation so you can determine whether
or not you will ever choose to be that
being again
consciously understand yes you can begin
in your terms to soothe and smooth the
whole idea out by first of all
acknowledging a that again this was a
co-creation that You' have attracted an
opportunity to see this aspect of
yourself that you are willing to
exemplify that you were willing to
personify in that sense to give you an opportunity
in that sense to give you an opportunity
to decide whether you wanted to
personify that particular aspect of the
total being you are
anymore so in that sense you can thank
the other being for providing that
opportunity and you can get all with the
business of expressing Integrity as you
choose to and move in your terms forward
in a positive way there is no need for
the idea of
Grudge mhm so any interaction
mhm so any interaction
even that type is always co-created
equally between individuals well of
course how can it be otherwise well
that's my feeling that's that's an issue
that we've discussed not you and I he
and I all right it does not necessarily
mean that you each have the same things
to look at mhm but it's always got to be
a co-creation it cannot be
otherwise it cannot be otherwise there
may be different meanings in it for both
of you different reasons for why it was
created things you have to look at
different approaches you can take
different resolutions but it's still a co-creation
resolutions but it's still a co-creation
for your own reasons even if your
reasons aren't the same even if what
you're going to get out of it isn't the
same still
co-created understand mhm is this of
assistance yes is it
sufficient maybe it's it's sufficient I just I mean
maybe it's it's sufficient I just I mean
I know I've been just yes the idea of
integrity and all a sudden I do
something like you know I participate in
this idea and I just all right all right
but again do not use it as a self
judgment remember this all of you have
existed in a civilization that has
fragmented and fractionated you more
than you can even imagine
sometimes sometimes you have created
yourself to be so many pieces and so
many compartments that you really simply
have that many compartments to discover
about yourself well you are discovering
some so apply it in a positive way you
don't have to sit around in a days just
because it was
unexpected okay is up to you all right
all right yes is is there something that
um you could share with both of us
because I'm going to share this this uh
tape um with him some of it to some
degree is remnant of an old Business
Association to some degree there was a
grudge to some degree some of that steam
is being released now in certain
ways there have also been from time to
time familial
connections that in that lifetime were
not worked out to either of your
satisfaction and this it you're now
getting an
opportunity an opport Unity to allow
those things to work themselves through
okay there is no need to have a lover's
quarrel be it that even though in this
lifetime you are as you say male and
male that have been other lifetimes when
that was not so
so
okay it's clear enough
thank you one
moment we would
suggest that you pick what you might
call neutral territory for the
discussion that you both Define as
neutral territory all right all right
thank you very much thank
you
sharing hello bishar good day to you
good day to you um I just would like to
share a couple things I've oh I go right
ahead enjoyed uh the experience of
listening to you for past year we have
enjoy the experience of listening to you
all as well it has been an
[Laughter] experience I I really I really enjoy
experience I I really I really enjoy
your sense of humor and I feel that that
that's really what life is all about is
to enjoy it and uh I'm finding myself
um just experiencing the reality
of creating one's own
attitude um I find that I'm more and
more able to label experiences as
anything I choose to label them oh thank
you and also perhaps simultaneously
finding that you do not have to label as
many things at all yeah yeah it's it's
uh I just tend to enjoy things kind of
just kind of go along with oh me too and
uh it's kind of fun there's an exciting
kind of
fun well you know I mean I can also
label things as with conditions as well
um exciting thing going on all right is
that uh I and a friend are buying house
and all right I'm kind of interested in
that and uh things seem to be developing
I have had absolutely no
um uh what's the word um
plan well yeah no no no anxiety about it
it's like I was just totally able to
have whatever came came down it was like
oh very good if we're if if it's
supposed to happen it's fine I'm excited
about thank I can make sometimes it is
the plans that create the anxiety
because then the plans are not met and
oh no everything's falling apart yeah I
I'm I'm finding that that's I it's it's
enjoy this is enjoyable because buying a
house is supposed to be one of the most
stressful things in the world right yeah
it says so right
there and it's interesting I creating a
lot less stress with it than I create in
other areas of my life where I Define a
lot of this must happen or else I will
be upset kind of thanu and uh thanku
fangu fangu so I just wanted to share that
fangu so I just wanted to share that
with you and and and I'm curious if you
could uh perceive any energy regarding to the
uh perceive any energy regarding to the
my relationship with the person I'm
buying the house with and there is
nothing we can comment on at this time
except that we will as always send you
energy that can be put toward your house
Waring well thank you Bashar well thank
you very much I do appreciate it good
Shing hello B and good day to you I find
myself interested in many many things of
the many many yes the crystals channeling
channeling
Sedona this a million different things
million different things yes but I don't
seem to focus in on any particular thing
no all right some of you are learning to
be generalists now rather than
Specialists and that in and of itself
can be one thing in a sense depends upon
how you approach it how you look at it
and to what purposes quote unquote you
apply it
it's up to you are you having a good
time I'm having a good time but it
doesn't U yes seem to uh yield any
career out of it so to speak I see you
know it seemed like I came to this
period of time because of the excitement
all right now now yes now many of you arrive
right now now yes now many of you arrive
at that particular timing and expect to
find an obvious in an age of inventing
your
own can you invent something new out of
everything you have learned can you
bring all the things that excite you
together into a career that maybe
doesn't exist
yet how about the career of creating
careers that's a possibility all right
that's one
idea it all depends on how you look at
it again watch your
definitions be very clear about whether
you have expectations in a certain line
because many times you will have and
then you will understand that you may
actually be proceeding in an opposite
direction so to speak from the way you
really say you enjoy moving if you find
that no career makes itself obvious in
the midst of a situation that seems like
it ought to then recognize in many cases
it is simply up to you to create create
the meaning and the
definition of the circumstances to suit
you to suit the expression you are so
invent a
career that's how any of them get
started to begin with someone had to
invent them to begin with someone had to
be
first maybe you can invent a new career
mean there's not a catalog around
somewhere in your imagination there is
yes and it is completely
unabridged is this of any help some some
all right anymore any more I think one
thing I run into oh run into like a wall
we've run into you know the different
fractured parts of ourselves talking
about what have you run into is the fact
of not trusting myself oh you trust
yourself you mean not trusting yourself
positively um Everybody trusts thems
um Everybody trusts thems
completely it's a matter of whether you
trust yourself positively or negatively
you all always trust yourselves
completely there is never never never
never a lack of trust never perhaps not
perhaps not having confidence that it
will work out be another expression of
trust I guess absolutely why would you
assume that something that really
attracts you would be pointless enough
to not work out
[Laughter]
not yet it hadn't on yet I'm still
working on it all right the idea is very
simplistic if you look at it that way
for every expression there is an
appropriate stage in which to play out
that expression if something excites you
then you can assume beyond the shadow of
a doubt that there must be a stage for
you to express yourself upon Express
that excitement of on there is no
creation no expression that does not
have an outlet for its expressiveness
therefore you can trust that what
excites you will be able to be played
out because there are no extraneous
Creations there are no one-sided
polarities in that
sense every expression has an outlet
attracted to you the only reason you
would keep it away and keep it
unapparent is by assuming that the
expression you are doesn't have an
outlet so you will create it to be ambiguous it
so you will create it to be ambiguous it
will hide within you and you won't find
it you won't see it in an obvious way
things will become as you say foggy in
that sense you will not see the obvious
Outlet because you do not necessarily
believe that there is one for what
really inspires you but there has to be
by definition otherwise the universe
would in your terms be
lopsided there are no Creations that
cannot expresss in the way that
represents the fullest measure of who
and what they are everything fits or it
wouldn't exist understand yes is this helping you
exist understand yes is this helping you
to choose the direction in which you can
put your
trust well I think I have to look at my
imaginary catalog and see where the
various attractions all right correlate
then when you find one that you would
enjoy purchase a ticket for that
attraction and go on the
ride it will always take you exactly
where you need to
go does that
help beginning all right good place to start
beginning all right good place to start
yes thank you very much thank you very
much
sheding hello Bashar good day to you uh
I had something happened to me that I've
been curious about for and it happened
well 17 years ago all right what is it
that happened through you well I was was
uh sitting in a bakery with a friend of
mine having donuts and coffee over in
Hawaii donut and coffee all right and uh
we both were talking about the idea of
different types of bodies just I don't
know why but it was an interesting
subject the time do you mean different
types of human bodies uh just different
types of bodies that one could inhabit
oh all right and uh what happened is I
started to perceive his body and my own
as like cats large cats all right and he
perceived the same thing yes and there
was no drugs or anything invol and there
was there was
real all right we understand I've not
been able
to it didn't seem like a past life or
anything what are you paying attention
when we talked about
identification when we talked about
telepathy when we talked about matching
each other's vibration and therefore by
definition experiencing exactly the same
type of expression at exactly the same
time oh yes well can you apply it to
this idea I can see why that would
happen but it was uh like the whole
physical reality took on a different
absolutely when you change your
perspective that which you create with
your perspective must
change your physical reality is only the
product of your
perspective great would uh certainly fit
oh yes it is whatever you dream it to be
and if you dream it in accord with
someone else you will usually see it in
a similar fashion do remember that what
you call the
feline in your Society is usually
symbolic of being able to see in more
than one dimension at the same time
anyway and when you talk about how you
say the big
cats then you're talking about a lot of
power a lot of change yeah it was a
little bit scary we both stopped oh all
right but at the same time it was very
fascinating yes well thank you very much
for looking into a
mirror and allowing your friend to do
the same shedding
hello B and you good day I um I'm
overwhelmed being up here in front of
you anyways why uh it's just
me little old
me I I feel little thin white skin bald
159 year old me
feel more at ease yes I do thank you I
you I
uh I would like to know more about my
ability to love the tools that are
available to me to to love my my your
ability to love well it's the same as
everyone else's it can be unconditional
it can be you all have the same ability
to love because you're all made out of
love it's the prime vibration of
existence that's why when you align with
it you're in synchronous Accord with
existence itself with all that is with
the one the infinite that's what love is
the prime frequency of
creation out of which you are all
crystallized so your ability is in that
sense quite
Limitless now in whatever way you choose
to express it with your integrity and
your excitement that's really up to the
individual you have chosen to be with
your free will and your direction of
intention and your conscious commandment
and your decision-making
capability it's really up to you that's
why we talk about excitement so much
because excitement is the key is the
arrow that points you in the direction
of the way you can express your love
most unconditionally because when you
follow what excites you the most you are
living an effortless life of joy and you
just can't help but spill over that
ecstasy and joy to everyone else because
you're having such a good
time is it all right to be that
simple yes anything
else do you feel that is
sufficient uh I don't know if that it's
probably uh that I'm not hearing what I
wanted to hear what did you want to
hear tell me what you want wanted to
here I um I guess I had some sort of
preconceived idea what I wanted to hear
well tell me what it is uh something
about the power of that's in me that I'm
able to I I feel as though I've tapped
into a power well yes and that power uh
and I know it's General when I call it
love yes but uh there's such a I get
such a good feeling inside when I yes
I'm able to communicate that didn't I
say that you probably did maybe like I
say I'm I might be a bit overwhelmed
being in front of you oh all right
underwhelm yourself for a
moment once again the feeling you feel
is being aligned with the prime
vibration of the infinite that's what
love is when you allow yourself to flow
that love through yourself when you
consciously recognize it you become
synchronistically harmonized to the fabric of existence
harmonized to the fabric of existence
itself that's the good feeling within
you that's what the that energy is that
Rush of alignment that love that
capacity that compassion that's what it
is the ability the recognition of your
ability to express in joyous ways all
that you have chosen to be with
integrity that's what it is you know you
have the capacity you can feel it so in
whatever way represents what excites you
the most and whatever way represents
your strongest intention and Integrity
Express it and you will be being a fully
realized facet of the
infinite let it flow through
you is that so
difficult no does this assist you yes
remember that you are only being
overwhelmed by what you are feeling
within yourself not by me you are
feeling your own energy it is simply
that we radiate a particular vibration
that each and every one of you has the
opportunity to match
and when you match it that's the energy
you feel you don't feel my energy you
feel your energy matching my
frequency that's what you're feeling
you're only being overwhelmed by you so
you can become familiar with it because
it's you after
all so own
it thank you well thank you very much
for a loving interaction had a wonderful
time
Shing hello I'm good day to you thank
you uh I talked to you a few weeks ago
yes oh you remember
um well since then yes I was having a
hard time with the idea about belief I
wanted to know what the secret was when
did you create him yes yes well after
that I realized part of my problem was
that belief in the past to me my beliefs
about belief were number one belief
worked for for people to a certain
degree no matter what they believed in
the other thing was I felt that when
people believed in something they did it
they were either turning over their
power to something or someone else some
people do yes and or they were too
stupid to figure it out
analytically those were my beliefs about
all right thank you you're okay very
clever very
creative you're all so very good at
creating definition oh yes and then I
since then so when I maybe you should
export
them well they're gone now oh so now
what I believe believes are has to do
with it's more I asked you what it was a
few weeks ago and you said it's a
definition I thought oh no I'm getting
one of these runaround again no no no it
was a very direct answer and that is
exactly what I realized that they are
yes but you know I hate to take anybody
a word for anything and um well by all
means do not I don't thank you I
appreciate that very much I know you do
thank you um so I I've been so excited
to share uh with everybody here uh
because I I speak to my version of you
all the time thank you and uh well not
all the time but frequently I understand
I thought I thought you were going to
catch me on that but I am giving you a
large leeway
now um I figure any catching that needs
to be done can now be done by you thank
you well at the time I I was explor the
whole idea about beliefs came up because
I I wanted to
experience Financial wealth and all I
kept seeing was this very in the future
for myself this very would be considered
Mass Consciousness wise rather crazy
crazy happy totally
poor fairy psychic woman that I was
totally Happ and I thought well that's okay but
Happ and I thought well that's okay but
you know I really I'm I'm ready to
change that
now and I realized something well I
realized a lot of things but and I want
to go one thing I realized is the reason
why I could not changed that belief now
was number one my ideas about beliefs
number two it was because I had the
belief that you could only be
spiritually wealthy or financially
wealthy you could not be both and being
better than the person who want to be
just financially wealthy um I chose
that nice
nice
um I'm just laughing me
too the other thing I realized is
that the I think it was the second time
I ever came to Bashar anyway I was was
really upset about
something anyway it I I spoke to darl
and he said well it seems to me like
you're more of someone that's from the
future than someone that's of the past
you know just speaking in time you know
time yes and since and I've been using
that as a tool and what I saw is that
that is true see I already was a very
happy psychic totally broke bag lady in
easy and I already did that so that's
why it was so hard for me to fight not
fight it but change it cuz it already
happened understood okay now since then
and then when I spotted the belief that
I could only be spiritually wealthy or
financially wealthy and I saw that I can
have it all and really
really and so what do you know what do
you know
no and um I wanted to um let's see just
second time's up oh
okay when I was talking to you a few
weeks ago I was saying well I you know
you were saying how to how one can
experience what it is they want to
experience and I said well I've done all
that and I'm not judging being poor is
bad and I'm and I'm making everything
equal and you know it's just going on
and on well I wasn't exactly lying to
myself but I did realize once I cleared
away all these other things is that
whenever I would get centered on an idea
or being poor was just as wonderful as
being wealthy I would always check to
see if maybe now I won the lottery or
you know okay I've got the idea now now
now where's the pay
it wasn't really there even though there
is the preference it was not equal to
the other things thank you so I realized
that very very sharp Discovery yes it
was great it was really really good the
other thing is
that for the last month this this person
that I knew uh she Jarred my whole
reality that's what friends are for
she charred my whole reality on that
idea of you can only be wealthy
spiritually or because I I I I didn't
know it but I had this idea that in
order to be wealthy you had to let go of
your integrity somehow we understand we
understand yes but here's this girl we
were roommates and she decided she
wanted to be a movie star well she'd
only acted in one high school
play and so she just started acting like
a movie started like being glamorous you
know kind of but all in a very playful
way yeah
right then when
I she already had a fan club before she
ever did anything
correct she got the major lead in a
major motion picture but I'm not
surprised and it was like it was
effortless she had an agent come to her
and said you know I'd really like to
represent you she said oh great are you
all catching
this and what's so funny that especially
have so many actors and actresses come
up here
see acting was a detail for her correct
so she just was being a movie star yes
and now she's got she's on a regular TV
series and she's done several emotion
pictures and you know it's just
great of course I couldn't understand it
at the time but but now you can and the
other thing that when you say act on it
act on
something I I was not comfortable with
that because I felt like I was lying I
understand but I am I am comfortable
with the idea of pretending or acting
like she did she just acted as if she
was a movie star not acting but I
understand pretending yes and it
happened yes
so now that I'm coughing here um you are
clearing oh
oh
um the other thing I realized about the
reality we a lot of times there's this
idea where someone will say well that's
not what I preferred or I didn't want
that I didn't know why that happened I
realize now that I'm not giving up my
belief to my higher self or anything
else that someone else or something else
is going to take care of it for me I
really do see now that anything I'm
experiencing right now is something that
that I've created and it's just
unfolding for me right now and that
beliefs are just the perimeters or the
rules or the or you could say the
limitations or whatever of of the way
that what I bought into in which I'll
play I'm going to play life like this
and I agree that I can't fly and I
agreed to this and I agree my hair won't
turn green and you know all these
things you know I'm changing them no
um uh and anyway so that that's pretty
exciting CU I didn't like the idea of
feeling kind of like oh yes I know you
know my higher St can do it you know
it's just not my way oh
F and the other thing is that the last
thing is that even now it is all
changing uh what I know what it is I
really prefer and I I can I can feel
what it is to experience the life that I
know is possible and somehow I feel like
it's already
happening in some way yes I have a very
hard time just saying it though like
like telling someone I I almost stutter
start coughing or whatever but it's okay
with me um but I do have the sense that
it's already occurring in in some
reality or yes
so I I started just relaxing more you
know like I already am thing even though
I may be experiencing something
different now I feel more at peace or
calm with it thank you very much for
having taken the opportunity to truly
look through that mirror to another
reality another world another dimension
of yourself the face that now can look
back is you in another f form in another
format in another
fashion we thank you for taking the
opportunity to Define your fear and
allow in the integration of that fear
your Consciousness to become truly truly
truly Crystal
Clear may we call you Crystal oh oh yeah
that' be great thank you well thank you
very much at this
timing now I extend to you our heart our light
now I extend to you our heart our light
our
energy our love our being and our
seed that will grow together in the
garden of your
lives I thank
you I share with you the dream that we
are together another dimension another
together another dimension another
Consciousness another way to see the
self is the same self seeing through a
different eye hearing through a
different ear and speaking with a
different mouth but all of the same body
body all of the Same
Soul the things that we share with you
may seem to be philosophy but are to us
reality we thank you we love you dreams
to your H and do not forget to join us
next week of your time and bring a bell
so that we may
play and raise the vibration
of love and
joy sweet
dreams warm
thoughts good day good day good day [Applause] w
how did everything go
[Applause]