I say how are you all this evening of
your time as you create time to exist.
[Applause] Allow us to begin this interaction this
Allow us to begin this interaction this
evening of your
time with the
entitlement
ignition. For it is now
timing to ignite that flame within your
minds. that flame within your hearts and
perhaps if you wish to ascribe any
degree of importance to something more
than anything else, then I shall say
most importantly that flame under your
feet and in your
hands, that which typifies that which
you do, the energies that you use in
your daily actions.
Ignition will deal with the idea now
that there is enough energy for you to
avail yourself of to very simply and
very effortlessly create the reality you
effortlessly create the reality you
prefer
physically. And ignition can be
described in perhaps what you may term
three phases of awareness.
The first will be
clear intention. For as you allow yourself to
intention. For as you allow yourself to
understand what it is that excites you
the most, as we have discussed many
times, you will recognize this goes hand
in hand with what may be termed your
intention in life. And the clearer your
intention, the more effortless and more
direct your manifestation.
Clear intention is simply getting in
touch with that which allows you to know
what you want to do in its essential form. The
form. The
motivation behind who you know yourself
to
be that which moves you that which
strikes the
code. Clear intention.
The second phase will be if you wish
humorously referred to as
3D. This will be definition desire and
deservability. The second phase clear
definition the absolute understanding
the clarity of vision of in what way by
what method you wish to express your
clear intention. In other words, how you
wish to be you, how you wish to be of
service, how you wish to express what
excites you, in what way, by what
methodology, by what design, by what
device? Definition. Now, this does not mean the
Definition. Now, this does not mean the
idea of expectation or overly
structuring your intention.
It is simply that the clearer the
definition of what methodologies
represent, the intention you have, the
more aligned they will
be, the more in accord they will flow
with each other.
Secondly, desire, strong and clear
desire, strong and clear
desire, which as we have discussed many
times is the activation principle of the
definition of the belief systems that
you have strong desire, the true emotional
have strong desire, the true emotional
knowledge that your definition and your
intention is you and that that is what
you desire to manifest. Remember that
sometimes even though many of you may
express a strong desire you say yes I
have a strong desire for such and such
to happen for my definitions and my
intentions to
manifest. Simply remember that sometimes
some of you have a stronger desire to
remain in the lifestyle you have already
created.
Allow yourself therefore to recognize
that it is the overriding desire, the
overriding definition which will allow the
definition which will allow the
manifestation to occur in your lives.
And remember that even though things may
seem to not
change, you are only
recreating over and over a new a
manifestation from the beginning that
may simply fall into the line of
continuity in such a way to make it
appear as if nothing new has been
created. But continuity is your
creation. You are always creating a new with your
You are always creating a new with your
desire. Even if you are creating a new
what appears to be the same old life,
you are still creating it in that sense
continuously to extend itself to carry
through the original momentum of
whatever definition is clearest to you,
of whatever intention is clearest to
you, and whatever emotion is strongest.
The true desire to change the life you
have or the true desire. That is why we
have always said the idea is that the
strongest belief andor fear that you die
with is usually where you will attract
yourself to in the non-physical reality
and therefore some of the same momentum
may still need to be straightened out.
There are even the possibility though
not so much anymore in your society that
individuals who have died do not even
know they have died.
That is what you typically used to call
hauntings. They simply think they are still
They simply think they are still
physically alive because they did not
know what to expect and in that sense
were very rooted to the idea of
remaining in their life physically and
eventually they are helped to realize
subtly bit by bit that they have in fact
become non-physical so they can reorient
themselves and choose what they prefer
from that moment forward.
Okay. Thank you. Thank you very much,
Shing. Yeah. Hi, Basher. Good day to
you. You just talked to Tweedle Lum, so
I must be Tweedled D. All right. Uh
there's a lot of fat between us, but I
won't discuss that.
Uh last time I talked to you, or you
talked to me, whatever the case is. Yes.
I said something and you made a comment
and when I was listening to the tape I
realized uh when we were discussing
about teleportation and the tone level
of myself have gone way down. Nice. And
my abilities got lowered after the
teleportation. You kind of agreed with
that and I was curious now uh what the
implication of that is or what it means.
The implication of agreeing with you.
No. Yes.
Uh I wait a minute wait a minute now. I
didn't look at it as you agreeing with
me. I looked at it as you said yeah
that's I kind of got the idea that you
said this is what usually happens not in
those words. That's what I wanted to
query on you. Uh it doesn't necessarily
seem to me that this has to be that. Oh
nothing has to be but as you define
yourself that defines your energy.
Uh would you say that so I could
understand it? If you define that you
are going
down, if you define in a sense that you
are somehow backing up or isolated, then
your energy will appear to decline in
its illusionary form simply to represent
the definition to reflect to you the
definition you are creating yourself to
be at any given moment. So if you feel
the energy to be going down then that is
simply a reflection of how you are
defining yourself that you are to some
degree removing yourself slightly in
your idea of yourself from the overall
flow of infinite creation creating an
isolation a cut off that allows your
meters to drop.
Okay. Yeah. Because I was kind of
looking it was more than just emotion.
And it was actually abilities and
awareness and a number of things that
all collapsed. Yes. But it's all
connected. It's all one thing. You see,
only your society and a few others make
the distinction truly between the
colloquialisms that we use in your
language of ability and emotion and
thoughts and beliefs. It is all one
thing. It is all one event. It is all
one act.
So in a sense if any one part goes down
in that sense it all does. Okay, that
makes sense to me. Yeah, thank you. It's
a good triangle. Okay, thank you very
much.
I recently worked on a television
commercial and all right. In this
commercial, we used a jet fighter plane
to race over a um Ferrari car and the
pilot crashed and was instantly killed
while shooting. And so I I've been
wondering um if he had an agreement with
the producers of that commercial and
with all of us to be witness to his
death generally. Yes. Generally in in
other words, in another life we In other
words, let us put it this way. Nothing
within your collective belief system
prevented that.
and a few individuals involved had a
very specific agreement for that
particular manifestation. The majority
of the individuals simply supported it
and allowed it to happen since it did
not conflict in that sense quote unquote
with their overall paths. They were
willing to at least support someone
else's specific agreements. Understand?
It is not that they had a specific
agreement with every single person
involved with a few. Yes. and then it
generally with everyone
else understand. Uh yes, but I'm curious
to how that relates to the other
question you just answered when you said
that sometimes people cross over and
they're very confused. Yes. Why would
would this pilot have been confused when
he crossed over? Depends on how he
crossed over with what intentions. In
other words,
individuals who are brought up to
believe certain things very
strongly may allow themselves to be
somewhat confused, as you say, when they
die and do not find those particular
manifestations that they expected to
find in the way they expected to find
them because they may not have been
aware of what beliefs they had
consciously. But their strongest beliefs
will usually
manifest. But if an individual for
example says that I am doing what
excites me and if someday I should go
out in a blaze of glory that will be
just fine will usually create for
themselves an opportunity to be very
aware very quickly of exactly what has
happened because they will in a sense
have been setting themselves up for it
by saying well I died doing what I
wanted to do. what gave me joy and they
were in a sense ready to die that
way if they had chosen to. So even
though there may be momentary confusion,
the overall definition they give to what
it
doing in life can allow them to set
themselves up so the confusion won't
last very long.
Understand? Yes. Okay. I I that answers
it pretty much. I'm just curious as if
if I was meant to be there to learn a
particular lesson.
If you were there, then you were meant
to be there for there are no accidents.
However, any particular event that
occurs can have relative degrees of
meaning to different
individuals, some more than most. So,
the easiest thing to do is to simply ask
yourself, well, what did that incident
allow you to examine? What is it you got
out of being there? What did you learn
about yourself by witnessing the choice
of someone else in that very bold
manner? How did it allow you to feel? What
How did it allow you to feel? What
chords did it strike? What did it bring
up from within you to the surface? All
those things are the reason for why you
were there because those are the things
you wanted to face about yourself to
integrate them within you no matter how
strong or subtle they are. Understand?
Yes, I do.
So, is that a simple thing for you to
do? Yes, I think it it helped me a lot.
All right. Thank you. Then thank you for
cocreating that particularly bold
expression. Thanks. And supporting that individual's
Thanks. And supporting that individual's
ability to in a sense do what they
desired to do in the way they desired to
do it according to the beliefs they most
strongly constructed in their lives.
All right. Yes. Thank you very much.
Well, thank you very much.
There is something else coming to you as
well. Can you elaborate one moment?
What is your given name? Jill.
We are scanning the symbols. One
moment. You are very strongly connected
to a network of consciousness upon your
planet that is of a specific type, of a
specific agreement, of a specific club,
I shall say. In a
sense, it is a network of bold
transition. The feedback from this and
other incidents that you have in that
sense participated in, witnessed in your
life is creating a shock wave within
you. And this is in no way, shape, or
form meant to be negative. Do not allow
the word to throw you. All right? Yes.
But the shock wave is one of
acceleration, of high speed in and of
itself. It is the high speed that
represents the connection that you have
to this particular network and your
place within it. Highly
accelerated transformation. Highly
accelerated transition. In our
perception, you have the ability to
explode like a
nova in many different areas all at
once. You do not need to find yourself
when and if this occurs to you to be
breathless. Let yourself understand it may feel
Let yourself understand it may feel
heady for a while,
but there will still be enough
atmosphere for you to keep your
head and you will still be able to keep
your feet on the ground no matter how
fast you move.
No more for now. Thank you. Thank you,
Bashar. Good evening. And to you good day. Uh,
Good evening. And to you good day. Uh,
my question is, I'm starting to write a
novel. All right. Are you excited? My
Yes. Yes. All right. Nervous. Excited.
Oh. Oh. Which? Both. Can't be. They are
both the same energy. One is positive,
one is negative. Versions of the same
energy. Anxiety. Excitement. You may
flip-flop back and forth, but it is
never both at the same time, except in
the blended sense. But then it wouldn't
feel like nervousness if it were
blended. Well, anyway, my my question is
I know I know I do. Go on.
Well, my question is uh I'm presuming
that I will be channeling this book and
uh my question is is there any further
processes that I need to adjust to or
need to ex stimulate to do any
processes? Now pay attention. Are you
paying attention? Yes. Any so-called
processes that you may discover are a
part of the
writing, not a precursor to it.
Understand? Yes. You are in that sense
channeling the moment you sit down and
write. No matter what comes out, if you
allow it to come through as what is
naturally representative of who you
are, the idea is to recognize that
whatever it is that does come through is
a part of the writing. Not that it will
necessarily wind up in what you would
call the book, but it is a part of the
writing. Do not segregate the idea of the writing
Do not segregate the idea of the writing
the book from the overall process of the
writing itself. You will know what needs
to be in the specific book and what
doesn't. But the process will be in the
writing itself. Of course, you don't
have to do anything beforehand. Just do
it. Just write. Everything that needs to
come out will come out. You will know
what belongs in the book and what
belongs simply for you. Understand? Yes.
Does that answer your question
sufficiently? Yes. Um, so there's no
need to like five minutes of meditation
before each session of writing or
anything of that sort. Not if it is not
something that represents what your
imagination has excited you into knowing
you can do. If it is not something that
you think is something you need to do,
if the writing in and of itself is
enough of a meditation for you, and if
that excites you more than any other
methodology, then that is your
meditation. Okay, fine. Trust your
imagination. All right. Right. Thank you. Thank you.
All right. Right. Thank you. Thank you.
Shutting. Hello, Bashar. Hello. My name
is Morgan. All right. Hello, Morgan.
Hello, Bashar. I am a channel and I am
learning to ignite myself as a channel
in class. All right. How might I um
specifically facilitate this
communication? Do you have any ideas on that? What do
Do you have any ideas on that? What do
you picture yourself doing with the
channeling? What images do you get when
you think of yourself as a channel? How
do you see yourself channeling? I see
myself vocally channeling. All right.
Where
specifically? Um, in other words, are
you channeling in a small closed dark
room? Oh, are you channeling to three or
four friends? Are you channeling to
hundreds of individuals? Are you on a
mountain top? Are you by the ocean? Are
you in a forest? Are you in a building?
How? I'm channeling two, three, or four
friends. Oh, all right. Does that feel
enjoyable? Yes, very much so. Oh, all
right. I'm experiencing some physical
I'm experiencing some physical
manifestations right now. Yes. Uh part
of which I agreed uh to experience. And
I wanted to ask you about this. All of
which you agreed to experience.
You may not prefer all of it now and you
may wish to transform it, but if you
have it, you agree to it one way or
another, unconsciously or consciously.
Uh-huh. Okay. Do you have any
suggestions how I can open up my throat
area more to trigger the words, images?
Yes. First of all, allow yourself to
cease to think of yourself as a
collection of parts. You do not
necessarily have to work on one
particular area over another. Allow
yourself to be a whole homogeneous idea
and understand that when you are
channeling your energy is becoming the
version of that idea. So the whole of
you is manifesting. Open up the whole of
you. Understand? Yes. Activate the
idea in whatever way, shape or form is
comfortable for you. Act out what your
imagination shows you. Get three or four
friends. This is a suggestion. Mhm. And
simply say without
expectation, if you are willing, simply
allow me as I will allow myself to let
whatever comes
come then let it come. It doesn't have
to make sense. Uhhuh. Understand? Mhm.
Just play for now. The more you
play, the more it will crystallize into
whatever format represents the format
necessary to make the most sense
eventually in your society's
terminology. But for now, play with it.
And if you have an image of what feels
correct, then play it out. Act it out.
Uhhuh. As best as you possibly
can with whatever help you can enlist.
Yeah. Well, that sounds great. Oh, all right.
Well, that sounds great. Oh, all right.
Is there a way to ignite the battery in
me to facilitate using the Ouija board?
Does it excite you to use that
particular tool? Yes, very much. Then
use it. It is the action in and of itself
it. It is the action in and of itself
which does the igniting. It is the trust
that if you are attracted to it, that's
an indication that that's the tool that
may represent at this moment the one
that will work best for you by
functioning as a trigger for your
ignition. That's what tools are. They
are triggers to ignite you. They are
exteriorized symbols of the way you
think of yourself, of the way you
symbolize yourself, of the way you
imagine yourself to function, what type
of frequency, what type of energy you
believe you are. So to simply act with
integrity and use the tool, the one that
excites you the most now, the one your
curiosity has been attracted to
strongest is to pull the trigger that
will ignite you. Mhm. Understand? Yes.
Thank you very much. Thank you very
much. Shannon,
Shannon,
greetings Bashar and to you. Did you
enjoy our celebration of our harmonic
convergence? Yes, I did too. I I also
experienced a lot of confusion. No,
right. I didn't know whether to say
happy harmonic convergence like at
Easter or merry harmonic convergence
like at Christmas time or have a safe
and sane harmonic convergence like on
Independence Day and it was just
tremendously confusing but I I will
wager that you had a good time
nonetheless. I had a terrific time.
Yeah. Thank you. And nobody seemed to
care what I said to them so it was fine.
Um, including me.
I'm I'm delighted to hear that. Fine.
I've attracted uh two related phenomena.
Very closely related. All right. Two
phenomena. Mhm. Plural. Uh, one is that,
um, maybe once, two, maybe three times a
day, I will have somebody ring my
telephone and as soon as I say hello,
there's a brief silence and they hang
up. All right. The other phenomenon is
that I get three or more calls a day for
Security Pacific
Bank, which has a very closely related
number. All right. It's like off by just
a digit.
So, um, I couldn't figure out why
somebody, it seemed like the same person
who kept hanging up when they would hear
me say hello. Felt like the same energy.
Felt like the same energy. All right.
Maybe there were two or three, but
primarily one. No. All right. And it
felt Why would they continue to call me
when they knew that they didn't get the
person that they were thinking they were
getting? Maybe they got who they needed.
Well, maybe. So, I mean, looking at the
mechanics and everything, you know, you
go, "Well, yeah, you know, somebody
goofed or whatever. Thought they were
getting But I know that there's
something more for me here because this
has been going on for a number of
months. All right. Suddenly I related
these phenomena to expectation today and I'm
phenomena to expectation today and I'm
not sure how they do relate to
expectation. We do not perceive that
they strongly do. Well, I wondered about
that. It I made the connection and then
I said, well, I'm going to ask about it
anyway. Um to some degree what it is
representative of at least to our
perception is now we do not mean back in the sense
is now we do not mean back in the sense
of having regressed but simply back to
the old idea of being a
switcher and facilitating as a switching
mechanism from one connection into
another through
yourself back and forth being what you
call the go between the
linkup for them in a sense for them to
whom to where it is they desire to get.
But in other words, you are functioning
magnetically symbolically attracting
them through you to whom they need
rather than more directly in between
themselves. In a sense, when they
contact you, you are imparting, however
slight, a small magnetic pulse, a
magnetic switching alignment to them
that changes something within them,
which of course, more properly put,
means that they are changing something
within themselves, but allowing you to
reflect that to them.
Yes, you are sending a pulse when they
reach you and the pulse is having an
effect. That's interesting.
You are being now used as a switcher.
They did get the correct
number for the effect they needed. I
understand that. Okay. How does it serve me? I
that. Okay. How does it serve me? I
mean, I It allows you to do your
job. It allows you to begin to open up
to new ways, new ideas, new symbols that
allow you to understand how magnetically
connected and how networking your energy
actually is.
It is perhaps for now a subtle thing,
but it can begin to grow in other ways.
Okay. I I'm aware of certain aspects of
u my job as a switcher. Yeah. Um so this
is simply a new phase. Mhm. And some of
them are are kind of what I see as
physically relatively narrowly focused.
Yes. uh communicating with friends um
reflecting to them a lot of um ideas
that I share with you. Yeah. And um now
to some degree you are getting a
representation of something a little
more expansive, a little as you say
broader in scope. Mhm. What is it your
society says? I believe it is the phrase
reach out and touch someone. Yeah. Well,
I had considered that. Uh I I knew that
I was making a connection in some way. I
wasn't quite sure what the service on
the connection was, which is all right
for now to function sometimes best as a
switcher. You don't necessarily need to
know all the specifics of what they are
getting from the pulse you are sending.
You are simply doing your job. Okay. Now
I would also create varying uh
responses. On rare occasion it would
piss me off because I would have to go
from one room to the next. Other times I
would be more centered. I would maintain
a a better centering angle. All right. I
would just know that well this is
exactly what I needed for my purposes.
All right. I didn't look at it so much
as my service to them. But your
reflection to me tonight has uh opened
that up. Thank you. And the subtle
nature of it now gives you the time
necessary to allow yourself to
understand that it always is a positive idea. Oh
that it always is a positive idea. Oh
yes. So it's giving you an opportunity
to lessen those times when you are
upset. Absolutely. Well, I knew even
while I was being upset, I knew it was a
positive situation. I just it was a
little bit of habit that I permitted to.
All right. You know, and I knew that was
okay, too. Thank you. Can you expand
even more on my job as switcher? I've
kind of just been falling into it, you
know, waiting across the the river and
not really
knowing. That's not really the analogy
that I wanted to use, but it sounded
okay at the time. I mean just kind of um
being there and not really knowing that
I was to flow with the direction. Yeah,
it was a good analogy after all. All
right. Um can you reflect to me more
about what job as switcher is? We can
give you a symbol.
All right, I will take that. All right.
Think in terms of the many different
inputs and
outputs that one of your circuits
exhibits. Mhm. Like a printed circuit
board. Yes. Okay. Hold that image and
understand all the comingings and the
goings of information that are being
processed through what you would call
the chip at the center through the
switching gate at the center. Mhm. And
allow yourself to by using that as a
symbol in your imagination to in a
meditative state follow in different
meditations each one of those conduits
and see where it leads in your
imagination. Ah, then retrace it back to
the center. Recreate. Breathe. Come back to
center. Recreate. Breathe. Come back to
the surface. Breathe. Go back in and
follow another conduit.
All right. Okay. I got that. And what
what will that do? You'll find out. Do
it and find out. Okay. It will give you
an opportunity to truly visualize the
vibration along each circuit and see
where it will lead and see how you are
connected to different events in your
life magnetically. Interesting. It's
very interesting because I have had a uh
printed circuit board kind of symbol
that um when I would see it seemed to be
very significant to me and it was now.
Yes. Yes. Well, I really appreciate you
reflecting to me the job that I was
doing when these people would call
because now I can make it a real game
and uh Thank you. Obviously, there's
been a a transformation of the kind of
energy because of this interaction here.
Nice. You're going to ask them if you
wish why they think they reached you.
I'll have to do that um empathically
because uh they're not on the phone
after about 1 second. So I'll do it that
way. All right. Maybe just a suggestion.
Okay. They might stay a little longer
depending upon how you answer the phone.
Any um more detail? Oh, okay. I'm going
to leave that one entirely up to your
creative furnace. All right. I'll stoke
the furnace. Thank you. Thank you.
Click click sharing.
click sharing.
Hi Bashar. Hi. Uh, since the harmonic
convergence, speak up. Speak up. Speak
up. Share. Share. Share with all. Okay.
Since the harmonic convergence, I've
been feeling disoriented and tired and
off balance. And my friends seem to be
going through the same thing. And we
were told it's from the energy being
beamed to the earth. Can you tell me
more? In a sense, keep it simple. will
simply recognize that you are now
allowing there to be the idea that there
is more energy than there used to be
even though there
isn't. But you are becoming more aware
of the energy that is available and
therefore to you it is the same thing as
having more energy. Again the
disorientation is simply the time you
are creating for yourself to get used to
the new level of energy. You are
disorienting yourself from the old
reality and reorienting yourself into a
new one. New definitions. This is why
this evening of your time we began with
the understanding of clear intention,
clear definition, clear desire, clear
definition, clear desire, clear
deservability and clear action. They
will reorient you very quickly. Use the
energy. Use the limbo state to define
what you prefer. Then act accordingly
and you will be aligned. You will be
reoriented. Remember that some of this
disorientation as we have said before is
also part of the process if you wish of
literal literal
disillusionment. You are redefining your
physical reality as an extension of you.
It is the same energy you are. It is the
idea you are. It is made of your
consciousness. So in a sense now that
everything is dissolving in its old
definitional sense you are becoming
disoriented because there isn't as much
solid structure to hold on
to. You are floating in the center of
your being making up your mind as to what the
being making up your mind as to what the
new structure will be like. Understand?
Yes. Thank you. Oh thank you very much.
Keep it
simple. Enjoy. Laugh.
shouting.
Okay. Hello, Bashar. Hello.
[Music] Um the uh you you've said that we create
Um the uh you you've said that we create
our own universe. Yes. Basically based
on our own beliefs. Yes.
Now I can kind of understand that from
my own
personal life that's fairly close to me.
Yes. But does this also mean that that I
have complete and utter uh control over
world events uh as I see them from my
point of view? Well, to some degree
there are mass consciousness agreed upon
ideas that you generally support and
share in to take you all where you are
all going collectively as well as
individually. But you have the
opportunity to weave in and out of any
mass event in any way, shape or form
that is representative of the reality
you prefer to be specifically. So even
though you may participate on the whole
in the overall mass agreed upon event,
you will be able to experience the
effect of your participation relative to
the vibration you set yourself up to be.
doesn't mean that it has to affect you
the same way it would affect someone
else even though you both participate in
what is essentially the same event
understand I think so let me let me and
you will add your unique perspective to
it the more you participate consciously
within it so in that sense yes you do
have an
impact you are a part of the overall
equation if you were different the
overall equation would be different no
matter how subtle that seems to you
remember that any change in the present
that is made that is subtle creates vast
and impactful differences in what you
call the future.
Okay. Now, now let me just give an
example to see if this is the type of
understanding that you're talking about.
All right. Let's just say that there are
two different ways to achieve peace in
Nicaragua. All right. There are two
different ways to achieve peace in
Nicaragua. All right. Now, I think that
that one way is the ideal way and my
neighbor think that the other way is the
ideal way. Yes. Will I experience in the
news, in newspapers, on television, and
if I went to Nicaragua the way I believe
and the neighbor right next door will
see on television, read in the
newspapers and go down to Nicaragua and
experience the belief he believes in,
which is different. It can happen that
way. Although generally what happens upon
Although generally what happens upon
your planet is that you both come to
some consensus or third reality that
represents enough of your individual
realities to be satisfactory and
sufficient for both of you to share it
because after all the whole idea is to
share not to segregate. So the idea that
will usually occur is an idea you can
both share somewhat rather than
completely segregating the idea. But you
can create a segregated effect. Yes. And
it in a sense it is done all the time
because there are different parallel
realities and one person who absolutely
believes one particular way and if that
is
absolutely not able to contain the other
belief then each of those individuals
will experience completely segregated
realities. It can happen that way but
the whole idea is to blend. So more
often than not, you will simply find
that you will meet on some common ground
that will allow you to experience the
ideas in specific ways that fulfill each
of you while still being represented
from an overall idea that is generally
satisfying to the majority of your
planet. Understand? Okay. So that means
that that uh as using the same example,
peace will occur in Nicaragua. Yes. And
my beliefs and my neighbors beliefs will
blend. Yes. And the result will be the
piece that we both wanted basically.
Yes. For when it comes right down to
your clearest definition and your
highest representation of integrity and
intention if the piece is created and if
it is done with integrity, do you really
care how it gets there?
Well, it it can make a difference in in
a sense because you in in one way
perhaps there could be a lot of
oppression and death. Did you hear what
I said? If the piece is done with
integrity, do you really care how it
gets there? I forgot what you meant by
integrity. So, keep it simple. In other
words, if the piece is created without
harm coming to anyone, does it matter
how it happens? Not particularly. All
right, then. Allow yourself to recognize
that you will both get what you want if
it simply fulfills the general
description of your desire. That peace
occurs with the most amount of integrity
it possibly can occur with. Okay? And
this can be done with beliefs. Today you
talked about about action. But can you
do it with beliefs only?
The idea is that something you really
absolutely strongly believe in you will
act upon. The two are not segregated.
There is no such thing really as a
belief only. For if you have what you
call a belief and you do not act
accordingly in some way, shape or form,
then it is not really a belief. It may
be a recognition, but it is not really a
belief. Not in the fullest sense of the
meaning of the word. For what you really
believe in, you act upon. Actions and
beliefs are tied together in that sense.
They are one thing. You act as you
believe and as you believe you will act.
Like for instance, I I work every day
doing work that has nothing to do with
the war in Nicaragua. Not directly
perhaps. Occasionally I will write a
letter to my congressman. Is that the
type of thing you're talking about? To
some degree. The writing of the letter
is an action and is representative of
your belief. Now it can expand in its
definition. It can expand in its scope
if that's what excites you. But the
writing of the letter is nonetheless an
action and that with a belief to back
that up then the piece that I'm looking
for can take place then just with my own
yes personal self doing it. Yes. As long
as you understand that you are not
segregating yourself from any
opportunity that might come along to
represent your ability to act on it in a
more expanded way. Okay. Thank you.
Thank you.
Shutting. Hello Bashar. Hello. Uh, I'd
like to ask you some additional
questions about tetrahedrrons.
Tetrahedron. Uh, I understand that it is
the building block of the universe in a
sense. Yes. In a sense. Okay. Some of
the questions I'd like to ask are uh
what's the difference on an energy level
between an equal and a non-equal
tetrahedrin where the sides are
different?
The idea can point in what you would
call direction. In other words, that
side or area that in your terms would be
unequal may simply represent the tensor,
the dynamic that is being used. Putting
it simply to literally point the way,
point out the direction in which the
energy is flowing. Okay, that's so in
other words, an
unequal idea would represent a universe
in motion to some degree.
That is why to some degree most of you
only see the unequal sides of things
because it is in a constant state of
fluctuation. When we describe the
equilateral tetrahedrin we are basically
describing the
fundamental template of the universe not
necessarily one in action in motion.
Understand uh somewhat the difference
between what you call potential and
kinetic energy in other words. Okay. So
when you have a tetrahedrin where you
have uh one side is say the back flat
instead of curving this way you have the
other two so that you can have the
bottom flat in a it represents the
specific frequency of the kinetic okay
then the energy is then going out the
the point uh the most unequal point is
that correct do I have that right
basically yes okay what what I'm
interested in in in knowing also
although There are reversals, polarity reversals
There are reversals, polarity reversals
of this idea that would allow it to
occur in the opposite direction most
strongly. In other words, if you have a
flat side and you stretch one side this
way, that is creating a type of tension.
Mhm. Therefore, the
manifestation may be exactly in the
opposite direction of that tension.
Okay. the tension, the point of focus
may then be the gateway through which
the energy flows through and out the
other side. It is like taking something,
narrowing it down into a pin, poking
through a bubble and allowing the flow
of energy to come through and funnel
out. But the way you distort the
tetrahedrin will indicate the type of
flow, the concentration of flow, the
direction of flow to come out the other
side, the mouth, the flat side. Okay. I
the side that is least distorted.
Okay. I'd like to use uh the tetrahedrin
shape for healing and consciousness
raising. It seems to me that there's
some good potential for that. Then you
can imagine the idea, this is one way,
allow your imagination to come up with
variations on this theme. But you can
allow the idea of a tetrahedral
structure, a three-sided pyramid
floating above an individual, allowing
the base to be undistorted and then
simply stretching the other three sides
up into an infinite point and allowing
it to pierce the light of creation and
allow that to flow down and over and
through the
individual. literally like you are
placing a funnel over them and then
poking a hole in creation and allowing
the light of creation to flood down
through that funnel into them. Okay. Um
I would like to bring some tetrahedrrons
into physical manifestation. Go ahead
for use in the home. Go ahead. Okay. Can
you trust your imagination now? Okay.
And just just do it do it with play with
it. Okay. Play with the tones they give
you. See what strikes a chord within
you. Okay. Allow your imagination to
tell you what each variation in the
shape and the structure and the material
will do. Great. Play with it. Okay. Like
an instrument. Like the instrument that
it is. Thank you. Thank you very much.
You may
all enjoy a short break. We will resume
contact in approximately 10 of your
minutes. [Applause]
How's it going? Pretty
good. It's 10 minutes, please. Remember,
10 minutes. 10 minutes, please.
In other words, at 9
couldn't figure it out. 9:43, please be
back.
All right. I'll say, by the
way, do any of you
notice that the energy tonight of your
time is a little more
lowkey? Now the reason for
this is because primarily that we have
reminded many of you that in these
interactions with us sometimes you feel
a very strong vibrational resonance and
an energy and you think oh yes I am
feeling Bashar's energy.
No, you are feeling your energy. For in
these interactions, in functioning as a
mirror for each and every one of you, we
are giving you the opportunity to see
your own capability, your own capacity,
your own energy reflected back to you.
The feeling you have of that vibrancy
when you have it is your energy. When
you have been willing to match our
energy, that is our way of allowing you
to learn to equalize, to meet us
halfway. Now, this night of your time, we are
Now, this night of your time, we are
being a little more, as you say, low
key, not to bring the energy down, but
to allow you to begin to create that
energy for
yourself without needing my mirror as
much.
So the idea if you wish is for
you in remembering as you
say the idea of when those interactions
those interfaces of what you call our
energy your energy were most expansive
were resonating in high
frequency to understand that your memory
is the creation of that energy.
Now, regardless of what you feel from us, of
regardless of what you feel from us, of
what you perceive our energy to
be, this is your opportunity to
recognize that the feelings has always
been your energy for you to understand.
And you can begin to create that
anytime, anywhere, anyone you
wish. to give us an
opportunity to kick
[Laughter]
back to have a
vacation to allow you to generate the
idea that we have reflected to you so
that you can be your version of what you
have imagined us to be. So there will be
more equality between us in that sense
and then eventually less of a notion of
between and more a matter of being the
same. You all follow along?
Yeah, you all follow along.
Thank you.
Shutting Good day, Michelle. And to you, good
Good day, Michelle. And to you, good
day.
Uh, a little over a week ago, my mother,
who is very dear to me, um, entered the
hospital. She had been having what
appeared to be an uncontrollable
diarrhea. They spent a week doing
tests, finding virtually nothing, and
then a day ago, day and a half ago, they
found cancerous cells in her stomach.
Tomorrow they are planning to do an
exploratory surgery as they don't know
the source of where these are coming
from. And I'm going to be flying back
there to assist. All right. And I want
to reflect to you now, you know, the
energy and beingness of my
mother. And I'm joining the two energies
between her and me now. And I would like
you if you will to reflect some
suggestions in best ways that I can be
of assistance.
As our perception of the idea happening
now between you is that she in a sense
of course with your
cooperation is giving birth to you all
over
again through this interaction that you
will have with her. We perceive that you
are going to emerge with almost every
single old definition
shattered. You are going to be
redefining yourself, recreating yourself
within the womb, within that crucible of
creation. And you are going to
emerge in the manner you would call raw
and pink and
new formable. To begin to extend new
formable. To begin to extend new
senses, to begin to learn a new world,
to see it from scratch, as you say,
without the old attitudes, without the
old definition.
This is the opportunity you are being
given by this act of love. This pulling
inward into the center of
self. It is our perception. She is
giving you an opportunity to utterly
redefine everything you have thought
about redefining but have not completely
redefining but have not completely
redefined. You are being given an
opportunity to use the emotionality to
do so.
to allow the intellectuality to be
recreated all over again from a new and
fresh understanding from what this interaction
understanding from what this interaction
will represent and mean to
you. to allow her as
well to be born into a new
existence in a new
direction. to be
allowed to laugh in new
ways. To allow the laughter to be
natural, to be born a new in a natural
way, fresh in a fresh
fresh in a fresh
world of new and fresh ideas. Seeing a
dawn for the first
time every
time. Seeing the
limitlessness that a child sees the
world within. This is her service and her love
within. This is her service and her love
to you. And in your loving
support, in your acceptance of this
service and this
gift, in a sense, you will allow her to
be
fulfilling one of the strongest
agreements she has made with you. For
this nexus, this interaction, this axis
of intersection between
you is to allow you to
know that truly in many senses of the
word and the concept, you have lived one
life up to this
point and now you're going to start
living a completely new
life in the same quote unquote
body without having to
die physically. You will allow yourself to
physically. You will allow yourself to
be born again within a new idea and a
new definition of
yourself. And she is providing the
atmosphere that is the
womb for your new birth.
You will discover many things about the
old you that will pale to the idea of
insignificance. Not that you will
invalidate them, but this experience as
we perceive it emotionally will touch
the cords that will allow you to send
these old ideas on their
way and will allow you to emerge
emerge
unstructured to decide step by step
clearly which ideas you now prefer to
grow up
within all over
Again, we thank you for your
strength. We thank you for your courage
at playing this particular emotional
game, for it will be a strong one, and
therefore, as beit such strong emotional
interplay, will move you fast and far.
If you but open
unconditionally and allow the energy to
flow through
you. Do not
fight. Let it
flow. Let it
flow. Portions of your idea of yourself
that you have carried with you through
this former life will begin to dissolve
and float away.
You no longer need them to be the you
you desire to
be. To all
involved in whatever way it is most
appropriate for
each. Happy birthday to
you. That is our perception of this
interaction. Thank you my friend.
Thank you most lovingly. Okay.
Shing. Hi Bashar. Hello. Good morning.
Good day. Fine day is it not? It's
beautiful. Exciting. Wonderful. Uh oh.
One moment. One moment. Let us
appreciate it together shall we? Yes.
All right. As you allow me to
right. As you allow me to
describe the dawning of a new
day over the greenery of my
world, the rising of what you would call
a yellowish star with a greenish
[Music] tinge and there
tinge and there
being
pale amber
light, coolish amber
light that allows the very trees to seem
to be waking up, to be stretching and
expanding under the
light, opening up, spreading
out farther and farther until all the
branches and all the leaves touch,
creating the canopy of a forest once
again. Whereas the previous night before they
Whereas the previous night before they
had been collected, singular stalks
dotting the
landscape, and now they spread out to
give their
shade to the creatures below.
And there
is now and then when one is in the right
place at the right time and has such a
vibration a small thin
flash of reddish
purple that will
signal the angle of the light through
the atmosphere that represents the
official quote unquote new day, new dawn
upon our world. A crispness, a
lightness, a
freshness, a smell, a touch, a
sound, a
vitality, and a smoothness, an assuress
of being, being,
activity, and
delight. Well, thank you for sharing the
new dawn with me. Thank you. It was
beautiful. So I will keep this image in
mind when I go up on my hill.
Um this is a very will appear to be
quite prosaic following that nonsense.
Uh uh over a year ago I talked to you
about the fact that I created a lot of
pain whenever I had teeth cleaned.
Remember that? Yes. And at that time uh
you said that I was balancing a lot of
different processes.
Um, and we would talk about it some
other time and I've never brought it up
again because I didn't think that the
processes were finished until well since
then I have found a hygienist who uses a
different method and I I don't have the
problem the
u pain mind you and I had a checkup
today. I I've also had a lot of uh
situations with my mouth. Everything
that happens in my life seems to be some
reaction in my mouth. out my teeth, my
gums, whatever. I had gum surgery and my
dentist said that
um the best we could do after the
surgery was to keep it stable or not let
it deteriorate too much. All the best.
All right. Right. And today I had a
checkup and he came and he said, "Hey,
it's getting better." Surprise,
surprise, surprise. And and he was very
surprised. I wasn't. I was very pleased.
But I but I thought, well, that makes
sense. Yes, you are taking bigger bites
of life now.
So I thought, well, perhaps this was a
in a sense that is what I really mean.
For when you don't, the symbol of what
you chew it with to digest it can
atrophy. Huh. Oh, how interesting. Well,
I thought perhaps this was the time now
where you might share with me those
processes I was balancing because I
finished with my balancing act. Yes, we
have just described them to you. In
effect, you are biting off bigger chunks
of life emotionally in that sense. You
are willing to digest more in that sense
rather than simply one particular level
which would allow there to be spiritual
malnourishment.
Understand? Yes. You are now nourishing
yourself more on every level. Okay. So,
at the time I was not nourishing myself.
Not on every level. Okay. You're not
biting into life as fully as you could.
And I am now, even though I told you a
couple of weeks ago, enough to allow the
balancing to start happening naturally.
The willingness, remember, the
willingness in and of
itself many times is enough. You don't
have to have it all in terms of your
conscious understanding of what is going
on. The willingness, however, to go for
it all can allow all the nourishment to
come in that needs to come in to give
you the ability to go for the rest of
it. Yeah, I think I do have the
willingness now. Yes. Right. Right.
Because I feel that Well, the reason I'm
talking to you tonight, I I feel that
I'm at the verge of something and all I
need is a little nudge from you telling
me which direction. Thank you.
What are you at the verge of? I have no
idea. Bash. Yes, you do. I knew you'd
say that. Well, first of all, you know,
repeat after me. I am
I am the I was that a question. No, I
am. I am. Oh, yes. I guess so. All
right. No, I am. I am the idea. The idea
of being on the verge of being on the
verge of discovery
of what of discovery of discovery of I
don't know that's what I'd like to All
right. I am I am the idea the idea of
not knowing what I'm on the verge of
of not knowing what I'm on the verge of.
How do you know you're on the verge of
anything? It feels like that. Oh, it
feels like it. All right, then. For now,
be the idea of being on the verge.
Explore what it is to be on the edge, on
the threshold. Explore that idea. For
now, that is the idea in and of itself.
Remember, many of you
invalidate the process itself. That's
true. As a part of the life you are.
Yes. Yes. When am I going to get there?
When am I going to get there? Oh, I
haven't done that. So, I am allowing a
little fun. Okay. No, but the idea is
that when you say, "Well, I'm on the
verge of something, but I don't know
what." Then, if you don't know what, let
the state you are in be the state you
need to be in and explore what you need
to in that state. Once you have explored
all you need to in that state, you will
know what the next state is that you
need to be. Anytime you don't
immediately know what the next state is,
you haven't finished with the state
you're in. For what it is,
not for where it's getting you, for what
it is, right here, right now. Yes. You
see, that is the idea we are suggesting
is that many of you allow states to only
be states that get you somewhere rather
than allowing them to be where you are
and understanding what it is, where you
are. So for a while be a verge. Okay. So
So for a while be a verge. Okay. So
thank you very much Bashar. Thank you
very much. Shilling.
much. Shilling.
Hello Bashar. Hello. I have a question
about a drawing that I'm holding here. A
drawing. Um which has been described as a
Um which has been described as a
talisman. All right. A talismanic
drawing or a mandala. Mandala. All
right. Mandala. And it has a number of
Hebrew symbols on it. All right. And I'm
told that the purpose of having a
drawing like this around is to allow the
message that it conveys to get past the
conscious mind sensor. All right. Into
the subconscious. Many times, yes, the
symbols will make more sense to the less
analytical parts of yourself. And so you
will allow the information to rub off
even though your analytical mind may in
that sense have filters against it.
Well, I'm told that this particular
series of symbols conveys an idea about
attaining goals. Oh, all right. But I
don't know what the individual symbols
mean. But you don't have to. That's what
I just said. Your subconscious mind
does. You understand? I think so. All right.
You understand? I think so. All right.
Does that mean that as long as the
symbols are in any foreign language then
they'll suffice?
Not always. Sometimes they can be
recognizable and they will suffice
because sometimes familiarity is what
you want. However, the idea does unlock
your guard. Does allow you to drop the
defenses because you don't think there's
necessarily anything there getting
through. Then you're not expecting it
when it does get through. So sometimes
yes, anything that you are not
immediately familiar with can serve you
in that way. Not that there are not
other things and other symbols that will
not work for you. How do these symbols
get through? Is it because they get
through by you knowing that you have
chosen that to function in that way for
you and then getting on about your
business of doing what excites you the
most and knowing that the information
that needs to get through is getting
through in a positive reinforcing way
that will allow you to do what excites
you the most in the most accelerated way
and you will simply see it come out in
the actions that you do. So it doesn't
even matter if the symbols are
completely meaningless as long as I
believe that they say what they say.
They always have meaning to you if you
have created them and or attracted them
into your life. There is no such thing
that remains meaningless if you have a
reason for attracting it into your life.
You are giving it a meaning. But no
symbol has built-in meaning. So it
doesn't matter know what it looks like.
You give it a meaning regardless. And
the meaning you give it determines the
effect it has in your life. Understand?
I think so. So this is this is a
valuable thing to do then if I'm perhaps
attracted to it. If your imagination
comes up with a way that seems to be
more simplified and that excites you
more then do that. That will work in
your terms best for you. All right.
Thank you that. Yes, I do. Thank you. It
is simply a mirror. Look at it as a
mirror. All right. Thank you. Oh, thank
you very
much. Sharing. Oh, one moment. One
moment. Remember that the idea also
carries a vibrational tone which to some
degree represents your signature
vibration and can allow you to be in
touch with that centered idea of
yourself. That is generally what you
call the reason that mandalas and so
forth exist in your society. They are
simply reflections of the vibrational
pattern that your particular persona is
constructed of.
So is that the reason that a person will
be drawn to a particular mund? Yes.
Because at that moment it is of your
frequency and therefore by definition is
the symbol if you need a symbol that
will serve you best and that's why you
were attracted. If something else would
have served you better you would have
been attracted to it and that's why you
keep emphasizing to do what excites you
the most. Yes. Because then as you act,
you see the result of that interaction
play out in the actions that you do. You
just see it come out in a chneled
spontaneous way that allows you to stand
there in utter amazement, scratch your
head and say, "I didn't know I knew how
to do that."
Understand? I think so. Thank you very
much. Thank you.
Shouting, my name is Barry. Hello. Hi.
Couple of questions. All right. Um, two
parts. One is All right. Part one. Part
one. One is um personal question. I've
spent many years
uh writing songs and music for other
people. Oh. All right. And uh now I'm to
the point where I feel I want to do it
more for myself. All right. You go right
ahead. Okay. Um it's a little a little
Okay. Um it's a little a little
difficult in in making this start. I'm
in well I'm in another business right
now which is uh I think I'm a little
addicted to the lucrative side of the
business. You are making an assumption
that what you want to do in life won't
be lucrative.
Possibly. There is could be a downside
to that. Yeah. All right. Why would you
assume that? Well, I think it's just a
fear of u maybe my own success at
something that I've been successful at
for other people. All right. Very good.
Do you
recognize that everyone in your life is
simply a reflection of a different
aspect of you anyway?
Do I? Yeah. All right. Then in that
sense, you have always been writing for
yourself.
Understand? It isn't really anything
new. Even when you write for someone
else, you are writing for yourself
because they are an aspect of you. They
are another reflection, another way in
which the energy you are also made of
can express
itself. So now that you have given
yourself the opportunity to write for
all these different aspects in
segregated formats, you now have the
opportunity to understand that each and
every individual you worked with in that
way was a mirror that allowed you to
integrate that aspect of you within
yourself. So that now the feeling of
wanting to write for yourself means you
have arrived at a point where you have
incorporated all the different
reflections you have been getting from
everyone else into the center of the
being you are
now. So in a sense you're still going to
be writing for the same people. It's
just that they're all within you now
because you have gone with your basket
and collected them together in the
persona you are. It is simply that first
you wrote for all those different
aspects of yourself exteriorized from
you. Now you are going to write for all
those different aspects of yourself
blended within
you. Understand? Understand? Does that
help you? It does. All right. And
remember the thing in life that excites
you the most is the thing by definition
that you can actually do most
effortlessly and most abundantly because
that's what excitement is there to tell
you. This is the thing that represents
the path you chose to be. Otherwise, it
wouldn't excite you. And if it is the
path you chose to be as represented by
your excitement, then by definition, it
must be the thing that you will be able
to do most effortlessly and most
abundantly to allow you to continue to
do it on whatever level really excites
you the most. Otherwise, you would be
defining an extraneous and pointless
creation. And there are no such things.
If what excites you the most couldn't
bring you, the effortlessness of
manifesting it and the abundance that it
might take in order to manifest it, then
it wouldn't be
realizable. And there is no such thing
in creation as something that you can
conceive of that represents what excites
you the most that you haven't got the
ability to manifest on all levels you
need to manifest it. That would be a
one-sided coin. And there are no such
creatures. Understand? Mhm. Mh. So your
ability to conceive of it and be excited
by it is your signal that you can
manifest it on whatever level it needs
to be manifested because you are a
complete kit and come with all the
ingredients necessary including the
ability to attract effortlessness and
abundance to allow you to continue to be
the idea you chose to be. You are a
complete kit. The abundance and the
effortlessness comes with the excitement
always never without it in order to
allow you to continue to do that idea.
Otherwise, it would be a pointless
creation. And there is no such thing.
All creations have the ability to
manifest themselves in whatever format
their free will has allowed them to
decide they wish to formalize themselves
within. Understand? I understand. Is this making
Understand? I understand. Is this making
sense? It's making sense. I'm just
curious whether the starting point comes
from the idea of
uh of um just like you were saying
before to somebody else just starting
and just that's it just sitting down to
take the first step and you initiate all
the momentum necessary to bring you the
opportunity to take the next step then
all you have to do to keep the momentum
going is trust it and take it. That's
it. As long as you do something that
does not represent what excites you the
most, then you in that sense are holding
yourself back from having a life of
ecstasy. That is your birthright. And
the second part of this question is um a
little strange but all right. I like
strange things, right?
I am strange myself.
That's okay. Several years ago, I had a
um I had a dream which in the dream
u a name came to me. It was and it and I
really identified with it that it was
like my soul name, something very
ancient, something maybe from another
time. All right. And it clicked in me so
strong. I don't know if it was my
warrior self or that very strong side of
myself that connected with it. Then when
I woke up, I totally forgot that. And I,
you know, I tried to remember it. I
tried to moment whatever. And this is
several years back. So did come back.
And I'm just wondering knowing that you
can say connect with the accashic
records of
myself would have a feeling about I
would have a completely different
interpretation of it vibrationally. I
can sense the vibration. But before I
give you what may result in a label,
allow me to remind you that the idea is
not to recapture the label itself. The
idea is to live the vibration you felt
at the time and manifest it in whatever
way represents your integrity and what
excites you the most. That is why it
came to allow you to simply see who you
were, not necessarily to use the label
it was represented by in the past. Just
to remind you of who you were so you
could now live that life without
necessarily attaching the same label.
Understand? It is the feeling and the living and the
It is the feeling and the living and the
acting upon the feeling that is the
recapturing of the name of the
information. Do you do you feel that um
that our parents let's say my parents at
that moment that I was born my mother
had a feeling if it came from her about
just the name I have now. Let's say that
I over the years have not been totally
satisfied with my own specific you know
uh material label. Let's say my name for
it could be whenever you change your
frequency. If you feel so inclined that
a different representational name now is
more precisely representative then by
all means use a different name. It's up
to you. Okay. Now without in any way,
shape or form coloring your decision
because it is your decision. And once
again reminding you that this is our
particular perception of your energy as
it passes through our reality and not
necessarily the way you would have
interpreted it. our particular
phrase and this is more than a literal
name. It is actually representative of a
level of consciousness itself to some
degree would be an
axion that is our
particular representation in part of the
overall vibration. And what would that
mean? Does it have a meaning to it? Uh
in our in our terms to some
degree it does mean warrior spirit
from one of our uh from one of our
languages here.
Not directly. There is a part of an ancient
directly. There is a part of an ancient
one of your languages in it but not
completely. It transcended physicality
and non-physicality.
How would that be spelled? An accent
in your language? A N A X I O N an axon.
Not M but A. An axion. An axion. Okay.
All right. Thank you very much. Remember
that in a
sense the phrase the word that we have
just shared with you actually
represents a
hyphen in the entire vibration that you
represent. That is
all. It is the midpoint. It is the
fulcrum and in that sense to some degree
that is also what it means hyphen space
or fulcrum that defines the rest of the
vibration. Understand? I understand. It
is if you wish an
accent literally.
Okay. One
moment exciting dreams and stories to
you. Yarns upon yarns, tails upon
Yarns upon yarns, tails upon
tails. Allow them
to unravel and
reweave themselves. For one of the other
terminologies of past life names has
literally translated into weaver or
rewaver for
you. Thank you. Thank you. sharing.
Hello, Bashar. Closer.
I Hello, Bashar. Hello. I'm called Ruth.
All right, speak up, Ruth.
I'm perplexed and um curious. Well, all
right. Exciting states to be in. Yes.
Yeah. States of discovery
about a particular situation
relationship with a person that uh is
one of the owners of the company that I
work for. All right.
I would very much appreciate anything
you could tell
me. Share with me. But what is your
definition of the situation?
The definition of the situation is Speak
up. Speak up. Share with all. The
definition of the situation is that one
of the owners of the
company has
um a very strong reaction to me. I'm one
of the top performers in the company. No
matter what I do, periodically with at
least once a week, he has an outrageous
outburst of anger. All right. Now, I
know that in some way I've co-created
this at one point. Well, yes. But that
doesn't necessarily mean that when you
interact with someone that what they do
is an absolute onetoone reflection of
what you're doing. It may simply be a
co-creation to allow them to see in the
situation what they need to see and you
can get out of it what you need to see.
But the idea of certain situations
doesn't necessarily mean that it is in
that sense relevant to you each in the
same way or to the same degree.
I would really appreciate uh if you
could enlighten me. Have you discussed
this with that person?
He's threatened to fire me three times
in front of the entire company. Have you
asked a reason? Mhm. And I don't get an
answer because the thing is I'm there's
no real reason. All
right. Do you desire to remain there?
The truth is no. Well,
then I do desire to stay there for a
while. Why?
Why? Well, it's my income. So, and um
I've got fairly high expenses.
What makes you think you will not be
able to attract yourself into a
circumstance that would be equivalent or
even more
expanded? Are you going to allow him to
take the responsibility of pushing you
out the door when you know you want to
walk? Well, he can't push me out. I'm
one of the top performers. Well, but you
are creating a symbol that could create
in your terminologies the friction that
would then force you to leave under what
you would call negative circumstances
instead perhaps of allowing yourself to
learn from your own symbol that you are
being given an opportunity to realize
that you actually prefer to be somewhere
else. This is a suggestion.
How does it ring within you? Well, I
know that I would prefer to be somewhere
else. Where? I don't have a clue. No.
Right. Will you give yourself the
opportunity to see the more expanded
version of what you would prefer to do
if you were not in the company you are
in
now? Can you have or do you have in your
imagination a picture or a play of what
you would prefer to be doing in a more
expanded way? Can you see yourself doing
something that you cannot do in the
company you are in now somewhere else?
Absolutely. All right. Then do you see
the you in that picture? Do you see yourself
you in that picture? Do you see yourself
acting in that picture as you would act
if you were in the new situation?
Can you picture it? I can picture it.
All right. All right. One moment. One
moment. Observe that you going through her daily
routine. Now from the little you have
observed is what you have observed
different than what you are now living?
Yes. In what way? I'm not doing any of
this kind of work. What are you doing?
I'm doing my artwork. All right.
Is the picture you have of this
person one of a happy person? Yes. An
ecstatic person? Yes. A freely flowing
person? Yes. An abundant person?
Absolutely. Well, then what are you
afraid of? Supporting myself in free
gifts. Contradiction. I just asked you if this
Contradiction. I just asked you if this
was an abundant person and you said yes.
Absolutely right.
Then what are you waiting for?
It's a bit precipitous to quit my job at
the moment. Precipitous.
Does that mean you're going to rain on
yourself? No. As in as at at a precipice.
Why? No precipitation. Why?
Why?
Why would it be precipitous to quit my
job right now? That is the question.
Why? Why? Why?
I'll
wait. Whatever reason you wish to come
up with. I can't I must say that I can't
conceive of supporting myself and my
children doing artwork. A very good
answer. I cannot
conceive of myself supporting myself.
But may I ask you another question?
Sure. Go ahead. Haven't you just done
so? Haven't you just pictured yourself
being a happy, ecstatic, and abundant
person supporting yourself and your
children? So, how can you say, "I can't conceive
So, how can you say, "I can't conceive
of it when you just have. You just
describe the picture to
me." So, obviously, you can conceive of
it. Now, maybe maybe what you mean is I
can't believe what I
see. Maybe that's what you mean. How
does that serve us?
I'm having t I'm having I can believe
it. I can't quite get the timing. Oh,
the timing. The timing. All right. I
love this technique.
This excites me a lot to use this
technique called the threshold of
believability. [Applause]
[Applause]
Are you willing to be very honest and
very direct? Yes. All right.
Now, recreate the image of the ecstatic,
abundant, spontaneous, carefree
artist that you are. All right. Got it.
All right.
Now, let me ask you, answer without
thinking. Without thinking. Just answer
what feels
correct. There is no right and wrong to
this. It's not a test. Understand? Yes.
All right. Now, do you perceive that you
will be able to be that you beyond a
shadow of a doubt, no problem, in 10 of
your years? Yes. All
right. Five of your years.
Yes. Why did you hesitate? I had to
really get five. I mean, that's a lot of
abundance for five from where I all
right now. Would you like to try that
again? All right. Do you beyond a shadow of a
All right. Do you beyond a shadow of a
doubt know that you are capable of
creating that reality in your life in 10
years? Yes. Why are you so sure that you
can do it in 10 years? I don't have a
clue. It just you asked me not to think
about it. The answer that came out. Very
good. But in other words, you simply
know. In other words, that that is
sufficient time for you. Yes. Yes. No
problem. More than enough time. Easy as
pie as you say.
Is that what you are saying when you say
I just know? Yes. All right.
Do you feel therefore that 9 years is
sufficient? If 10 years is sufficient to
create that lifestyle, is 9 years
sufficient? Sure.
Sure.
Do you really believe it? Yes. All
right. Fair enough. Do you believe seven
years is sufficient? The shadow. The
shadow of the doubt is there. The shadow
at seven years. Yes, the shadow. All
right. What does that shadow look like?
What is the little voice that says, "I
don't know if I can do this in seven
years." What allows you to believe it
would take longer than seven years? What
came in? What was the doubt?
All right. Go back to nine. Go back to
10 years. No problem at 10 years. What
is the difference between doing it in 10
years and doing it at seven? What is the
definitive difference between the two
scenarios in your
mind? What do you see yourself capable
of doing at 10 years that you don't see
yourself capable of doing at seven?
Well, I'm not so sure. Yes. A lot. It's
the economics and the timing. Economics
and the timing. All right. Can you be
more specific?
You are saying to me as I interpret what
you are saying that you cannot imagine
that you will be economically abundant
in seven years but that 10 years is
enough. Is that what you are saying?
Well once you said it like that I'm not
quite so sure. All right. What are you
saying? What is the difference between seven and
What is the difference between seven and
10 years in your ability to be that
image? All of you can be applying this
to yourselves and what excites you the
most. I'm sorry to be so hesitant and take I
I'm sorry to be so hesitant and take I
beg you. Sorry. Did I ask for an
apology? No. Hey, you said you beg your
pardon. [Laughter] [Laughter]
Thank you.
Now we're on the
track. See what happens when you get
born all over again. You start being as
much of a smart alec as
me. And I love it.
Thank you for speaking to me as an
Esasani would. All
would. All
right. Now that I am no longer begging
and you are no longer
sorry, can you define the difference?
Are you creating within your mind an
assumption of a particular type of
structure that you think you need in
order to have the economics at 10 years
that you can't have through that same
structure at seven?
Is it the structure of how you think you
have to get the economics? No. All
right. Then what makes seven different
than 10 aside from three?
The sooner you all become equal, I shall
have to pay close attention so that I am
not surrounded by smart Alex.
The more you talk, uh, the less
difference there is. The more I talk,
the less difference there is.
I'll take that as a compliment.
Absolutely.
Do you understand you're only listening
to yourself, however? Yes. All right.
Now, it isn't necessarily a matter of
analysis, but the more willing you are
sometimes to talk about it, what you are
saying is that the more equal everything
becomes. Yes. And so in that way you can
recognize there really isn't any vast
difference between your ability to do
something in 10 years, your ability to
do something in seven years or your
ability to do that thing in the next 7
seconds. It's all a matter of how you
define it. That's
it. And those definitions are not
chiseled in steel. You are not using
definitions that represent the
fundamental laws of creation. You are
only making definitions and creating
definitions that are simply the result
of your society's beliefs and the
beliefs that you have bought into. You
don't have to buy them. You can buy into
other ones. Sell those. Use the money to
buy another
belief. You'll get a fair price for
them. Someone somewhere will want that
belief. The belief you no longer need.
belief. So the less difference you create there
So the less difference you create there
to be in terms of the idea of time and
space then the more flexible you are at
any given moment in your ability to
create whatever you really want right
now. Understand? Yes. Pay attention to
the scenario you have created. You have
seen yourself as an ecstatic abundant
creator. that is you. The only thing that
that is you. The only thing that
separates you here from that you there
is assuming that that you is in fact out
there and not right here. All you have
to do is be that you. Act like that you.
Do the things you see that you doing in
your imagination and you will be that
you and because you will be of that
frequency, you will have the life of
that person. I guarantee it. Guarantee
it. Because any frequency you are is the
reality you experience. It can be no
other way. I understand that. All right.
So you also do not have to berate
yourself for however long it does take.
That's your under your timing and
however you do it will be just fine. So
simply recognize that you do have the
ability however to go where you really
want to go right now.
Understand? Yes. You have that
ability. Your ability to recognize it in
and of itself can be
considered a recognition of your ability
to manifest it. Your ability to
recognize it can be considered a
reflection of your ability to manifest
it. Understand? Yes. That's why the
clarity is all it takes. Because once
it's clear, that's who you are.
clear, that's who you are.
Understand? Yes. And all you have to do
is
act in the clear way that
represents the you you imagine yourself
to be. Now clear.
Now clear.
Yes. Does that serve you?
It does. Can I ask you one more thing?
Yes. It's just my curiosity about this
relationship which triggered the um
information and sharing you did did with
me which I appreciate very much. But I'm
the being is throwing a tantrum.
being is throwing a tantrum.
The being Uhhuh. has been one of your
children. Thank you. You are welcome.
Thank you. You are welcome.
Thank you very much.
Is that all?
Yep. It's been great. Thank you. It is. Just checking. Shooting.
Steve, how are we on time?
Okay. Uh, hi. Hi. Hi.
[Laughter] Understand that we were in your
Understand that we were in your
terminology about to say thank you.
Thank you and good night. However, I
know continue. Okay. Um, on the issue of
archetypes. Archetypes. Okay. Archetypes
are the product of a mass consciousness.
Yes. and our arch the archetypes that
are involved here uh not just the ones
that were created here but also through
our journey through Orion and other star
systems those archetypes I assume are
aware of themselves as archetypes
correct sometimes some not always
depends upon the definition and the
play how they interact with you in other
words okay are those archetypes that are
aware of themselves as archetypes are
they also going through similar
transformations that we are at this
time. Some of them and some of them
actually are given enough energy in your
terms to
evolve and join your cycle in a
different way. So an archetype can sort
of wake up and say I no longer wish to
be an archetype. Yes. But I wish to be
independent. In that sense, yes.
Although that is a colloquialism, but we
understand what you mean. Yes. It will
do as an analogy. And do they manifest
physically as a part of that process?
They can incarnate directly. Yes. Is
this happening at this time? Yes. Would
the physical expression realize that it
is an archetype? Not always. Sometimes.
Okay. A lot of times some of that
realization might come up in a very
strong attraction to archetypal symbology when
attraction to archetypal symbology when
referring to the self.
Okay. In other words, as an example, now
this doesn't always mean this is the
case. But let's just say as an example
to choose one archetypal symbology that
you would call, let's say astrology. An
individual might actually say and truly
feel I am not a Libra. I am Libra.
Okay. Understand? Yes. I am the idea
itself. Many
individuals again not all of them and
not even the vast majority directly as
we are discussing this particular idea
but many
individuals who most strongly
identify. One moment.
The wind has just been taken out of my
sails by what?
by what?
By the mass consciousness.
Can you identify that aspect of it that
interacted with you?
No. Can I put the wind back in the
sails?
by your actions in your own personal
life as it attached to your
civilization. Yes, in this sense because
of our relative positions, you have more
ability and power to do that than I do.
Since I am not a part of your main
archetypal substream, yes, not directly.
Indirectly, yes, but not directly. Am I
supposed to learn something from that or
did that just sort of happen out of left
field? What is happening is an indication that
What is happening is an indication that
you are learning something from it in
your own way. And to say more would be
to in a sense open your present before
it is Christmas.
Great. Just what I need another mystery,
right? You all love them. Yeah. Okay. Uh thank
You all love them. Yeah. Okay. Uh thank
you for your willingness at
selfdiscovery. We thank you. We thank you. One moment.
We thank you. We thank you. One moment.
One moment.
was the wind.
A tangent another
direction. Many of you are beginning to
realize we have discussed many ideas and
aspects of dolphin consciousness with
you. The idea now is that many of you
are awakening to the fact that there are
in your terminologies the ideas of mass
death of dolphin life upon certain
shores of your planet. We have discussed
to some degree the idea at that time
that it was our sensitivity that their
electromagnetic patterns had shifted.
This was causing some misdirection and
confusion within them. Another door has
now opened that allows us to see even as
you are discovering that it is their
identification with you in your dreams.
states that have allowed them to
incorporate within their physical state
enough of an identification to have done
something we did not know they were
going to do and did not even perceive it
in that way until they created it with
their decision-making process. They are
assimilating and mimicking and
reflecting a lot of the ideas of
negativity that are going on in your
system now and they are to some degree
acting as safety valves to bend and
balance the idea of that system within
yourselves at this time.
The idea is that they have created among
themselves the ability to shift their
electromagnetic frequencies to allow
themselves to create a form their
version of the main diseases you are
dealing with in your society now that
you would call AIDS.
They have dropped their immunity. They
are assisting you in blending and
balancing that idea so that you will not
have to in a sense endure it
alone. They are willing to be members of
your society and blend with you even in
the negative sides. to show you that
they share your world with
you. They do not remain
aloof. They love you dearly, dearly
enough to take upon your own creations
and in that sense to assist in the
alleviation and the transformation of
those negative
ideas. We extend our thanks to them as
we know you do in this way. Their love
interacts with you always. And we firmly
are now given an opportunity to see that
by this action you are becoming more
closely intertwined on many different
levels than even we at first were
allowed to
perceive. We thank you for your loving
sharing dreaming. We thank
dreaming. We thank
you and we bid you fond and loving and
gentle new dawn. Good day. Good day.
[Applause]
Ah, good job.
How did it go? [Applause]
[Applause]
As I mentioned before, those of you who
would like a copy of tonight's tape, you
can have it tonight.