All right. Al, how are you all this
evening of your time as you create time
to
exist? We thank you in this way and we
begin this evening's interaction with
the Ivy that we have discussed with you
a few times about your physiological
reality being a shadow of the real you,
the physical reality being a shadow of
the soul. in this way. Now, in no way,
shape or form do we intend with this
discussion to denigrate the idea of
physiological reality for physical
reality is valid as an experience, as an
expression of life, and it is in every
way equal to any other level of being.
It may be more focused in many ways.
Other levels of being may be more
expanded as you call it, may be grander
in their scope. But the idea of
physiological reality is simply another
way in which you can express yourself as
spirit. And the idea of your physical
body is simply once again spirit energy
coalesed into a particular frequency
pattern and in no way shape or form is
meant to imply that physical reality is
any less than any other level of
existence upon which you already
exist. And therefore in this way by the
examples we will now give no denigration
is meant of physical reality. We are not
in a sense making light of it. But we
will remind you of something you are
very familiar with. You know and you
have seen many times and many of you
have yourselves played this game. This
idea of shining a light on one of your
walls and raising your hands and making
shadows upon the wall and living out
through the idea you call
fantasy the images and the shapes that
are projected
therein. In this way as you play this
game you may use this as an analogy as a
reference in the sense that the soul is
doing much the same idea. It is in a
sense using the light of creation and it
is allowing that light to pass through
itself in such a way that upon the
artificial screen it creates are
projected the images the shadows that
you call physiological reality. Now the
soul from that level from the level you
are as a non-physical being knows that
this physical reality is simply the
shadows and in this way it recognizes it
as and again no denigration meant as a
game. It simply knows that what is
projected upon the wall is not literally
who and what it is is not the end all be
all of its existence but is simply one
way in which it can present and
represent ideas. It is one way in which
it can play scenarios out upon a
particular type of stake if you will.
And just as the shadow seems flat in a
sense to you, seems twodimensional in a
sense to you, at least the part you can
see on the wall, you recognize that to
the higher self, physical reality is
also in a sense flat in a sense an
illusion and a projection. In that way,
it contains really no substance. All of
the substance, the essence is in the
soul that is projecting the image. But
that image is still a part in that way
of the soul. It is a representation of
the substance of the essence of the
soul. It is an outline that represents
an idea, a configuration if you will.
And thus for the purpose of the scenario
being played out, it will do as a
representative symbol. It will get the
idea across. But there has a time come in
across. But there has a time come in
your reality when you have, as we have
discussed, forgotten that you have been
playing this game. forgotten that these
images are merely projections upon the
wall of the soul's reality. And many
times you feel that these shadow images
become more substantial, more and more
solid than even you feels at times
yourself to be. Many times you allow the
idea of these shadow actions to
overwhelm you in that way. You think of
these ideas as impenetrable. You see
only the darkness of the shadow and
think that there are many things hidden
within. Not realizing the true
insubstantiality and flimsiness, if you
will, of the shadow. It is only a
projection of your minds, of your ideas,
of your beliefs, of the things you think
are real, the things you decide are true
for you. And therefore, when you allow
the idea of this shadow projection game
to
become something that happens not from
you, but to you, seemingly from outside,
seemingly not under your control, then
many of you have allowed these shadows
to take on your own illusionary forms.
You give them more dimension in a sense
than they truly have by themselves. And
it is that added dimension of fear that
gives them the substance and the
solidity they seem to have many times.
In this way, the fear is what makes the
shadow overwhelming. But it is only an
appearance. It is only something that
you label the shadow to be. It is only
the label of an actor in a play in that
way. Fear. It is only a name.
The idea in and of itself is no more
intrinsically overwhelming than any
other way to look at physical reality.
Any other idea you could label the
shadow to be. Recognize therefore that
many times all of the so-called
suffering, all of the so-called
struggling that you are doing in life is
really nothing more than shadow boxing.
You are in this way fainting with
specters, with reflections in the mirror
of your existence. They are no more
substantial than you believe them to be
or want them to be. But while you are in
that play because you have decided to be
one of the actors, then you will believe
that it is real. You will play it out in
that sense. And the play, the more you
believe it is in that sense real, the
only reality it will become, the less
you will remember that you have the
ability at any given time to step back
from that stage and be in the audience
watching yourself in that sense
recognizing it for the scenario that it
is, for the play that it is, for the
prop that it is. It is a prop and it is
a valuable prop. And you can learn much
from watching a play. And you can
understand much about yourself from
participating in a play. But recognize
you are the author of the play. And at
any given moment, you can decide what
lines to say, what actions to write into
that play. No one pulls the strings. You
are not a marionette. You are not a
puppet. In that way, you have set the
stage. You have ordered the props. You
are the designer. You are the author.
You are the producer. You are the
director. You are all the actors and
actresses. You are the stage
itself. You are playing life within
yourself within the idea within the
universe that you
are. In this way, therefore, allow
yourself now to know that what is
occurring in your play is that the house
lights are coming
on. You are lightening up. You are
awakening self-enlightenment. You are saying, "All
self-enlightenment. You are saying, "All
right, up with the lights." And now I
can see that this has only been a play.
Not that that invalidates it, for it has
been a beautiful piece of art. But it is
a play and plays come and
go. You can change now. The new play
that will be on the stage that you are a
new show, a new
opening, opening
night. That is the title of your
tape. And so as you now lift pen to
paper if you will and begin to write the
first act, allow yourself now to know that you
act, allow yourself now to know that you
are writing with the lights on and you
can see clearly the paper before you.
And every word that is there will be in
your penmanship. You will decide what you
penmanship. You will decide what you
will be, what you will play, what the
act will be all about.
You will orchestrate it. You will direct
the play that you are. And all the other
characters will be there because they
chose to
audition and you gave them the
part. And this goes for each and every
one of you. You are appearing in
everyone else's
play, starring in your
own, starring in everyone else's. In a
sense you
are that creative, you are that
simultaneous and you are that
spontaneous if you are willing to
believe it. You are very creative
playwrights. The play that you have been
acting out has been going on now for
some several tens of thousands of years.
The seats have been full every
night. Sellout
performances every life. And
life. And
so have no fear. Any new play you write
will be just as
popular. You will still find as many
individuals who will want to act in that
play with you. You will not be alone.
Just because you now find that the play
you wish to write is something that
perhaps has not been a part of the play
you have been acting in does not mean
that it will not be seen for what it is
and it will not be enjoyed for what it
is. And it does not mean you will not
find all the individuals necessary who
are willing to participate in the new
play.
create. We know you are quite capable of
it.
Thank you. The curtain is going up.
Sure. Hey, I was creating a very interesting
Hey, I was creating a very interesting
play at work. All right. And I really
enjoyed it uh while it lasted. And I
create I created this job where I was
working on a seminar that Shirley Mlan
was putting on on connecting with your
higher self. Which is something that I
really strongly believe in. All right.
And I was really enjoying it. And I
created this lady coming in as the new
office manager and producing a lot of
turmoil and laying me off. All right.
And I've been wondering about why that I
created such a short play because I was
really enjoying myself. But the play
once again is still going on. It is
simply act
two. What is the part now you can play
in the new circumstance you have written
for yourself? I don't know. What does
this allow you to now make room for?
Unemployment. [Laughter]
[Laughter]
Perhaps it is simply time to realize
that you were playing under stududy. Now
perhaps it is time for you to take over
the park.
What about putting on your own?
I like that idea, but I don't feel like
I'm ready to do it. If you say so. How
long do you think it will take before
you are? Well, I'd like to be in contact
with my own higher self before I put on
a But you are, and you always have
been. Now, different individuals will
allow themselves to recognize they are
always in communication with their
higher selves in different ways. It
doesn't have to be the way someone
else's play has written in the part.
Oh, in this play I will be in contact
with my higher consciousness over all
the telephone. In this play, I will be in
telephone. In this play, I will be in
contact with my higher consciousness
simply in the events I discover while
walking through a
park. There are many different ways to
allow yourself to know you are in
contact with all the information you
need to be in contact with at any given
moment. There is no reason to assume that it
There is no reason to assume that it
must come in a specific methodology
before you are allowed to act upon what
excites you at any given moment. Also
recognize that whatever it is at any
given moment that does excite you many
times is representative of communication
from your higher self. And if you will
but act upon it, you will then show your
higher self that you are listening.
You follow me? Yes. What do you think
you need to do to be the idea you wish
to be? But act as that idea and allow
yourself to draw into your life all the
props that are necessary to allow you to
continue to be that idea. Is this
something that truly excites you? Yes.
Then use your imagination, put pen to
paper and start outlining the things you
think would be very exciting for people
in the idea of sharing and being of
service and giving your own seminars as
you say. See what you come up with and
see if you are not more creative already
than perhaps you are willing to give
yourself credit for. When you allow
yourself to explore within your
imagination and allow that information
through without bias, without
invalidation, and without judgment, you
will recognize that you have already a
very strong conduit through you from
your higher self. Let it spill out. Let
it come
forth. It is always there. Only your
assumption that it is not is what is
holding it
back. Jump in. be creative.
You follow me? Yes. If you wish, we
would enjoy very much after you sit down
and write out the scenario you think
would be exciting for your seminars if
you would share that with us.
Will you? Yes. Um, what I would like to
do is sort of to merge emotionally with
my higher self so that I would always be
coming from the emotional
point of view that all right I am like
here but you are still a physical being.
This does not mean that just because you
are connecting empathically that you are
going to lose the ability to reason. No,
I don't mean that. All right, then.
Right now, describe for me what do you
think that will be like to merge, as you
say, emotionally with your higher self?
How do you think that will be? How will
you recognize it when that occurs? What
will it look like? Can you describe it?
I know what it looks like cuz I've done
it already. All right, describe it. I
feel that everyone on Earth is one of my
loved ones just like they were
physically my brother or my sister. Yes,
they are. And I feel like we're all here
just to have fun. Yes. Now,
thank you. And I'm in bliss. Yes. And
that's what it feels like. As you
describe this to us, are you not at that
moment generating that vibration in
order to be able to recall it and
describe it?
No, because I'm not feeling it. I'm just
feeling nervous. Why aren't you? Oh,
nervous. Nervous. All right. But perhaps
what you are missing is that what you
are feeling as nervousness is the same
energy, but you are putting an
invalidation on it. So it comes through
as nervousness instead of excitement.
Anxiety and excitement are the same
energy. You are feeling it, but you are
interpreting it as nervousness because
of your frame of mind. That is the only
difference. You have the energy. Anytime
you quote unquote recall any experience
you would like to quote unquote have
again at the moment of recall, you are
having it right then and there because
you are invoking the vibration, the
feeling. You are creating it in the
present in order to be able to describe
what you quote unquote would like. You
are it at the moment you describe it.
Even if you feel it as nervousness or
anxiety, you simply are that energy. It
only comes through as nervousness
because you are putting stipulations
upon it. And do not think that you are
feeling it in the way you should. You
are putting your belief system as a
filter in the way and allowing it to
come out as anxiety rather than
recognizing it for what it is, as
excitement, as knowingness. You follow
me? I'll listen to the tape.
I'm sort of getting it. Oh, we know you
are. No matter what you think of
yourself, we believe in you utterly and
know beyond a shadow of a doubt that you
have the capability of doing anything
that excites you. Yes, sir. Once again,
do
remember that as we have said, the
universe does not throw you a one-sided
coin. Your ability to be excited by
something is your ability to manifest
it. Both sides of the coin are there. To
be able to be excited is to be able to
manifest or you would never become
excited about it to begin with. You
follow me? Yes. Trust in that. Trust
that if you have the capability to be
excited about something, that is your
sign that you have the ability to
manifest it effortlessly.
I also wondering, I would like to teach
half of this seminar and then channel an
entity who would teach the other half of
the seminar. You go right ahead. Well, I
have not been allowing myself to
channel. But there are many ways to
channel. And when you allow yourself to
channel first as you, then you will open
yourself up to anything else that can
communicate through you. Because first,
the only way anything else is going to
be able to communicate cleanly through
you is if you communicate cleanly with
yourself as
yourself. So be yourself and act upon
the things that move you. And when any
other consciousness sees you in the full
joy of simply being who you are, they
will know that you are open to other
levels of communication as well. You
follow me? Yes. All things will proceed
in their proper timing. Trust. Trust.
That is all you need.
Enjoy. Thank you. Thank you. I wanted to
ask you again why that I created this
lady in all of this turmoil because I
really felt like I was sort of a
bystander. You are perceiving it as
turmoil instead of perceiving the idea
as a part of the path and not an
interruption in it.
You follow me? Mhm. You do not have to
perceive it as turmoil. That is your
choice to pull turmoil out of a neutral
situation. Well, I wasn't really into it. Both
Well, I wasn't really into it. Both
sides were telling me how bad the vibes
were. And you bought into it. No. Well,
then why do you experience it as
turmoil? I don't. But I was wondering
since I wasn't uh they were saying so
but you have related it as a personal
experience. You have related it to
yourself personally because you find
yourself in a different scenario. You
had made the implication that the
turmoil was directly responsible for
your movement away from that
scenario. You follow me? Yes. Uh maybe I
stated it incorrectly. Not really. But
again, the idea is mostly to allow you
to know that while you can be of
assistance to many other individuals,
you cannot be responsible for them. And
in this way, if you find yourself quote
unquote being moved around because of a
scenario that you are involved in, then
why not simply take it for granted in a
positive point of view that the
vibration going on there is not the
vibration you are. And you removed
yourself so that you could stand clear
of something that has nothing to do with
you. Maybe in your terms once they resolve
Maybe in your terms once they resolve
themselves you will be able to go back
in. Maybe
not. But you know what reality you are.
You know what vibration you are. And if
you see a vibration in a situation that
has nothing to do with what you know to
be true for you. You will remove
yourself. You will allow it to remove
itself from you. I like that. Thank you.
Thank you. You have the ability to
recognize that yourself. Yes. Thank you
very much.
Please all remember one or two brief
questions. We have so many people
nowadays. So please keep it uh brief as
possible. Thank you. Hi Rashar.
Strawberry. How you doing? Perfect.
Daniel. Great. Often you speak of
following your
excitement. Uh why when I follow my when
I eat what excites me do I get fat?
Thank you.
[Applause] Recognize if you will that many times
Recognize if you will that many times
the idea that may in your terms pass for
excitement is actually the manifestation
of the energy as
anxiety. And that is
why perhaps the idea once again is to
recognize the difference between going
to something and running from something
because it is the same energy. Many
times you will not necessarily in
general be clear as to whether or not
you are allowing the energy to manifest
as excitement or anxiety.
I see. So it's a judgment on eating the
lasagna that results in the fat to some
degree, but it may also be the judgment
that creates the type of energy that
moves you to the lasagna instead of
using the energy in another way.
Maybe you follow me. Yeah, but it
doesn't sound very Italian,
but I followed a concept. I'll play with
it a bit. All right, it's up to you.
Okay, one other short one. All right. I
have observed that there is a
fascinating apparent mechanism which
goes that when you invest a lot of joy,
excitement, marvelousness in something
that that that for instance I go to
create a mockup, a dream, a vision, a
great love affair that uh then there
appears at times to be the manifestation
of intense
uh fear or terror at at the idea of not
achieving that, not pulling off the
objective. Wonderful. Then you are
giving yourself a prime opportunity to
examine what the beliefs are that you
have ingrained within yourself that
should cause such
fear. The beliefs that you have that
would allow you to think that it is more
probable that you will not get what you
desire than it is probable that you
will. It is your opportunity to use that
fear to recognize you have those beliefs
and examine why you have them so that
when you understand that you can change
them. Yeah. Since that's what I said to
myself, I figured that's what you would
say. Thank you. You're welcome. Thank you,
Thank you. You're welcome. Thank you,
Mr. Shann.
Hi, Bashar. Hi. Um, I uh was uh creating
my reality
was well, this is a a quote unquote past
situation. Yes. Um, I'm going to use
some uh fill in some uh generals for the
specifics. Say somebody tells me that
I'm going to get cancer if I do such and
such thing. Dad, and I say no, I'm not.
And I choose to consciously create that
I don't uh create things like that in my
life. All right. And uh I get it anyway.
All right. So, may I remind you many
times, first of all, again, that these
things are opportunities to truly
recognize what level of self-empowerment
you know you have. For if you have
co-created that idea and created it for
yourself in that way, it is again an
opportunity to recognize how much power
you do have in creating the scenario to
begin with and in recognizing that you
can create the scenario in another way.
But the idea also is to recognize that
the way you usually respond to
individuals who offer you these
suggestions is indicative of the fact
that you do actually have a fear and a
belief in the reality of that idea more
than any other. for the idea of your
response no I don't in a sense is a
conflictive one rather than the idea of
pulling out of them why they believe in
that reality and assisting them to
change that belief which will then
change you in that way but just to say
no I
don't many times is an indication of the
fear you actually have because you are
reacting you are in this way being
conflictive in your response which is an
indication that you actually are perhaps
buying into what they have offered to
you as a suggestion. Otherwise, you
would not need to recoil in that way
from it. You would dive head first into
it. How fascinating that you should
think so. Why do you think so? What has
created this belief within you? And so
forth to explore full speed ahead, head
first as you say, the idea of why you
should attract in your life someone who
would even suggest that idea to you. For
again many times the attraction of an
individual into your life who would make
that suggestion many times is an
indication of beliefs that you do have
within you. But in no way, shape or form
does that mean that it must remain so.
And you can look at it from the positive
point of view that having attracted an
individual into your life who might
suggest that to you is an opportunity to
show yourself that you perhaps do in
fact have those beliefs or you would
never probably have had to have heard
that individual say that to you. Now it
is your opportunity therefore to
recognize that the belief system has
been brought to the surface that it has
been pointed out and now you can deal
with it. Again, the situations that
happen in your life are not there to
show you you are stuck. They are not
there to show you you are a failure.
They are there to show you what the
beliefs are you have so that you can
know what they are so you can change
them so you can change the reality that
they have shown you exists within you.
You follow me? Yes. Yeah. Well, it just
uh it's like well I I was pretty sure
that I didn't have a belief in a certain
situation and then I situation but again
you are acting as if you think you have
failed. Change that
attitude. Listen to yourself. I was
pretty sure. Well, it really broke my
confidence. I've been sailing on pretty
quick. Did not break your confidence.
Nothing can break your confidence but
you. And again, you are once again
looking at it from a judgmental point of
view. As if there was the idea that your
confidence could even be broken. As if
you had to have the idea of confidence
so that it could be broken. Knowingness
is knowingness. Many times when
individuals in your society talk of
confidence, they talk about it as
something that might be able to be
broken. You talk about it as a wall rather than
You talk about it as a wall rather than
a foundation rather than an
understanding. You talk about it as a
tenuous thing. You talk about confidence
as if you are walking a tight rope.
Please don't do anything to upset my
confidence. You follow me? Yes. If you
watch yourself, if you are watching for
when situations might break your
confidence, then in a sense, all you're
saying is that you really have never
allowed yourself to simply know what is
true for you. And this is an opportunity
to recognize that that may be what you
have been doing. so that you can
dispense with the idea of needing to
maintain confidence, but rather you can
simply live your life in a knowing
way. There is a difference, a profound
difference between the
two. Again, each and every one of these
scenarios is yet another opportunity to
realize how many layers of beliefs you
have created for yourselves. You are
peeling yourself like the proverbial
onion. You are discovering that you have
wrapped yourself in thousands of
cloaks. You think you are dealing many
times with the foundational ideas. But
yet again you discover that you have
wrapped yourself with another illusion.
And so you will always peel them away.
Give yourself an opportunity to explore
these ideas.
Now you have an opportunity to
understand that you have been dealing in
the idea of confidence as if it were
something that someday might let you
down, might break down, that you might
not be able to hold it up. You were
treating it as if it were something that
you had to carry through life that you
had to watch out for every step.
Otherwise, there might be something out
there lurking in the darkness, lurking
in the shadow that might pop out and
someday break the confidence. Many times
when you talk about confidence, that's
the definition you give it. Now you have
given yourself a prime example, a prime
opportunity to realize that that is the
definition you gave to confidence. So
now you can change the idea. You can use
this like anything as an opportunity.
recognize the universe, yourself, the
idea of infinite creation. Never, ever,
ever, ever is there a scenario created
in your life that is too much for you to
handle. Never. In a sense, you are being
paid a
compliment. For in this way, the amount
of the idea that you think you must now
deal with is directly representative of
the actual strength you have to deal
with it. So, lighten
it. So, lighten
up. Lighten up. You can, if you are
willing to laugh it completely away.
That sounds like a good uh way to do it.
The curtain is going up.
This will be a comedy
definitely. If you are going to think,
if you insist upon thinking of the idea
of cancer with a capital C, at least let
the C stand for comedy. Okay?
[Music] Uh and also for
Uh and also for
catharsis, for that is what it is for
many individuals. A gate and a doorway to
individuals. A gate and a doorway to
walk through. So that in one sense, in
the old sense, you will recognize that
you as the person you have been will in
a sense die. But you do not have to
physically die to be born as the new
person you prefer to be. If you use the
idea of cancer as comedy and catharsis,
then you will allow yourself to become
the person in whose definition there is
no need for that tool or
disease. But that will invoke from you a
willingness to be that new person. And
that new person is one who enjoys life
itself. You follow me? Yes. Thank you
very much. I have a another quick one.
Uh, in Maui, I asked you about my camera
and you I asked you specifically if you
could tell me if the camera was in the
house. And you said yes. Yes. Were you
saying yes, you could tell me or yes,
the camera was in the house?
Why are you still concerned? I'm still
looking for it. Mor camera concern. I
love them. Crystals.
Crystal, does everything to you have to
be in your estimation picture perfect
before you will allow it? Very much not.
All right, then. For now, perhaps you do
not need to focus on that.
Well, it's just like for some reason
it's always there in my mind and I' I'd
like to just forget about it, but it's
like part of my life that seems like
that I would I just wish knew I knew
where it was. I'll tell you exactly
where it is. Oh, good. It is within you.
Oh, listen
carefully. It is you. You are the camera
for now. You remember what we have been
saying to many of you. Your recording
devices are an externalized idea. Many
of you will now find your recording
devices disappearing and in your terms
malfunctioning because you are now going
to function as the recording device. You
are now going to take the pictures and
create the pictures to be what you will
know will be the life you prefer to be.
You take the picture. You make the
picture. You are the camera now for now.
You will find it again physically after
you become it
first. Makes you shudder, doesn't it?
No. No. Thank you.
Thank you.
Understand the idea in a very literal
sense. In a very literal sense. We are
not simply being philosophical in your
terms. When we say you are the camera,
we mean it. Take me literally and start
acting like
it. Then you will see a difference.
I like the way that sounds because a
camera just like takes each second and
holds each second. All right. But you do
not have to hold on to it. The idea is
that you will always be existing in a
new second. The idea is not so much to
second. The idea is not so much to
collect images of the past.
You follow me? I do. I just like to
collect the images. Even though I don't
do anything with them, I just like
collecting them. It is representative of
an idea that you say you are attempting
to change for now
collecting another wide.
Thank you. Thank you Shannon.
Hello. Hello. Your uh humor is terrific
as is yours. Thank
you. I have two questions. The first one
is I've experienced considerable
difficulty in getting a clear career
direction and would like some guidance
in the matter. What excites you the
most? That's the problem. I haven't
found that problem.
All right. Let me ask you a question.
Yes. Why are you here this evening of
your time? Did it excite you to come
here? Yes. Then it is as simple as that.
What will you do when this conversation
is
ended? What will be the most exciting
thing you can think of to do that you
are capable of doing after you leave
this interaction this evening of your
time? Take it one step at a time. A
career can be many different things.
Doesn't have to be one thing. You are a
malleable being. Change being the only
constant in creation. Maybe the type of
career you will have will be a
multiaceted multi-changing one. If you
are focusing upon the idea just because
your society says that you should of
having one thing and one thing only that
you can consider and call your career
for life, then you may not be allowing
yourself the degree of
flexibility that will truly allow you to
know that perhaps simply life itself is
your
career. I'll accept
that second question. Speaking of our
society, in our society, organized
religion tends to condemn homosexuality.
What are your comments in regard to a
person being homosexual and the
relationship to spiritual growth? All
right, we will keep this brief since
there already exists literature in the
idea of our viewpoint upon this
subject. Nothing is either in your terms
right or wrong. But the idea has
blossomed in your society for a very
specific reason. And that is because for
many tens of thousands of years, what
you may refer to as the mainstream of
your society has refused to accept and
acknowledge that each and every
individual has within them the capacity
to blend the masculine and the feminine
energies into one idea. In refusing to
blend these ideas, in maintaining them
as separate dichotoies, then many
individuals simply took it upon
themselves in being born into your
society to attract life styles that
would generate within them an obvious
manifestation of the polarity energy
within them regardless of their
physiology. This was at first meant to
be a reflection to the mainstream of
your society that each and every
individual contained the potential of
both energies and that each and every
individual if they are willing to blend
these energies together will then
function in a balanced way. Not
separating the idea of this is
masculine, this is feminine and forever
shall they part. But the idea was not
understood. More and more invalidation
was heaped upon it to the point now
where it has blossomed in the idea of
spreading the idea of what you call the
diseases that now drop the barriers you
have set up, forcing the mainstream of
your society to interact and face
themselves on all the different levels
throughout time that they have refused
to face. When individuals marry within
themselves the masculine and feminine
energies and blend these ideas not
because it is right or wrong but simply
because it will no longer be needed.
Homosexuality will simply not exist in
your society. There will be love for all
in an
equal way. But the idea of an individual
who chooses to be born as one sexual
expression or another will simply
manifest the balance in that way.
manifesting blending of male and female
as a male or manifesting blending of a
male and female as a female and will not
need to reflect the dichotomy because
there will be no need for that tool any
longer. You follow me? Yes. Does that assist
You follow me? Yes. Does that assist
you? Yes. Thank you very much. Thank
you. [Music]
[Music]
Hi Bashar. Hi. Someone I work with uh
recently uh called in sick and uh then I
learned later on that they were in the
hospital that had an anorism, a stroke
and apparently the doctors had given
them no hope. Um about Well, that is all
right. Hope would not help them too
much. That's
true. And uh when I heard about it, I uh
wanted to go there and
um do all the healing and so on. And
then I stopped myself and I said, "Wait
a minute." Um, let me get in touch with
what was going on. And I sat down and I
kind of got in touch with myself and and
I believe him. And uh, instead of going
gung-ho and bringing tapes and all of
this, I said, "Wait a minute. Maybe he's
going through something that I need to
respect." All right. Very good. And um,
there are also many things you yourself
can learn from it while that individual
learns from it. Yes. That's that's why
I'm asking describing this and asking
the question. I uh then went there and
his family was there and we were all u
helping to heal him and I've been doing
some meditation and he's now
um well he was in a coma for 3 days and
he's now going to survive. Very good. We
thank you for
utilizing his chosen way of allowing
each and every one of you to
blossom of luring you into your higher
selves. This was by the idea of an agreement to
This was by the idea of an agreement to
shock you in a sense into a different
state to focus you on the idea of the
hard energy to know that unconditional
love is what will connect all of you and
allow all purposes in life to be
revealed.
We thank you for using the scenario in a
positive way and thereby generating the
positive result.
Thank you for your sharing and your
observation. We thank you. Thank you.
Shooting. Hi Basher. Hi. A very dear
friend of mine um just passed away from
cancer uh last week. All right.
uh she was 32 and she left a husband and
two children that
uh
I I want to know where her soul is right
now and how she's doing in her
transition to the other world. Um
always there is the assistance that is
necessary to acclimate the being to the
new understanding, the new
perspective in what you call the astral
realm. There is orientation going on.
There is now the understanding of what
the creation of disease is.
There is also the opportunity being
presented to this individual that she
can function for a while as spiritual
guides for her own
children. There may be maybe
maybe for this is not yet decided but
there may be an opportunity for this
individual to reincarnate as one of
their own children's
children. Maybe you follow me. Yes.
That's what I I really wanted to know
because I she was a very enlightened being and
I she was a very enlightened being and
she shared a lot of wonderful love and
light with many people and she had over
500 people at her memorial service.
Um and I just had this this thought
which I don't want to continue to create
was that once you get there there's no
longer any need to be alive on this
level and so you die. and she got there
at a a very young age and so it was like
I don't my myself started saying you
don't want to strive anymore for getting
perfect because if you do there you go
all right we understand what you are
saying however recognize that you will
never attain perfection no matter how
much you strive anyway for you are
already perfect now you can become any
sort of different perfect idea you wish
to
You can become a more expanded perfect
idea, but you will always be just as
perfect. You follow me?
Yes. I guess that she just seemed to
have everything together except her
health. Um, understand there is a reason
for the timing. That is not an
indication of an
imperfection. It is an indication of the
timing that was necessary so that she
could now be of assistance in another
way. The idea was that she was accelerated to
The idea was that she was accelerated to
the point where then she could
accelerate herself to another level to
be of assistance in another way in the
way she agreed to be of assistance to
those individuals still
physical. She can now in many ways
actually do the thing she agreed to do.
If she had remained physical, she would
not necessarily have been able to do
so or of themselves because they are
stretching to reach
her. You follow me?
Yes, everything functions within perfect
timing. Everything. It was simply a
convenient way to accelerate the idea of
the physiological death.
You follow me? Yes. And that that's
helping in in my own grief over her over
her loss for it's as as much as I know
that um she is now free of the pain that
that uh wrecked her physical body for so
long. Um I had my own sadness for missing all
Um I had my own sadness for missing all
right for missing her of course
recognize there is no loss for she still
exists and she is still here and now in
her own dimensional way and the idea
that many individuals in your terms who
do choose to accelerate themselves in
life not that they have to but simply
many of them have chosen that if there
is going to be any exploration of
negativity of pain then many of them choose to
of pain then many of them choose to
accelerate it rapidly. So in a sense
they will get it all out of the
way. The next life this individual has
if she chooses to live again will be one
of complete and absolute ecstasy for the
time frame in which she'll be born will
be very solidly within the next
transformational age. You follow me? Yes. She has in that
age. You follow me? Yes. She has in that
brief spasm, if you will, of pain,
completely accelerated herself beyond
the complete old karmic
cycle. She has lived in that brief spasm
what other individuals may have chosen
to experience as lesser negativity in
many lifetimes. You follow me? Yes. And that
lifetimes. You follow me? Yes. And that
was for her a measure of how powerful
she knew she was.
She is still that powerful and more.
Feel her
power, not the loss because there is no
loss. Feel the power that she knew she
had to have created the scenario in that
way. And you will be bathed in the idea
of that being. And you will then allow
that being to allow you to be bathed in
your own energy of self-empowerment.
identify with the power that she is.
I sense that very much at her memorial
service her presence and all will be
fourth or fifth dimensional now is it
let us say fourth basically fourth
non-physical but in that way the fourth
non-physical will be the level that
maintains a connection to the earth
plain so it can still be of assistance
in many different ways fifth density
would usually take that being beyond the
realm of the earth plain for now she is
in your terms hanging around
to be of assistance and guidance.
Thank you. Thank you very much, Bashar.
Sharing. Good evening, Bashar. Good evening or
Good evening, Bashar. Good evening or
good day from my point of view. All
right. All right. I have two questions.
All right. One I came with and one uh
arose from your opening remarks. All
right. I'd like to ask about that.
First, when you uh gave us the analogy
of the pictures on the wall, yes. Is
that in fact what the Egyptians were
telling us with their two-dimensional
paintings? And if so, how does that
relate to their pyramid? Very good. To
some degree, yes, they were. The
stylized art form was an understanding
that the physical form is very much like
a shadow in that way. To the higher
self, it is very
two-dimensional. The pyramid in that way
was their tool for accessing that higher
self, for aligning the vibrations that
they were so that they could in fact
realize that the physical dimension you
think of as very solid was in fact
simply an illusion, simply a shadow. In
being in many of the chambers within
those pyramids, they allow themselves to
exit the body and get the perspective
that gave them the understanding of the
physical reality's
shadowness. You follow me? Yes. It was
the fourthdimensional tool that allowed
them to understand the third
dimension in a sense in a
two-dimensional way. You follow me? No,
you I fell off. The pyramid is a fourth
density tool. They projected themselves
into the fourth dimension and therefore
their perspective of the third dimension
lost its solidity. Okay. Many times
individuals when you are in your terms
walking down your street and you all of
a sudden for your own reasons and your
own timing snap into that awareness and
that alignment. Have not many of you
felt that the physical dimension around
you all of a sudden was very
flat almost as you say made out of
cardboard like a set not quite real not
quite solid that you could look behind
solid that you could look behind
it. This is the analogy to some degree
of their
art and the reason for the pyramid. It
is a magnet. It is a
lens for the electro and
athethereroagnetic field of your world.
When you allow that lens to focus that
energy into your vibrational oric field,
it will then instill imprint upon your
oric field the idea of that pattern that
will allow you to expand and blossom
into the more expanded higher self.
You follow me? Yes. Does that assist
you? Thank you. Thank you very much
sharing. I have one other question. All
right. In our continuing efforts to uh
explore our relationship with our
brothers, the dolphins, we have
discovered an unusual boy who in two
weeks will be the youngest college
graduate in the history of the United
States. He'll be 10 years old. Uh they
tell me that his IQ is in excess of 200.
They can't really measure it. Uh he's
building his fourth computer and he is
obviously clairvoyant. They are not
they're downplay downplaying that side
of his personality, but I'm told he
spoke fluent uh ancient Greek at the age
of three. Any event, he loved dolphins.
He is feels very close to dolphins. He
dreams about dolphins and we have now
very fortunately connected with him and
we are bringing him down to be with our
dolphins in about 10 days. All right. My
question is who is he and where is he
from?
This is again as we have said one of the
many individuals as most of the idea of
the children of your age now are who are
forgetting less of themsel and
remembering more because this is the
transformational age. This ability is
equal to all of you. Any of you can
express this ability this recognition.
It is simply that this child has allowed
himself to be born into your world and
has not forgotten as much of who he is
collectively. You follow me? Yes. There
are many connections that can be made.
All of which in a sense will be
arbitrary. There are connections to
other levels, other realms, other
civilizations. For now, you do not
really need them. But the idea can
be that in showing this child what you
will call a double tetrahedrin, one
facing up, one facing
down, and allow this child to function
in the notion of
triads. Then this child may be able to
begin to explain the understandings of
how consciousness itself fits into what
you colloquially call your scientific
equations. particularly regarding what
you call your artificially intelligent
computers. All right. What the child
will be learning also from the dolphin
is how to allow computers to become
empathic. Now let us remind you once
again as we have recently done for other
individuals upon your world that you
usually think of telepathy as a
primarily mental process. We have
discussed the understanding that of
course telepathy is emotionally
activated. Therefore, let us put once
again into fruition the idea of coining
a new word and recognizing that the more
precise definition of what you colloally
call telepathy is actually
teleathy. This is what the child is
exhibiting. the acute ability to
completely identify with and as any
identify with and as any
concept with whom this child
interacts. This child can also be
responsible for the idea of bringing
back techniques as many other
individuals are from Atlantean times to
increase the learning process 10fold
100fold for any individual. this child
may be able to revolutionize the idea of
the learning process ease and
revolutionize the idea of what you call
school to begin with.
You follow me? That's what he said. Yes. Enjoy.
Enjoy.
When simply treat the child as a
reflection of yourself as well. Do not
place the child above you in that sense.
for the child only reflects the
understanding without forgetfulness of
what you all are capable of doing. Not
that you have to express it in that way.
If if the child is going to in fact
revolutionize computers as we know them,
which I believe and we've discussed
before that the dolphins are in fact a
collective 31 million year old computer.
Nice. uh and that each and every dolphin
on the planet is is a is a station to
that computer is a key to it. Uh if this
child can break through and
interpret then it really is an
extraordinary event, isn't it? Of
course. Okay.
But the idea also is that the so-called
revolution has already occurred in your
collective consciousness and the child
is simply the representative tool of
that revolution. You follow it? It is not
revolution. You follow it? It is not
that the entire idea of the
revolutionizing of these notions is
contained within the child specifically.
It is that the entire revolution already
exists in your consciousness and thus
the child was capable of existing in
your society at this time. No one is
ever truly ahead of their time. Everyone
is always exactly a product of their
time. Will will will the child have
credibility? I mean in the world the
child doesn't [Applause]
[Applause]
care. This is not an issue. You follow
me? It is not an
issue. It is not an issue. Okay?
It does not exist in the child's
reality. It will never be encountered as
a
problem. Actions will speak for
themselves. They will be the line of
credit and it will be unlimited.
You follow me? Yes. Thank you. Thank
you. Shedding.
You are of course applauding yourselves.
For you are creating the reality.
Hi Var. Hi. How are you? Perfect. And
you? Just great. Yay. Um, I have this
thing called epilepsy. The doctors say I
have been called epilepsy for 28 years.
I've been taking medication. And I tell
you, I do not believe that I have
epilepsy and I want a cure of it. I'm
I'm I'm ready to say hey I don't really
have this you know all right why did I
create it and you know how can I rid of
it let us tell you something about the
notion of epilepsy okay you will
understand that first of all of course
it is the product of your society's
belief systems with regard to the way
energy comes through your brain or
expresses itself as your brain from your
higher self you have now fractionated
your idea of the brain into many
components and you have fractionated
into the idea of a left and right
hemisphere when in fact the brain is one
whole idea. Right? It is the maintenance
of this idea of a left and right
hemisphere that many times can allow
there to be the lack of communication
that goes on between the hemispheres
that creates what you call the epilepsy.
Right? The epilepsy itself is the result
therefore of when the brain begins to
act as a homogeneous unit and fires as a
unit simultaneously but fires through
the filtering belief system that it
exists as a collection of parts. then it
throws everything out of whack so to
speak. It shorts the system out because
you do not create the idea that the
system can handle that type of
unification firing. M now one idea one
exercise if you will that can assist in
alleviating this notion is to think if
you already do of the two hemispheres
and allow yourself to generate the idea
of energy flowing simultaneously in both
of those hemispheres in a circular
motion and then allow them
smoothly to cross. Oh yeah. Do you
recognize the symbol that is being
created? I believe that you said that.
Because I I'm going to a doctor, not a
doctor, but a psychotherapist, and he
put me in a meditation. And the
meditation that I saw was exactly what
you're doing. It went like this. It was
like this. Recognize that you are the
infinity symbol. God, it was just
exactly that. At the crux point of the
infinity symbol is you, the gate, the
door through which your consciousness
comes. Now, understand something else
about the idea of seizures and epilepsy.
Many the vast majority again because of
the belief systems of the society of
individuals who have become what you
call very obvious channels in this life
including the physical channel before
you have during their life experienced
some sort of shock to the head seizure
or epileptic attack. Well, I was telling
my friend tonight that I would really
like to be a channeler myself. Is that a
possibility? Oh, yes. Easily, huh? Oh,
yes. Oh, God. You understand the idea is
that the epileptic shock takes you all
at once out of all of the preconceived
notions you have bought into in your
society. Right? You are a completely
fluctuating being commodity. Sounds
great. You are a completely randomized
factor. Now, it does not have to express
itself as loss of control if you are
willing to allow it to come through in a
homogenized way and express itself as
creative service.
Okay, you follow me? I follow you. To
some degree. Also, what you experience
in your reality as stuttering is a
result of minor epileptic seizures. And
again the blending of the hemispheres
through the center which is you can
alleviate this idea. See it as an energy
orchestration. Feel yourself to be one
homogeneous energy not a collection of parts. Right?
energy not a collection of parts. Right?
When you are one homogeneous energy,
then you will not necessarily think that
all the parts are difficult to allow
them to communicate fluidly with each
other. Right? You will not have to feel
that you are juggling many different
things. You will not have to feel that
you have to coordinate many diversified
ideas. Okay? You will function as a
conduit. And can I just how to do this is just
And can I just how to do this is just
like uh close my eyes and go into my
mind and just like visualize what you're
saying right now. Just visualize in your
mind and breathe deeply slowly deeply.
Does this mean I can stop taking
medication in the whole You will know
when you no longer need that tool. Okay.
I thank you very much. I thank you for
your willingness.
[Applause] Hello again, Bashar. Hello. Boy, are you
Hello again, Bashar. Hello. Boy, are you
getting popular. It's hard to get up
here. You are very popular with many
civilizations as well. Thank you.
You put on quite a show. I bet I do.
Thank you.
[Music] First of all, I want to tell you how
First of all, I want to tell you how
grateful I am for these sharings and I
my love to all of you. Our love to you
and our appreciation for your
willingness to co-create these
interactions. Um but I want to ask your
reflection on a prop that seems to
reappear in my life quite frequently.
All right. um this last Christmas
unbeknownst to one moment before you
continue hear what you have said it may
be a prop that reappear but that has
nothing to do with the meaning behind
the prop which always can change right
it's the symbology I'm interested in
that is your doing continue okay this
last Christmas the first two presents I
opened were both hummingbirds there was
a little crystal hummingbird that you
hang in the window and then there was a
wooden one do you remember what we have
said about the symbol of the hummingbird
I wanted to ask you that again. It
represents your higher accelerated
consciousness. But recognize that the
hummingbird exists at a highly
accelerated rate of perception. To the
hummingbird, you appear to be moving
like this. The hummingbird therefore is your
this. The hummingbird therefore is your
symbol of communication with your higher
consciousness. Many of you have had an
increase in interactions with the symbol
and the reality of the animal of the
hummingbird in this fourth density
reality for it represents your
accelerated rate of awareness. It is you
looking back at yourself from your
future self. I like that also Bashar
that it triggered a realization that
birds in general have played a very
significant part in my life. I've raised
some very unusual birds and I've taken
care of injured birds and look for them.
come to me and I've had many many kinds
and I wondered if birds in general um
represent oh and when I was thinking
about asking this question on the way
here huge owl flew over the car and I
thought oh how gorgeous and it turned
around and flew back over again you know
oh great I have to ask this question so
do birds in general symbolize something
that you see or you already know in
general what they can symbolize in terms
of flight in terms of freedom you know
that each and every one of them can also be
each and every one of them can also be
specific as a symbol and there can be as
many references to these symbols as
there are individuals that perceive
them. The owl in that way not only the
general idea of the wisdom you associate
with it but also the owl is a very
spiritual symbol. Yes, I realize that
it's a very ancient symbol, right? Yes.
It represents the idea purely of spirit
itself. It is an astral symbol. I was
going to ask you because I'm real
fascinated with astral travel. Always
have been. Yes. And I've had some
unusual experiences with that. Become
the owl and you will experience astral
travel. Identify as it as completely as
you can. I like that. Okay, one more
question. You have had this ability in
other lines. Um, I had a feeling that I
had. Yes. Would it be the Egyptian life
to some degree, but more specifically
what you would call the idea of North
and South American Indians? Oh, that's
great. Machu Picchu.
Try it on here. No comment. Okay. No
comment. Okay. Bashar, this last week I
read Whitley Shrivever's book Communion.
Hi. And it's about his encounters with
extraterrestrials that he's had all
life. And I experienced when you know he
he speaks about his terror he had about
beings that were so different than human
in form. and following him through the
book, I got to a point where I got so
excited about the idea and I realized
that I've been very excited about that
since I was much younger when I used to
run outside the house at night and say,
"Take me, take me." Everybody would
laugh and I thought that was great and
you know, but I was really a little
afraid of it, very fascinated with it.
We assume in this way that one of the
portions that stood out strongly to you
was the reference to the symbol of the
owl. Do you remember?
Do you remember?
You mean the wisdom, the the uh the
idea, the within that individual,
there was the memory of having seen an
owl to replace the actual memory of
having seen the extraterrestrial. His
coverup memory. Yes. Very interesting.
Yes. Oh, I wanted to ask you, I got so
excited that I started drawing a picture
of what I thought this bean, one of the
main beans in the book, would look like.
Yes. And the more I worked on it, the
more excited I got. And I I it suddenly
occurred to me. I thought maybe this is
because I'm going to have an experience
such as going to in this life. Yeah.
Well, that I'll remember, you know.
You have tapped into that energy many
times. It is now a recognition.
Okay. Follow it. Follow it. Okay. Thank
you. This is the time for remembering
lost time. I like that. Thank you very
much for We thank you.
chatting.
Hello my friends. And you? H wonderful
tonight. Always. Always. Yes. Uh I find
that life is very exciting by
definition. Yes. And also I find that um
I have been experiencing so much shall
we say quote hell last year going
through many things learning. Right. And
experiencing and coming out feeling
wonderful about it. Yes. And creating
heaven out of hell. That's right. That's
what I've been doing. And uh I felt up
until a couple of days ago, I felt like
I was ah back in my hell again. And then
through Steve's fantastic counseling, my
I'm flying high. All right. And really
looking forward to many things. And I
wanted to share uh something with you
that's been happening since then. All
right. And it's so exciting because um
I've been wanting now for a year and a
half since I retired I've been wanting
to travel to Shasta too many places but
then postponing it and I wanted to get
rid of the big heavy furniture that
apartment somehow they never did it and
then I kept giving my landlord notice
and then withdrawing that notice and so
they finally said well why don't you
move out next month and I said I think
that's fantastic and so now I went into
action And today I have the whole thing re uh
And today I have the whole thing re uh
what what do you orchestrated? Yay. And
it's I know now that I'm going to sell
most of the heavy furniture. I'm going
to move in with a friend for a while.
Also, you are also lightening up. All
right. So, no more heavy furniture.
Yes. It was just like a symbol. I kept
that heavy furniture around and I said,
I don't want it anymore. And so, I'm
looking forward to many fantastic
Absolutely. You have a hell of a good
time.
And another thing I wanted to uh ask and
to have uh all the people here blend
their energy if they wish to and that is
that they are have decided now to we
have through the government decided to
shoot a bunch of the mountain lions open
them up for hunting and tomorrow at Long
Beach there's going to be a big meeting
to try to get this or to uh to stop
this. And I thought if we would all just
put our energies there, whether we're
there or someplace else, uh I know that
uh I for one don't want to see those
beautiful animals killed. All right. Use
your unconditional love. This is not a
conflict. Mhm. This is an opportunity to
express a reflection of the true natural
grace and power that that animal
represents. teach and show these individuals that
teach and show these individuals that
they are symbols of their own natural
grace and power and that all killing in
that sense is actually suicide.
Yes. Of a portion of themselves.
Teach them to learn they can identify.
Teach them to learn they can learn
much from those beings, those
reflections, those guides, those
animals. that they can
that they can
become
those mountain lions.
Thank you. We thank
you. You may all at this time take a
short break.
How's everything going?
All right, we will say proceed.
Thank you. My name is Terry. All right.
You shared an experience with us in
which you took responsibility once for
another person's actions and in order to
balance this act which occurred in the
now you went back into one of your past
lives presumably in an alternate time
track and produced a disease. Now if you
create your own universe, if you create
your own reality, if the universe
reflects whatever belief system you
have, why didn't you change your reality
or belief system such that the issue of
integrity or the balancing of actions uh
did not enter? Now if you could not do
that, it must be that there must be uh
some absolute cosmic laws which must be
adhered to. If that's the case, then
believing in your own reality is limited
to uh adhering to these cosmic laws or
at least within the boundaries of those
laws. Are there any absolutes in the
universe? If there are, what are they?
If there are not any absolutes in the
universe. All right. Thank you. Then why did you
All right. Thank you. Then why did you
adopt that belief system? Thank you.
Recognize first of all that the
so-called absolutes for all universes is
but one. the fact that you exist. Now
each and every universe can create its
own apparent absolutes to some degree
and by that particular rule by those
particular rules of that particular
game. Then there are generally agreed
upon absolutes that will generally be
followed and in abiding by those you
will then maintain the balance of the
energy within the total game that you
are playing. That is also dissolvable
but only when you extract yourself from
that universal absolute that you have
agreed to create. They are not absolute
absolutes, but they will appear to be
just as solid as a so-called absolute as
long as you agree in general to abide by
them. Within the universe in which I
exist, I agree to abide by the notion of
the balancing in that way that there
were scenarios in my past life wherein
the playing out of certain positive and
or negative ideas was quote unquote
acceptable then. And therefore any idea
that would fit into allowing that being
I was then to learn what it needed to
learn through that particular
understanding or disease at that time
was put in your terms to good use.
In our universe is karma an absolute law
in the same sense? No. Except in the
sense that it is only a representation
of a
momentum. Karma in that way is
completely self-imposed. The idea, the
methodologies so to speak of the karma
are completely self-imposed. The
so-called absolute within the universal
game is simply that it will represent a
momentum, a balance, a carry through of
an idea once initiated. How it carries
through and how it balances out can
occur in many different ways. Evol. Yes.
The karmic absolute is simply that the
energy once initiated will carry through
as a momentum. But how that plays itself
out will depend upon the reasoning
within any given life that requires that
manifestation and can use that
manifestation to learn something from.
In other words, the generation of that
balance point that I created was usable
in one of my past lives. So I allowed it
to stand in that way knowing that that
past life had the belief systems that
would generate that type of reality and
therefore it could use that type of
reality to learn that it did not need to
create that type of reality anymore. And
that is what allowed me to maintain the
existence that I do now where I know I
am the creator of my reality. For the me
that had the disease was not in
cognition that they were the creator of
their reality. And that disease allowed
them to learn that so that I could be
who I am today. You follow me? Yes. Does
that assist you? Yes, it does. The
personality in that previous life was in
an alternate time track. Was that
personality associated with your soul?
In which case, does that mean that one
soul has multiple number of
personalities? Oh, absolutely. The
oversoul has an infinite number of
fragments. It may choose to project these fragments
It may choose to project these fragments
into any given game at any given moment
in an infinite number of time travel.
Yes. If the soul is that infinite, what
comes after the soul? What could be more
infinite than that? Nothing. But you are
assuming that there is an after and
there isn't. Everything only is now
simultaneously. The notion of a before
and an after is one of the games you are
playing. It's my understanding that
there comes a point in evolution where
one no longer needs a soul. Is that
true? One is a soul in a sense.
You may no longer need particular
manifestations of the spirit that you
are, of the soul that you are. But in a
sense, a soul is what you
are. Although there may be many
different definitions to that, many of
which might be semantically arbitrary.
Your meaning of a soul and a fifth
density being's meaning of a soul might
be pointing to two different
fluctuations or representations of
energy. You follow me? Thank you. Thank
you. You are simply
consciousness if you will. You will
always be that in whatever way you
choose to manifest yourself. Thank you.
Thank you. Shannon. Hi Vashar. Hi. Um
about no exactly two Saturdays ago while
Barnett and I were sleeping at the
beach. Uh my imagination tells me it was
about 3:00 a.m. He awoke abruptly and
woke woke me up immediately. And in the
picture window right over the ocean.
Yes. Uh there was you saw another
picture window.
Yes. And in that window there was a very
bright light that either was getting
closer or very or brighter dome-shaped.
All white lights. Very bright. And uh
around the circumference of the center
dome or little white light. Nice. We
stared at it I'd say for about 30
seconds. And then all of a sudden to the
left of the uh dome-shaped light there
was a flash in the sky in the shape of a
perfect square that was huge.
As if and I felt Oh well there a picture
was just being taken. A picture window.
Yes. Okay. Uh from your window through their
Okay. Uh from your window through their
window. from their window through your
window, window to window, interface to
interface, facet to facet, doorway to
doorway. It was a gate, an energy gate.
Would you be willing to tell serious?
Okay. Um, and uh, how I read the energy at
Um, and uh, how I read the energy at
this time is that we will have more
opportunities to go through that gate
again. Oh yes. Okay. Thank you. Thank
you very much. Thank you.
chatting. Hi Bashar. Hi. Um I have one question
Hi Bashar. Hi. Um I have one question
and one sharing. All right. Both are
sharing. Both are sharing. One is in a
question format.
Um a a couple months ago when I started
learning how to channel, I was
experiencing a lot of gratitude for the
relationship that I had with the entity
that I channelneled. In addition to
that, I was experiencing a lot of
gratitude for all of the entities who
are channeling through beings on the
planet. And my personal experience at that time
And my personal experience at that time
was like why are entities choosing to
channel? And I woke up in the middle of
the night um after having an experience
um and I think it was it wasn't a dream.
It was like I was on your ship and you
were expressing to me your deep
gratitude and excitement and love,
enormous love for all of those
individuals involved in both the
channeling process and those individuals
who have chosen to receive information
from entities who are coming through
and I wanted to thank you for that
experience. erience because it had
profound impact on my own channeling and
um you are the most profound impact upon
your own channeling but thank you again.
Thank you.
Um then I also wanted to ask you um the
entity that I channel
um his name is Utar and he is presently
on the planet Essani. Yes. And
uh although the name is not that since
you know that Bashar is not my name
right we do not have names in that
sense. Right. My understanding of the
name Utar is that it
means relatively it means communication
and blending. Hey, in a very ancient
aspect of our dialect, it means
lightning bolt or lightning rod. Oh
wow, that's amazing because that's a a
powerful symbol in my own life.
Um it's a symbol I use for manifesting a
lot. Yes. Um that is why the name was
chosen. What a coincidence.
Um in any event, a lot of the
communication between myself and Bashar
is not to me perceivable in language per
se. What I do is I receive or I perceive
the whole concept. Right. Concepts. Yes.
And um at first this was rather
difficult for me but I'm adjusting to
that. Yes. And one of the things
that I do get a lot of images. Oh yes.
For example, I see blue hills all the
time and at the base of the blue hills
like a appears to be like a lake or an
ocean. And my understanding is that Utar is
And my understanding is that Utar is
somehow very deeply involved with
dolphins or some kind of dolphin-like
um animal on your planet. And um there's
some kind of
blending and communication that goes on
between himself and the dolphins. And I
was wondering if they are your dolphins.
They are but they are on our world.
so that we can use them as a model to
also assist in the understanding of the
blending of the dolphin consciousness
with your human consciousness upon your
planet.
So in other words, you uh your planet
has essentially teleported or something
those dolphins up there.
Yes. Okay.
[Music] Well, that explains a lot. We have no
Well, that explains a lot. We have no
natural dolphins. They are the product
of your planet.
My sense is
that the blending that Utar does with
the the dolphins is like a consciousness
blending where
there's in essence there are times where
I almost see him identified with
dolphins. So it's very difficult to say
this is a human this is a human form
that is blended with dolphins or this is
a dolphin form that's blending
with human form or Essonian form. Yes.
Um is there any other comments that you
could make about or expansion on these
communications I've had with Utar? You
can focus on the blue energy.
It'll guide you.
Okay. Talk about it as light
in any particular shape or form
as the beam as the bolt from the blue.
Thank you very much. You are welcome.
Daughter sister.
Thank you. Sure.
I was doing nothing. But
But
Hutah was doing
Be lightning. Be lightning. Be
lightning. Yes, thank you. Uh, two things uh I'm
Yes, thank you. Uh, two things uh I'm
excited by in life for many years. One
is my pursuit of yoga and the other is
music. Have you caught it yet? Yes. Just kidding.
And just a short question about each.
All right. music. In uh terms of the of
the physical, I've uh I had a bad
accident in 1958 where I lost my left
kneecap and uh through yoga and physical
uh exercise, I regrrew it. But but I've
al always been bothered in the knees and
wondered if you had a technique that I'm
missing for the final perfection of
having good legs again. Perhaps in this
way, there are simply remnants. Let us
say what you might inherently be
believing to be
impurities in the crystallin growth or
regrowth of that
idea. Allow yourself to dissolve
yourself down again. Dissolve in your
imagination in your meditative state
while you are breathing very deeply and
rhythmically to think of the idea of
your knee as being in a crucible and see
great heat of your intention melt the
idea down again into liquid.
Then feel the
vibration, the vibration of the
idealized feeling of the flexibility of
the idealized structure of the knee.
Then place that template in the liquid
and let the liquid cool according to
that template and regrow without the
impurities. You follow me? Yes. You can
use tone for this as well. tone can
represent if you wish or you can have a
tonal analogy of the template energy
upon which you can allow the new reality
to recristallize,
regrow, take it back to a liquid state.
Let the so-called impurities or old
belief systems flow to the surface if
you will. Skim them off the
top and then know that you have a pure
liquid to deal with. Let it
recristallize according to the new
template that you drop into
it. Then insert it into the idea that
you are. That is one idea. Utilize this.
See if that is of benefit to you and
allow your imagination to alter in
whatever way, shape or form it feels so
inclined. Thank you. Thank you very much.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
is that I've uh always wanted to have a
uh a fantastic memory and u it's never
been there. That is all right for that.
Many individuals in your planet now
because this is the transformational age
will begin to recognize that they no
longer need the way you typically use
your memory. For the idea is that as
soon as you are living completely in the
moment, you will know what you need to
know when you need to know it according
to whatever idea you are truly fully
being at that moment whether you have
ever known it before or not.
So memory begin to treat it as a thing
of the present not a thing of the past.
And in terms of retention again you will
know what you need to know when you need
to know it. And when you don't need to
know it, you won't
[Music] follow it. Yes, that is living in the
follow it. Yes, that is living in the
moment. Look at the idea of an animal,
if you will, as an analogy for a moment.
Let us say you have well, let us use the
fourth density symbol, the cat. For you
know it exists in more than one
level. It knows the spiritual side as
experientially as it knows the physical
side. It exists in both worlds. what you
call the ethereal and the physical
simultaneously and knows it. It crosses
one of your streets and along comes one
of your automobiles. The cat avoids it,
runs across, goes under a fence or over
a fence and surveys the yard beyond the
fence and jumps into the yard. Now for
the task the avoidance of the idea of the
task the avoidance of the idea of the
automobile is at that moment the total
absorption it is in as soon as it is
approaching the fence. The total
absorption is on the fence on climbing
the fence. As soon as it sees the yard
the total absorption is in the
yard. The idea is completely lived in
the moment.
There is no need for the retention of
the aspect of the interchange with the
automobile because that does not serve
the cat in looking at the
yard. When it looks at the yard, that's
all it is doing. Doing everything it
needs to do to look at the yard. If
there is an aspect of the interchange it
had with the automobile that will serve
it in allowing it to look at the yard
more completely then that aspect will be
there in its knowledge. But it will not
be memory in the same way you think of
as memory. It will be absolute
understanding knowing in that moment
what the animal needs to know to be what
it is and what it needs to do at that
moment. That is what many of you are
learning also to do. So an
individual who is completely at any
given moment being the idea of the
musical piece that they desire to play
will play
it. They will know it note by note
exactly when they need to know that
note. And if they allow themselves to
channel that trust and knowledge, then
their fingers will move magically
automatically. It will be an
It will be an
inspired performance.
You understand? Yes. Thank you very much
for your inspiration.
Thank you. Breathe. Inspire. Breathe
within. Inspiration. Mikey.
Mikey.
Hi Bashar. Hi. Physically I'm known as
Kenny. Oh, what I'm trying to work on.
Trying to work on Oh, excuse me. What
are you working on?
Working on. Well, I hate words are
certainly limiting, aren't they? All
right. What are you being right now? I
am try I am being an astral projection
and I want to bring that into my from my
uh higher consciousness into my physical
life at will where I can uh all right
remember it all the time go back and
forth as I please and carry it with me
and have you attracted into your life
many of the ideas that other individuals
have experienced as techniques that seem
to work for them and see if any of those
work for you. Yes. And uh I feel some
success. I would like to become I want
to I shall become proficient at it very
soon. All right. May I ask you a
question? Yes. Why? Uh I'd like to
experience it, live it, and share it.
All right. What are you experiencing,
right. What are you experiencing,
living, and sharing now? uh as a
physical being the beauty of of our life
here on this planet as we are in our
form. All right. The way we can help
each other uh heal each other uh share
our experiences to make us grow to
remove all the poison around us today
and be perfect beings here. Poison.
Poison our I our poison society that is
sick and ill and wrong society.
sickened, sick, ill, wrong, sick. Wrong.
Dying. I don't I want no part of that.
And I want You want no part of it.
So you are saying you wish the astral
idea to run away from something you
chose to be born into. No, I just want
to make it better if possible. Allow it
to. Not make it. Allow it.
know first of all that there are many
different versions of your society
already in
existence. Allow yourself to act as a
reflective example of the
vibration that already represents the
society that in your terms is not
poison, not sick, not wrong. These are
all value judgments.
You if you are not that reality will not
experience any effect from a society
that is choosing to be that reality. I I
I I feel I'm not that part. I know I'm
not that part. But yet every day by
reading the newspaper, by watching the
news, by experiencing the media that is
thrown at us. So you are seeing how
other individuals are choosing to
believe their reality exists. Yes. And I
don't none of that in any way, shape, or
form needs to rub off on you. It
doesn't, but I'd like to help change
that completely. You can. Now, we would
suggest, not tell you, but simply
suggest that the more willing you are to
be of service physically, the more
capable you will be of expanding
non-physically as well because you chose
to be born into this society. Makes
sense. So, act as if you are already
expanded. Act as you know you would act if you
Act as you know you would act if you
already had the ability you desire to
have. Act that way physically. Act how
you would act physically if you had that
ability. And then you will be the being
that has that
ability because you will know you chose
to be where you are to be of service in
your own unique way. And if you are
willing to put that out and share your
understanding with all these other
individuals, not that they have to
change, but so that they can see in you
the possibility of choosing another way
to be, then you will be changing and
allowing to change the reality you are
in into the type of reality that
supports the notion of astral
projection. That's very good. I like
that. Uplift your society by being an
Uplift your society by being an
uplifting example. You will be uplifted.
That's all I want to do. Then be of
service in whatever way, shape or form
excites you the most. And we will thank
you for having that amount of impact for
every individual makes a difference in
the ability of the total whole to choose
more and more what reality they
prefer. But it must be on all levels if
you are truly seeking equality.
The physical reality is no less valid
than the spiritual, no less valid than
the astral. This is also a dream. Your
astral. This is also a dream. Your
physical
reality, it is really no more real than
the astral
reality. They are equal, different
expressions, but equal.
Be a shining example of the vibration
you prefer so that others can see in you
the opportunity to choose that for
themselves if they prefer
to pleasant dream. It's been done
already. It
is. Thank you. Thank you.
Hello. Hello. Um my question is uh my
brother got killed uh in a car accident
when he was 14. All right. 16 years ago.
And uh I would just like to know where
his soul is. 8 years ago reincarnated.
Will I uh meet him in this lifetime? Possible,
Possible,
probable, a symbol, a representative
symbol, a signal of who it is. Maybe the
animal you call a raven or a crow.
He was reincarnated as a bird. No, no,
no, no, no.
[Music]
But a symbol that may let you know who
it is you are looking at when you meet
that person might be the symbol of a
raven or a crow. So, I haven't met him
yet. No.
Is it a man or a woman? Our perception
is masculine.
But you do not have to go looking for
it. If you are willing to simply allow
yourself to discover more of you, then
you will expand and contain the idea of
him because you already do contain that
idea. Expand as yourself. blend as your
own brother sister energy and then you
will be able to contain the idea of
another reflection in another way of
that same energy reflected in his
incarnation again. You follow me? Yes.
The idea is not to search outside
yourself and not even necessarily to
think you have to search inside
yourself. The idea is to
be both of those energies. You are that
blended energy. You have piouetted and
revolved and danced around each other
many times. He has now in a sense allowed you
times. He has now in a sense allowed you
an
opportunity to experience a new octave
of
yourself. As you so expand and use that
opportunity, you will expand to once
again include
include
him. You follow me? Yes, I do. You don't
have to think about it. When you see the
signal, you will know it and you will
recognize it. You will feel
it. You will feel
it. You will not have to wonder. You
follow me? Yes, I do.
Um, I have another question. All right.
Um, I uh feel very partial to the RN the
Renaissance and wondering if I had Oh,
yes. Both of you have. Both of you have
and it is one of the reasons why the
symbol that we have said will be used
because it was a very strong symbol to
you then as well.
You my brother is that you said the
raven. Oh, I see.
Allow yourself to recognize that it is
the symbol of exploration and
curiosity. Explore
yourself. Become your own renaissance. One moment.
What in your
terms was the manner of the physical
death? He uh crushed his head on the curb of
He uh crushed his head on the curb of
the
street. That's how he
died. In what area of your world? Where?
Where?
Where? Wherever? Uh, I think it was up
in the hill in uh the valley. Valley,
the Los
Angeles. In your terms, the birth date
of that individual.
What was it? April
4th. Um, I don't know the year. That
will do.
There is much that will unfold in your
understanding and your
connections and a vast
explosion of information An
understanding and
awakening is waiting for you in
approximately what you would call your
year
1,988. Many pieces of what you may have
been feeling to be a puzzle will fall
together for
you. In that time frame, enjoy.
frame, enjoy.
Thank you. Thank you.
Sherry. Hi Sh. Hi. How are you doing? Perfect.
Hi Sh. Hi. How are you doing? Perfect.
And you? Very perfect. Thank you. Very
perfect. I first have a very quick
question and then I have a very grand
question. All right.
Time's up. Oh gosh.
The very quick question is, have you
ever enjoyed a lifetime on planet Earth
one? The channel before you? Aha.
for simply the purpose of creating a
model through which we could interact to
understand your society. I
see. And I'm glad you did too. I'm glad
you took the time.
The other question I have is in my truth
I perceive that there is a creative
intelligent force that some may uh refer
to as God. That's Godhead, the God
force, whatever, all that is infinite
creation. Exactly. Yes. Now, yes, it is.
As far
[Music] Well, you can't get away with Moar
Well, you can't get away with Moar
around here.
Um my question is that well in my truth
I also perceive um
that at one point there were no souls
and there was a creative force that
created and there was a pouring out of
all men's and creatures souls. Well in a
sense although to us that is somewhat of
an analogy in symbolic terms. Okay.
Since you are now implying the idea of a
beginning, which is a linear time
concept, right?
But continue. Okay. Well, you're
straightening me out here already. But
it will do as an analogy.
Okay. Um, my question is why? Why not? Yeah.
Yeah.
Is there a reason for us being here or
being having been created to do what we
do individually and be and well in a
sense but that reason is simply to
continue to create to be the creation in
constant motion to be the expression of the
motion to be the expression of the
ongoing creation which is always now and
forever new and yet
exists forever. ever and always
has. But let us put it in more linear
terms as
well. You are looking for a purpose to
creation. Why does it exist to begin
with? But recognize that the notion of
purpose was created by infinite
creation. That which has existed before
the idea of purpose was created does not
need a purpose to
exist. It exists because it does.
What is is and always will be. Purpose
is created within
creation. But creation simply is what it
is. We understand that that may or may
not have much reasonable meaning in your
society. But there is not really the
terminology that
exists. Existence simply exists.
Everything is now
simultaneous. One existence, one whole
idea expressing itself in all the
multi-dimensional simultaneous ways that
it can because it can.
Period. And so it does.
Therefore, let me let me just see if I
understand what you're saying. All
right. Does that mean
that there is maybe no separate or
dissociated dissociated um force or
energy that we would refer to here as
God and that in essence the collective
consciousness of creation it is both is
God. Yes. The idea of God as you say is
that which recognizes itself as a
singular identity. It can recognize
itself as a singular identity, but it
also simultaneously recognizes itself as
the combination of all identities it has
created itself to be. Yes, it is both.
Mhm. It is always the polarity both.
I see. Does that assist you? Yes, it
does. I have one other quick question,
if I may. I'm sorry people. No apology
necessary. I'm just curious. I've asked
another channel or another entity um
this question and what was your dying or
transitional experience like out of the
a physical body mine? Yes, I am still
physical. I am not in the form you
understand as spirit. What you are
perceiving is a telepathic
communication. I still have a physical
incorporation. Ah but I am transitional
fourth fifth density. My entire society
is about to no longer need physical
expression of any kind.
However, in the times that I have died
before in my society, it was always
joyous because we understood that we had
created the idea of the timing of our
deaths and stepped into that idea,
stepped through that doorway with open
eyes and open hearts.
And it was as easy and simple as it can
be for
you. From going from one room through a
door into another. That's it.
It is simply a transformation.
Doesn't that assist you? Yes, it does.
Thank you very much. Thank you for your
expressions of love and light. Bye.
There will be but a brief period of your
time frame remaining for these
interactions. Continue. Good evening,
Bashar. Good day.
I have two short questions. All right.
First of all, I had a a very interesting
dream about dolphins in which there was
a large ceremony that the dolphins were
going to finally speak to the people of
Earth in such a way that we could
understand what they were saying. So,
you received advanced bulletins. Yes, I
did. Now, do you understand that the dream is
Now, do you understand that the dream is
representative of the type of
communication you were dreaming about?
Somewhat. All right, that's what I'm
asking you about. Yes. Anyway, in the
dream, well, maybe the question is answered,
well, maybe the question is answered,
but I'll finish. In the dream, I was uh
taken by my newly wed husband to this
place where the dolphins were going to
speak and all the news stations were
there, ABC,
NBC. It was quite hilarious. But anyway,
I was standing in the crowd and the the
newscaster went to interview the dolphin
and the dolphin wouldn't say anything.
And then all the dolphins had this
little meeting and then they ran over
and they were saying only we'll only
talk to her and they were pointing to
me. All right. What does that dream
mean? It means that you can be of great
It means that you can be of great
assistance if you wish in
cocreating the understanding of
communication between the dolphin
consciousness and your own humanity. It
means you have a desire to do so and you
can be very proficient at it. I like
that. If it excites you, go and do it. I
will definitely the communication will
basically be again
telempathic not necessarily literally
vocal involvement. I understand.
Thank you. Okay, one more quick
question. Uh I had a son 19 years ago
that I gave up for adoption and I've
tried to locate him. I'd like to know
what method I could use at this point in
time since all the doors have seemed to
be closed in my efforts to find this.
Open up the communication with the
dolphins.
When you are more familiar with them,
you may find that you will run into this
individual again and not even recognize
who it is because there may be a similar
penant in this individual eventually. I
see. Thank you. One moment. That particular
That particular
individual was also of a very strong
Orion
connection and adopted into an Orion
family in a sense and much needed to be
worked out between them. You were simply
willing to be the vehicle in that way
that would allow that individual to come
into the earth physical frame at the
timing that was appropriate because no
one else was
available. So again the idea is that the
dolphins were pointing to your
willingness to be of service in that
way. It is a habit with
you. Go and enjoy and you will open many
doors through which the unexpected will
walk. All right. Shine like a beacon so that
All right. Shine like a beacon so that
others may see you. Then they will
locate you. Well, thank you. Oh, thank
you.
Oh, by the way, when you speak to the
dolphins, say hi.
[Music] chatting. Hello, BR. Hello. Uh, I've had
chatting. Hello, BR. Hello. Uh, I've had
uh pain in my back for about a year and
uh numbness down my leg and
uh the only thing a doctor said about it
was uh uh premature degeneration of
discs. So, what I've been doing is
exercising and that seems to increase
the pain. Do you have anything that I
might more the idea of the breathing and
some of what you have heard to be the
yogic centering may be of more
assistance to you to allow the energy of
your total body to disperse itself
wherever it is truly needed to realign
the original template idea of
yourself. See yourself as a whole
homogeneous idea. Again, cease to think
of yourself as a collection of parts and
you will not feel that you are unable to
support yourself in that
way. Begin to flow energy in your
imagination, scintillating
scintillating
vital energy, golden energy, blue energy
to those areas. Allow the entire spine
to become a communication link, an
unbroken communication link. Be willing
in your meditations to breathe and
energize, oxygenate yourself in that
way. Supply your body with the energy.
It will know how to use it if you let it
rather than feel like you have to force
it to do so. Go back to your zero rest
natural balance point and you will be
the blueprint that contains no idea of
imbalance. For all imbalance is the
product of you holding yourself in
tension out of balance. When you let go,
you always snap back to zero rest
balance. You follow me? Yeah, I do.
Float, float,
float. Energy to you this night of your
time. gates will open and pour forth the
soothing coolness of the liquid
energy. Let it sink into every cell,
every bone, every nerve. Let your body
and your spirit and your mind pulse with
one message. I am whole. I am whole. I
am whole. I am one idea.
Pleasant dreams. Thank you, Bishure. And
at this time to each and every one of
you, exciting and vibrant dream lives
and life dreams. It is all one and the
same. This is as we have shared with
some of you once again day zero moment
zero curtain going
up. Applaud yourselves. You
You
always have in us and the members of the
association that you are becoming at one
with a
willing audience and co-authorship.
We thank you for allowing us the
experience of the gift of the being that
you are.
We bid you a fond and unconditionally
loving good day.
[Music]
How'd it go? [Applause]
Thank you all for being here. Copy.
Sorry. That's right. Anyone who would
like a copy of the United States, you
can have it tonight. We've got the
already paid. We have a highspeed tape
duplicator right around the corner. And
you see the girl hugging this guy over
here. She's in charge of it. Used to be
my
wife. We'll be here next Thursday. And
every third