All
right, I'll say how are you all this day
of your time as you create time to
exist. Allow us to invite each and every one of
Allow us to invite each and every one of
you this day of your time into the gate
firmly on the threshold.
Allow yourselves at this timing to
realize this interaction is not the only one
this interaction is not the only one
taking place upon your planet. This day
of your time,
many such interactions are being
cocreated between yourselves and many
members of the association. This day of
your time, you are but one facet of the
truly multi-dimensional crystal taking
place in this gate, on this threshold this
in this gate, on this threshold this
day, now here,
throughout your world.
Allow us therefore at this timing
to remind each and every one of you
that anytime you decide
to recreate
the interaction we will be creating this
day of your time.
Whether it is in your terms a live
interaction with us or whether you are
referring to one of your tapings
at some point in your future. Anytime
you recreate this experience, this idea,
this vibration,
you will be back in the gate.
You can use it that way any place, any
time. Placing yourself in that vibratory
Placing yourself in that vibratory
awareness will recreate the gate around
you, within you, throughout you,
and manifest all that you desire to
manifest in your lives, in your physical
worlds, in your spiritual goals.
All that you desire
comes through you from infinite
creation. As each and every one of you are willing
As each and every one of you are willing
to function as
your unique facet of the
multi-dimensional crystal of all that
is. We will in your terminology explore
We will in your terminology explore
therefore
the idea of your bodily consciousness,
bodily awareness.
We will explore the idea of your psychic
sensitivity and its linkage to
synchronicity. We will explode
We will explode
your creativity and your natural
abundance to allow that to blossom as you desire.
to allow that to blossom as you desire.
And we will explode
transformation and the expression of your willingness
and the expression of your willingness
to awaken
into full
creatorhood.
As we have suggested,
this is a gate. You are now in the
threshold. This day of your time, as you
term it, March 15th, your eyides of
March, your full moon day.
All alignments this day are
representative of the gate you as a
collective consciousness have created.
Anything that you experience externally
as a symbol is your symbol, your
collective symbol of this gate, this
day, right here, right now and again.
In a sense, anytime you choose to
recreate this idea, it will once again,
not in any way, shape, or form taking
you backwards, but once again will be
the vibratory frequency of March 15th,
the gate of a full moon. Anytime you do
this interaction again
to place you in that limbo state,
that disconnected state
disconnected state
that is where you can reconnect into
anything you wish.
As we proceed this day of your time, we
will, as you say,
begin softly
to allow you to relax into the mood of
your new frequency, your new vibration,
the new vibration
you will leave with this day of your
time. For again remember
For again remember
the old you and all the ideas
that comprise the old idea of yourself.
All of these will remain
on the entry side of the gate.
The you that leaves this day of your
time will be the you that exists on the new
will be the you that exists on the new
side of the gate. not the same person.
Literally, we are speaking literally not
the same person
in many ways. Therefore,
this is a death. This is a birth all in
one.
No need exists for sorrow of loss of the
old you.
It will not be lost. It will always
exist. But you will learn to allow the
old you to exist in a way that supports
the new you.
In the same way
that the decomposition of matter forms
the fertile soil out of which new seeds
will blossom.
You can use the old you to accelerate
the new you in the direction that
represents who you desire to be.
And that new you on the other side of
the gate
is a you of love, unconditional love,
unconditional trust
and abundant creativity. By definition,
by definition,
that is what the you on the other side
of the gate is. And that is the you you
will be when you step through that gate.
It is a transcendence, a transference
of title, if you will.
A handing off from the old you to the
new you.
The right to live as you desire. The
permission to live as you desire.
the ability to live as you desire.
Bit by bit through this interaction
we will build and build and build
accelerate the momentum of each and
every exercise technique that we will be
utilizing this day of your time.
One final understanding.
Rely upon your imaginations this day of
your time above and beyond any other
day. For in this interaction, in this gate,
For in this interaction, in this gate,
in this threshold where you actually are
is in the dimension of your imagination.
This idea you are in, you call a room,
will be your bubble,
your representational new universe.
And when you leave this day of your
time, you will take it with you.
you will take it with you.
And as you disperse,
the bubble will expand to include all of
you wherever you may be.
So that you will know
that you who have decided to participate
this day of your time are always linked
in that universe. And the apparent space
that separates you is no separation at
all. All of that will be contained
All of that will be contained
in the new universe in the new bubble
and wherever you are there it will be
this new universe.
You are the valves. You are the gates
yourselves through which the new
universe will will
pour
into your physical reality. And allow
all that comes into contact with you to
feel the energy
of your dream, of your excitement, of
your life and love, of your trust.
to feel your willingness and awareness
to know you can live in the moment now
and forever.
So this day of your time,
let us begin.
Relax yourselves
with three
deep loving
loving
beautiful breaths of energizing life
in whatever way, shape or form.
Allow yourself to know that you are
comfortable. Allow yourself
Allow yourself
to trust and rely upon your imagination
in these exercises. What we will suggest
to you is but a suggestion.
You may visualize or feel as literally
as you desire to the things and the
pictures we will describe and define,
but it is not mandatory that you do so
in all of the specific ways that we do
define. Your own imagination may alter slightly
Your own imagination may alter slightly
the ideas to fit the vibratory frequency
you happen to be. Therefore,
allow yourselves to continue to breathe
in a relaxed way, not forced, in a
relaxed and enjoyable way.
Begin to feel the vibratory energy of
the air itself, of life itself,
and place yourself in your dimension of
imagination, in your ideal place of peace,
in your ideal place of peace,
wherever, whenever that may be.
Allow yourself to be there. Now,
you can be lying on the grass, lying on
your beach. You can be deep under the
ocean. You can be floating on a cloud.
You can be walking through a forest.
Anywhere you feel at home with yourself,
allow yourself to be there in your
imagination. Now, Now,
all places
can be places of peace.
For a moment, simply drink in
all of the aspects
of your place of peace,
the light, the darkness,
the temper at you,
the wind if there is one.
the sounds you may be hearing,
the smells,
the thoughts.
Let yourself wander
in spirit, in mind, in body. Drift
in your place of peace.
Feel the nurturing the nurturing
energy
all around you that allows you to exist
at once alone and yet at once
connected to everything.
Knowing knowing
knowing
that everything everywhere
has the ability to experience in their
own way
their place of peace.
Think of your body. Now allow yourself
allow yourself
to muse of your body
to let your mind wander through the
different aspects of your corporeal
form. Floating Floating
gently,
comfortably at ease.
Bring your consciousness
to the idea
of your limbs.
Feel your limbs outstretched.
Feel how good it is to stretch
in your imagination.
Feel every cell in your body stretching with
every cell in your body stretching with
new life, new awakening
to greet a new day.
Feel every cell,
every molecule, every atom
breathing in new life,
drinking in new energy.
And feel the gladness
of your body as it awakens
into new experience. savoring savoring
every movement,
every little subtle nuance,
every cell literally savoring,
tasting, touching, feeling,
loving, caressing
with your consciousness. Caress your
entire body and the earth around you.
And feel the earth caress you back.
Feel the arms of the earth
hugging you, holding you,
supporting you, loving you.
Love the earth back.
Everything you need is there.
You are at peace.
You have all
that you need. All the tools,
all the wisdom,
all the intuition
is there
within you and all around you.
All the reflections of anything
you ever need to see
is all there.
Now, as you allow yourself to be wrapped
in the warm arms of love,
of light,
picture or feel a bright a bright
blue
transparent crystallin energy sphere
around your entire body,
extending across Approximately 1 foot
above your head, one foot below your
feet, extending through the ground if you are
extending through the ground if you are
lying on ground so that it encompasses
360° all around you.
Feel yourself floating
in this sphere of energy.
It is not hollow. It is not but a shell.
It is filled with blue liquid light,
electric fluid.
And you
are breathing it in.
As you breathe in this electric light,
let it flow and fill all parts of your
body. Feel it flowing into your
extremity to every finger equally to every toe
to every finger equally to every toe
to your feet to your hands to your arms
filling you up bit by bit
all the way up your thigh
through your pelvic area. Feel it
bringing you to life.
Feel the sensual earth vibration. Feel
it in your lower organ, in your internal
organ, in your intestine, in your lungs,
in your stomach,
in every organ you have, in every gland
you have, in every cell you have. Feel
it going, filling your shoulders, your
chest, your throat.
Feel it filling your brain, your eyes,
your nose, your sinuses.
Your mouth, your tongue, your ears,
every follicle of hair upon your head
become filled of the blue white light. Feel
Feel
a clearing as you breathe the fluid out.
It takes out with it all the old ideas
of limitation
in whatever way, shape, or form you
imagine them to be. You may imagine them
to be little specks
of dust, of debris.
As they leave your body, as you breathe
them out, see these little specks
dissolve in the sphere until you can see
them no more. And then when you take
your breath in, all there is to breathe
in is the clear blue fluid of life
and transfiguration. Now imagine,
Now imagine,
imagine that you are filled with this
blue white light to the point where you
shine through your skin. Your skin is
transparent. You are a form, an energy form inside
You are a form, an energy form inside
the blue white sphere, just barely
discernable from the energy of the sphere itself.
And now allow yourself
to blend
to blend to dissolve to become dispersed
throughout the sphere
so that no one portion of the sphere
stands out
above any other portion.
You are breathing as a whole idea. The
whole sphere all the energy in the
sphere is breathing as one pulsing
is breathing as one pulsing
as one heart
as one lung.
You are one
beat, one
one
flow. You are the energy itself. You are
completely
one single homogeneous crystalclear
idea. A pure A pure
essence,
a pure fluid, a pure form, a pure light, sparkling, scintillating, sparkling, scintillating,
effervescent, glowing. Now
Now
within the very center of that sphere
that you are within the very depth of
your being in the very center of the
soul you are now expressing yourself to
be
allow a tiny crystal seed
to form a seed which is created out of
the same fluid.
And allow that seed crystal
to bud, to grow, to fish, to split, to
turn into many, many seeds.
And allow from that seed, that primal
seed through the primal gate at the
center of your being, allow a new body
to grow.
Allow it to take the form of your
idealized image of yourself.
It does not necessarily have to be
specific in the sense of having to hold
a specific image. Just know
that that body now is growing
upon an idealized
energy template
and that that template represents
all of the desires,
all of the directions,
all of the idea. the total idea
that you
know is what you wish to be. Allow the
body to grow and crystallize
and know
this is not
the same body
you started with. You have redefined,
redesigned literally
literally
the vehicle of your expression in
physical reality.
It is a new
you. This body
This body
allows all
in, all light in, all sound in, all
all light in, all sound in, all
experience in because it is a
transparent crystal.
No barriers, none of it is opaque.
It allows everything
in
into the gate within the heart, the gate
within the mind, the gate within the
spirit, the gate within the soul, the
gate within the consciousness.
Because this body consciousness
knows that all experience
that all experience
when allowed in
will be integrated
and become a part
of the body consciousness of the body
experience. But only
But only
in a loving
beneficial way way
that represents
your highest service, your highest
light, your strongest and most unconditional
your strongest and most unconditional
love.
You are
the master crystal.
You are a master crystal.
You are a master
crystal. You are a master crystal.
You are a master crystal.
You are made of light.
You are faceted
light. Literal light.
Literal light.
Loving light.
Living light.
You are living light.
All is light.
is light.
All is you.
Your consciousness is all.
It is not in the new body.
The new body is
your consciousness.
All reality around you is your
consciousness. It is all living light.
It is all living light.
You
are the master key,
the master crystal, the master prism
through which all light will pass and
from which all experience,
all preference, all desire
will manifest
now and forever.
You may now turn your tape over.
Three deep breaths.
And as you now breathe,
breathe as the new body.
Breathe in the new light.
Breathe in the new knowledge.
Breathe in the love that is yours
by right by existence.
You are living light. Any light
Any light
you now wish to be shed in your lives.
All you need to do to convert anything
into light is to let it into the prism
that you are. You You
are
the crucible
of creation,
the furnace of creation.
the molder, the sculptor,
the reflection, the mirror of creation.
All that you now allow in
will be converted
into light
and will shine
from you and illuminate your path.
And there will be
no shadow of a doubt that remains.
All in your life will be as crystal clear as
in your life will be as crystal clear as
you have now created yourself to be. Relax.
Shake yourselves out.
Feel the new body that you are.
Regardless of what might in your
terminology be an old illusion, an old symbol, an
be an old illusion, an old symbol, an
old outer image.
You are now a new body. And bit by bit
at whatever rate
represents the perfect fulfillment and
unfoldment of the path you are, the body
you used to be
will transform into the body idea you
now are.
You will crystallize.
You are crystallizing.
Feel the new body. Feel the stretch, the
pliability, the flexibility
of the new crystallin body, the new
crystallin idea that you are. Feel
Feel
the affinity you have for light.
Feel yourself drawn for light is what
now feeds you. is what now sustains you.
You will feel
from this point forward in time as you
create time
new paces, new pulses,
new rhythms, new cycles entering your
life. Allow yourself to simply lose in a
Allow yourself to simply lose in a
natural way
any urges that might have been old urges
that represented old ideas.
You are now different in that aspect.
You already are no longer the same you
you were when we began this day of your
time. In many ways, right now this is another
In many ways, right now this is another
day, another March 15th,
another full moon.
Throughout this day, you will experience
many days.
Each and every new day will be the day
that is representative
of the new you you are. For it is that
you that woke up upon this particular
day to create the experiences you are
creating.
The March 15th the old you woke up upon
is long since passed.
You are moving not only through time.
You are now moving as time as space.
You are a new dawn, a new day.
Three deep breaths.
But let them be light breath,
easy breaths, breath
of certainty,
breath of knowledge,
breath of your own truth,
of your own light, of the light of
creation, which is your light as well,
which is the light of all beings within
creation. Now hold on
for we are going
up another step. You You
can now
allow yourselves to love
to become
in a very specific way
the crucible, the furnace
of creation,
of life, of light, of balance,
of hell, of ease
without disees.
In any way, shape or form you wish to
apply the following idea is up to you.
This will work with any disease,
will work with any disease,
any fear you have within you. We will be
dealing with the idea of the
transformation of fear in specific ways
in another day this day of your time
later on.
But for now,
the next specific technique and exercise
is one of highintensity
focus.
Before we begin,
allow yourselves once again
to shake yourselves out.
Wake yourselves up and then and then
relax.
But recognize now
in your relaxation, in your idealized
state of relaxation, that there is
always a bit of an anticipation, always a
a bit of an anticipation, always a
curiosity, always an underlying
excitement, not a nervousness, not an anxiety,
not a nervousness, not an anxiety,
but a knowingness,
a true inner
smile of recognition
of recognition
that all things
are where they belong.
That all circumstances
are for your benefit to learn from as
you choose to learn.
That all ideas that you used to call
negative can now become positive. Specifically now
using as a symbol the idea of disease
for any disease.
Imagine. Imagine. Imagine. Close your eyes and
Imagine. Imagine. Close your eyes and
imagine
into the realm the dimension
of creation. Imagine
that you are now inside
of your body.
A point of view somewhere
where the cells of your body
are quite large and they are all around
you living, breathing, pulsing. Now Now
picture
among these cells.
Not cells that are transparent.
Not cells that glow with life, but cells
that are dark and opaque,
dry, rough. rough.
See them.
See the dullness of the sheen. Feel
Feel
the idea of the sickness that they
represent of the disease.
Any disease you have ever had,
any fear you have ever had
can be symbolized by these
charcoal like graphite like cells.
Rigid, inflexible,
dry like bark long since dead. flaking
flaking
and in your terminology
sucking the life out of the adjoining
cells, fossilizing them one by one
fossilizing them one by one
until they are but skeletons of their
former self,
dehydrated and dry.
See this process with no fear, for you
are simply an observer.
But recognize it for what it is.
The deprivation
by yourself, of your own life's blood,
of your own ecstasy,
the reflection of doubt, denial,
self- judgment, invalidation. Now, Now,
now,
now you
you
in seeing this
can now learn to use your natural anger
in a positive way.
See this
and not in judgment
but in simply alignment. That burning
alignment that lets you know that what
you are seeing is not you, not of your
vibration, not of your reality,
is in your terms within your reality an
injustice.
Something that does not belong in your
preferential vibration. That anger,
feel it.
See it,
taste it.
Let yourself be angry
at this condition that exists or has
existed within you or anyone.
But do not invalidate it, for it has
reflected and been of service in reflecting the
and been of service in reflecting the
old idea.
and has now given you the opportunity to
know you no longer prefer this old idea.
But maintain for now that anger,
but maintain it as the burning alignment
of what you know is true for you.
Radiate it.
Let it become
hot, hotter, hotter,
hotter.
And now
go while you are glowing
up through your body into the center of
your brain.
Into the very center.
There is at the center a gate, a door, a
black hole of infinite space.
It is there,
but perhaps it is closed.
Awaken, you say, open to that door.
There is something occurring
that can be changed,
that can be transformed,
come alive,
open. I consciously
I consciously
command it.
Watch the gate.
Iris open
like a gigantic valve.
And beyond that gate
is the depths of infinite space and
time. And at the very center of that dark gate
And at the very center of that dark gate
is a pinpoint
of white hot laserlike light
ready waiting
waiting
for your direction. You
You
are now as the observer in your body,
the mirror reflection of that point of
white hot light at the center of that
gate, the creative force, the seed of
your existence. Now turn
Now turn
back around and look down into your
body. into every conduit, every nerve, every
into every conduit, every nerve, every
vessel, every fiber, every cell, every
tunnel. And look at all the cells that in your
And look at all the cells that in your
terminology are still healthy.
And
visualize them now
becoming mirrors. Each and every cell
forming a reflective shiny face
like a tiny dish
curved inward
so that any light
that would hit that face would be
focused into a tight pinpoint beam.
Aim every one of those reflective cells
towards the diseased cell
towards the flinty surface, the
slatelike surface, the bark-like
surface, the graphite surface
of the diseased cells. Nothing
Nothing
can penetrate those healthy cells at
this point. They have formed a wall
around the dead cells. Now
Now
they are all aimed
at those dead cells.
You as the observer
are the switch, the prism.
You are going to allow
the bright pinpoint
of light to pass through you and as it
passes through you to be amplified by
you. For you as the observer are the
conscious commandment within your soul,
within your body, within your mind. You
are the director
and where you point is where the light
will go.
Now once again before you allow that
light to pass through you,
look upon the idea
the symbol of the disease.
Do not fill yourself with hate, but fill
yourself with anger, with alignment,
with the certain knowledge that those
cells do not belong in the idea you are.
Feel the white heat building at your
back. Hear the engines that drive you
whining to fever pitch building behind
your back
until you are almost a molten crystal.
Then let the white hot light enter you.
Build in you. Build. Build. Build.
Direct your finger down the tunnel
toward the diseased cells and let from
your finger burst forth the searing
white hot light, the laser light, and
see those diseased cells burnt to ash.
See the white hot light bouncing off all
of the reflective surface of the cells,
the healthy cells, flaring and flashing
and cutting through your entire body,
burning to ash
all that does not belong.
And then all at once, your entire body,
let it build and build and build and
reflect and flash all at once.
All at once and let it cool.
Let it cool.
Let the fires bank themselves.
Let the white hot point of light recede
to a dim and distant star. always there,
always ready,
but existing at the center of that dark
gate. And now,
And now,
and now
see the ashes
of the dead cells, the things and the
ideas and the disease that no longer
belongs within you.
see it converting
into gases into wisps
and all of these are being sucked
through the vacuum that is on the other
side of that gate. They are all being
pulled through all the tunnels and
conduits and nerves and veins of your
body. They are all being vacuumed,
leaving behind
clear clear air, clear space, room
clear air, clear space, room
for the healthy cells to regrow and fill
the body and form the link and the
bridge to solidify and crystallize
as a complete homogeneous
clear idea.
Let all of the wisps of gas out through
the door.
Let them
go on.
Release them into another realm, another
dimension that has nothing to do with the life you
that has nothing to do with the life you
are. Then feel
Then feel
that blue white light, that blue
electromagnetic fluid that you created
before. Feel it wash down the corridors
of your body, washing all the cells,
letting them come back to their natural
transparent state of light.
Washing you clean,
cool, invigorating and alive. Feel
Feel
the ocean of life
which fills you, cools you,
cools you,
soothes you, renews you.
and allows you to be reborn
on this new day, this new dawn.
That gate is always there. You may now
close it a little bit,
but know it is always
open just enough
to allow
the knowledge of whatever you need to
come through
effortlessly, easily, instinctively, automatically.
instinctively, automatically.
It will never be shut again.
And that white light
is always there,
always ready to align you with whatever
idea you consciously command will be the idea
you consciously command will be the idea
you are. Three Three
deep breaths
and know once again
that this is a new day, a new dawn.
And that the body you are now
is two times removed from the body you
were when we began so very long ago.
on another day in another world
altogether.
Relax and allow yourself to stretch.
And in a few moments of your time, we
will begin to move into the area and
understanding of that which you call your psychic
of that which you call your psychic
sensitivity.
You may, if you wish, stand and stretch. [Music]
Oh my god.
Seat yourselves.
How are you all feeling? [Music]
[Music]
All different. All right.
Believe it or not. All right.
Now. [Applause]
Now. Now. Now. As As
the spirit
of this interaction
moves you,
do remember
to allow yourselves to truly enjoy
what you are cocreating with us. What we
are cocreating with you, this is your
creation. What we are sharing with you, we are
What we are sharing with you, we are
spontaneously pulling from you.
You are our source material
and we are now
going to thank you
for allowing us to create
from the elements of your being.
The beautiful picture we are all
painting today. This sensitivity,
This sensitivity,
this artistry within you
is your expression
of psychic beingness.
to be psychic, to be telepathic,
extra sensory perception. These things
are not extra. [Music]
[Music]
They were with you when you were
created. They are a part of the package
you are.
They belong to you.
They are forms of your natural
expressiveness. It is simply another way of expressing
It is simply another way of expressing
your emotionality, emotion, energy,
motion. But it is spontaneous
But it is spontaneous
and activated by desire.
All of the idea of psychic sensitivity
and identification
is simply that identification.
It is allowing yourself
to identify with identify as another
individual to match their vibratory pattern to the
to match their vibratory pattern to the
extent that you begin to think like
them. That is telepathy.
It is not the direct reading of another
mind. It is that your vibration matches their
It is that your vibration matches their
vibrational frequency so closely that
you think like they do. You translate
the universal energy in the same way
they do. That is why individuals that
are in love often share apparently each
other's thoughts. It is a spontaneous
sharing. Many of the ideas
Many of the ideas
of your laboratory sciences in
attempting to prove the existence of
psychic phenomena and telepathy.
create environments that are not
conducive to the creation, the repetition of the
to the creation, the repetition of the
experience of telepathy and psychic
functioning. The spontaneous interactions of life
The spontaneous interactions of life
that is the laboratory of telepathy.
It is a process that must be observed in
the natural state in which it is created
in which it has meaning and birth. Consciousness itself
Consciousness itself
is that laboratory
life itself. Now, precognition prediction, prediction,
telepathy, ESP,
psychic sensitivity,
it is all the same idea. It is all one
understanding. It is the knowingness that everything
is the same one thing.
manifesting in all the different aspects
that it can simultaneously.
And this is also the definition of
synchronicity. Telepathy, psychic functioning
Telepathy, psychic functioning
is synchronicity.
It is the same thing.
The allowance of the recognition that
everything is connected to everything
else and interacts with everything else
because everything is everything else
manifesting in all the different forms
all the different expressions
it is capable of manifesting.
So when you are functioning psychically,
you are not truly attempting to bridge
some chasm between you and another
person. It is simply learning how to identify as
It is simply learning how to identify as
that other person to be the idea the
vibration of that other being of that other
of that other being of that other
concept. Even
you can identify with a concept with
what you typically call an object
which is simply another form of
consciousness. Your inanimate objects
are quite animated
on many level
but they have different cycles
different frequencies. That is all.
Rocks, as you call them, are quite
alive, quite active, but not in your frequency. Now
each and every one of you,
let's jump back in to that dimension of
crystallin imagination
and explore and greet
some new friends.
friends that have been around for quite
some time,
but with whom you may wish a little
reacquaintance.
Close your eyes. Drift back
Drift back
to your place of perfect peace.
Whatever that may be, wherever that may
be, whenever that may be.
doesn't matter. Now,
if there are none present in your place
of perfect peace, then in your
imagination, conjure up the image
conjure up the image
of a rock.
Any rock, any color, any size, any
shape, any degree of hardness, any degree of
any degree of hardness, any degree of
softness,
but a rock,
a friendly looking rock, a war,
a war,
happy little rock.
Yes, happy little rock.
Look at it from all five. Turn it around
in your imagination.
If that is with your imaginary hand,
that is all right. If you must walk
around it in your imagination to see all
sides, that is all right, too.
Observe it from all sides.
Look at it. Tilt your head this way and
that. Observe the light, the
reflections, the colors, the smoothness,
the roughness.
Place your hand upon pat. Good rock.
Nice and friendly rock. Then
Then
look down from above.
Observe its new face if you will. Then
sink down below it. Even if you go
through the ground, look at it from
below. See it from all sides. All sides. Now
Now
in whatever way, shape or form is
comfortable for you. Address the rock.
Hello my friend.
my friend.
May I
May I touch your soul?
The happy rock will say, "Of course,
do come in.
Now let yourself walk
in to the rock
so that you are now surrounded by the
rock. If it is a small rock, let
yourself shrink.
If it is a large rock, walk into it.
Walk right through the surface into the
very heart of the rock so that now the
rock has a chance to see you from all
sides.
Let it touch you. Let it taste you. Let
it hug you.
Let it snuggle you.
In many ways it is very soft, very
gentle.
Now look at the rock from inside. Look closely.
Look closely.
Now, as you are looking at the substance
of the rock,
allow yourself to shrink and shrink and
shrink and shrink
until you are able to actually see the
molecules of rocks.
until you are actually able to see the
atoms that make up the idea you call a
rock. Look at these atoms. See
See
what makes them
the atoms of a rock as opposed to the
atoms of anything else. Learn them.
Learn them.
Feel the pulse. Feel the frequency.
Touch them. Calles them.
Love them. Love them for being the atoms
of the rock.
So that the rock could exist so it could
be your friend.
Thank you, little atoms.
Be small enough
inside, humble enough that you allow the atoms
humble enough that you allow the atoms
to be bigger than you.
Explore them. Walk through
the cave full of atoms.
Look at the little flicker and glow of
electricity within them.
How joyous, what a magical place,
how beautiful,
how lovely.
Now allow yourself
allow yourself
to expand and grow and grow and grow and
grow until you are the size of the rock.
bigger than the rock. Bigger and bigger
and bigger and bigger until the rock
is deep within your heart,
safe within your soul.
And then pour all your love over that
little rock.
Love it, caress it,
kiss it if you wish
with your whole being
until you feel the tears of joy because
you love it so much and it loves you so
much. Then
let yourself become once again
the size you were when you first
interacted with the rock. and let the
rock be outside of you.
If it is small, hold it in your hand. If
it is large, hug it and let it hug you.
And say, "Thank you, my friend. Thank
you for being my friend.
And thank you for allowing me to be your now. now.
Step back
and allow everything
to fade into gray.
Take three deep breaths
and upon the third
breath, allow the gray to reform once
again into your place of perfect peace. And now
And now
and now
now now
you notice something different.
Well the rock that used to be a rock
is now somehow
different more shall we say
more shall we say
refined.
It is now a single element.
It is now
a single element.
It is in your terms
a sphere
of metal.
Shiny metal.
Can be steel, can be copper, can be
silver, can be gold.
See it first as steel. Still a blending
but refined.
See the silvery surface and the
reflections.
Then see it transform into copper
ruddy red.
And know that even though it may not be
in your terms as hard as the steel,
it is in many ways now a single element
and pure.
See it become silvery,
silver, pure silver. Then see it shine
as pure polished gold,
pure and bright.
It is each and all of these things.
And allow yourself now,
allow yourself
to go to the sphere of metal
and say
hello. Hear its response. Perhaps a little
Hear its response. Perhaps a little
different than the rock.
Hello. Perhaps a little more
Perhaps a little more
vibrating.
But it is no less friendly,
no less giving, no less warm.
Look at it from all sides. Even though
it is a sphere, see the reflection from
all sides. Let it float in the air
before you.
Walk around it. Look under. Look from
above. It will move to accommodate you. It can
It will move to accommodate you. It can
go around you. You can go around. It
does not matter. Now
place a finger, a hand upon the surface
and feel all of the elements within it.
Everything. All the pure elements.
All the pure elements.
in various combinations and in various
refinements. Blending and pure, pure and blending all
Blending and pure, pure and blending all
the elements.
Feel it changing under your palm.
Feel the variety of textures and
temperature. Warm, cool, shiny, slick, rough,
Warm, cool, shiny, slick, rough,
airy, solid, heavy, light, glass-like,
sandlike, metallic, tar, tar,
perfect,
flawless. Then allow yourself
allow yourself
to ask
ask the sphere.
May I enter your soul?
Yes, says the sea. Yes,
says the sea. Yes,
enter and be welcome.
into the kingdom of elements.
Shrink again. You go deep into the soul
and allow yourself to see, to
experience, to feel, to taste,
to touch, to smell
all the different elements.
Become familiar with each and every one.
each and every identity,
each and every idea,
each and every way there is to
experience them all.
Taste them all, touch them all
and know that they are all within you
and that you are within them and that
they are the idea of your being. Then grow,
Then grow,
grow and grow and expand
and contain
the sphere and feel it changing and
pulsing within you.
And know that alongside the idea of the
rock, it is always there within you as a tool.
it is always there within you as a tool.
So that anytime you can understand and
identify with the natural elements
of your planet of the universe
in whatever form they occur be it
natural as the rock or refined as the
sphere. You are
You are
the mineral kingdom.
It is you.
You support each other and you are
friends. You are friends.
You are friends.
You are one another.
Now place the sphere outside with the
rock side by side
and know they are tools for your using.
Anytime you wish to get in touch with
any idea, any mineral notion,
psychically, intuitively,
repeat this and you will have all the
information through the gate of your
consciousness that you require.
Now allow again the grayness.
Allow the picture to fade.
Three deep breaths.
And on the third allow once again
your place of perfect peace.
Another change. My my another friend. What have
change. My my another friend. What have
we here? A crystal.
Bright and shiny.
The third phase of the mineral kingdom.
A crystal.
Hello, you say with much exuberance.
Hello, says the crystal, reverberating through
says the crystal, reverberating through
many dimensions at once.
Hello, welcome. welcome.
Welcome.
Won't you explode with me? I will. You
say I will.
Come forth.
touch my surface
my surface
or thank you. Thank you. I shall.
And as you do so, you feel not only see
but feel and taste and smell and hear
all the different colors that the
crystal becomes, all the different types
of crystal manifestation.
It is like liquid pouring through your
veins and you are on fire with knowledge
and you are on fire with knowledge
of all the crystallin forms that there
are. And you dissolve into the crystal into
And you dissolve into the crystal into
the very heart and see the atomic
structure and it vibrates with light all
around you like a crystal palace.
like the cathedral of your soul.
And it chimes
and resounds and reverberates
with beautiful crystallin tones of such
beauty that you feel you will cry with joy and
that you feel you will cry with joy and
ecstasy.
Such a sound you have never heard.
And this sound sets up a vibration
within you, a harmonic vibration,
and allows you to sing with the crystal.
And you are singing and floating. And as
you are singing and floating, you grow
and expand until the crystal is in your
heart next to the sphere, next to the rock.
next to the sphere, next to the rock.
And the three are the triad of the
mineral kingdom.
And they dance and are joyous
expressions of one another. And all are
joyous expressions of you. And you are a
joyous expression of them.
And you return to your normal aspect,
your natural size. And yet know that as
you place in front of you the stone, the
sphere and the crystal that they are
your tools and they are your friends.
And anything you need to know about the
mineral kingdom
you will know because they will tell you
because they
are the symbols of the gate
you are choosing to be.
And you bid them
farewell, but know they are going nowhere, but
but know they are going nowhere, but
simply that you are now turning your
attention to another idea and they are
always with you on the journey that you
are. They are in your toolkit
always. And that toolkit is your heart,
your soul, your mind.
They are snug
and nestled
within the velvet pouch
of your spirit and your soul. Now
Now
in your imagination,
turn three times. Rotate
Rotate
and let the scene fade and take three
deep breaths.
And upon the emergence of the third
breath once again
is your place of perfect peace. But now
things are different in general. The
colors are a little bit brighter. The
vibration is a little bit higher.
And you look around and lo and behold, a
lushness of plant life exists before you. All
of plant life exists before you. All
around
grass, tree, flowers
all around you
and you marvel at the richness
of verdant life,
the fertility,
the depth of the emerald.
green vibration
and you know you are in a new world, a
new level
and you greet
in turn
the grasses
and recognize them
as the foundation as the carpet.
The plush and loving carpet
upon which
the bushes, the leaves, and the trees
grow. And you recognize
And you recognize
the strength
and the vibrancy and the reaching to the
light expressed in the bushes and the trees.
expressed in the bushes and the trees.
And their joy of reaching to the light
blossoms forth from them as the flowers,
the colors,
the vibrant
energy all around you.
all around you.
These
are the levels
of the vegetation kingdom.
You may now turn your tape over.
And you sense within them
the fruit that they bear, the seed they
bring forth.
Everything around you is lush
and abundant beyond belief, but not
beyond yours.
For everything that you see
is a reflection in the crystallin body
that you are and you contain it and it
is you and you are it. And you feel the
love that has allowed this to blossom,
from the earth,
from the mineral kingdom, from the
stone, from the seed, and from the
crystal. Together they provide the soil
out of which the vegetation
rises into the light
and brings forth the beauty
and the abundance, the sustenance of the
fruit and the nuts and the seeds
and the grains
and all.
That is the sustenance
and the vibration of the fourth density
earth in its greenness in its
emeraldness in its qualities of life
in its qualities of life
in the germination of life
and the continuence of life
and are fed by the waters.
of life.
And you in glorious joy shout
your love for the grasses and the shrubs
and the trees and the flowers and the
fruit and all the seeds.
and all the seeds.
And in one resounding chorus,
they with the rustle of their leaves in
the wind
caress you back
and invite you to partake of their
lushness and fertility
and unlimited abundance. And you are
in the garden of your own creation, in
the garden of infinite creation, in the
garden of your Eden,
which in all reality
you have never really left.
It is now all around you.
You are within it. It is when with you
always, always,
always,
always and forever.
Anytime you wish to know of any
information of the vegetation kingdom, go within any
of the vegetation kingdom, go within any
grass, any bush, any tree, any fruit,
any seed, any grain, any idea of that
nature. Go within nature and see around you the
Go within nature and see around you the
cells, the structure of the vegetation.
See the molecules, see the atoms, and
see the life coursing through them.
Go into anything you wish to know about
any herb, any grain, any grass,
and you will know what you instinctively
need to know. And you will understand
the healing and the balancing that they
provide that you create through them.
For they are aspects of your
consciousness and they are aspects of
your love.
and set that greenness. Now
that whole emerald greenness, that
lushness next to the rock, next to the sphere,
next to the rock, next to the sphere,
next to the crystal,
the green gel of life, the substance,
the cell from which all cells grow
and sustain
your eternalness
forever. In the garden
In the garden
of your consciousness,
the garden of your love,
which will always bear fruit
and never be barren.
And now breathe
three times and allow once again
the idea to dissolve within you and reemerge
and reemerge
and resolidify
and reconstruct your perfect place of
peace.
And oh my goodness,
the eyes of the animal kingdom that are
looking at you.
The bright
and shining eyes that love you so very
much.
The bright and shining eyes,
that love you
deeply,
that wish for you only the joy of
release and expressiveness that they
feel.
The tears and moisture of joy
that you see in every bright and shining
eye of every type of being and creature
and animal
that loves you
and is you
and beats in your heart
and reflects and guides You
run to them,
hold them, hug them, love them.
They love you so very much.
Let them love you.
So that you can leap with them, swim
with them, fly with them,
fly as them,
feel as them. Open your heart and you
will hear them speaking to you
in their native tongue.
See in them
your strength and your power,
your grandeue,
your naturalness, your birthright, your
essence. For this is what they reflect
to you.
Release and dissolve the barriers
that you have placed between what you
call your civilization
and your naturalness,
your naturehood
and be and become any animal.
And feel what it is to run as swiftly,
to leap as high, to swim as deep.
to fly, to soar,
and feel the infinite, inexhaustible
power and the serenity
and the serenity
that that assurance provides. and let
and let
their great collective heart beat within
you and be
and be
all that they are.
Invite them into the home and come into
their home
and live with them. And they
And they
will carry you
wherever you wish to go
as far and as swift
as imagination itself. And now
as you embrace them all
and you hear them and you feel them, [Music]
[Music]
let them care.
Let yourself care.
and see them frolic in the vegetation
and among the minerals [Music] [Applause] [Applause]
and dissolve.
And in dissolving the image with three
deep breaths,
know that they will ever remain in your
heart and that you
and that you
are never separate from them.
Exist for a moment in the gray space
and know that you can walk in the light
of day and through any night without
fear feeling the power
of your being. And now
And now
as you resolidify your place of perfect
peace, lo and behold, there is beings, human beings,
human beings,
dolphan beings, beings from every
civilization. standing
standing
in greetings to you,
sending their emotional
empathic message.
Come, join us, join us,
be
as one with us.
Grant yourself your own individuality
and grant the individuality of all
female, all male, all beingness
in its own expression
and embrace and love each in their own
environment. Be it water, be it air, be it another
Be it water, be it air, be it another
dimensional plane.
Greet and hug and love
and feel the joy
of allowing yourself
to be home
where all beings
can be together.
Home is not an isolated idea. Is not an
idea of protection for you need none.
And any being, any mind,
any heart that you wish to identify
with, that you wish to communicate with
psychically, telepathically,
intuitively. Know that you have the ability to be
Know that you have the ability to be
that idea,
to be your version of that being
and to know them.
Love them and you will know them. All
beings upon your world, human and sitas.
All beings throughout
the universe,
Plleadian, Arcturin, Reticulum, Esasani,
Sirius, all that you may care to name and all
all that you may care to name and all
that are unnamed. All
All
are your sisters and brothers and
cousins and family and all
are in one home
which contains
many mansions.
Look through the window
of the heart.
That is what connects you to all.
Anything you truly have a strong desire
to know,
you will know.
For a desire
is the activator, is the link
that allows you to be
synchronistically with any
with any
level, any idea,
anywhere, any how, any how,
anywhere.
You are connected.
Let your lives become ecstatic
explosions of synchronicity, of love and
of synchronicity, of love and
interaction.
And you will
you will know
that you are always communicating to
everyone to everything
always. And you will hear the messages.
And you will hear the messages.
You are all
switchboards. You are all
format. You are all forums. You are all
chambers
in which communication from all aspects
of creation takes place.
You are all the switching stations
and through you pass all
levels, all dimensions, all experience,
all times.
All that is breathe
the new day.
It has now been at least a week since
you started.
It is truly
a new time in a new world
and you are all new beings of light.
You are all
from what you used to be.
Refreshed, a new,
full of joy, full of play.
And it is play
that we will
explore in creativity.
in creativity.
And it is in play
that we will explore
the idea
of abundance
and we will go together
through the golden gate. And together
And together
we will expand the bubble
of the universe
you are now creating yourselves to be.
And allow me to remind you
all the members of the association.
Thank you for your willingness
and your participation
and for joining them in passing through
this gate
and for choosing
to join
the association
of beings
of which you by The
by The
day we will be at
upon completion of this
day.
You will be a member
a member
of the association
and acceleration in that direction
from this point forward
will take your breath away.
And so now
we bid you in your own fashion, refresh
yourselves and we will
and we will
recconnect
at the beginning of another day
in one half hour
of your time.
We thank [Applause]
All right, I'll say
somebody turned on the lights.
You're all shining so very brightly now.
All expressing self-illumination,
self enlightenment.
Thank you.
As we continue. Oh, let's see. What day
is it now? Oh, yes.
Another March 15th yet again.
Allow each and every one of yourselves
now that you are feeling
a little more fully who and what you are
to begin to recognize the idea that it
has been your creativity that has
brought you to this point.
And you always have
that creativity to rely upon, to draw
upon, pun intended.
The idea of any picture you paint, any
way in which you choose to express
yourself is most easily
is most easily
the way to create the image that you
desire to see upon the canvas of life
around you. You are the brush.
You determine the strokes.
And together with everyone else, you
will create the overall picture.
Again, remember that an overall picture
and the impression you get from it is
still created from many individual
strokes. Each and every one of you by
putting in your individual creativity,
by remaining as a strong individual in
that way, by expressing yourself as the
individual that you are, that is what
will create the homogeneous overall
effect of the grand picture.
Creating that unity is not at the
sacrifice of your individuality. It is
what will strengthen it. The
strengthening of your individuality is
what will strengthen the unity. For you
will allow it to be all right for every
individual to be who and what they are,
knowing that it takes every single one
of those brush strokes to make the whole
picture what it is. And the essence you
get from that is a combined
product. Now, Now,
your three
primary colors colors
of light
are red, green, and blue.
And we will now use those three colors
to allow you to align within the
centering of your own creative energy.
to allow you to become the pallet
from which you will draw the colors with
which you paint the life you live.
Close your eyes.
And now in many ways we will be using
everything that has gone before and
incorporating this in different ways in what you are
this in different ways in what you are
now about to experience.
So first and foremost
allow yourselves
three deep breaths,
deep breaths,
expanded breaths, light breath,
full loving,
expressive breaths.
And as you do so,
imagine your body
your body
and imagine
in whatever way, shape, or form your
imagination so desires
the color red.
Imagine it as a field around you. If you
wish feel your body identify with the
feel your body identify with the
physical vibration of the color red.
Feel its warmth in every cell of your
body. And understand
when you feel its warmth, you are
actually feeling the action of that
energy in every cell of your body. It is
creating aliveness within you. It is allowing you
aliveness within you. It is allowing you
to know that when you focus on that
vibration, every single aspect of your physical
every single aspect of your physical
being
will be aligned,
made homogeneous through the overall
warmth that you feel from the red
vibration, the vitality
again, the sensuality.
Your creativity on all physical terms is
represented by the red vibration.
Feel it. Let it wash over you, through
you. Again, visioning all your
extremities, all the way up your legs,
down your arms, through your torso, all
your internal organs, your head, inside
and out. Feel the red energy
bringing life, sensuality, sensuality,
vigor
to each and every portion of your
physical body. And let your physical
body melt
into this red warm fire light vibration.
as if you are lying near a warm and
cheery fire.
Feel the comfort into which you are
nestling.
Let that comfort extend into every
single area of your body.
Relax your feet.
Relax your lower legs.
your lower legs.
Bring your attention to these areas of
your body and with your conscious
commandment which is not a forceful
thing, not a demonstration of willpower,
but simply a knowledge, tell that
portion of your body to relax. Your
knees, allow them to be flexible.
Feel the warmth interpenetrating the
joints. your thigh,
your pelvic area. Feel the warmth
creeping up your body.
Feel it leaking in your torso, splashing
through your internal organs, your
intestines, your stomach, your liver,
your stomach.
Feel it creeping up into your lungs,
into your muscles, into your rib cage.
Feel all the bones of your body, of your
all the bones of your body, of your
hand, of your fingers, of your arm, of
your elbow, of your shoulders, of your
neck. Feel all the bones warm and
comfortable, releasing and relaxing and enjoying,
releasing and relaxing and enjoying,
basking in the red warmth, the cheery
fire, the bright sunlight. Feel
it
ooze into your throat.
Feel as you breathe that all portions of
your throat are relaxing.
Feel your jaw untightening.
All the muscles
untidening and laying smoothly upon the frame of
and laying smoothly upon the frame of
your skeleton.
Just basking,
laying almost as if each and every
muscle were lying on a warm beach, breathing in
were lying on a warm beach, breathing in
and out. All your muscles breathing
independently but in unison.
Feel your mouth,
your facial muscles relaxing,
your sinus cavities, your eyes, your
ears, your brain, your scalp, your hair,
your skin, all over your body.
soft and resilient and relaxed.
A beautiful, pleasant, warm and
wonderful red relaxation.
You are breathing as one body.
All portions of your body are breathing
in synchronous harmony with all other
portions. of your body.
Allow yourself now
as that red warm vibration basks
over every inch of you.
Allow yourself now to drift into
awareness of your
mentality.
And as you begin to picture your
mentality,
picture all the ideas, all the thoughts,
all the analyses,
all the observations,
all of your material senses.
Picture a soothing
emerald green vibration,
a pool of green light into which all of
your mentality
can submerge itself
float upon the green pool
of liquid light. Let your entire
idea of mentality,
let it float,
let it bathe,
let it be soothed and cool
in the green essence.
Feel, smell
smell
the mint like fragrance,
the coolness of breath.
And now know
that your mentality is relaxing. The
mentality within each and every physical
aspect of you is relaxing.
joining the pace of the physical body,
centering, blending, blending,
balancing,
enjoying.
And as you allow your mentality to relax
with your physicality,
then focus ever so gently
upon your spirituality,
upon the idea of your emotionality. And envision
And envision
a beautiful
blue transparent clear light. Invigorating, Invigorating,
soothing, uplifting,
clarifying,
so open, so bright, so clear, so pure,
like mountain stream,
washing through your spirit,
becoming your spirit, and allowing your
spirit to relax alongside and within
your mentality which is relaxing
alongside and within your physicality.
So that these three vibrations,
the red, the green
the green
and the blue.
When you have allowed yourself to
envision in that order these three
energy, then know
then know
and trust
beyond a shadow of a doubt.
No matter what any portion of your outer
aare ego consciousness may tell you,
regardless of that,
the inner voice,
the inner peace,
the inner calm, and the inner vibration
of the red, the green, and the blue
light. They tell you
They tell you
that right now
you are at your ideal place
of creativity.
Your pallet is full of color.
Your brush is in hand.
You can dip into that pool
of creative color and draw from it any
color you wish,
any image you desire.
Simply trust
that when you allow yourself
to go through the red, the green, and
the blue blending,
no matter what you think at that moment
of blending, you are in your idealized
state of creativity.
And from that state
you have the ability
to access
anything from anywhere
from anywhere
because it is all within you.
You are the spectrum. You are the
rainbow. You are the prism that creates the white
You are the prism that creates the white
light of your consciousness to be the
spectrum of your physical reality in
whatever way you choose to arrange it.
The more you trust,
then the simpler you can utilize this
particular technique. Simply by placing
yourself in your ideal place of peace
and imagining the red,
letting your physical relax, imagining
the green, letting your mentality relax,
and imagining the blue, allowing your
emotionality and spirituality to relax.
You will be at the very center of your
soul. And from that state
And from that state
you can creatively program
any image
at all, any desire at all, anything you
wish to create at all.
Then with brush in hand,
the desire within you
moves the brush across the canvas of
your imagination.
Paint the picture. Then allow
Then allow
yourself to fill
with desire, with excitement,
and blow upon the picture. Breathe life
and dimensionality
into the image you have painted.
See it coming off the canvas. See you
surrounded by the image in a threedimensional
by the image in a threedimensional
way.
Live in the painting
and then
look around.
If you are standing in the image of your
own creation and it has now become real
to you and solid to you,
exhibit within you the level of excitement and
within you the level of excitement and
ecstasy you know you would have if you
were placed in that reality.
radiate and your radiation of ecstasy will
and your radiation of ecstasy will
solidify
that idea all around you. Then Then
allow yourself
to simply know
that you have placed it into action in
the universe
and in very short order
aspects of that reality will begin
to crystallize
all around you.
Synchronicity, coincidence,
coincidence,
all the right people at all the right
places in all the right times
because that's what the image you have
painted is all about.
Then simply bring yourself back to what
is the level in which you wish this
image to manifest
and go joyfully on with your life
knowing you have activated and
solidified this idea trusting it 100%.
You will see manifestation.
We guarantee it. guarantee. No, your creativity
is in many ways
your abundance. As we have defined
abundance, it is simply the ability to
do what you need to do when you need to
do it.
Your painting contains synchronicity.
So you automatically guarantee and
ensure that all the things that truly need to
that all the things that truly need to
be in your life will be there exactly
when you need them.
Exactly when.
Not a moment later,
but not a moment sooner either.
You will know what you need to know when
you need to know it.
And that will allow you to relax and
live in the moment.
Because when you don't feel like you
have to go searching
in that way out there,
then you will simply act in the moment
upon whatever opportunities present
themselves to you in here
on whatever opportunities have presented
themselves to you around you immediately
around you.
Once again, it is
as if you can imagine that you are
within the inside of a ball 360°
around you.
Anything you see in life
is projected by you on the interior
surface of that ball.
No matter how far away the image may
appear, it is always right within your reach
it is always right within your reach
because it is all on the interior of
that ball and that is right around you
right there.
Even if you create the illusion that it
is very far away,
it is the only the angle from which you
are taking the picture that makes it
seem so.
The image itself, the projection itself
is no farther away than your screen
which is inside you.
All around you is inside you.
You are the projector.
You determine what images they will be.
And when you determine what images they
will be,
live in them.
Live as them.
Be that idea. Now you
Now you
as this projector
are a gate in and of yourselves,
the golden gate. This gate
This gate
exists between
the plastic molten
fluid of nonphysical
of nonphysical
reality of what you might call potential
reality. And on the other side is the defined
And on the other side is the defined
crystallized
reality that you often refer to as
physical experience.
You are the gate through which the
molten Clay, if you will, passes and is by your
Clay, if you will, passes and is by your
beliefs
crystallized into the forms and the
structures that you deal with, that you interact
that you deal with, that you interact
with in your physical reality.
Now, this is not a oneway gate.
Two-way gate always.
And that means that any crystallized
structure, any solidified fluid
that you no longer prefer to remain in
the form into which it has been
crystallized. If you are willing
If you are willing
to take that circumstance, that object,
that relationship, that idea
that you no longer prefer
in that format,
and instead of rejecting it as something
that has nothing to do with your life,
but take it back within you, acknowledge
that it was your creation. Accept it for
what it is at the moment. Then you take
that crystal and place it back in the
crucible, the furnace, the gate that you
are. and taking it within you is the
only thing that will allow the crystal
to once again melt down into the fluid.
the pliable plastic malleable fluid
that can then be
reolidified
into another crystallin form more
representative of the new template, the new belief, the
of the new template, the new belief, the
new idea you have decided to be based
upon what you learned from the old idea.
So it is as simple as that.
Close your eyes and breathe.
Imagine yourself now
yourself now
as this gate, this doorway
which at one in the same time is a
crucible, a furnace.
That power of transformation is within
you. Now again take the observer attitude so
Now again take the observer attitude so
that you can while functioning as the
gate in the center look to one side or
the other and see either the golden
fluid or the golden crystals on the other
or the golden crystals on the other
side. Allow yourself Allow yourself
to
watch the golden flute.
Look at how beautiful, how deep it is,
how dimensional,
like thick warm honey,
amber, richness.
This is abundance itself. The very
essence of abundance.
The nectar of the gods.
The golden amber fluid of your eternal
unlimited abundance.
It sustains you. It feeds you.
It is the golden light.
of life.
Pretend now as you are a gate that you
still have your hands.
Dip a hand deeply into the thick warm
fluid.
Even though it is thick,
it is not sticky.
It is more like oil.
Roll your hand, swim your hand around in
it and feel
feel the softness
it imparts to your hand.
How instant contact
with this substance
completely and utterly rejuvenates and
regenerates you.
It is the substance
of the fountain of youth and the nectar
of the god. same thing.
The life force
out of which all your physical
experience is crystallized.
Please turn your tape over now.
physical experience is crystallized. Now
Now
it is like dipping into the heart of the
sun. It is
It is
nuclear material in that sense. Glowing,
brilliant, clear.
Now allow yourself to remove your hand
and then look upon the other side and
see the bright spires
of the crystal reality you have created.
Now some of these crystals
well may stand tall and true. Some of
them may be slanted to one side. Some of
them may be quite symmetrical. Some of
them a little uneven. Some of them may
be lying in shards.
It is all right. Take it all in. Look at
the entire landscape
you have created. Now,
Now,
as you are looking
at the crystal landscape,
hold your attention
for a moment on the ones that stand
most in the direction you prefer, the
ones that are in the configuration most
representative of what you prefer.
Exercise your conscious commandment.
Sheathe them in white light.
Let them glow. Let them look different
from the rest.
A little lighter. Now know
Now know
that is enough to allow all the elements
you desire to remain in your life to
remain.
Now move your attention while those
original crystals are still glowing.
Move your attention to the other
crystals, the shards
the shards
upon which perhaps you allow yourself to
be cut many times.
Bring your attention
to these crystals
and look at them.
And as you look upon them,
create it as if you are looking through
a wave of heat. You have all seen in the
air heat waves rising from the ground.
Things become shimmery, less solid, more
mirage like.
See all of these other crystals begin to
waver and shimmer
while the ones you have placed the
sheath of light around stand firm
and solid.
Allow the shimmering effect to continue
until all of the other crystals
begin to dissolve,
melt, run together,
run together,
and form a liquid
around the bases of all the other
crystals you have decided to remain in
your reality.
Let that liquid
now be siphoned, vacuumed back into the
gate that you are.
Let it bubble within you, like the
furnace that you are.
Now let it pour out into the pool of
golden liquid on the other side,
blending and mixing and merging
until all the liquid is the same.
All beautifully golden and sweet. Then Then
allow yourself
while that is bubbling,
while it is cooking
to look back upon the land side, the
crystal side.
And now you see the bright and beautiful
crystals you allowed to remain. And you
see lots of lovely room
for more crystals.
Now, the sheath of light you placed on all
the sheath of light you placed on all
the crystals that were standing tall,
do not send it away,
but remove it from each crystal and
place the sheet like a ghost image next
to the crystal that you covered in it
before. So that now you have your solid crystal
So that now you have your solid crystal
and a ghost image
of the same crystal.
So now there are many solidages and many
ghost images
but they are all exactly in the format
you desire them to be in. And each and
every one represents
unlimited creativity creativity
and abundance.
Those primary crystals represent your
initial abundance
in the way you wish to express it.
Now the ghost
crystals, the shells of crystals
represent your ability to duplicate the
abundance in the way you prefer to.
So now all of these ghost crystals will
function as shells, as molds, as
patterns, as templates. Now,
Now,
now that you have filled your landscape
with the shells, the patterns, the
templates in the image
of the abundance
you prefer to manifest.
Open the gates.
Let the liquid flow back in through you
and splash into the crystal landscape.
Let the liquid fill
all of the shells of the crystals
all the way up to the top
and let the liquid solidify,
crystallize in the mold. Now
Now
remove the skin
of the mold.
Place them back upon your idea shelf for
when you may wish them again.
And look at your new landscape.
Now there are always going to be
simply because each is in a different
angle a slightly different reflection from
a slightly different reflection from
each facet even though all the crystals
are now identical in that way.
So you will always have
variation but at the same time all the variation
but at the same time all the variation
will be representative of the ideal
blueprint the ideal template
that you allow the fluid
to crystallize into any time
any time
any of those crystals
Should they ever become
worn, chipped, cracked, broken into shards for
chipped, cracked, broken into shards for
whatever reason, anytime natural erosion
of your evolution
changes their shape, that is an
opportunity for you then
for you then
to pick the one that are remaining that
represent the direction you wish to go in from
the direction you wish to go in from
that point and create
new molds by taking the skins back off
your shelf of imagination
and allowing them to conform to
whichever crystals you prefer them to at
this point. For those skins do not have
to be in any one shape,
but it is your tool, your mold, and it
will always conform to whichever aspects
of the idea
you are living that you prefer.
And then allow the fluid to fill them up
so that you will always be creating new
abundance in different ways. But yet all those
in different ways. But yet all those
different ways will always fit the
pattern of the original crystal of your
preference. Always. Always.
Always.
You are a golden gate. Allow yourself
Allow yourself
the opportunity
to be that flexible
to be that malleable.
Accept any situation
that you have created in whatever way
you have created it. Accept it as your
creation. Let it back in to the gate.
Let it back in to the gate.
For only there
can you create
the atmosphere and the temperature
to melt it down into its primal energy.
So that you can once again determine how
that fluid primal energy
will manifest in your physical reality
will crystallize
as the idea, the format, the template,
the vibration
you prefer it to be that you know
represent represents who and what you
are. You are all
You are all
infinitely abundant.
Infinitely. And remember that there are
many tools that represent abundance.
Many ways in which you can be creative.
Creativity and your willingness to
express it will always link
with your abundance and your ability to
experience it in all the different ways
abundance can be experienced.
The range
of expressions that you are willing
to have in terms of your creativity
will also determine in direct
proportion. The number of ways in which you will
The number of ways in which you will
allow, not make, not force, allow
your abundance
to manifest in your life.
directly linked to your imagination,
to your creativity,
to your willingness to cease to limit
yourselves with assumptions,
with structures that you think may
represent the way it must be,
but which have no more weight than any
other assumption
that you place upon these structures. Everything
Everything
that you experience in your physical
reality, everything
everything
is your creation
and is an expression of whatever level
of abundance you believe yourself to be.
You are unlimited
being. Unlimited Unlimited
being.
Release yourselves into the world.
Splash the colors
of yourself over the canvas of your
world.
As long as you know you are doing it
with integrity,
then everything you do will harmonize
with your natural spirit
and with all the reflections of your
natural spirit, the animal, the
vegetable, the mineral,
all will work in harmony
with you
to create
an abundant
existence. Be Be
the blossoms
of your world.
Lift your heads
to the sun
and drink in
the natural golden abundance of light
and creativity.
that are yours
simply because
you exist.
It is what you were created from.
Light and love.
Let that love wash
over the surface of your world. Love
Love
is creativity is abundance.
All things, all aspects, all expressions
of creativity and abundance will be
found in unconditional
love and trust.
All of them. So share So share
share
with the world and you will be
expressing your own abundance.
Share the idea that you are.
Share the creativity, the way you choose
to express yourself, the method you are
at any given moment that you desire to
be. Share that. This does not mean forcing
Share that. This does not mean forcing
it on anyone.
It simply means beaming,
living as what you believe to be true for you.
Please go to tape four, side one.
You are all
in your own way now.
artists, poets, poets,
any idea
you wish to be. It is another day.
Good morning.
Second morning for sure. This day,
This day,
this new dawn and new dawning within you
of your own inner light
now shines forth.
And as you create yourself to be this
idea, from time to time you may discover
with this new search light.
Old corners, old fears,
things that now you will gladly seek
out, gladly search out. So eager will you be
gladly search out. So eager will you be
to incorporate them within yourself, you
will no longer run from them.
You will go searching for them. Transformation
is what you are.
Transformation. You are natural transformers
You are natural transformers
from one level of energy to another.
It is your natural process,
your natural existence. Now
is the time for you to recognize
once again that because you contain both
polarities, you can decide which one you prefer. And
you can decide which one you prefer. And
one of the easiest ways to transform any
fear into positive action is again
perhaps to use your fear.
In some ways you can play its game
and always in your terms win
because you are just as powerful as any
fear you will ever discover within you.
just as powerful.
All you need to know
so that you will act as if you are just
as powerful.
All you need to believe
is that within you, each and every one
of you, male and female alike,
beats the heart of a dragon.
Close your eyes.
One and a half deep breaths.
Take it in and hold it.
1 2 3.
Let it out. And take another breath in
and out.
Now, one more time. Three deep breaths,
but one and a half. Hold it for a count
of three. Then let it out and continue
to finish.
All right. The reason for the pause
is for you
to learn how a dragon breathes.
For in that pause is the buildup
once again of the cleansing fire.
And then upon the release of your breath
is the cleansing fire.
So
allow yourself now in your imagination
dimension
to pick anything something of your past.
I am referring also to anything that you
may think is in your present as your
past. So pick anything at all that is either
So pick anything at all that is either
once again the idea of any expression of
fear, disease or anything of that nature
and symbolize it
by picking an idea. Now for this
exercise for a moment it will seem as if
we are going to be somewhat judgmental
but that is because we are going to let
you use your invalidating negative
qualities for a moment so that you will
then know you can match them and then
you can transform them into positive
ones. So for right now, symbolize this
one overwhelming negative idea that you
think might be within you somewhere
somehow. If you believe you do not have any for
If you believe you do not have any for
the exercise, pick one. It will make no
difference. Symbolize it in some form, some dark
Symbolize it in some form, some dark
animal form that generates fear.
Pick anything.
Give it the sharpest teeth you can. The
nastiest disposition you can imagine.
The most intimidating eyes you can
picture.
Make it something to quake at.
See it. gnarling,
snapping, foaming, drooling, foaming, drooling,
complete
unreasoning terror
terror
is what it is.
All of the irrationalities, all the
negativities, all the fears, all in one
being, in one reflection, in one aspect
of you.
all rolled into one. Let it be any size
it seems to naturally want to be. But again,
But again,
just observe it. Detach from the
emotionality. And now just observe it as if it is
And now just observe it as if it is
behind an extremely thick glass barrier.
for a moment. Just observe it.
Now allow
allow
yourself to know
to know
beyond a shadow of a doubt
that you can be if you choose to just as
nasty. that you can be, if you choose to, just
that you can be, if you choose to, just
as vicious.
That your teeth, if you want them to be,
are just as sharp. Your eyes just as
beady, just as ominous.
It's not so tough. You
You
are just as powerful on its own terms
because you are the creator of it.
So right now
reflect it right back.
Be the same creature on your side of the
glass. The identical creature. are the
The identical creature. are the
identical size and the identical
disposition.
Be it, mirror it, match it, snarl for
snarl, snap for snap.
And then you will begin to see,
well, it is only so much show,
so much shadow play. I have been afraid
of my own shadow.
It is only a blown up image inflated
with hot air.
That is all. It is only an exterior skin
perhaps full
of some sort of fluid, some sort of
blood
which may give life to it.
But that is all it is.
And so right now
what you are going to do is you are now
going to become
three times bigger,
10 times bigger.
100,000 times bigger.
times bigger.
Now fear has a look of fear in its eye. Now
allow yourself
as you now are
in the format you now find yourself to
be. Even though at this moment it may seem
Even though at this moment it may seem
momentarily
violent. Allow yourself with your teeth to reach
Allow yourself with your teeth to reach
down and snap the head off that creature
and allow the blood to flow from it into
the ground. And understand
the blood is flowing out and clearing
out all of the ideas of negativity
that inflated the shadow and gave it
life. It is all flowing out
as you watch it deflate and flow.
Now transform yourself into a gigantic
dark dragon the same size that you were
a moment ago. and then see the exterior
dark shell crack,
splinter, and fall aunderder to the
ground, revealing a golden white dragon.
This is you, your essence, your divine
and angelic self. Spread your wings.
Look down upon the idea of the fear that
is now allowing all the negativity to
flow from it and deflaining and becoming
nothing more than a skin.
Take one and one half giant dragon
breaths in and hold it.
And as you hold it, look down with your
gleaming eyes.
Feel the buildup of the cleansing fire
within you
and let it out in a searing blast of
let it out in a searing blast of
cleansing fire. The entire skin and all
the blood is rendered instantly into
white hot ash. Now Now
feel
the release.
Feel the release
the release
and allow
giant, not sad, but releasing dragon tears
not sad, but releasing dragon tears
out and down onto the ground
as a light and beautiful rain from the
cloud that you are. Spread your wing.
Fly up into the air, light as a feather.
Are you flying on light
and become a giant billowing cloud?
The crack of
thunder and lightning, a huge cleansing
torrent of rain washes to the ground.
And all of the ash that remains of the
fear washes down the river, through the
valleys, and out to sea.
And as sediment
settles to the ocean flow,
it is still within the world.
But now the ashes and the sediment
can form the foundation
for all upon the surface of the new
world to allow new life to blossom. To allow
to allow new life to blossom. To allow
you to fly free
with the heart of a dragon.
A heart,
a spirit,
and eyes of shining gold
of brilliant white light.
Your breath is light.
White shining light. Anytime you wish to
feel the dragon's breath, the cleansing
fire, one and one half breaths and hold
it for the count of three. Feel it. Feel
yourself soaring in that moment. And let
it be a leisurely three. One,
two, three.
three.
and then let it out
knowing that with that outpouring of
breath all the fears are blown away
and everything is light.
Brilliant, clean, clean,
pristine. Now,
how do you all feel?
All right. Now,
allow yourselves to stand and stretch
as the new dragons that you are having
hatched from the crystallin eggs.
That's a spicy drink.
Just feel
the increased flexibility.
Feel the lightness.
The entire world
is your egg
and you have hatched from it and you can
soar over the entire thing. All around, everywhere,
you will have the ability
to transform
anything, anything
anything
into whatever you desire it to be. Your
desire is the cleansing fire of dragon's
is the cleansing fire of dragon's
breath.
That is how hot your desire is.
Sit.
Good morning. Good morning.
How are you all today?
Beautiful day, is it not?
Probably it's next month now
from when we began.
Time to wake up.
Time to know.
Time to know beyond a shadow of a doubt
that waking up into the physical reality
is one of the most joyous things you can
do
because the physical reality is but an
extension of your dream
especially now. And so
And so
let us now
move from person to person in the world
and tap everyone on the shoulder
in the world
and whisper to them that it is also time
to wake up into the joy, the love and
the light that awaits them with each and
every new day they create themselves to
be. Time for the awakening.
Now, now, now, now, now.
Right now,
we will put
two awakenings.
awakenings.
One that involves
the count of 33.
One that involves a count of 40.
The 40 count symbolizes
the vibratory pattern
that is most often represented in your
society to allow for a complete
transformation to take place in any
aspect of your society. 40 days for an
individual, 40 years for an entire
culture. We will do three counts of 33 and two
We will do three counts of 33 and two
counts of 40.
The three counts of 33
will be
in the creation and acceleration
of a blue light that will connect you to
every being
telepathically. of an orange light that will connect you
of an orange light that will connect you
to all beings emotionally and of a white
light that will allow you to be all
other beings so you can all wake up
together.
Then once everyone is away
there will be one count of 40.
We will describe the picture later.
The first count of 40 will represent the
40 days necessary for you as an
individual to become who you desire to
be. The second count will represent the 40
The second count will represent the 40
years necessary for all of you on your
entire planet to become the world you
want to be. Ready? Yes.
Ready? Yes.
Are you sure?
Oh, I don't think so.
All right.
I think you are already there.
However, because it is so much fun,
we'll go through the exercise anyway.
Before we begin,
allow us to remind each and every one of
you
we love you so very much
and we thank you so very much
for allowing us to play together
today. Whatever day this is
Whatever day this is
does not matter
any longer what day it is.
You any day are a gate
any day are a gate
in a sense
every day, not that you must label it
this way, but every day will now be
March 15th. Symbolically we will
we will
count from 1 to 33
with each number.
Allow yourself to envision
first blue energy.
blue energy.
And envision this blue energy
enveloping your entire world. And
with each and every number,
pump more and more and more excitement
and ecstasy
into that blue energy.
When we get to the number 30,
increase the excitement and energy
by a factor of 10.
When we say 31,
increase it by 100. 32, increase it by a
thousand. When we say 33, increase it by
a factor of a million and then cut it
absolutely blank.
Erase the image, fill it with blackness.
We will assist you by distracting you
with other imagery.
But when you think with each building
number that you cannot add another iod
of excitement,
add some more
until you think you are going to burst.
Add some more. You will not burst. You
will contain it all. So, first
So, first
close your eyes and take
and take
your three drinks of energy. Now imagine
Now imagine
your entire world bathed in blue light.
It is the blue light of your mentality.
It is the electromagnetic field out of
which your mentality is created and in
which you are all mentally one.
Add more and more energy to it.
Beginning now. 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11
12 13 14 15 16 17 18 19 20 21 22 23 24
25 26 27 28 29 30 31 32 33 cut black
space the stars at night. Small streams
of cool water flowing through the trees
at night in a forest on a hill.
Three deep breaths.
You have now prepared
a mental blanket,
a carrier medium around your world so
that the next level of energy. you will
send will be sent with hyperonductivity
will be sent with hyperonductivity
through that magnetic field and will be
far more accelerated
than the last one. So
So
now picture yourself
starting to radiate from your heart,
from your solar plexus, a brilliant
orange, warm, emotional,
beautiful, loving light.
And when we begin,
allow this light to radiate from the
middle of your body just
in the middle below your rib cage at the
pit under your rib cage.
Allow it to radiate out in all
directions across that magnetic field.
On the count of one, allow it to go
around the entire earth. And then with
each and every number pump more and more
and more energy until it is glowing and
glowing and glowing and you think it can
glow no more and it is the brightest
orange emotional light you have ever
seen. Let it glow more, more and more
and more until you think you can give it
no more excitement than give it more.
For you are infinite and unlimited. Start glowing
and allow yourselves
to send the light now. 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9
10 11 12 13 14 15 16 17 18 19 20 21 22
23 24 25 26 26 27
28 29
30 31 32 33 Cut. Space planets revolving
around the stars, swirling in their
clear motions, spiraling in orbits
eternally. Relax.
Relax.
Take three deep breaths.
You have now laid a very strong
foundation indeed.
The next energy
that you will radiate
will be the white light,
the clear light of crystallin
consciousness itself. Allow
Allow
yourself when we begin
to start glowing
by becoming the transparent crystallin
body we created in the first energy
exercise. Allow yourself
Allow yourself
to be a crystalline being. And at the
very center of your soul, wherever you
imagine that is, once again, see that
white hot spark that exists in the gate
within you.
While we count,
you are going to allow that white spark
bit by bit to fill you up
and allow yourselves to glow more and
more and more and more brightly
from the count of 30 to 33.
Then flash the white light to the entire
world and see every other being in the
world flashing with that white light in
recognition and reflection of the light
within you. Then on 33, cut it.
Are you ready?
Then carry within you now the image of
your body as a clear
crystallin container.
See the spark in the gate wherever it is
and invite it to begin growing and
glowing within you to fill you up.
Begin now.
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 16
17 18 19 20 21 22 23 24 25 26 27 27 28
29 30 31 32 33 cut black space. The gate
itself. The white light diminishes back
to a point. The gate closes to a
comfortable diameter. Always open. You
You
have just communicated with every member
of your society
in whatever way, shape, or form
is comfortable for them to receive your
message of love and light. To allow them
to awaken to their existence as love and
light has been received. They will
interpret it and manifest it and you
will now begin
to see the changes in a more accelerated
way in your society because you
are now
almost on the other side of the gate.
You are now almost
totally different people. Three Three
deep breaths [Applause]
before we begin
the final awakening exercise. Allow Allow
yourselves now
to look back through the gate at how far
you have come. To take stock
as an observer
of all you have been.
Look back through all of this life
and all the other lives you have lived.
Look back.
Feel the connection.
Feel the compassion.
But recognize nothing is lost. It is all
still there.
But you
have now decided
with your conscious commandment
to be
who you prefer to be.
And that everything you have ever done
doesn't control you,
but allows you now the opportunity to
choose out of all the probable realities you
out of all the probable realities you
can be and have been,
which reality you now decide you are.
So send a kiss back down that tunnel to
all of the you have ever been.
Send your love to all the individuals
that have gone through the many
thousands of lives with you. In whatever
system, in whatever time, thank them and
love them
for allowing you to be where you are
now. For this is the life you have been
For this is the life you have been
waiting for for hundreds of thousands of
years.
You are truly
newly born.
Everything now as you turn back around
and face the future,
everything now is truly representative
of the ecstasy that you are. Feel the joy
of the birthright you are now
reclaiming. You deserve it.
You deserve it.
You always have
and you always will.
Do not forget that.
You never need to forget that ever
again. [Music]
[Music]
We thank you for all that you have gone
through. We thank you for all that you have been
We thank you for all that you have been
willing to explore as a society.
We thank you because you're willing to
do so.
so that the many of us that exist
would not have to.
We thank you for allowing us to learn
from you
what it is like
to be as focused as you have chosen to
be.
We thank you for your gift.
And so in our way,
as best as we can,
while still leaving it up to you to
create your own reality,
we return the gift to you
by reminding you
as many times
as is necessary,
that you are the creators of your life,
that you are free
that you are free.
Close your eyes.
As we begin the next count of 40,
imagine yourself
on a mountaintop.
And imagine once again
looking down that tunnel and looking at
all the tunnels of all times and places
and seeing you
where you are now
as the convergence point
of all those tunnels and see all the
other you's you have ever been or will
ever be or are right now
as their own convergence point of all
the tunnels from their point of view.
Become the web, the net that connects
you to infinite creator.
And as we count from 1 to 40, understand
and know beyond a shadow of a doubt
that as you place more and more
excitement and energy and ecstasy into
the picture of the web of all that you
are, knowing that every being you are
seeing is you and that you are every
being, you will expand yourself and awaken
you will expand yourself and awaken
yourself and allow yourself to see
through all eyes.
Through all eyes
and feel the sharing and the love
from each and every heart.
And then at the count of 40,
take a breath in
and let it out. And know that that first
breath you let out on the other side of
the gate
will be the breath that expands forever
and creates
all the reality you desire.
Start your picture now
in whatever way it comes to you
and to each and every aspect and
reflection within the crystal.
Beam your energy and ecstasy
now. 1.
13 14 15 16 17 18 19
21 22 23 24 25 26 27 28 29
30 31 32
38 39 40 Breath In, breath out.
That breath is now an expanding shell
that shall forever precede you and
create the reality you desire to
experience by the time you ever arrive
anywhere. That reality will already be there to
That reality will already be there to
greet you. And now
And now
using your laughter and your joy
on the next count of 40,
feel the steps, the march step by step
through all the ages of all eternities
of all the cultures and societies you
have ever been, are now, and will ever
be. And feel
And feel
all of that as one hub. And see the
infinite universes,
each its own hub,
all as aspects of each other. The
multiverse, the glorious crystal before you. That is
the glorious crystal before you. That is
the infinite creator.
And with this next count of 40,
pour all of your love
and all of your ecstasy
as a complete and total reflection of
the creator back to the creator
to thank infinite creation for the
creation that it is.
And as you support the total multiverse,
so the total of creation will support
you now
and forever will it be now.
Create as the creator you are the
picture of creation
and begin.
1.
2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12
13 14 15 16 17 18 19 20 21 22 23 24 25
26 27
28 29
30 31 32 33 34 35 36 37 38 39 30 40
Breath in
breath out.
With that breath,
the entire universe
is within you. You You
the you
are now
is a member of the association.
you. The you are now
has all that you need
to create any connection
anywhere with anyone with anything
with anyone with anything
how any time.
You have your journeyman's kit.
You are now
of the guild,
the association of all worlds in love,
light, creativity, and abundance.
I welcome you.
Thank you for sharing. [Music] [Music]
[Laughter] All worlds All worlds
sing
for you.
All worlds sing with you.
All worlds dream
with you now.
Your world
is now
and shall accelerate
as
a reflection of all other worlds of
light.
Welcome. Welcome. Welcome to a new new
day, a new dawn.
a new dawn.
You are not only
within the reality in which you now
exist, not only a new person,
not only a new person,
each and every one of you,
but together you are a new culture.
You are a culture of the stars.
You are all star children.
You are all
star beings.
Shine and you will be seen throughout
and you will be seen throughout
creation.
For your light is that bright
and its beauty
belongs in the heavens.
We thank you dear angels.
Our love, the love of worlds
to you all. With three
With three
more breaths,
crystallize yourself on the other side
of the gate.
Use your tools well.
They will stay sharp forever
for as long as you decide you need them.
But always remember
with all the tools we have shared with
you, you
you
are always the master tool.
You
are de Mashana. [Music]
How did it go? Uh
Uh
thank you all very much for being here
and for uh
coming to the first one.
find somebody you can talk.
Thank you all very much for coming to
the very first self-empowerment workshop.
self-empowerment workshop.
Uh Daryl and I were both feeling when we
both got the rush the same day when the
association decided to uh
theme it on us. And I called Daryl. I
said, "Uh,
you wouldn't believe what's happening.
I've never been so excited." He says,
"Funny you should say so. I was just
going to call you."
And I have like many of us have felt the
excitement for uh since then.
Oh my goodness.
Nothing to say. Thank you, Margot.
Thanks, Paul, for being the only guy who
didn't get to do the meditation.
Next time we'll find someone else. I got
to sneak in a little here. Little little
hit here and there. Thanks Alice again
for the goodies.
Thanks Lynn. Thanks all of you. Thank
you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
The association for those of you who
don't know are the 359
planetary civilizations
which are m broken down into five
galactic associations
and uh welcome.
We're we're now 360
and that is for real for real for real.
An interesting number. Yeah. Carry a
card now. Huh? Carry a card. We're gonna
make a card.
That's a great idea.
What's that? The association, which is
the least exclusive club in the world.
That's great.
I decid I'm going to make Daryl a
t-shirt. He likes t-shirts. Do you see
mine, by the way? Yeah. I like
motorcycles. It's through the stars. All
right.
I I've got a neat one I want to make up
for Daryl which says while he's
channeling, it says uh with
unconditional love from 500 light years
away. All right.