how are you all this dream time of your
time as you create time to
exist allow us to begin this evening
with the interaction of an idea that we
shared with some of you of recent time
when there was the occasion for
transmission or communication with you
in your Hawaii area we
will discuss and share in this
interaction the idea we will now term
the Golden Gate you may if you wish use
that for your entitlement of this
tap it will involve the idea of
channeling but channeling in a much more
open definition for recognize that what
you are perceiving through the physical
channel before you at this time is only
one way that the idea of channeling can
be expressed in your society and that
really as you say when you do anything
you love to do you are channeling the
idea is to Simply form a
connection between that idealized
blueprint version of yourself and the
physicalized representational Persona
that you are in physical reality to
allow the two to blend to allow the two
to merge in that way so that you are in
synchronous Accord with what you know to
be true for you harmonious alignment
with the vibration that represents what
in your life truly moves you and truly
excites you the
most therefore you are all channels all
the time because you take the idea that
you are as a non-physical Consciousness
and are constantly channeling that idea
into physical reality through the prism
of the Persona you have created yourself
to be in this life everything you do and
everything you experience as your
physical reality therefore is the
product of your channeling that idea
into the notion into the experience of
physical reality you all follow along so
far recognize however something that we
have not discussed before many of you
think channeling is a one-way Street it
is two ways coming and going back and
forth back and forth you are a gate
you are a valve you are a door way in
that sense many of you have assumed that
the channeling simply comes from what
you call the higher planes into physical
reality and that is it but recognize
that channeling also goes in the riverse
direction and that physical reality also
constantly reverses itself back through
the gate that you are into non-physical
reality we will use an analogy we have
used used recently that called the
Golden Fluid which allows you to
function as a Golden Gate which allows
you to create golden crystallization or
physical reality if you imagine and
envision yourselves as this gate
recognize that on one side of the gate
that you are exists an infinite amount
of Golden Light Golden Fluid in that
sense now this is an analogy you do not
have to take us very literally in this
way but this analogy will work the
Golden Fluid is simply a
representational idea of the primary
energy out of which all matter of
physical reality is created is
crystallized you follow me therefore on
one side of yourself one side of the
doorway that you are is this Golden
Fluid out of which all physical reality
is Manifest when you funnel that Golden
Fluid of nonphysical ESS through the
prism through the gate of your physical
identity your physical Persona that
Golden Fluid
crystallizes solidifies as the physical
reality you experience in day-to-day
life the physical reality you perceive
in day-to-day life
now recognize the two-way street you
when you change your physical reality
what you are doing then is in a sense
allowing the
crystallization to become molten once
again by taking it inward adopting
accepting acknowledging the reality you
create encompassing that reality taking
it back within you into the very center
of the gate that you are so that it can
become fluid molten and plastic once
again so that then you can transform
that plastic fluid back into another
crystallization that is more
representative of the new idea you are
being so you see it is always coming and
going going and coming becoming fluid
crystallizing melting down becoming
fluid becoming Crystal becoming fluid
back and forth back and forth through
the valve through the gate that you are
recognize therefore that is why if you
wish to change any
crystallization of the fluid any
physical experience any physical reality
that you do not prefer if you have taken
that fluid and allowed it to solidify to
crystallize in a format that may be
slightly off-kilter from what you would
prefer it to be the way to allow that to
transform into a more precise crystallin
alignment more representative of the
idea you truly imagine to begin with is
not to deny that that is your creation
is not to run from that crystallized
reality but to take it back with in The
Crucible that you are so it can melt
down once again and then give you the
material to work with so you can reform
it so you can pass it through the gate
that you are one more time and allow it
to crystallize upon the template you now
set for it within your
imagination that is why when you run
away from any aspect of life that you
perceive around you as a physical
reality denying that you had anything to
do with creating it denying that it
belongs in your life then you do not
give it the opportunity to melt down and
reform into the reality you prefer it
stays crystallized and it becomes more
crystallized becomes colder in that
sense becomes more solid more physically
dense in that way sets itself in stone
in that sense becomes calcified in that
way when you are always willing to
reopt any crystallized ation quickly
fluidly then it remains in a highly
plastic State a highly fluid State and
therefore it is not as difficult to
transform that situation that you do not
prefer into one that you do because you
do not let it stay in physical reality
that long and solidify into steel into
cement you always maintain a high degree
of fluidity taking it back in melting it
down saying what else can I do letting
it come back out and crystallize along
the lines of the template that are
created in your
imagination so you are a two-way valve a
two-way gate you are on the side facing again
gate you are on the side facing again
this is an analogy on the side of your
gate facing the fluid you in a sense are
crystallized on the side facing crystal
in reality you are fluid so that always
in that way you have the opp opportunity
to interact to be the
interface that always shows the pattern
for what is out there and what it can
become so that you as a fluid will
interact with a crystallin reality in a
very softening way just in the same way
that water wears down the rocks of your
physical reality if you remain fluid
relative to the crystallization you have
created then you will always be able to flow in
then you will always be able to flow in
and around and over and under and
through the reality in a very flexible
way when you allow yourself to know you
are crystallin on the side of the fluid
reality of the fluid energy then that
crystal inside of you represents the
patterns the templates the imagination
the ideas the experiments the formats
that you wish to impose upon that fluid
fluid it represents the patterning of
that fluid so that the fluid can take
its cue from the crystal inside it sees
and so that the crystal inside can take
its cue from the fluid side of your
being always you function within
polarity to these ideas so that you are
always a gate that is twisting both ways
and never set and solidified when you
interact as Crystal to Crystal then you
reinforce the reality I've created for
you give it nothing else no polarity to
interact with when you interact as fluid
to fluid then you do not manifest your
realities into physical nests you do not
allow them to crystallize because
everything is still very nebulous and
washing around and nothing has anything
to take a pattern from so the gate that
you are in that sense is bipolar in an
opposite way to the way you experience
your reality and the way that the
materials are set up to create that
experience but it always flows both ways
allow yourself in adopting this
imagery to therefore know that any
crystallized reality that you do not
prefer is simply formed along a template
an idea that you have created which is
at that time the perfect representation
of the idea you are being and that
therefore once you crystallize that idea
that's what gives you the opportunity to
decide whether or not the template was
in the form you wished it to be physical
reality is only clay you can soften it
up again just because you allow yourself
to create an idea in physical form and
you find you don't prefer it doesn't
mean you're stuck with it
only by refusing to take that
crystalline substance back within you do
you then create it to remain where you
do not wish it too but once you accept
any situation that you have crystallized
in physical terms back into your heart
the warmth of the vibration of the love
the unconditional love in your heart in
your Center is what melts crystallin
reality and turns it back into the
Molten Golden Fluid out of which you can
create any reality you follow
me then take it to
heart and flow and
grow
sharing Bashar hey happy New Year and to
you um I would like some more of a
technical picture of the fluidity of
your craft as we talked about that was
portrayed in Flight of the Navigator
that was in the channels memory banks
could you give me some but it is mostly
the interior that is fluid in that way
not so much the exterior could you give
me the molecular counterpart and the
gradient to us creating that here you do
not quite have the technology for it is
a metallic crystallin State refined in
such a way by what you would call a cold
fusion process you do not have the
technology for that at this time the
idea is that it is instilled or if you
wish programmed to act in a holographic
fashion and when certain types of
current if you wish to call them
electrical that is all right are
introduced Bo into that crystall and
metallic Matrix then it will take upon
itself the form of the identity that it
is infused with and will become
crystallized according to that template
when the template is removed it will
collapse back into its original state
until another template is introduced in
electrical form but this goes on on very
deep Atomic levels concerning the actual
interactions between subatomic particles
in that sense it will be as we perceive
it a little while in your terms of
counting before you even have the
support systems necessary to create this
type of effect but how do you create the
substance it is once again grown upon
the energy templates that we create once
we have refined the particular substance
it is then grown molecule by molecule
atom by atom along the lines of the
energy template we lay down for it to
grow upon understood thank you Bashar thank
you Shing Bashar hey I believe you're
familiar with the uh Crystal Skull the
anti- Crystal Skull that was found in
Guatemala and lives in Toronto now don't
touch them sorry um the skull is
presently on display in Phoenix Arizona
where a group of people has looked at
the skull and seen dolphins in the skull
I it is a gateway and a your way to many
different dimensions and levels of
consciousness this group has is trying
to arrange with me they
are arranging they're arranging sorry do
not be sorry
to transport the skull to Miami and then
to Marathon Florida to put it in
proximity to our Dolphins how exciting
maybe the Dolphins will see humans in
the
skull I wondered if you could comment on
that proposed interaction and tell me
what you what what is there to comment
on it sounds very exciting it is a
dimensional doorway and because you are
willing to open up communication between
your land humans and water sitations you
will allow yourself to learn from them
how to telepathically communicate the
proper code sequence into the skull to
open it up to doorways through which
many other civilizations upon your
planet have already stepped and closed
the door behind them the idea is that
encoded with within the skull is the
Matrix to open that doorway and any
individual that wishes to find it simply
needs to sit down and commune in a
meditative state with the skull locking
eye contact to eye contact if that
individual cannot integrate all the
fears within themselves they will not be
able to unlock the code and that is the
safety valve on the door you you you
said that the Dolphins would be able to
communicate with the skull they will
know what it is for some of them may be
able to utilize it some of them may be
able when they are in its presence and
when it is in their presence to activate
certain electromagnetic phenomena around
it that may be visible to you look for
ionization of the air in the dark look
for certain sparklings of light in the
air that may represent
Moes in a sense representing the idea
you call miniature gateways miniature
doorways the preamble to the opening of
a major door a major gate you may see
them as sparkling
light some of them may be ghostly
nebulous at first some of them may be
very bright pinpoints of light in the
air all of these phenomena will be
indicative that the skull will recognize
when it is in the presence of an
integrated mentality an integrated
Consciousness that wishes to use it as a
doorway because of your telepathic
Communications with the dolphin you can
allow them to tutor you to guide you as
to the proper use of the opening of that
door way to help integrate the fears and
the different levels that you have
fragmented your Consciousness into so
that you can approach the doorway as an
integrated being many individuals when they
being many individuals when they
approach that doorway as a
non-integrated being will conjure up
images and vibrations on the emotional
level in the emotional body that will
generate fear within them and that is
what makes them back off and make sure
the door stays close to individuals who
are not
integrated you follow me yes will
when the Dolphins are in communication
with the skull and then they in turn
communicate with us will this
communication be along the lines that it
has been all along a sort of a
subliminal mood perspective very subtle
shift or you may feel great tuggings in
your emotional form anxiety rushes at
first perhaps temperature differences
within your solar plexus these will all
be indications that you are standing in
the presence of a very powerful ethero
magnetic field so the so the dolphin our
contact with the dolphins will be in
fact enhanced and dramatized by the
presence of the schulls oh
yes will you be aware of what is
happening there will you uh through to
some degree we will keep
tabs a little bit thank you very much we
thank you for your excitement and your
willingness sharing hi Bashar I it was your
sharing hi Bashar I it was your
introduction was absolutely wonderful
totally New Concept for me and I'd like
a little clarification on that because
in the past uh when there were
situations I didn't prefer I would view
them as being neutral and and not really
assign any value to them one way or the
other and now what you're saying really
is to actually love the situation and
take it back into yourself now that is
what we have always said the idea of
allowing a situation to be neutral in
that way does not mean that you simply
let it remain so what we have always
shared with you is the idea that once
you allow it to adopt a neutral format
then you can inject whatever meaning you
wish to whatever meaning you prefer to
into the situation that according to our
suggestion is simply the idea of then
loving it and allowing yourself to
extract positive manifestation from it
rather than negative because you choose
to fear it we did not ever suggest that
you simply allow it to remain in a
neutral state of course unless you
simply wish to with it for a while okay
no I understand it but I guess not
totally the idea of allowing it to be
neutral is so you can then put into it
what meaning you wish to rather than
simply inherently assuming it comes with
a built-in meaning right I understood
that but but to me what you said tonight
was was
like more than allowing it to be neutral
but in fact to see even the one you
don't prefer to see it as something
wonderful well when you are working from
automat atic trust you do not need to
hang around in neutral you simply
automatically assume that everything is
positive and worth loving that's true
thank you thank you very much
sharing
he more on the uh dolphin film that I
mentioned to you about three or four
weeks ago and I wondered if you had uh
any uh suggestions I seem to be moving
in the uh direction of the Chumash
Indians who have uh for a long time been
called the keepers of the Dolphins if
one could keep Dolphins I'm not sure
anyway I wondered if you had anything to
add to that have a good time thank
you there is nothing to add when you are
following what excites you the most
because everything will automatically
lead into whatever situations are
necessary to unfold the life you have
chosen to live there is nothing else to
say if you are doing what excites you
okay trust it I will trust it okay trust
it okay trust it thank you thank you
chatting yes for
sure um I I I came here tonight because
I've been dealing just today with some
nonpreferred situations and and that was
very interesting that you should come up
with that dialogue at the beginning um I
have this feeling for some time that
nonpreferred situations are getting more
and more numerous and uh there's going
to be some uh big uh template changes
coming in my life going to be when well
yes this is I don't know um oh I'm not
even ah okay well I'm not I haven't yet
discovered for myself when and what form
the new templates will take oh perhaps
that is because you have not been
willing to create them yet you only
discover what you create ah yes okay
there have been many ideas many ideas of
templates all right and it's just all I
wanted to share was that uh along with
the um
uh the unsatisfactory things which are
okay um
I I just have a certain anxiety about um
when in what form the new uh lifestyle
will take and just anxiety why not
excitement well anxiety is the same
energy as excitement it is simply going
through your process of invalidation
rather than being allowed to be trusted
when you inv validate that energy it
becomes anxiety when you trust it it
becomes excitement knowingness oh yeah
it is the same energy you are right on
the threshold but not willing to believe
that you can have in your life what you
truly desire perhaps a few suggestions
or one in particular might be in order
please repeat after me if you are
willing there there is is no no such
such thing as as something something too
too simple simple or or too too good
good to be true to be
true all right now perhaps if you allow
that to sink in you will begin to
exercise more trust and allow yourself
to realize that it is up to you to
create the conscious decision to live
the way you prefer to live trusting that
when you make that conscious decision
the universe will support you just as
much as has always supported you in
whatever decision you have been willing
to believe in most is the most likely
reality you will experience ah ah yes
you see the universe always supports you
100% according to the definition of the
reality you believe the most likely
reality you will experience so when you
change the definition to one you prefer
consciously then the universe will begin
to support you in that definition
s very convenient yes it is very simple
very simple well thank you very much for
that thank you very much for allowing us
to reflect back to you what you really
do already now thanks again sharing bash
yay um I have two questions and I'm
going to sit down for them all
right um I I went on a ski trip and I
Had An Occurrence with my leg mic and I
Had An Occurrence with my leg hey and I
was breaking in a new
act thank you yes um I was wondering if
you can help me connect up a little bit
I've been reflecting on this quite a bit
oh help you connect up all right with
the idea as to why I've manifested this
in in my life at this time and what I
might do to continue the healing process
and to expedite it in a
very good way you can do to expedite the
healing process is draw upon the many
times you have been a very very strong
magnetic healer you are very expressive you have
healer you are very expressive you have
the ability to express that magnetism in
many different ways one of which is
literally directly through the
manipulation of the electromagnetic
energy around you and in your body to
allow the healing process to speed up
and accelerate to knit by imposing upon
the leg in that way the ideal ized
electromagnetic pattern that represents
the blueprint zero rest state of your
leg and at the same time by sharing
expressiveness full emotional Spectrum
expressiveness with other individuals in
terms of excitement in terms of healing
in terms of sharing in terms of ideas
then you will also be putting out that
magnetic Beacon and that is what will
allow the homogeneous Oneness of of
energy to flow through you and as it
flows through you to straighten out the
gate that you are and connect any things
that are
disconnected you follow me yes I do
okay there is within you our perception
of many many lifetimes as a very strong
magnetic healer you have to some degree
now simply because it was your general
choice to experience it in this
way giv yourself an
opportunity to support yourself in
another way entirely you have so to
speak cut yourself in mid stride but at
a time of high exhilaration High
acceleration and high excitement so that
you can take that excitement and allow
it to transform into something else it
is not cut off you simply are now
allowing all of that builtup EX
excitement that you may have believed
got cut off mid stride to now transform
and burst forth in a number of different
ways so that the momentum will be
completed on another level on another
slope alt
together it is as if in a
sense you at the same time one of the
same time ran into and also passed
through a doorway
at that very moment was a very strong
pivot point in your life to allow you to
now use that downhill momentum and
acceleration in a very different way we
would recommend this only a
suggestion involve yourself in the study
of what you would call the pivotal point
of conversion of energy within the
movements you often refer to as Tai ch
all right there is a point when massive
amounts of energy are being directed
toward an individual when that
individual can redirect all of that
energy and the reason that they can
redirect all of that energy at
absolutely no stress to them is because
there is a point at which they
absolutely match the motion and the
speed of the energy coming toward them
so that relative to each other no one is
moving when nothing is moving it is very
easy to create something to move in a
gentle direction to reroute the energy
you follow me we sense that this will
bring you back into a center that you
have not experienced for a little while
in your lifetimes but it will be
something that once you begin will be
very very familiar to you and will
create within you a new understanding of
support a new understanding of balance
that will then allow you to endure what
other individuals may consider to be the
most tremendous of energy waves or
shocks to the system and you will not
experience it as a shock at all you will
bend and
flow you follow me thank you yes
anything else um no I think that's just fine I'll
else um no I think that's just fine I'll
get to work on it right away thank you
it does not have to be a struggle and
enjoy enjoy relax enjoy thank
you sure
hey um I'm sure you're aware that I
understand what you've talked about in
terms of polarity all right and uh I
find myself in a definite bipolar fluid
situation how exciting yes how
momentous um the confusion comes not in
allowing myself to the template that I
would prefer it comes from receiving
pressure from my wife receiving pressure
to do something different all right to
not to not allow the space for the
universe to you know
fulfill what I would prefer to do and
being taken by another you know given a
force by another person to do something
that I would prefer not to do and it
creating a A
disruption why are you accepting
delivery of that
package um I've been fighting it and
there is no need to fight it that is
only creating the package to be heavier
that's true I have received that
message um can you in your imagination
allow yourself to
realize that you can do what it is that
excites you the most and at the same
time therefore anything else that needs
to be done automatically to allow you to
continue to do that idea will
automatically take care of itself and
all the individuals that you interact
with will also find that the timing in
your life will make room for the things
that need to be done on many different
levels there is only a fear that doing
what it is that excites you the most
will allow another individual to feel
that they are left out or that things
will not occur the right way or when
they should or when they need to this is
all simply an experiment and an
exploration and a reflection in trust
for both of
you correct so how do you get rid of the
judgment and expectation by not getting
rid of it by not getting rid by knowing
that when you used to use it it served
you and simply realizing that you do not
need it anymore as a tool that the use
of the invalidation is in and of itself
self what prevents you from creating
what you
desire so why use a tool that prevents
you from getting the job
done why not simply now change your tool
into one that is simpler to represent
the Simplicity that you desire to work with which
with which
is what is it you wish to
do I am most happy doing uh bodyw work
all right using using the energy using
the bipolar currents all right and what
if you will the argument given against
such an Endeavor uh I'm not able to
bring in money right away but you can
always attract
abundance doing something else right
away yes doing something
else abundance abundance abundance
abundance doesn't necessarily mean money
when it needs to it can but money is
only one of the tools that represents
abundance abundance is simply the
ability to do what you need to do when
you need to do it period That's
abundance now sometimes money can be the
representational symbol that delivers
abundance but it doesn't always have to
be if there are ways that represent a
path of least resistance that are easier
and quicker to get what you need in life
to support you in the life you have
created would you not prefer that they
came in the easiest and quickest way and
if money was not the easiest and
quickest way would you not prefer that
it did come in the easiest and quickest
way or would you insist on waiting for
the money I wouldn't all right my wife would
money I wouldn't all right my wife would
but that individual simply in attracting
herself to you also has created for
herself an opportunity to explore her
understanding of abundance and her
understandings of trust we understand
because we are working through one of
your human templates we understand the
idea of what may at any given time seem
like reality and seem like nonsense to
members of your Society they will say
you can't just wish for it and have it
you have to work for it and you have to
struggle and you have to work hard and
you have to do all of these things
otherwise we will not have any kind of
real life oh get your head out of the
clouds oh grow up oh stop dreaming
what's wrong with you
and all sorts of wonderful phrases like
that but the idea no matter how insistent the
but the idea no matter how insistent the
belief systems are that you have been
taught in your
Society you still create your reality
based upon what you believe to be the
most likely way your reality will
manifest and an individual that has been
taught to have an overriding fear that
they will not have what they truly need
in life
unless they struggle for it will then
spend their life struggling and even if
they get it at the time they get it they
may be too worn out to appreciate
it but the idea is to truly trust that
what you need in life you can have and
you can have it right away and you can
have it effortlessly if you are willing
to
recognize that by doing what excites you
the most in life you are doing the thing
that allows you to create what you
desire in life quickly and most easily
because excitement is the indicator that
says this is what in life you can do
most easily and most quickly that's what
excitement is in your life for it's the
barometer it is the measure that lets
you know that this is the thing that
represents the vibration that for you is
most easily the way to create abundance
in your life that's why you have
excitement it lets you know here it is
here's the thing that represents the
vibration of the path you chose to be do
it and when you do it you will attract
abundance into your life if you do not
believe you are seeing the attraction of
that abundance into your life it is
because you are not yet fully giving
over to the trust of your excitement you
are still hanging on the
threshold so your reality will be one of
threshold you follow me you are creating
an abundance of
uncertainty exctly because that's the
definition of your trust
5050 so the universe says all right
50/50 if that's the way you want it
spread out that's the way you get it
when you
decide that you will place 100% of it in
the direction of the trusting of your
excitement the universe will supply you
with whatever you need to allow yourself
to maintain the thing that is the
vibration you are the universe always
works that way you are not getting it to
do something it doesn't already do it
always supports you 100% in the idea you
are being but if the idea you are being
is a 50/50 idea then that's the way the
100% is sprad
out that's the focus I'm not sure well
maybe this well maybe that so that's the
way you get your reality and therefore
the individual who is most strongly
individual who is most strongly
generating that idea of a uncertain
reality well if you do that we cannot be
certain we will survive if you do that
we cannot be certain that we will be
successful that
individual will then always create and
attract into their life the ability to
reinforce the negative scenario and will
always be able to come up with I told
you so I told you so you see it doesn't
work I told you so but they have never
seen you work 100% in the direction of
what excites you the most they are
simply with you co-creating the reality
of I told you it wouldn't work I told
you it wasn't enough well in individuals
who say I told you so always get
reinforced with a reality that always
allows them to continue to say I told
you so you follow me
so you follow me
yes let that assimilate you do not have
to attack you do not have to accuse she
is doing nothing wrong she is simply
learning what she needs to learn the
idea is that she is not behind you you
are not better the idea is that you have
attracted yourself to each other so that
you could explore the particular facets
of abundance you are exploring with each
other and the levels of trust you are
willing to put out in your realities but
you always get what you believe and or
fear will be the most likely
reality thank you thank you pleasant
dreams sharing hello Bashar hey hi hi uh
I just first of all I want to just thank
you for sharing your awarenesses and and
understandings with us because and you
thank you I have found them very very
helpful and so have we found your
Reflections very assistive thank you uh
I was wondering if you could help me
with the confusion I've had for many
years on just the topic and the activity
of meditation meditation yes I'm always
confused about what what exactly I'm
supposed to do and how that differs just
from thinking is up to you uhhuh
thinking can be a form of meditation to
some degree
the idea however most generally
representative of meditation is to allow
yourself not so much
analysis but more the idea of a
seemingly detached observation what you
may most colloquially refer to as
daydreaming now have you ever daydreamed
oh definitely and in the Daydream state
do you not feel a little more floaty
shall we say than when you are actually
sitting there thinking about something
in a very precise way yes then allow
yourself to recognize that in terms of
what you generally call
meditation that energy moved in the
direction of the
Daydream is more precisely
representative you follow me yes but I
don't see myself as as an observer uh or
what was the word you used is detached
did use that word the idea of Detachment
is to actually know that you are
attached to everything
that is true Detachment Detachment is
not actually separating yourself from
anything true Detachment is actually
encompassing everything when everything is absolutely
everything when everything is absolutely
on the same level and equal then nothing
gets an undue proportion of attention
and to many individuals that may seem
like a Detachment but it is actually a
very centered state of awareness and
peace mhm so allow yourself to Simply
expand in your imagination expand expand
expand expand until you feel in whatever
way is correct for you in whatever
methodology and by whatever terminology
you feel so appropriate expand until you
are a bubble that contains
everything then simply explore all of
the different things you contain that's
meditation MH you follow me yes and if I
choose to focus on one of those aspects
than that would be meditating on that
particular aspect that is all right okay
okay well that clarifies even analysis
can lead you back into a form of
meditation it is also a form of
meditation in and of itself let us put
it this way almost any particular State
of Consciousness can be one that you can
ascribe to a form of
meditation as long as you do not bring
worry into it mhm you follow me yes
simply observing focusing exploring
examining no matter how minute can be a
form of meditational
focus the worry that often comes with
many of the ways you analyze things that
is what is not truly in that sense
meditative so similar state of awareness
but without the worry all right great I
could do that yes you can yes thank you
thank you very
much getting
hello Bashar hello well I'm Daphne and
I've heard you a few times I enjoy all
the channeling that I've heard yours and
others and I learned a lot over the past
year in terms of um getting into
accepting and uh realizing abundance
things you're talking about today and I
do feel that um able to Channel at all
times I understand that idea um recently
I heard again about the idea of
universes nice and uh well I guess my
question would have to be about that Al
there's a million things but um there
are more than a million universes
trillions an infinite number that's it
okay now you're bringing me back well um
just whatever you would like to share
with us about uh the in infinity and
Eternity of of of a universe and uh
possibilities and all that I I plan on
sharing more and um I just I I've lost a
lot of fear and I'm willing to
experience a lot of things and it's been
going on for quite a while but right now
I just feel uh you know very much better
about it all
right Infinity everything all that is all at
Infinity everything all that is all at
once right here right
now universes are simply different
points of view of the you you already
are in an expanded
sense you contain all the universes of
all experience and the experience of any
experience and the experience of any
particular universe is simply the
shifting of a point of
view you
already exist not only in all universes
but as all
universes and therefore it is not and
does not have to be difficult for you to
have have the experience of many
different ideas many different locals in
that sense that you have nowhere to get to
sense that you have nowhere to get to
that you are already there that another
version of you already exists there and
all you need is the desire to see
through the eyes of the you you are
there to be in Another Universe I
understand thank you um and that reminds
me of us being mirrors yes for each
other yes do not forget that every
moment of time that you create to
experience you actually create yourself
to be quite a few number of universes
anyway you are always a different
Universe no matter how slightly
different you might be from the last
Universe you were when one variable in
the equation changes the whole equation
is
different yes um well since I've been a
child I felt that I would always be
taken care of I I mean I've been called
naive and apola and stupid and
everything but you are also Eternal and
infinite but it's been true though I've
never been so out of it that you know
out of out of what supposed to be
in that uh that I haven't found some
type of Salvation and found myself well
you know I haven't killed myself or
anything yes you
have well not recently
no although all of those lives are still
going on simultaneously with all the
other lives you have ever lived I
understand that too I really don't
believe in death anymore I think there's
uh it is simply
transformation okay now would you just
say one thing more about breathing what
what do you have to say about breathing
because I've discovered something and
crying I found that the um where you
where you centering energizing
oxygenation of the system
crystallization of the cellular atomic
structures breathing breathing is the
primary fundamental meditation allow yourself to
fundamental meditation allow yourself to
know that when you breathe deeply in a
relaxed and calm State you are centering
yourself into the idea of being at the
center of all probable reality
sight becomes clear
Insight allow yourself
to know you are regenerating when you
breathe you are actually aligning
yourself with the very pulse of the
particular Universe you are in at any
given moment you are going with the
pulse with that breath a deep relaxed
breath at whatever rate
represents your normal relaxed rate of
breathing any time you find yourself in
a situation where you feel anxious all
you need to do is rep replicate the
breathing cycle when you remember
yourself having been in a relaxed State
use your
imagination invoke that breathing cycle
and it will always bring you back to
Center always thank you it is your
always thank you it is your
energization symbol your energization
tool when you breathe in that way you
may also find yourself sleeping less and
eating less because you are drawing
sustenance from the Primal energy of
creation itself thank you very good okay thank
itself thank you very good okay thank
you I'm for sure I'm Janet ni I have
this um problem with feeling you have a
what seemingly problem cing to of
feeling chronically fatigued oh
and and I'd very much like to have an
abundance of energy oh right are you
doing in your life what you would prefer
to do what excites you the most well I
try to but you what well I have trying
is tiring yes well if I feel that if I
had an abundance of energy
I other way around when you do what you
really prefer to do you will have an
unlimited Supply if you are waiting to have that
Supply if you are waiting to have that
energy before you will do what really
excites you in life you will spend a
long time I'm waiting do what you truly
are excited about doing and that is what
will generate the Unlimited Supply of
energy have you not heard it said upon
your planet that a labor of love is no
labor at
all recognize therefore that when you do
what you truly love to do what do you
know the energy is there well I never
had so much energy I've never had so
much fun because doing the vibratory
thing that repres presents the path you
chose to be is effortless so you will
not be expending energy trying to do
what you wish to do is tiring because
all of the trying in the world is never
the doing of the thing you wish to do it
is only the doing of
trying okay I do pursue um what I really
want to do but I'm just wondering if I
maybe have some blocks or fears that I
can't release that I that AR not at the
surface or maybe some past karma
karma yes I cuz I
worked I've worked with this for like
eight months or so and I can't all right
all right all right first of
all recognize right now there are
doorways and bubbles popping within you
there are Gates opening within all
levels of caught
you your Consciousness right now allow
yourself to understand karma is
self-imposed now now now now now now now
now now now if there is any karma in
your life you are holding on to it now
it is not from before there is no before
everything is always now no matter
paradoxically how many lives you have
ever lived you are living them all now
across the board in other dimensions
simultaneously on multiple levels in all
directions in all times in all spaces
you are living them all
now who you wish to be now is completely
totally up to the discretion of your
conscious mind now let go of the anchor
that holds you to the concept of the
past whether it be the past of this life
or any other life you are only holding
on to an anchor and that prevents you
from moving forward because of your
concept of time because of your concept
of
energy you right now are free you are a
balloon Whose Line has been cut you are
unlimited you are not bound you are
absolutely free let those
ideas appear now
rather than Len to be simply bubbles of
thought let them
pop let them pop feel them popping hear
them in your
imagination popping now let them pop
away let them burst back into the energy
let the fragrance the
aroma of of those bubbles surround you
breathe it in all of the ideas that you
have thought have been holding you down
all of those ideas have only been the
idea that you can be held
down that's it nothing weighs
anything let yourself float
free this life right now you have right
now this moment right now all the tools
necessary to do anything you want right
now give
yourself the conscious
permission right now to let yourself
know that you can do what you desire to
do and that therefore because you are
doing what excites you the most you will
be in alignment with the energy of the
whole universe and therefore the energy of the
universe and therefore the energy of the
whole
universe will support you and therefore
What You Do by going with the
flow will be an effortless
expression thank you very much turn
around you do not have to go
Upstream just turn around and flow down
Downstream blocks are only ideas of blocks
blocks are only ideas of blocks
blocks are only unexpected directions in
the path you are that you simply do not
believe will lead you where you want to
go so you stand at the crossroads
refusing to move because your ego says
no no no not that way even though it's
obviously the way you need to go even
though the path does not move in any
other direction you stand there and
treat the bend in the road as if it were
a wall because you have been taught to
believe you can't go in that direction
you can't get there from here but you
can because you will always only be
getting back to here from wherever you
are anyway which is always here to begin
with all Journeys are all from here to
here all of them you never really go and
anywhere it is all if you wish in your
mind but that does not invalidate it and
I do not mean to make light of it no pun
intended the idea is that you are
creating yourself to be the physical
life you think you are living in this is
your creation you are in
creation you are in
control allow yourself to Simply allow
your reality not to be chiseled out of
steel and therefore highly immobile
allow your reality to be sculpted in
light made out of bubbles which at any
given moment can pop back into the Rare
Essence out of which they were created
to begin
with then as you breathe that Essence in
and exhale it out into new bubbles they
will be more representative of what you
in your heart know to be true for
you express that express yourself and
then what comes out of you what forms
into your externalized reality will be
more representative of what you truly
believe within you is what you wish to
experience when you let what is within
you out that's the physical reality
you'll experience let it
out okay thanks a lot thank you very
much and exciting
and exciting
dreams for you have opened many gates
and many different levels of
communication between yourself and
higher aspects of your own Consciousness
will commence
commence
tonight thank you very much for allowing
us to blow a few bubbles with you good
job hi bash hi
uh I I've been standing here thinking
about the question I was going to ask
and a lot of the questions have been
answered how synchronous thank you for
co-creating such synchronicity and trust
with us well the trust is what I'm
struggling with
oh that's the the area of my life that I
hear you saying give yourself permission
okay and somewhere inside here there is
a block that doesn't allow myself to
give myself the
permission where inside you where it
feels up in my throat and um in my solar
plexus I just that's two blocks or is it
a big block
it's it's two it's it's I guess it's two
blocks you
guess well I feel it here and I feel it
here so I guess it's do you feel it
anywhere in
between no all right then for now we'll
call it two blocks two blocks two for
the price of one all right what a
bargain you
got a bargain in blocks you know I am
not making fun of you yet I know I am
creating fun with you for that is what
will allow the blocks to
melt I've been finding myself
um getting progressively more depressed
as I've been out of work longer the
longer I'm out of work the more
depressed of becoming and the less trust
I have in myself and my ability to find
work in something that's going to excite
me I then create what excites you to be
your job that's the whole idea the idea is
job that's the whole idea the idea is
not to look around necessarily for the
things that excite you that already
exist the idea is if you do not find
them then allow what excites you to
become your
job somebody had to start the job that
exist in your Society they didn't just
always exist in the format that they
exist in now someone had to say wait a
minute look around the thing that really
excites me the most there isn't a job
for I guess I had better start it and
now later on you think that's a typical
job because someone once started the
idea but if you look around and do not
find something that excites you in that
way if you look around and find that
your passingly does not lead you into
these things then allow yourself to truly
things then allow yourself to truly
examine in all honesty what it is that
really would be truly exciting and
simply take it for granted that you then
if that thing really excites you and no
one else at this point is doing it or
you do not attract into your life an
opportunity to do it where it already
exists then take it for granted that
your ability to conceive of what it is
that excites you the most also
represents your ability to create that
to be the job that will support you
automatically again this is simply as you have said a
again this is simply as you have said a
matter of truly trusting that what you
come up with that what you really know
would excite you in life you are capable
of doing whether any structure already
exists for it or not if no such
structure exists then that means that
because you thought of it you have the
structure inherent within you and all
you have to do is let it out let it
unfold and then the reality will be able
to build itself on that template
structure but you're not letting it
out I I feel so incompetent I feel that
I I feel so incompetent I feel that
means you believe you are we have
discussed with you before the idea that
no feeling comes without a belief
already being instilled within you there
is no such thing as simply feeling
something for no reason out of the blue
feelings are not generated out of thin
air out of a vacuum if you feel
something it's because you already
believe something to be true feelings
are a reaction to a belief they are
secondary to a belief feelings are not
the primary experience of reality belief
is the primary interface first you
believe something is true then you get
the feeling then you have the
reinforcing thoughts which may re
reinforce the belief and then regenerate
more of the same feelings but the
feeling that you are incompetent comes
from the fact that you simply choose to
believe you are incompetent it's your
choice to believe that but you don't
have to I want to let go of it and every
time I go to I keep getting these voices
that tell me but remember this time
remember that time remember this time
what does that time have to do with this
time I know but it but they come up and
the voices are there let come up so
what you see you are trying to shut
portions of yourself off you think that
when you integrate you will never hear
those voices again and that's not true
you will always hear those voices as a
matter of fact the more you integrate
the more you will hear them because the
more you accept everything every way
that you are into your life and those
are some of the ways you can exist but
they come up not to show you you have
failed not to show you you are stuck
they keep coming up to give you the
opportunity to realize how much you
changed because you don't relate to them
the same way you used to unless of
course you choose to do so so when you
say oh well look the voices are still
coming up that must mean I have failed
that must mean I'm not doing the right
thing the right way you are choosing to
maintain the same relationship with
those voices but you don't have to the
voices are there as an opportunity to
realize you can form a different
relationship with them all right here
comes the voice well remember when this
happen that way well yes yes but so what
that was then I have learned since then
and because you oh wonderful Voice have
now reminded me of the way I did it then
then now I have a great and positive
opportunity to see how differently I am
going to do it
now you are giving yourself a measure
look this is the way it happened then
all right now in your imagination you go
well all right now I know it's going to
be different this is the way I prefer to
see it happening now see how much
difference there is it is the way to
allow yourself to recognize you are
going through an evolutionary process if
that's what you believe you must go
through because from time to time you
may find well the voice comes up look
this is the way that happened then and
then you may say all right well this
time it happened almost the same but
there's the key word if you are a
positive individual you'll lock onto
that almost the same it was a little bit
different a little bit different and
that's good enough for me because if it
can be a little bit different it can be
a lot different and next time when the
voice says well yeah but remember when
it happened this way now you recognize
yes but the last time it was more
different and therefore I know because I
choose to look at it that way that next
time it will be more more different so
you keep reminding me of the way it was
little voice because when you keep
reminding me of the way it was it gives
me an opportunity to see how much more
different it's becoming all the
time everything in your life can be used
in a positive way even the same old
Little Voices it's up to your willingness to
Voices it's up to your willingness to
allow your imagination to work for you
trust it have the positive attitude that
will determine
Everything You Follow Me
use it as a tool if it's there use it as
a tool don't think that just because
it's there it means you failed that's
your old attitude that's your old belief
I just get reinforcements from other
people in my life telling me all you
have to accept
reinforcement no one can give you
reinforcement well they're agreeing with
thees what the inner reality is the outer
what the inner reality is the outer
reality it is one and the
same if you have the Little Voices
within you of course you're going to
have the voices outside of you as well
but when you start using those little
voices in the way we just described then
the outer voices will also
change you understand yeah the inner is
the outer reality the outer reality is
the inner reality they are not two
different things it is one so as you
believe in so you see
out as you seow so you reap that's what
that means the seeds you plant within
yourself are what you see growing in the
garden around you so if you do not like
the flowers you see growing then change
your order of
seed plant something different and then
something new will
grow you follow
me the inner is the outer the inner is
the outer if the outer is not the way you
outer if the outer is not the way you
prefer it to be change the inner and the
outer will
follow I've worked on saying I I've
worked on saying things I guess the the
belief was still the old one I didn't
get rid of the old belief you cannot get
rid of anything okay what I did was I
said okay I can I can do this and I can
hand the job and somewhere there was
that belief that's that still was
hanging on to the other one listening to
the way many times you phrase things as
well because many times the way you
phrase things is an indication of the
way you really believe okay okay I can
handle it I can handle it right there it
lets you know the way you are saying it
means you think it is overwhelming to
begin with and that's what the real
belief is the belief therefore is not
really that you can handle it because if
you knew beyond the shadow of a doubt
that you could you wouldn't have to
convince yourself if you find yourself
using phraseology that indicates that
you are attempting to convince yourself
then you do not believe it naturally let
yourself know that you do not have to
think twice about something you already
own when you phrase things in that
manner when you say all right all right
I can handle it I can handle it then you
are indicating that you do not really
believe it is
handleable you do not have to handle
things in that way you already control
everything you already control
everything therefore if situations occur
in your life that seem to be non
preferable manifestation you controlled it for a
manifestation you controlled it for a
reason for a positive reason into that
format even though I don't see what the
positive reason is let the positive
reason at least the fundamental reason
that you're giving yourself an
opportunity to realize you don't have to
relate to the scenario the way you used
to and you may be checking yourself to
see if you still
are what phrases could I use that would
be more beneficial to me how does this
serve me exactly the way it is exactly
the way it is how does it serve me what
can I learn how can can I positively
learn something from
this then when you let it be the way it
is is when it has the greatest
opportunity to change into something
else but if you deny it the form in
which it comes then you are not allowing
yourself to see what is inherent within
it you are not allowing itself to
present itself in the way you have
created it to present itself you are
denying your own creation your own
format only when you acknowledge your
own format of delivering messages to
yourself exactly and completely the way
it comes to you do you then create the
conscious freedom to transform that
delivery system into a way you would
prefer it to
come but if you constantly treat your
delivery system as if it is
malfunctioning then you are not
listening to it you are thinking
something is going going wrong within
you and therefore that's the belief you
reinforce and therefore that's the cycle
you repeat something is wrong something
is wrong something is wrong and so of
course your reality constantly reflects
back to you something is wrong something
is wrong something is wrong everything
is just fine in what you used to
consider the most dire circumstance let
yourself realize everything is just fine
I'm in control of this look look at how
much control I have to have created such
an absolutely exciting scenario
everything seeming to be wild and hither
and thither and all over the place and
seemingly wild and unconnected and out
of control but since I know I'm
controlling that look at how much power
I
have are you beginning to get the Habit
yes for the only thing you are
experiencing is the idea that you have
old habits that are difficult to break
so if that's where you're coming from
all right I have habits that I believe
are difficult to change so if I believe
in the idea of habits then use the idea
of habits in a positive way and create
positive habits I love myself I love myself I am
habits I love myself I love myself I am
in control of everything even when it
seems like it's out of control I'm
controlling that get used to thinking in
a positive way get used to knowing and
Bel that there is a positive manifestation
that there is a positive manifestation
that can occur from every
scenario no
exceptions
none I felt like I was and then when I
lost my job I just but you see you
assumed that not being in that job for
some reason has to be an inherently
negative scenario why make that
assumption it is only an assumption how
do you know what losing that job may be
making room for that you would just
explode with delight to receive that you
wouldn't have room to receive if you
still had the old
job trust that when things like that
occur in your life if you know you are
doing the best you can do at that moment
and those things still occur then assume
it's for a good reason and let yourself
see how it is for a good reason only
when you insist that those things occur
not for a positive reason do you then
keep the reason from coming to you that
would let you see why you lost the job
for a positive reason because you're
sitting there moping on the idea oh well
the only thing I can think of that
losing my job means it must be negative
something's wrong and when you are
focused in that way you can't see the
positive side of the coin you can't see
it until you choose to look at it you
have to decide consciously that you will
look at the positive side of the coin in
every single circumstance or you will
not be able to see positive
manifestation if you are constantly
insisting that circumstances are
inherently negative losing a job must be
a bad thing has to be everyone knows
that if that's the way you choose to
look at it that's the way you'll
experience your reality when you insist
just as strongly that losing a job must
be leading to a more expanded and
broader positive experience that's what
you will get in your
life that's it it's that simple guess I
got impatient because I stated that I
have said that exactly and I and what
happened was I did get an interview for
for a job that paid more
yes and then what did you bring back the
expectations if I don't get this I'm
failing yeah and then I and then blew
the interview and I didn't get the job
and you know so then I started
to to go into my old remove the
expectations it doesn't have to manifest
exactly as your ego or your habits think
it should it doesn't have
to let it manifest along the path of
least resistance stop fighting
resistance stop fighting
yourself you do not have to push
yourself into mold you fit exactly where
you are you do not have to conform to a
are you do not have to conform to a
particular idea of what success
represents you are successful exactly as
you are I have a suggestion all right
there are several people waiting and
what works for me is to get the tape and
listen to it again you will get more and
more and more out of it as you listen to
it and sleep on it thank you thank you
very much wake up and dream
yes thank
you thank you B I want to thank you for
sharing with a friend of mine
mine
um about a ceremony you described for a
thunder dreamer the hyoka ceremony and I
want to thank you for that I've been
doing it quite often we thank you thank
you um I have experienced in my life
life the 50/50 that you've talked about
creating both negative and positive
synchronicity right I've realized of
late that I have chosen to believe more
the negative synchronicity than the
positive all right I'm changing that all
right and integrating Within Myself all
right what I'm doing and what I'm
creating the uh creating both of them
has been a source of excitement for me
yes and to you all or you wouldn't have
done it
you all have good reasons for doing
everything you have ever done yes when
you let yourself believe that and let
that sink in then you'll realize that
you can create whatever you truly prefer
that's what I'm doing now yes thank you
thank you I want to ask you about an
incident that occurred at my business
which has been a lot of the business
that I'm in has been a lot of source of
both positive and negative synchronicity
a uh you are the source they are simply
the reflections of the source you are
yes yes a cat walked in and this cat
walked around a black and white cat my
mind yes I understand a lot of the
yes I understand a lot of the
significance how your symbols are
becoming yes and I thought the cat wanted some
yes and I thought the cat wanted some
food which of course it ate a little bit
of and then didn't and then I was
standing and it basically walked around
visiting every one and but kept walk
coming back to
me and I was working in the front of the
store and the cat just decided to sit
down in the
front and stare out to the door watching
uh just watching and it was a great
experience between me and the cat I
wanted to see if you had any comment
about that what did you wish to do
that perhaps inhibitions did not allow
you to
do talk more with the can all right what
do you imagine you would have learned or
do you imagine you would have left and
done something with
it
h um I would have imagined I would have
learned that the cat I felt that the cat
was acknowledging the integration that I
all right cre back up yeah if you in
your imagination
had been the cat how do you imagine you
would have seen the place the cat walked
into if you were looking as the cat
explore that idea and see what you come
up with in your imagination okay be the
cat identify not only with it but as it
and see what you get okay when you
identify fully as any symbol in your
reality no matter what it is that's when
you are in complete and total telepathic
communication with it because you are
identifying as it that's how telepathy
works you become your version of that
idea and therefore of course you
experience the same thoughts it does
that's telepathy it is not direct
reading of mind it is total
identification as your version of that
idea of that being of that object then
you know what it is like to be the cat
the table your friend your family your
world and so
forth then you can put into action what
portions of it you prefer what portions
of it represent the idea you as the
being you are can most effortlessly
apply to your real realityy therefore
the animal and any object will function
as a multi-dimensional symbol allowing
each and every individual that interacts
with it to get out of it what they wish
to identify as it in whatever form
represents the being they are and to
apply through themselves in whatever
format they are the idea they get out of
it in the way that represents the way
they are living their
lives multi-dimensional multi-dimensional
multifaceted Crystal
so I can walk back in with the cat you
can walk back in as as the cat and then
see the place as you would imagine the
cat sees it be the cat in that way now
we do not mean you have to get down on
all fours you can if you wish depends
upon your willingness and your sense of
humor but the idea is that you can still
see as if you were the cat
yes at this time we will let you curl up
with that idea While You all take a very
relaxing short
break thank
you while you are preparing yourselves
for sharing allow me to share something
with you if I may all right all
right just to show you
that there are many points of view that
exist within many of the civilizations
we have
encountered we will simply
relate that your particular
civilization is an our Viewpoint as we
have stressed to you many times in this
sense unique to some degree in the
degree of the
focus of limitation that you have
experienced but as we have said to us
this can also be a positive thing in
that it does make you masters of
limitation so that you have experienced
all there is to experience on that
particular idea of limitation and
therefore have that completely within
you as a total experience to draw from
that you can utilize to share and assist
with other individuals as you will be
doing perhaps in your future with other
planetary systems to assist them in the
limitations they have created for
themselves if they need such a assistant
to be reminded that they have also got
the ability and the inherent power to
create the realities they desire this we
perceive you will be doing in short
order even as we are doing this with you
however there was one time when we
encountered a civilization that came
into contact with the
association and eventually in sharing
information back and forth as you say it
came time to describe and Define
Your Existence and what we were doing in
interacting with you now do you realize
that one of the closest times we have
ever approached what you would call
although not exactly in the same way no
negativity no real violent emotionality
in that sense but the closest we have
ever come to what you would colloquially
call an argument with anyone was
that they simply could not believe
that there could
exist any expression of individuality
within the physical universe that could
not be aware of its own power that could
actually forget that it creates its own
reality it took some
[Laughter] convincing they call you a
convincing they call you a
liar not
really but simply it was beyond their
conception in that way not that they are
any better than you but simply to show
you how many different ways there are to
perceive reality and that there are
civilizations who have created
themselves to inherently not even be
able to conceive of the ability to
forget that you are a part of Infinite
Creation so in this way recognize it was
quite astonishing in that sense to them
to realize that you were actually able
to funnel your great power inside such a
manner as to use that power to create in
yourselves the ability to forget that
you even had the power you were
using they learned something new about
themselves that way learned something
new about the universe that day and you
taught them to their great amazement
that that was one way that all that is
can express itself and now they have a
much broader understanding of the way
Infinite Creation can express itself you
have taught them something in that way
by your willingness to experience such a
high degree of limitation and focus in
that sense they in turn began experimenting
sense they in turn began experimenting
to some degree with that idea not that
they [Laughter]
[Laughter]
created not that they created exactly
the same degree of forgetfulness but you
see the ID in their civilization became
a source of enjoyment because they found
as you also found to some degree that
the ability to impose the illusion of
forgetting upon yourself however
momentarily allows you to experience
things as if you are experiencing them
for the first time and for them they
realized that that was an experience
they had not
had and so in that way they were able to
generate for themselves a whole new
understanding of creativity simply from
the altering of the perspective the
altering of the point of view of
creating the scenario of not remembering
that you are connected to the
experiences you are creating your
reality to
be therefore recognize that even out of
all that you have considered to be such
a Negative experience other individuals
in the universe have benefited greatly
from your unique willingness to create
such a reality that can then be shared
in many different ways as a learning
tool by men individuals in the
universe you also have assisted Us in
assisting other worlds because our
thought patterns would also be highly
alien to you and yours to us and without
the use of the idea of a model upon your
planet a life without having experience
the idea of a life upon your planet as I
have experienced in the form of the
physical channel before you in what you
would consider my past then I would not
have the model to draw from the
experiences to draw from to be able to
assist you now or even speak with you on
the same terminology at all and so in
using your high degree of focusing
limitation we have been able to know
that if our model works on your world it
works marvelously on many other worlds
that do not have such a high degree of
limited Focus because you are then the
master lock for almost any other
civilization that is experiencing
limitation to any
degree and so we thank you for the high
focus you have created because then in
dipping into your well we have almost
all the tools necessary to deal with
almost anyone
[Laughter] else we thank you for forging that type
else we thank you for forging that type
of
Steel that allows us to be able to cut
through the bonds of the illusion that
exist in many other societies and yours
as well we thank you sharing we
did hello Bashar it's nice to see you
again UND you um
sort recently um my boyfriend's
5-year-old son transitioned on and it
was a time that we were coming very
close to seeing him he hadn't seen him
since he was an infant and we had been
meditating and and sending him a lot of
love and a lot of energy and shortly
after we had decided that we were going
to see him he uh drown and we have felt
his presence especially around his
father um around the house a lot lately
I was wondering if you could give us any
insight as to why he decided to choose
this time to leave and well a it was all
the time he needed to experience in
physical reality okay many Souls that
choose to be of service in many
different ways will realize in their
estim oh let's say we have one or two
little things to understand about being
in physical reality but we will impose a
timing limit on it so we will not live
out a full life because we do not need
to we need to experience the idea of
just a few ideas just getting our feet
wet in that way to allow us to
experience the idea that we can then be
of greatest assistance with in assisting
the entire civilization to go through
the transformation it is going through
so that Soul picked up whatever ideas
whatever remnants of ideas of
self-created karma it needed to to allow
itself to become balanced and aligned
within its own polarity so it can Now
function as a guide and be of greatest
assistance in that way it can lead and
lure many of you into the realm of light
in which it now
exists in your dreams will be the
strongest contacts and in your physical
reality will be very strong contacts but
generally speaking the contacts you have
between your respective consciousnesses
as they express themselves in physical
terms will play themselves out as
synchronous events that unfold in your
life rather than the idea of recognizing
yourself actually having what you would
call vocal or verbalized or auditory
communication yes he he has been very
present in my dreams for some time um
and wish yes you may
find that the individual May from time
to time use in various ways as a calling
card if you will to let you know there
is communication going on specifically
from that Consciousness they will use as
a calling card the symbol of water to
represent transformation and fluidity it can come
transformation and fluidity it can come
and will come in various ways
watch for it and recognize the vibratory
chord that is struck within all of you
when you see it when you do see it you
will know it is a symbol of the
communication going on at that moment
and simply you do not have to wait and
stop and listen do not stop your lives
let your lives play out knowing that
what is going on is a guidance a
cocreation from that soul from that
guide not being in physical reality for
a very long time in your terms of
counting has allowed that soul to remain
relatively unfettered uncluttered it did
not need in your terms much work much
orientation upon transforming to
non-physical reality it simply went back
into the idealized state of functioning
as the guide that it wished to function
as for many of you still experiencing
physical reality so watch for the signs
of water and you will know that
represents communication not that you
have to go out of your way to look for
them simply continue to live your lives
you follow me yes I do thank you thank
you fill yourselves with the light that
you
are and you will be more open and more
receptive to Communications from a being
that now knows itself to be composed
utterly of
light all right
thank you Shing Bashar two questions one for a
you Shing Bashar two questions one for a
friend her name is
zenine and she had a talk with me and I
thought that it might uh uh help her if
you sh had some light on this idea also
uh she's wondering the meaning of the
experience of finding herself at 46
being pregnant okay the meaning of it no
no well she had
well let me take a wild
gu let's see
[Laughter] now she is going to have a child
now she is going to have a child
no that can't be
it 46 well is there something strange
about having a child at that
age uh well she's already had a few
children and she doesn't really um from
my talking with her uh have the feeling
that she wants to have another one but
obious she made an agreement to a
certain point right to allow that
individual to experience a certain
degree of physical
reality okay that's part of the question
she has all right it may not
conclude in your
terms in
what month
uh I think she's the going on to the
third month all
right there may be
changes that will occur toward the
ending of the third month in that
way it may not
conclude it
can but it does not have to for the
being to get what it needs the being
that would be the child the child okay
one of the questions she had was at what
point is there the full connection with
the fetus and that new soul body
Consciousness exists now an extension of
the Soul Consciousness exists now but
full connection is not until birth
itself and sometimes not even until
after mhm the soul can still come and go
for a very long time after physical
birth body Consciousness will maintain
the body but the connection generally is not
body but the connection generally is not
actually until physical
birth okay if she actually chose then to
uh not to continue she's wondering if
there allow her to get in touch with the
reason she made the agreement
telepathically she can the agreement was
made allow her to get in touch in Her
Imagination in her meditations with the
reasons for the agreement the pictures
that come into her imagination May at
first not make much sense because some
of them represent connections to other
civilizations that are a part of the
overall child's agreement and origin
points but let her drift within the
images let her describe and write down
the images she gets in her emotionality
in her
meditation and she will allow herself to
begin to realize the reasons for the
agreement which can then also allow her
to choose and to recognize that there
may be portions of her that does wish
the child to come to
term okay she was feeling
um like Barren and sterile obviously
physically and emotionally previous to
this then perhaps the child has allowed
her to realize that she is always
fertile on many different levels
depending upon the agreements and the
timings that she creates and perhaps
that is one of the reasons why the child
may not have to quote unquote quot stick
around if she will be willing to learn
that she is never Barren on any level
all right okay once that is understood
then one of the primary reasons for the
existence of the child may have already
been fulfilled
fulfilled
also no offense
46 she is still a child to
[Laughter]
me allow her to realize that one of the
other ideas the child is sharing with
her is how to always function in that
childlike mode and that when she does
function with her child now then she can
live in that modality as an ageless
being for once again
recognize the transformational age one
of the reasons for it is to learn how to
live in the
moment now we are not saying act in a
childish manner but in a child like
Manner and in this way your society
allows you to act in a childlike manner
two times when you are young and when
you are very
old recognize therefore since you know
that this childlike behavior is actually
very closer to your natural state many
of you will allow yourselves to create
the idea of physical age so it will be
all right to act like a child again when
you allow yourself to act like a child
now you won't have to age to be able to
do
so and that is one of the things that
will make you ageless when you learn how
to play
now tell and share this with that
individual I will thank you very much oh
you're welcome she thanks you and so do
I one moment now
moment now
this may be only as it translates
through our interpretation of your
energy but we will share this with you
see if it means anything at all it may
not consciously to
her and again this is only our
interpretation and Her Imagination May
provide her with a vibration that is
closer to what she feels to be more
appropriate or accurate for her
representation of this idea but we will
share this one word about the child step
all right all
right all right thank you thank you
shoting okay the second question
yes listening to um the principles that
you bring forth and when you answer
almost every question concerning
interaction and when you come in contact
with another entity when they act as a
mirror unto yourself I okay when you run
across somebody that you perceive that
you're coming forth in an in an act of
Love unconditional love and they come
through with what you perceive as a
judgment does not mean we are talking
about a on toone reflection many
individuals will attract individuals
into their lives to allow that other
individual to see in them the lack of
judgment that the other individual is
putting forth so there can be polarity
mirrors as well as onetoone mirrors so
it's not necessarily yourself that
you're seeing you are seeing an aspect
of yourself that you certainly have the
potential to manifest but if you simply
know that that's not the aspect you are
manifesting at this time then simply
take it for granted that you may be then
functioning in that person's life as
something they need to
see because they may be considering ways
to change whereas you have already
considered and the way you are is the
way you wish to remain then you give
them an opportunity to see that they
also have the potential to create in
their lives the stability you have
created in yours you follow me yes so
it's okay to perfectly be in a
um a lack of communication like one
person presents one thing and another
presents the like a polarity yet but
that is not a lack of communication
right it is very powerful communication
okay simply it does not necessarily
represent the vibration of the reality
that that you find you create
experientially in your life but you can
still communicate and do communicate
back to them that your reality is the
way you prefer it to be and they can
decide whether what they see in you will
work for them or not and if not they can
be on their way right and likewise you
can choose well if I don't want to
interact with this person because I keep
getting that that judgment or that
reaction from them then if you choose
but recognize if you are in a reality
that is non-judgmental you won't feel it
negatively you may recognize that they
are doing it but you won't take it
personally okay so it will not affect
you that way so you won't care whether
they interact with you in that sense or
not because you will perceive anything
they have to say as something that you
can glean something positive from right
and then when they see how you treat
their attitude then is when you are
showing them the way they can deal with
themselves you follow me yes it is not a
matter of cutting them off if you have
attracted that individual into your life
then obviously you have also co-created
it for a reason an individual you do not
need to experience in your life you
never experience right so if they are
there obviously they are there not only
for their reason but for your own as
well one of your own being that you can
be of service to them and also learn on
your part how to not accept
their offer of being affected by their
negative point of
view follow me yes is the only way to do
that then to stand there and reflect who
you are right give them the echo back to
what they have given you that represents
the way what they have given you changes
when it hits you and bounces back if
they say I hate you say I love you
yes otherwise then you are simply
offering to reinforce the reality that
they are coming to you with and then you
are creating that reality for yourself
if you judge their judgments you follow
me mhm so in a sense you
never choose to walk away from any
anything you can choose that attitude
but you never really can right because
everything is right here right here
right okay anything that is in your life
is obviously there for your own good
reason begin to trust that you know what you
begin to trust that you know what you
are doing and then you will allow
yourself to realize you are in control
and the things that exist in your life
are there because of your own choosing
for some
reason deal with it accept it
acknowledge it and you will understand
why just by being true to yourself okay
thank you thank you very much
sharing hi Bashar hi um well I don't
know where where to begin how about at
the beginning uh there there is no
beginning oh very good then begin
anywhere it won't matter okay that's
right hey um I've been trying out this
idea oh trying it out oh yeah it's it's
a beauty that that idea of um Beauty all
right yes it is uh of of taking a
neutral Viewpoint and
um oh God there's so many I'm certainly
not going to take time here to to give
all the specifics but oh everyone can
feel them you don't have to
but but the idea that um I decided to
really do this really really do it to
really really honest and truly do the
idea of being just as grateful for the
things that I judge to be negative or or
reacted to even slightly negative or or
or judgmentally before you go on yes you
know there is a difference between
accepting negativity in your life and
preferring positivity just because
things occur in your life that may be
negative in that way or negative
manifestations we are not saying that
you cannot prefer positive manifestation
but that the way to allow the negative
to transform into the positive is to
realize that it is not truly or
necessarily has to be negative that that
is only a value judgment right all right
you bet okay so what yeah that that's
really what I was going to say
um what I did what what I did was what I
know when I did that what I what I
noticed is the things that I created as
being quote negative or things that I
didn't desire would start coming up and
they would kind of sneak up excuse me
and go okay Pammy how are you going to
deal with this one huh huh and it was
almost like a tease that I created for
myself like so so what's it going to be
and all of a sudden I actually had this
feeling of joy and I just thought how
humorous that can sneak in there too
yeah but it what it was was was just
simply that I would you know we're just
going to keep presenting this to you
until you get it straight and and of
course I'm doing this for myself does
that make sense what I'm saying yes um
perfect uh uh anyway it was just so
wonderful and I I decided I I a ah did
you hear that I decid no no no yes that
too but
anyway it was so wonderful
that's any way it was that's right B
that's it that's really I mean I can't
even find words to say this I'm oh you
have found them
perfectly and again when you radiate
that knowledge you don't need as many
words everyone can see the
light you don't have to describe the
light when you actually
shine that's really true um thank you I
just uh there's one more thing I was
going to say about oh I I said something
like all that is is always guiding me to
my highest expression or something like
that I decided to just operate on that
and then then I had some realizations
about when I used to perform I used to
be an opera singer and I used to love
performing and you know people always
saying well ego ego ego wasn't ego at
all what it was I was describing this to
someone the other day and I realized
something about it in in um it is simply
the same format as when a bird sings
that is not ego and also when when you
have the total attention of the audience
you are the focus of it and that's a lot
of energy to take in and focus and shape
and it's the and give back and that's
the same thing that all that is does for
you when you allow it and since you're
an individual you get to shape it even
though it's all part of you it's all one
thing it's like a circle you'll know
what what your planet is sounding less
and less third density all the time
are you sure I have the right [Laughter]
[Laughter]
planet yes I know I have exactly the
correct Planet because we believed and
knew when we began our interactions with
you that this is what you had already
chosen to understand
yes yeah you bet it's fun yes that's the
whole idea even the parts that are that
we were all kind of afraid of and uh
scared by and all that that stuff was
fun yeah all the limitations oh God
we're just so I'll tell you something
since i' since I've been on this it's
just a constant thing I can hardly I'm
numb actually I actually feel so much
energy searching through me all the time
all the time yes that I can hard I I'm
actually numb from it yes um I can't
sleep at night I'm so excited I can
hardly breathe and yet you are breathing
just fine and there's one one more thing I
fine and there's one one more thing I
wanted to share I guess that's it it's
just a thank you for exploding in my
direction thank you for coming here
B
shedding sure yes um so many things have
been going on the last time since I saw
you can you feel it oh
God can I
feel I have been uh for the first time I
controlled one of my violent dreams that
we spoke about last time and that was
really joyous it was amazing and it was
because I had controlled something in my
life it it reflected in that way and it
was was wonderful um I just have one
question because most of my questions I
am answering myself um continuously now
that you have created freedom in your
life definitely definitely which I'm
very grateful for but one thing that
just hit me today is this I'm
boring it was like a jolt it was like a
all right another Awakening yes you
um I am exploring the idea of abundance
meaning being able to do what I what I
want to when want to and all of that
sort of thing and all of that sort of
thing yes um oh very exciting
I I am wondering why is it I just
realized this I started a new job about
it'll be three months in a couple of
weeks this is uh I am at the lowest
level of abundance as far as money that
I've ever been in my life in order
things I want to do or as far as as
being able to do the things that I want
to do which
require that
which require money to do that anyway
I'm I I'm I have no no money but I'm
working in Beverly
Hills okay which is like the richest
community in the world this polarity
this polarity I mean I am creating this
I am poor and I'm working in Beverly
Hills and I I I want to be able to flip
the coin I mean the other side is there
list listen
listen when you are in your your Beverly
Hills listen and look around you I do
constantly all right okay not out of
desperation right not out of desperation
for with that attitude you are saying I
am not one of you right right I'm
learning that all right relax okay
relax no matter how much time you choose
to create up to the point where you
realize you are completely abundant when
that point comes you will not care how
much time went before when it hits you
it will hit you and you will be abundant
and it won't matter how long it took so
relax mhm all
right simply begin to
identify with those individuals mhm mhm
be as them right flow in that
school swim in that
school if you have created and attracted
to yourself the opportunity to surround
yourself with an environment that
represents abundance then realize you
are giving yourself the tools you need
at whatever rate you truly can handle
them right so
relax know that if you have the ability
to do that that is represent
reprentative of abundance that is
inherent within you or you would not
have attracted yourself into that local
if you didn't have that vibrational
ability you would never have experienced
that reality around you right you are
that vibration so you are giving
yourself the opportunity to get used to
that you are surrounding yourself with
that environment much in the same way
that you know you learn what you call a
foreign language best by living in that
country and having to use it all the
time and only hearing it all the time so
now you are living in the country of
abundance let the language rub off on
you use the language and when you use
the language when you use one symbol you
will learn how to use all the
others let it flow into
you mhm do not be impatient
for then you truly keep it away you
create desperation you reinforce the
belief that you are separate right if
you are there you are not separate or
you would be somewhere else
right so enjoy what is amazing is I
have felt and I've heard you say that to
me these I've been feeling that all the
time and when I do get impatient or at
times when I do get wild about it or
desperate about it I hear that Rel relax
you know this is thank you for creating
that reflection within your mentality
thank you very much search within
yourself also at the same time and
explore there may be different things
that you can do to attract that
abundance to you that you may not be
doing because you are sitting and
waiting rather than doing these things
you are now in a new modality MH do the
different things have the different
attitudes that an abundant individual
has see things the way an abundant
individual sees them with that type of
abundant perspective look at everything
and see everything as another expression
of
abundance and another opportunity for
you to exercise your abundance well
there's another way it's not what I
prefer but there it is right okay you
follow me I do then when you know you
are truly surrounded by it then you will
not be surrounded by it you will be
immersed in it as long as you still
believe you are surrounded by it you are
not a part of it I see if you are
surrounded by it all of that which
surrounds you
360° had to come from the center you so
it's all you so there you are you are
abundant okay thank you thank you
Pleasant dream exciting dream which is
the same as physical
reality sharing uh this feeling is very
very good thank you for co-creating it
um very well put thank you could not
have said it better myself um I would
like something clarified if possible all
right um You said about the don't
confuse accepting negativity with
whatever you said I don't even know
uhing it okay um all right in terms of
every effect can be positive is that a
true statement situation can generate a
positive effect
right um which of course in of itself
effects are also situations
yes okay how does the issue of Integrity
for example an act that is highly out of
Integrity that that which causes
segregation that which reinforces the
belief in separation in other words what
you colloquially refer to as forcing or
domination generally are representative
of your belief that you are not
inherently connected to infinite
abundance and must Force something upon
someone else to get what you think you
need in your life not believing that you
have all you need right at hand to
create whatever you want without having
to hurt anyone else or yourself in order
to create it okay so the issue of
Integrity is far from a follow the rules
y y y it's far from a strict one oh yes
okay very very pliable it simply means
acting in an integrated way okay knowing
that you are the total you and have
access to Total infinite ability
abundance and power
negative situations negative expressions
are acting in a separated seg reated
limited way I don't have the ability I
am a victim I have to manipulate
everyone else in order to get what I
want I have to force this on someone
else in order to make them listen to me
in order to validate me because I do not
believe I can validate
myself that's
negative total validation self-love
integrative lack of self-worth guilt
invalidation judgment segregative
negative all right understood in terms of
all right understood in terms of
homogenizing oneself any suggestions
either for me or for everybody simply
that when you allow any Creation in your
life whether it be positive or negative
when you allow yourself to let yourself
look at it and say all right that may
have been a negative act it may have
been functioning without my Integrity
now I recognize that now I prefer to
understand I do have the ability to
create what I want while functioning
within my integrity that's the way I
prefer to exist so in having created
this negative act that has allowed me to
learn that I prefer now to only generate
positive effects so now even that
negative act has transformed into a
positive one because I have learned
something positive from it everything is
on the same level everything is equal
then when everything is on the same
level I can choose and pick what I
prefer because I don't have to reach for
it as some sort of unreachable ideal nor
do I have to climb up from something as
some abysmal act I can never ever ever
redeem myself
from okay I'm I have a question about
whether I was manipulating in a in a
specific way sometimes I find that for
example when I want a day off work yes
and there are people that I see at work
that create illness in order to get a
day off work I choose not to participate
in that all right thus is it
manipulation to call in sick something
simple like
that it is acting outside of your
integrity basically it is because you
are not communicating the honest
vibrational situation of your being you
are thinking once again that the way you
are is not reason enough to create the
reality you want and that you have to In
This Way create an illusion to get
someone else to go along with
it when you know that you are as strong
as you need to be to create whatever you
truly need in your life without having
to manipulate the true signature
vibration that you are then you can
function totally always in harmonious
Accord with your integrity your integral
vibratory signal and still attract into
your life what it is you truly need and
also ask yourself many times why you may
want that day off Perhaps it is an
indication that you actually do not want
want to be where you are at
all perhaps then you can attract into
your life whatever it is that will
support you and bring with it
automatically a schedule that you can
live with then you won't have to make
with then you won't have to make
excuses because you will attract the job
that represents the being you are and it
will automatically be patterned and
structured in the way that represents
your flow okay the the the way that I used
flow okay the the the way that I used
the calling in sick was to postp
something and if I had shared my honesty
yes they would have said oh oh oh
assumption assumption granted but it may
be true however again no matter what
they would have said it would have been
an honest reaction to an honest
communication and that would have let
you know if they had said all right now
that we recognize what your idea is what
your attitude is we cannot deal with you
you cannot be a part of this idea mhm
but so what then that means you free to
attract into your life the idea you can
be a part of they have actually given
you the opportunity to recognize within
yourself that perhaps that job is not
for you by truly giving them the honest
idea of who you are then you truly learn
the quickest whether a job is for you or
not why stick around someplace that
really is not representative of the
vibration that you are why would you
want to stay around there anyway why not
let them tell you it's not going to work
that's not who we are you don't blend in
what they are really saying is be who
you are find and attract into your life
the job you can live with because if you
don't want to be here then you are not
being of value to us
anyway you are not serving and we cannot
serve you because you are not where you
want to be attract the job into your
life that brings with it the schedule
that is all right for you then you will
be able to serve them and let them serve
you you follow me yeah this is a onetime
thing that I was talking about but still
does not matter
yeah does that assist you yeah a lot
thank you very much for being willing to
express the ease of your integrity for
with that life is effortless and obvious
thank you thank you there will be but a
few moments remaining for this
interaction this day of your time
continue y hi there bet how you
doing buter from your point of view what
is the mechanical source of voices that
come that start talking to
you it can be many different things I
thought you'd say that it can be
portions of your own Consciousness that
you have created a vocalized symbol of
so that you will hear them in the way
you are used to hearing things it can be
a vocalized symbol of communication from
another Consciousness alt together it
can really come from anywhere generally
speaking when you hear it
thank you it is also a way from time to
time to allow them to instill within
themselves a degree of further
trust they will make it seem as if the
voice is removed so that they will not
at first have to think that they're
doing it then when they get used to the
it then when they get used to the
understanding that they're communicating
with another portion of their own
Consciousness no matter who it is they
are communicating with because they're
always communicating with their own
version of that idea anyway then they
won't necessarily have to experience it
in that way although there's nothing
wrong wrong with doing so excellent
thank you very much my pleasure one more
yeah when I create uh parallel universes
in which I fly down Hollywood Boulevard
as Superman or in a sleigh you know y
some of my goody games here
um I want to be able to parallel the
visual with the same um experiential
pattern that you get physically through
the body can you assist me in being able
to develop that perception
more if that is your dream act it
out act it out act it out put the suit
on you
mean is one way that's what being a
thunder dreamer is all
about that's what the idea of a Hoka is
all about when they have a dream they
know represents the idea of the being
they are they create replicate that and
create that in the physical dream as
well as the non-physical dream it will
give you an opportunity to truly
experiment with the threshold of your
believability oh that's great that's
great go get the go get the reindeer in
the sleigh and start moving around here
besides which even though there may be
individuals that choose to think you're
out of your mind many other individuals
will enjoy
it and most importantly
if that's what represents your reality
and if you know you are doing it with an
Integrity go right ahead yeah and again
you may find that the second you do that
you may get another way another way may
come to you that will also be a way also
be a method that the majority of
individuals may also allow into their
lives to be possible lovely that's neat
thank you very much
at this time
time we will once again extend to each
and every one of you our unconditional
appreciation of your willingness to
cocreate with us fourth density
reality playground child
playground child
time exuberance and
excitement trust knowing
and conscious
Choice are
yours play we thank you for
play we thank you for
sharing the
dream we bid you a fond and
loving good evening good night thank you
how' It Go