Let us say how are you all this evening
of your time as you create time to
exist. Allow us to begin this interaction this
Allow us to begin this interaction this
evening of your time with an exchange of
a few ideas that are all if you wish to
be labeled under the title
tools. Tools are what in general we will
be discussing within each and any
sharing or question or discussion we
have this evening of your time. Tools
the basic tool by which you each and
every one of you individually and all of
you together
collectively can learn how to create the
lives you prefer to create. This is what
any discussion between our society and
your society always as you say boil down
to the recognition that there are very
few simple tools that you can utilize in
your daytoday experiential life by which
you will know beyond a shadow of a doubt
that you are a in control of your life
and b can choose to create the life you
desire, the life you prefer because you
all create your own reality. If this is
a concept that is unfamiliar to some of
you, we will discuss this briefly as
well. The idea simply is that
you are the
sole individual
responsible for all that you experience
in what you call your dayto-day physical
life. for all that you perceive your
reality to be. Your own scientists at
this time in your history are beginning
to realize that there really is no
separate physical reality aside from
what you perceive it to be and that your
perception in and of itself is what
creates the reality you experience.
There is no way for you to know
otherwise anyway because anything you
could perceive will by definition be a
subjective perception. There is no true
objectivity. You can have an objectified
approach, an open mind, a balanced
attitude. But anything you perceive is
your perception and is going to be
colored by your thoughts, your emotions,
your beliefs, what you have been taught,
the reality of your world is all about.
What you have been taught to agree with
and disagree with. Now we are talking
about something that is more than just a
philosophy. We are speaking about an
actual literal mechanism.
You as the perceiver of your reality are
actually the creator of your reality
because it is only what you believe it
to be, what you think it to be, what you
feel it to be, what you imagine it to
be. There is no distinct reality that
you have a perception of that is perhaps
different than someone else's perception
of it. Your perception and their
perception are in and of themselves the
literal reality you are experiencing.
Reality is only the perception. The
interaction itself between the observer
and the observed.
The observer and the observed are side
effects if you will of the
observation which is the only real
reality. That which is in the center of
all dichotomy all polarity positive
negative. All polarity is a side effect
of the quote unquote true reality in the
center which is always both the opposite
and in a sense sometimes more than that.
But the idea is that the interaction
itself is what you really are. You are
not so much exactly the person doing the
perceiving. Nor is the reality the thing
that you are
perceiving. The reality is the
perception the act of perception itself.
For you in that sense as you understand
in your biblical literature are made in
the image of God as you say. Now what
does this mean to be made in the image
of the infinite creation? Well, to be
made from our perspective in the image
of infinite creation means you
yourselves must be infinite creators,
multi-dimensional creators. In other
words, as you think, so you create. Your
very thoughts are things themselves. And
you have created on your physiological
earth a particular type of reality that
you can call the illusion of separate
physical reality. There is no separate
physical reality except that which you
believe to be true. Physical reality is
actually very made of you, made of your
thoughts, of your consciousness, made
out of the very energy that you are as a
consciousness. So every time you change
the idea you are, every time you change
your thought, you literally change
physical reality. And that's what
creates the apparency of space and time.
for they are real while you are in it.
But time and space are your illusions as
well. The idea simply is is that as you
limit your focus to a
particular set of
awarenesses, then you create a need to
segregate different expressions,
different ideas one from the other so
that you can tell them apart. This is
the very definition of physical reality
of you as a consciousness behaving as a
physical reality creating compartments
within your consciousness to keep all
the different concepts separated from
each other so that you can experience
the idea of one at a time. before,
middle, after, ago, now, then, past,
present, future. All of these linear
time concepts are simply one way to
perceive the consciousness that you are.
By far, it is not the only way. And
there are many levels of consciousness
that have no awareness of the concept of
time and space at all.
They recognize themselves to be
literally be the dimension that you
would say they existed within. And this
is one of the changes that is going on
now upon your planet. The recognition
that your physical reality is not
something that you actually exist
within, but that your physical reality
is literally you. It is a projection of
an idea of the consciousness that you
are and so powerful a multi-dimensional
creator are you all individually and
collectively that you can create the
illusion that the physical reality
experience that you are is actually
separate from yourself. But we can begin
this evening of your time in discussing
these tools that we mentioned, these
pragmatic stepbystep techniques and
exercises and awarenesses of self. You
can begin to show yourself in no
uncertain terms beyond a shadow of a
doubt that you actually utterly create
your physical reality. For the tools we
will be discussing will put you squarely
in touch with the fact that you are
always creating your reality. will show
you how you can create the reality you
prefer to create. And by doing that, you
will see the feedback that will be the
result of the changes that go on in your
thoughts, in your beliefs, in your
feelings. And when you see those changes
as they correspond to your thoughts and
your feelings and your belief, then you
will know as surely as you look in a
mirror and see your own reflection that
your reality, which you have for so long
thought to be outside of you, is
actually within you. And that anytime
you see anything anywhere, anyone, you
are only looking in a mirror at another
version of you.
You all follow along. So
at this
timing, allow us to extend to each and
every one of you our deepest and
heartfelt appreciation and unconditional
love in your willingness to cocreate
with us this day of your time, this
interaction. your willingness to function as
your willingness to function as
ambassadors literally of your world
because that is what you are in this
interaction and allowing me to function
as an ambassador of my world so that
through these interactions bit by bit
day by
day we will together grow closer and
create an atmosphere that will allow and
become more conducive in allowing
your society and our collective
multi-world societies to begin to
interact more and more face to face in
blatant ways.
This will be allowed when you allow
yourselves to truly be equal to all
ideas, all situations, all
circumstances, all ideas and beings and
experiences of reality, equal among
yourselves, sharing, growing in
harmonious ways. Now, we perceive that
your energy is changing rapidly in this
transformational age upon your planet.
And we perceive at this time that within
what you call a maximum of three of your
decades, there will be very blatant
interactions between your society and
many of ours. And some of these
interactions can begin much sooner than
that. It is completely up to you. We are
absolutely noninvasive. It is your
world. We cannot interfere in the way
you choose your world to be. We can
assist you. We can recommend in a sense
suggest a way that you can allow your
world to be which is conducive to
allowing us to interact with you. But
you do not have to choose it. You do not
have to listen to us just because we are
who we say we are. It is completely up
to you. This whole
interaction as you say bottom line is
for the purpose of allowing us to remind
each and every one of you that you have
the power to create your lies. Don't
give it to me. I have enough of my own.
I do not need yours.
So the whole idea is to allow you to be
equal to us, equal to each other so that
together we can share, explore, enjoy
the universe ecstatically forever. That
is our desire to share with you for you
are a gift to us. You allow us to see
that many more ways through each and
every one of you that the infinite
creation has of expressing itself within
the creation that it is. For this gift,
we thank you. And in return for this
gift, I ask you now, how may I serve
you? Yes, you and then you.
I'd like to know about the the tools to
use. I'll try to use some of your words,
Steve. tools to use in creating my own
reality when I am involved with another person
when I am involved with another person
who's coming from a place in energy or a
a life of the mind who is the most
ethereal person I have ever met and I'm
coming from let's say the denser level
and I am beginning to rise my my levels
up through my spiritualism it's very new
for me not really well I'm remembering
slowly yes And you are remembering at an
absolutely perfect rate for you.
Wonderful. No need to judge yourself.
Slow, fast. It is the judgments which
make it seem to take longer, not the
actual activity. You understand? Yeah. It is
activity. You understand? Yeah. It is
the invalidations of yourself always
that create more
time. You are not moving slowly. You are
not moving fast. You are moving exactly
at the rate you need to be for who you
are at this given moment. If you change
the idea of yourself in the next moment,
you will move at a different rate that
is absolutely representative of who you
are at that moment. It will not be
better or worse. It will simply be
different. Now, let us remind you before you go on
Now, let us remind you before you go on
that when you see someone in your life
that represents something you desire to
be, remember that because you can
attract them and have attracted them
into your life, it must already be on
some level representative of who you are
or you would not have attracted them.
Life attracts life.
So you can take it for granted that if
you can experience that in your reality
and if it is something you prefer then
it must already be an indication of your
ability to be that way and the only
thing quote unquote standing in your way
is your assumption that you are not yet
that way by making a comparison of
invalidation rather than a comparison of
life vibration. Understand?
vibration. Understand?
Is this making any sense? Very much so.
Is it assisting you? Yeah. Anything
else? Well, in exploring each other on a
professional level,
um perhaps being connected in healing
purposes or teaching together? Is that a
question? No, not yet. Will will we be
able to explore deeper intimacies
together because there are some
limitations in the way we interact that
um are you allowing the relationship to
be what it is rather than what you think
it should be? I'm trying to trying.
Do you trust that the relationship is
there for a reason? Yes. Are you sure?
Yes. Then why do you have to try to let
it be what it is? If you really trust
that it is there for a reason, let it be
what it is. Because all those reasons
must serve your purpose or you wouldn't
be in the relationship.
Yes. No. Maybe. Yes. No. Maybe.
All right.
in in planning in planning my
professional involvement with this
person, I'm concerned about um the
relationship that the irritations of our
differences will prevent us from working
together smoothly. And what I'm asking
is for tools in trying to explore each
other and and
uh extend to each other in a loving way.
We are giving you those tools but we are
giving you the simplest tools possible.
There is no need for these tools to be
complex. Now processes we can recommend
but we have already recommended one
right now. The idea first and foremost
of allowing yourself to realize that any
interaction any relationship and this
goes for any of you that you draw
yourselves into must be a part of your
life or it wouldn't be there. So first
and foremost recognize that in that
sense because you are together at least
for now you belong together at least for
now. The idea is always as
follows. Be who you are fully. If you
are willing to be who you are with
integrity fully, then you are giving the
other individual the best opportunity to
be who they are fully. And in being who
you are together fully, the relationship
will automatically work out as it needs
to. And there is no need to cast an
assumption that things do not change,
should not change, for change is the
only constant in the universe. Let them
change in the way they need to change.
Knowing that all the changes in some
way, shape, or form benefit the things
you each need to get out of that
relationship to learn about yourself to
integrate within yourselves to grow and
expand in the way you really want to. If
you simply recognize in any relationship
that another individual is a vibration
that you do not prefer, then you will
automatically go your separate ways
since in that sense unlike vibrations
will repel each other. But this does not
mean it has to be a repulsion of
conflict of friction of negativity. It
can simply be a recognition of what you
are and what you are not. Understand?
So assume that if you are in the
relationship that it serves a purpose
first of all that is step number one
that it fulfills your purpose or you
wouldn't be in it. Understand?
Then allow yourself to fully be who you
are. Not who you think you should be.
Not who they think you should be. Allow
them to be who they are. Not who you
think they should be. You follow me?
That is step number two. Then ask
yourself, what am I learning about
myself by being in this relationship
with the individual the way they are?
That's step number three.
What is it you are learning about
yourself within that relationship? Then
you will understand why you are in
it. Then you will understand how it
might or might not change in certain
ways to allow you to continue to learn
what you need to learn. But any changes
that occur if you are being fully who
you are are the changes that need to
occur. And they do not have to be
assumed that they will be
frictionoriented changes because
everything automatically falls into
place when you trust that it is there
for a reason, a positive reason.
Understand? Is any of this assisting
you? Very much. Does that work for you?
Can you relax into the relationship and
let it be what it is? Yes. And can you
be yourself in the
relationship? Trusting that if being you
means that the other individual needs to
vibrate out of your reality that whoever
does represent your vibration will
vibrate in. So you won't care who it is
because they will feel
correct. Understand? And even if it is
the same physical person, if they change
to match your vibration, it really isn't
the same person
anyway. Really not the same person
because a personality, a persona is not
who or what you are. It is an artificial
construct of your consciousness to
represent an idea you are being at any
given moment. So when you change the
idea that you are you change your
personality and you literally literally
I am not speaking philosophically
literally become another person
literally you may look the same to all
the individuals or actually you may not
for as you change yourself in very
radical ways sometimes other individuals
will notice the change even in your
physiological structure. So recognize that any change
structure. So recognize that any change
of idea, any change of thought creates
you to be literally a different person.
And you will always attract and can only
attract those that are of light
vibration. Does that assist you?
Thank you very much. Number two,
okay, speak
speak
up people. share with all
everyone everyone can learn from every
single thing any of you have to say.
There are no boring situations only
bored minds.
So if someone thinks, oh this has
nothing to do with
me, then they are not realizing that
there are no accidents and anything you
are in a group to overhear yes it may
have a relative degree of significance
but it is there for a reason. You are
hearing it for a reason. It would be in
your own best interest to pay attention
to what anyone has to say because there
can be something within it. If you apply
it in your own way, shape or form that
can assist you as well. So be bold and
share so all can hear and apply
accordingly. Okay, thank you.
Okay, thank you.
I saw a being when I was swimming in my
parents pool like Egyptian. All right.
And I was wondering if this being was a
past life of mine. It is a past
association that now may function for you as an
that now may function for you as an
energy guide. Energy guide especially if
you are in water where you are very
relaxed. Many of you may have already
discovered that your pools and even what
you call your shower cubicles are
excellent meditation
chambers. The running water will put you
in the actual appropriate centered state
of meditation to receive almost any type
of information you desire. And so you
can connect and extend your senses
through different levels of spirituality
very easily different levels of energy
of consciousness. So that is simply in a
sense an energy guide. It is an
associate to some degree of your own. It
does represent some past life
attachments but in that sense it is more
of a guide for you.
The other one is I've been hearing
rumors that Shasty Mountain is going to
be closed as in retreat. Is that true?
You can more easily find out by asking
around on your own planet.
[Music] I have mistakes.
I have mistakes.
There are certain areas that will remain
accessible. And allow yourself to
understand that the energy vortex of
that area spans a far greater range than
specifically just the mountain. And
anywhere you are within what you call
visual range of it, you will be within
range of the energy.
Understand? Does that answer your question?
Does that answer your question?
Thank you very much. Yeah. Uh I have a
question related to
uh well actually from time to time I I
experience a reality that I don't
necessarily prefer being what being that
um it seems it's it's easier for me to
uh get rid of positive thoughts in my
mind than negative thoughts. And and and
tying in with that it seems that
negativity has a tendency to man
manifest itself faster than posit
positive thoughts. That is only because
of the habits you have been taught in
your society to believe that the
negativity is in a sense more likely
than the positive reality. It is simply
habitual ritual. That is all there is to
it. Let me point out a few
examples. Happily ever
after fairy tale not real life. Too good
to be true. Too simple to be true. No
pain, no
gain. Now, with belief systems like that
repeated to you over and over and over
and over again, is it any surprise that
the negative reality will seem to be
more likely than the positive ones? You
do not believe that positive reality is
as valid as the negative. You do not
think it is realistic. You think that to
believe that positive reality is the
only reality you will experience is
naive, childish.
Oh, grow up face reality. Many of you
say nothing good lasts
forever. Oh, this is too good to last.
Yes, something has to go wrong
sometime. You have been indoctrinated
with these beliefs since you were a
child. What do you expect now? The way
you can easily transform this idea not
get rid of because there is nowhere to
get rid of anything to and you never can
get rid of anything. You can only change
it. So the way most easily to transform
the negative energy into positive
manifestation is to first and foremost
realize that these are only habitual
ways of thinking and that in and of
themselves there is absolutely nothing
inherent or
intrinsic about negativity having to
occur more often than positive reality.
Nothing says that one side is tipped in
one particular direction more than
another except your belief. And it is
always your belief which can also be
translated out to your strongest fear
that a certain thing might happen more
likely than another thing and that is
what will usually attract it to you.
Understand? So first of all, if you
recognize that it is a habit, then you
can also start to generate within
yourself a new belief, a new habit that
anytime you recognize an old habit for a
habit, it is no longer a habit. And if
you keep doing it, then it's just an
excuse, not a habit. is uh speaking for
myself the constant bombardment that you
have from the society you know from our
society that that basically funnels us
in into those types of you know really
restrictive thoughts um what's what's a
good idea or what's a good method for
you know avoiding that type of you know
because we're we're exposed to it on a
daily basis how about don't pay
attention to it yeah I I I think that's
that's a good rule for living but on a
on a realistic oh here we go Not realistic
Not realistic
enough. Too simple. Oh, that's too
simple to be realistic.
I agree with what you're saying. All
right. Will there be a point uh or is
there is there actually a point that we
can come to um where the there aren't so
many moving parts and aren't so many
tools and you can just take thought to
to reality? That point is right now. If
you wish it could be. If you wish it
could be. Now you see the idea all has
to do with your own threshold of
believability. And this is something you
can all use as a measuring device for
almost anything. Let's say now you are
to use your reference talking about a
time when you think in your life the
idea of positive reality will be able to
be manifested more often than negative
reality. Now let me just ask you a few
questions answer as honestly and as
quickly as you can. All right.
Now, do you believe beyond a shadow of a
doubt that in your own spiritual growth
and your own investigations and your
research and your expansion of knowledge
that within what you call 10 years of
your time, you will have been able to
allow yourself to create more positive
than negative realities. Do you think 10
years of your time is enough for you to
learn how to do that?
Yes. Absolutely. Beyond a shadow of a
doubt. Yes. Five years. Yes. One year.
Now, right now,
yes, I I believe so. Are you sure now?
Want you to be sure? Yes, I'm sure. One
year you think is enough. 6 months.
It's pushing it.
Then allow yourself to realize how very
accurate that is as a barometer of your
threshold of
believability. Wherever it starts to
falter or waver or doubt starts to creep
in for right now, that is a precise
indication of how long it will take you
before you will allow that to happen.
Now once you find where that threshold
falls, your awareness of that threshold
now can actually transform it to take
less time because now you're aware of
what your belief is and now you can
examine it. Now you can say why do I
believe that I can do it in a year but I
can't do it in 6 months. Why do I
believe that? Now you can start to
explore the definitions you have about
time and the things that take time and
the processes you think you have to go
through in order for it to take that
much time. Now you can explore it. Now
you can decide whether you really prefer
the processes that will make it take
that much time or whether you can say
well I really don't need to go through
that process. So now let's see if I now
know I don't have to go through that
process. Do I believe it will take 8
months? Well, yes, I think I actually
do. What about 7 months? No problem. 6
months? Again, no problem. Oh, goody. 5
months? Easy. Four months?
Easy. Four months?
Oh, 3 months? No, no, no, no, no. All
right. I have found my threshold of
believability again. Now, what beliefs
would I have to have in order for me not
to be able to manifest instantaneous
creation any sooner than three months of
my time? Then examine those beliefs.
Find out what processes you think you
have to go through in order to create
the reality you desire. And the more you
examine these ideas and get in touch
with the beliefs you have, then you can
redefine those beliefs. And as you
redefine them, you will change your
experiential reality because your
physical reality is absolutely the
product of what you believe it to be and
you can prove it to yourself very
easily. Is this a system? It sure is. and I will
Is this a system? It sure is. and I will
be and and I I know everybody else wants
to get involved, but I just wanted to
say that uh um it seems that I'm somehow
waiting for some kind of a you know
feeling or emotional type of of a change
to take place. Oh yeah, I'm taking that
that thought to reality. I don't feel
like I'm getting that. That's I
understand what I'm missing. But that's
because you are not creating the reality
that can generate those emotions. You
see, all emotions, all emotions are
reactions to something you already
believe to be true. So, in order to have
a different feeling, you have to change
the belief first. You may think the
feelings you have and the experiences
you have generate the beliefs, but it's
the other way around. You have once
again all been brought up to think
seeing is believing. It is believing is
seeing just the opposite. But because
many of your beliefs are unconscious,
then you do not allow yourself to know
you have the belief until you have the
feeling or until you have an experience.
Some of you will then use an experience
so that you will have a feeling about
the experience so that then you will be
able to understand what you believe to
begin with that has created the
experience that gave you the feeling
that pointed out the belief you
had. But because you do not understand
that you are in touch with your
unconscious mind because you create a
portion of your consciousness to be
unconscious. Then many of you do not
understand that the experience and the
feeling are extremely secondary reaction
to a belief that already exists. But the
experience and the feeling is there to
show you what the belief is you have. So
that if you don't prefer it, you can
change it. The experiences in your lives
and the feelings you have are not there
to show you you're
stuck. It's not there to show you that
you're a failure. It's there to show
you, hey, this is what you believe.
Because this is what you got. This is
what you're feeling. Do you prefer this
belief? Yes or no? If no, then because
you had the experience and because you
had the feeling, now you know what the
belief is. Change the definition of the
belief. You will change the experience
and you will change the feeling. It is
simply that many of you think you have
to have a reason before you will have an
effect. Cause and effect. Cause and
effect. I refuse to be happy until I
have a darn good reason to be happy.
Many of you
say, "So I will search and search and
search throughout all my life looking
for a good reason to be happy. and I
refuse to be happy until I find
it. However, if many of you would simply
stop and realize that there really is no
reason why you simply can't choose to be
happy because that's what you prefer,
then you will create an effect in your
life. And since nature will not allow
there to be a vacuum in creation, if you
create an effect, it has to supply you
with a cause. for the effect you have
created. The cause does not have to come
first because cause and effect are the
same event and they must occur together.
They must and you can work it backwards.
It doesn't matter. It doesn't care.
Create the effect in your life you
prefer and you will automatically place
yourself in the vibratory state to
attract all the
circumstances causes to reinforce,
bolster up and accelerate the effect you
have created. Simple physics, simple
mechanics. Keep it simple. It always
works. It never doesn't work. And there
are no exceptions. Not even you.
Do you understand what we are saying?
Yes, I do. Thank you very much. Can you
apply that? I think I can. Well, thank
you very uh uh
desire and
to develop my ability for telepathic
communication. All right. Now, you've
already given me one tool just now. Yes.
Uh I would like to know other tools to
accelerate the simplest tool
possible love because telepathy is actually
love because telepathy is actually
telempathy. You see no one is actually
reading each other's mind. What you are
doing when you experience psychic
manifestation or
teleathy is you are
identifying with someone. so strongly
that you operate on the same frequency
that they do. So you interpret creation
in the same modality. You create the
same thoughts out of the primal energy
of creation that they do. You parallel
their vibration. Strong
vibration. Strong
identification with another individual
is called unconditional love.
That is how you can be
telepathic. Do you not all recognize
that the individuals in your society
that almost always seem to know each
other's thoughts are those that are in
love? That's why because they identify with
That's why because they identify with
each other so strongly that they in that
sense truly create the same thoughts
synchronistically at the same time. They
know what each other is thinking because
they are thinking the same way. That is
love. That's all there is to it. More
willingness to love unconditionally and
grant absolute validity and equality to
all other beings will allow you to
become extremely sensitized
telepathically. 1%
I believe I understand that that what
you're saying. Let me let me verbalize.
All right. You go right ahead. Thank
you. uh
uh
is by loving all of humanity. Yes.
Deeply, yes, and unconditionally without
judgment. Yes.
Then I will have
you will become empathic. Empathic with
all humanity. Yes. And also with your
civilization, our brothers and faith.
Why not? Don't forget the
sisters. Little kids.
Okay, great. Thanks. Thank you very
much. You and then you and then you
Hey, do you have any suggestions for
participating uh in the harmonic
conversion? Can you all hear that?
Well, thank you.
Any suggestions for participating in
what has been referred to on your planet
as the harmonic convergence?
First of all, the harmonic convergence
represents the idea of an overlap of two
vibrational epics in your history. The
old ways of segregation and negativity,
the old cycle as you may call it, and
the new understanding, the new energy of
integration and expansion of
consciousness. The so-called harmonic
convergence where all these harmonics
converge is approximately to be
recognized upon your dates of August
16th and 17th although it has been going
on for quite some time. That is simply
in your terminology the actual midpoint
of where the two vibrational epics in
your history overlap. It is the gateway,
the doorway that will allow you to begin
to see more and more acceleration upon
your planet of the reality you desire to
experience. Now, what can you do to aid
and assist in the acceleration of the
harmonic convergence? Whatever excites
you the
most. That's what because if you are
doing what excites you the most, then
you are functioning at your highest
level of energy and will have the
strongest impact. So use your
imagination. All right. Thank you. Thank you very
All right. Thank you. Thank you very
much. Next.
I just recently ended a career.
Congratulations. And I feel kind of lost. Oh, all right.
And I feel kind of lost. Oh, all right.
Well, here you are right here. See,
found you very
quick. May I ask you a question? Yes.
Thank you very much.
What excites you the most in life that
you may not be doing?
Oh, thank you very much.
Do you have a good answer?
Oh, it is very simple. Do not make it
complex. Keep it simple. Let's start one
thing at a time. For example, we will
assume, not because it is us, but simply
because you are within this interaction.
We will assume that right now this
interaction is the thing that excites
you the most or you'd be doing something
else. Yeah.
Yeah. All
right. The idea simply is to understand
what excitement represents. Do you know
what excitement is?
[Music] You can say no. No. Thank you.
You can say no. No. Thank you.
Pay attention now. Are you paying
attention? Yes. All right.
Excitement is your physical
translation of the vibratory energy that
represents the path you chose to be in
this life at any given moment. So what
we are saying and suggesting is that if
at every given moment, moment to moment,
you are doing the thing at that moment
with integrity that excites you the most
out of all the things that are capable
of being done by you. then you are
absolutely right on track with what you
need to be doing. And if you do the
thing that excites you the most with
integrity that you are capable of doing
out of all the opportunities that are
available to
you, then you will automatically lead
yourself into exciting situation after exciting
into exciting situation after exciting
situation because all excitement is a
thread that leads to all other
excitement. because it is the path you are. And if
because it is the path you are. And if
you do the thing that excites you the
most, you will be able to do that thing
most effortlessly without struggle,
without pain, without strife. And if you
do the thing that excites you the most
because it is your path and because you
can do it most effortlessly, it will be
the thing whether you have been taught
to think it can't be or not. It will be
the thing that will allow you to
experience the highest degree of
abundance in your life to be able to
support you to continue to do the thing
at any given moment that excites you the
most. So if there is something that you
have always wanted to do and you simply
have not allowed yourself to do it
because of any number of various reasons
that your society tells you it should
not be done. That's no way to make a
living. You have to work hard if you
want to get anywhere. You have to suffer
and struggle or you'll never amount to
anything. Grow up. That's a very
childish idea. Do not be naive. No one.
No
one. Is any of this making some sense?
Yeah. So, you can take it a step at a
time and keep it simple. When we say the
thing that excites you the most, we do
not mean you have to come up with the
thing that will be the most exciting
thing you will ever do in your entire
life. Some of you may know that and
that's all right and all well and good.
But if you don't, then act upon the most
exciting thing you are capable of acting
on at any given moment. It
will believe.
No, but
it's like I know all these things and I
know them, but I can't seem to make them
put them in my life, you know. Yes. But
this individual has said it all in one
word. It is a matter of trust. You may
know them intellectually, but if you do
not really believe them, you will not
act like you believe it. And if you
don't act like you believe it, you will
not initiate the momentum that will
prove that it works. You have to act
like you believe it. Not just sit and
think you know that it will work. You
have to move on it. You have to act upon
the opportunities that present
themselves in your life. That are the
opportunities that excite you the most.
excite you the
most. Even if it appears that these
opportunities have no apparent outward
connection to some other thing you think
excites you, if this is the thing that
excites you the most at any given moment
that you are capable of acting on, then
do it. Because whether it looks like
it's connected or not, it is the
excitement that lets you know it is. And
if you do have an idea of a particular
thing that you say excites you, if you
are not acting like a person that really
believes they can do that thing or that
they deserve to do that thing, then it
also will not occur in your life. You
have to act like the person that lives
that life before that life will come to
you to be lived. If you are not in your
estimation ready or willing to live it,
it won't come. And the way you show the
universe that you are ready and willing
to live it is by acting as if you are.
Because you know that if another person
were doing something you say you really
want to do, they would be acting far
differently than you might be acting
now. So simply see in your mind the
thing that may excite you and see
yourself doing that thing fully doing it
in every way, shape and form that you
can imagine it can be done. And if you
see any difference in that imaginary you
that is doing that thing in terms of her
actions as compared to your actions then
copy her
actions. Understand? Yes. Thank you. So
any idea you wish to be act like you are
that idea and you will attract the
opportunity to give you the opportunity
to be that life to be that person. If
you do not act like that person you
cannot attract that lifestyle
understand. Yes. Does that assist you?
Yes. Thank you. Thank you very much. For
sure. One moment. You are met
after you. I just wanted to know what
happened before. Before the dinosaurs.
All right. Many different things. There
have been many other civilizations upon
your planet from time to time
visiting. There have been many different
types of civilizations that no longer
exist upon your planet.
There also have been many changes within
the surface of your planet before you
say the
dinosaurs. There were other forms of
life upon your planet before the
dinosaurs. Some of which eventually
became as you say evolved into the
dinosaurs. But
also there were other dimensions of
experience, other beings that have come
and gone. whole civilizations that have
arisen and
fallen before the
dinosaurs. Does that answer your
question? Well, thank you very much.
Okay. Um, I've been doing the dolphin dance.
Um, I've been doing the dolphin dance.
Speak up. Speak up. Since 1971. Speak up
again. I have a harpoon and it's
difficult for me to speak. Question. How
do I remove the harpoon?
Where do you believe it is?
Blonde lost in the center of my back.
Are you willing to grant absolute
validation to the circumstance that
placed it
there? Are you willing to own your part
of the
creation of that?
I don't understand.
Are you suggesting that there is
something that is in your terms
inhibiting you
when you refer to the haru?
It's not a matter of inhibition. It's a
matter of pain.
But it is a type of inhibition. I am not
talking about the idea of ideological
inhibition. Anything that in your terms
prevents something from happening is
called an inhibitor. You follow me?
Partially. All right. It is simply a
term inhibitor. Something which blocks.
You understand? Yes. All
right. What does the idea of dolphin
energy representative?
representative?
Movement together with my brothers and
sisters. U with a telepathic connection.
It's excitement. It's prayer,
excitement, yes. Ecstasy, yes.
Flexibility, yes. Above and beyond
everything, it is play in a very
childlike way. Not childish,
childlike. Now, can you imagine yourself back to a
Now, can you imagine yourself back to a
childlike state?
That's a part of the ritual.
ritual. Do you need a ritual?
Do you need a ritual?
I have two aspects of my life. I have a
a
professional that involves a different
kind of energy than the dolphin dance.
The dolphin dance I have to enter into
it. But why must it be different? If
that is what you say is the most
exciting energy you wish to experience,
why cannot that energy be used in all
aspects of your life?
Why do you create the separation?
It's simply a translation.
It may be more than that.
You have said there are two types of
energy. Yeah. The dolphin dance is a
trans I translate that in my work. Yeah.
As a a computer programmer. Yeah.
So they're both the same kind of energy
just different expressions. All right.
So, they both give me they both give me
excitement, joy, you know, their creative
joy, you know, their creative
expression. All right. But I found that
in the dolphin dance itself, Yeah. I've
become aware over the last three years
of the harpoon. Why are you calling it a
harpoon?
Our tel empathic
link inform me of that just as easy.
For how long have you had the pain? For
3 years.
In your terminology, let's play with
some time here. How long do you
imagine if you began to heal right now?
Both of you, how long do you imagine it
would take to heal?
Twinkling of an eye. Are you guessing?
No. How long do you really believe it
will take?
Once I understand the twinkling of an
eye. Yes. How long? But since you are
suggesting that you don't understand
now, how long will it take?
You do not know. I don't know. All
right, fair enough. Can
Can
you in your own estimation, in your
imagination, play the scenario
responsible for the creation of the
harpoon backwards to a time before the
harpoon?
Then let that be the reality and begin
from then. and understand that you can
take a different time
track that you can change the past
because you create the past from the
present. The present is not a result of
the past. The past is a result of the
past. The past is a result of the
present. Do you understand that?
Do you think you can do that? Yes. Then
that can assist in alleviating what you
experience as pain. For if you simply
allow yourself to understand whatever it
is you have learned from this shared
experience, get what you need to out of
the lesson, and then realize you do not
need to learn your lesson that way. Then
you can diverge onto a parallel path
wherein you do not need to experience
that type of restriction, that type of
pain. Nor does any counterpart you share
with. But of course, dolphin
counterparts are always more than
willing to take upon themselves the idea
of infliction to assist you, humanity,
in learning the lessons it needs to
learn because they love you that much.
So if you are willing to take the
absolute responsibility for the creation
of your life now and what you are
feeling telepathically now, then you can
feed back that understanding in present
time. reroute the whole past idea onto
another parallel track that doesn't need
that negative experience. And as you
say, you can in the twinkling of an
eye transform that pain into another
time track that has nothing at all to do
with you or any of your
counterparts. Understand?
Does that work for you? I think it will.
All right. Then allow allow allow allow
yourselves back into
alignment. For all pain, physical,
emotional, mental, spiritual, all pain
is the result of the cutting off of a
portion of yourself from the total
energy that you are.
So allow yourself to reintegrate by
allowing the past and the future to be
in the now and allowing yourself to have
absolute conscious commandment over what
you decide is your reality now
regardless of anything it has ever
been. I think 3 years is long
enough. Don't you? Me too. All right.
Thank you very much. Oh,
one. There also can
be some
whale energy that you can allow through
in dream time which will be so
powerfully overwhelming to the whole
experience that a tiny small harpoon
would be lost and dissolved inside that
massive amount of
energy. Understand?
So let it come.
Let the idea be within you and then it
can be dissolved. As long as it seems to
be something
external, it can cause a pain in the
back. It is not external. It is
internal. The whale knows this even
though the human and some dolphins may
not. Thank you.
Thank you.
You sure? Speaking of pain. All right.
Speaking of pain. Speaking of pain.
I have had um two concussions in the
last 10 months. How exciting.
Two concussions. Two concussions in my
head. I have um had a headache because
of that. Another very uncomfortable
symptoms for the last five weeks. Okay.
Do you like yourself?
Yes, I like myself. Yes, I do. Just
kidding. Continue.
I like myself a lot.
Do you like the idea of being psychic?
I feel that I am psychic. Yes. Well,
everyone is psychic ability. Everyone
is. How strongly consciously psychic do
you wish to be?
I do wish to develop my psychic ability
more. All right.
Why? Always.
Always.
We have all the time in the world,
right? Yeah. Why? Um it excites me. Why?
Well, it makes me feel good. I feel I
feel positive. Yes. Um I feel that um
I'm helping people. Oh, I feel like I'm
I'm I'm able to to share
um with um people um that which they're
saying. It's like reflecting them. May I
ask you a question?
Thank you very much. How badly do you
feel people need that help?
I think things that they can do fine
without you know they if they if they
need me to be there in order to um
assist them then um I have and I have I
have done that in the past dream and
stuff like that. Do you understand that
some individuals in your reality have
created the idea of concussion to assist
in the releasing of their psychic
potential? To assist in the releasing of
the idea of what you call the channeling
vibration. Do you understand that the
majority of all individuals who in your
terms are strongly psychic or are
channeling today have at one time or
another in their lives experienced
either a concussion or a strong electric
shock? No, I do not. Now you do. Well, I did,
No, I do not. Now you do. Well, I did,
but I think
the idea simply seems at this timing in
your reality to be a habit to unlock
completely unlock you from the habitual
rituals and belief patterns that you
were brought up with in a sense
literally scrambling your circuits.
Understand that the idea of channeling
in a controlled fashion is very similar
to the experience of shortcircuiting
that many of you call
epilepsy. The idea of the seizures in a
sense are miniature
concussions. And the idea of channeling
in a sense is a controlled seizure of a
sort wherein it regards the electrical
activity of your brain.
Concussions many times are simply
another way that many of you have. Yes,
a drastic way I will admit of releasing
certain patterns of electrical
conductivity within your brain to make
it more conducive for you to channel the
amount of energy in the way you wish to
channel it that you wish to channel in
your life. one
moment. So like many others, it simply
has been your way to take it upon
yourself to believe that you needed to
shock yourself out of those old belief
systems very quickly, very rapidly
rather than taking years and years and
years and years of your time to process
yourself through it. Now you are wide
open. Your circuits are now interchangeable,
Your circuits are now interchangeable,
very loose, very malleable,
interconnectable into different reality
patterns. Do you understand? All of you
literally physiologically every thought you have
physiologically every thought you have
actually changes the neuronic pathways
of your brain.
Literally, it
does. So realize now what you have done
is opened yourself up for very rapid
change. You are now very loosely
connected, not strongly connected to any
one particular reality so that you can
plug in like what you might call
colloquially a switchboard to many
reality so that you can funnel and
integrate and channel that energy
through you. Now you do not have to keep
beating yourself up to do this.
You can allow yourself to realize that
you are integrated sufficiently and that
all the necessary electrical
conductivity is inherent within you.
There is another way to allow this to
occur. All of you can use this technique
for various reasons. It can be very
strong for the idea of also centering
you out of
disease as well as aligning the entire
electromagnetic crystallin structure of
your body and your
brain. It is
called the
BLT if you wish the blue light
technique. The idea simply is to allow yourself to
The idea simply is to allow yourself to
close your eyes and imagine yourself
drifting in a place of perfect peace.
Whatever that may be, whenever that may
be, it does not matter. Trust your
imagination. And as you are floating,
drifting, laying, dark, light, cool, warm, doesn't
laying, dark, light, cool, warm, doesn't
matter. in a relaxed and meditative
state. If you imagine yourself
surrounded by a crystallin sphere of
transparent blue white
energy extending at least one to three
feet above your head, one to three feet
below your feet going all the way around
you so that your body is floating in the
middle of it. Even if you're lying on
the ground, allow the sphere to go
through the ground. Then you can imagine
that not only is it a hollow sphere, it
is filled filled with blue effervescent
electric liquid light and that you are
actually breathing this life in and
out, in and out
slowly, comfortably. And as you breathe this
comfortably. And as you breathe this
light in and out like a thick electric
liquid, you begin to feel the liquid
actually penetrating the pores of your
body, the cells of your body, the
molecules, the atomic structure of your
body. You are now literally breathing
this fluid in and out with your whole
body. Not just your mouth, not just your
nose, your whole body.
And as you begin to do this more and
more in your imagination, allow your
physical body to begin to
dissolve to become the blue
liquid. Allow yourself to become one
homogeneous blue liquid light
sphere. And as you imagine this, picture
it to be a completely homogeneous sphere
where no one part stands out more than
any other part. And the whole sphere is
breathing, beating with one pulse, one
breath, one
heart. And it is your consciousness
itself made out of electromagnetic
light. Electromagnetic fundamental
energy, the primal vibration of
creation. You are completely
harmoniously synchronized with it at
this point in this exercise.
Then focus your consciousness inward to
the very center of the sphere and see a
tiny crystallin seed sparkling shining
forming at the center of the sphere. Out
of the liquid this seed is formed. This
crystal is formed and it grows and
multiplies to 48.
more and more crystals growing and
growing and growing and growing into the
shape of your body, your idealized body
state. And know as you see this body
grow that it is now made of the
homogeneous liquid, the homogeneous
energy. It is balanced. It is regrowing.
It is transparent. It is pure. It is
crystalline. Allow the body to reform.
and know beyond a shadow of a doubt that
it is not the old body. Literally, it is
a new
representation, a new body to represent
the persona you prefer to be made out of
the vibration you prefer to be and nothing
vibration you prefer to be and nothing
else. It is a laserlike monochromatic
single crystallin
form vibrating on one frequency, the
frequency of the reality you
prefer. Then take three breaths with
that new body. Lock it
in. Let the energy sphere dissolve, but
know that it is always around you.
Always is your body within it.
Out of this sphere, you will now create
the rest of your seemingly external
experiential reality. But you will always remember
reality. But you will always remember
the following
things. Consciousness is not in your
body. Your body is in your
consciousness. It is your idea of
yourself. Then simply continue to breathe and open
Then simply continue to breathe and open
your eyes from your meditation and know
that you are
different. That your world is not the
same world it used to be literally
because you create your universal
reality literally. And that now it is more
literally. And that now it is more
representative of who you desire to be.
And that every time you do this exercise
bit by bit, whether you choose to be
fast or slow about it does not matter.
Bit by bit or in the twinkling of an
eye, you will be representative and
completely made of the same substance as
the reality around you. You are one
thing. One
thing. And you can allow yourself to
know whatever you need to know when you
need to know it to be who you desire to
be. You can use that
technique for
centering. It can be used to alleviate
almost any form of
disease. You can in that sense use it
even to sustain yourself from time to
time. You may find you will need less
sleep, perhaps even less food because of
it. But it is up to you. Let your
But it is up to you. Let your
imagination be your guide and let
yourself know beyond a shadow of a doubt
that a difference has been
made. All right.
Um I sometimes have a problem when I use
the blue light for healing.
Then use it in whatever way you wish to
and assume you are centered. Do I need
to see? I don't feel that I need to see
the blue light. One more time. Pay
attention. Let your imagination alter it
in any way, shape, or form you feel
represents the vibration that you are,
it will be correct. Take it for granted
that it is working. Even if your
analytical mind keeps jumping in and
saying, "No, no, no. That's not what he
said. No, no, no. You're not getting it
right. There is no right and wrong with
regards to this idea.
do it in the way that is representative
of who you are.
All right. Yeah. Does that serve you?
Yeah. How does my um engineering
background tell you this?
You can understand vibrational tones and
crystallin structures very well. It is
very natural to you and so it should be
a very natural thing for you to
understand what is being accomplished by
this particular visualization. You are
understanding that all is made of
vibrational energy. So it is eminently
changeable without having to knock
yourself around to do it.
All right.
Thank you very much. Accelerated dream
life you you
[Music]
than you. Okay. Um I am becoming much
more aware of contact
with uh being the son of this planet
uh being the son of this planet
presently
and this is true for many of you
continue and it has been for a long time
but I'm just remembering these things
now many of you are now remembering what
you colloquially call lost time
I also am feeling very much that I'm
coming closer to realization of a prior
our commitment as
um to serve many during this time of
transition. Good whole idea. And I am
feeling that an imminent contact will
aid me in this realization.
Back up. You have already in a sense been
up. You have already in a sense been
contacted. Yes, but I'm not conscious at
this point. It doesn't matter. You don't
need to be. The idea of allowing you to
be somewhat unconscious is for the
purpose of allowing you to continue to
live your life
spontaneously without the idea of a
particular format to follow. The
knowledge that you need to have is
within you and it will come out in the
actions that you do when you do what
excites you the most.
But the structure of the agreement is
not always necessary and many times need
not be there because it would hamper you
in your spontaneous interactions with
life. Understand?
I believe so. When you really need to
know the specifics, you will. And many
times it will come in the form you call
a deja
vu. After you have lived it through
spontaneously, you let it be all right
to remember the agreement you made, the
planning that you did. That's what you
call a
data because you have already seen it
because you planned it out. You agreed
to it. But you did not want to know
about it because knowing about it would
not have allowed you to live it
spontaneously in the moment. It would
have hampered you. Made you watch every
single step. Oh, am I following the
plan? Oh, I might diverge here. I don't
know. Got to be careful. One small step
at a time. You wouldn't get very far. At
least not as quickly.
Okay. I guess my question of trying to
bring in these thoughts in one focus,
okay, is that I'm I'm trying to release
a fear that I have. I All right.
I am releasing. Yes, you are. Good. I'm
feeling joy of a conscious connection. Yes. And
joy of a conscious connection. Yes. And
I'm feeling it to be soon. And I guess
my question is, is there something that
you can say that would perhaps make you
more joyous of this connection?
Remember, first of all, that these
connections and contacts are all
happening within perfect timing.
We know what we're doing because we've
done this before. Trust
it. When you are truly ready as an
assimilated being, as an integrated
being, nothing will prevent that
contact. Nothing.
Nothing.
Understand? All dates with destiny are
on time because you create them. You
will not miss it. Do not worry about it.
Live the life you are living because
that is the fulfillment of the
agreement. That will take you into more
conscious recognition of what the
agreement is. It is not fully time yet. And many
is. It is not fully time yet. And many
of you who think you are ready for a
face-to-face encounter are
not because there are still many
portions of yourself that you have not
integrated. And if you maintain those portions in a
And if you maintain those portions in a
lack of
integration and you encounter a being
that is integrated and in no way do we
mean this to be derogatory to you. You
will be overwhelmed by the aura of an
integrated being. It will force to the
surface all those portions of yourself
you are not ready to face and can cause
terror, fear and psychotic shock within
you. Many times when you think you're
ready, many individuals who have fought
so have come very close to having an
interaction. And our members of our civilization know
And our members of our civilization know
what they are doing when they only come
close. And those individuals who thought
they were ready all of a sudden become
very afraid because they realize that there
afraid because they realize that there
are still things within themselves that
are not resolved.
And anytime you are in the presence of a
being that is totally integrated, their
energy will force you to face all the
things within yourself that you may not
be ready to face. And we will not do
that to you.
Any individual that has come into
contact as you say face to face and
experienced some degree of fear is
actually experiencing the last
vestigages of their fear. They simply
are functioning on a level where it is
deemed safe for them to go through the
last vestigages of their fear because
they have already integrated most of it.
Some of them to their way of thinking
still go through a great deal of terror.
But that great deal of terror or what
you call a great deal of terror within
some of those contacts is actually a
very small portion of the terror we
sense has been bred into many of
you. So we wait until we feel that a
small enough amount is left to assist in
accelerating it through
you. But again, the timing is what it
is. And many of the individuals that
have had some face-to-face encounters
and gone through that fear have actually
added to your society a type of energy
that makes it more available for the
rest of you not to need to experience
that fear when and if those interactions
take place. So, continue to live your life.
place. So, continue to live your life.
Yes, agreements have been made. You will
not miss
them. Enjoy where you are now. This is
the key. This is the key. Enjoy where
you are
now. And that will allow you to get
wherever else you want to be, that much
more quickly. The longer you deny that where
quickly. The longer you deny that where
you are now has anything at all to do
with your life
impatiently and avoid understanding that
you created it there for a
reason, then the longer it takes for you
to get anywhere else. Because if you're
not willing to live now, then you cannot
get to the next moment until you live
where you're
at. So stay in the present. Do not think
that something is coming along that is
better than where you are now because it
isn't. It's going to be different. It
may be more expanded, but it isn't
better. It's just
different. Understand?
Does that assist you?
Well, pleasant dreams to you.
What are you guys? One moment. You are
next. I was wondering if you could help
me understand the dream. Um, speak up so
that all may share. Okay. Um, the
background was like Persian temples and
it was all in pinks and blues and
greens. I and there were a lot of
children and there was a lot of laughter
and joy and people were going down these
huge water slides and then the next
scene of that we were standing in a
group and somebody handed me an alien
child. I see. Um, and that's all I
remember about the dream.
To some degree, it is an indication of a
probable future on your planet.
Meaning that the child in that sense
might be yours and it also at the same
time might literally be
you in what you call your future upon
your earth when there is more
interaction, more joy, more ecstasy when
you have in your own terms created
heaven on
earth. It is a sensing of the likely
most probable reality that you are
vibrating in accord to right now. It is
representative of a new birth of new
ideas, new
intermingling, new
interactions. You follow me? Um, I'm not
real clear about the alien child. Could
it be literally an alien child? It can
be. Yes. It is also symbolic of the growing
Yes. It is also symbolic of the growing
of the experience of sharing between our
respective cultures. Not just mine but of many
cultures. Not just mine but of many
others as well.
Do you understand? Yeah. You are simply
giving yourself
previews of certain ideas that will be
manifesting upon your
planet. If you say so.
It is also to some degree a past memory
of connections in Atalantean times because
because
similar interactions took place
then. Similar experiences of paradise and
Similar experiences of paradise and
interactions with extraterrestrial
civilizations took place in your
Atlantis and you are now recreating that
reality upon your planet.
So is it possible for a human to have an
alien child? Yes. Okay. Because
understand in a very real sense, none of
you are original to Earth anyway.
And don't forget that as far as I'm
concerned, you are aliens.
Does that answer the question? Yes.
Also, a large portion of what you think
of as your human form bodies are already
the product of
interactions between yourselves and
extraterrestrial civilizations. Yeah,
especially in adalantean times.
Does that answer your question? I have
something else real quick. I woke up
with menstrual cramps the other night
and I heard somebody say, "Go into the
cramp." Yes. And twice it happened that
evening. I found myself literally in the
middle of a cramp and it went away. Yes.
Anytime you go into something and do not
fear to face it, you will transform it
because you go into it and when you do,
you own it
utterly. You cannot change what you do
not own. Was somebody working with me
that evening to some degree? Yes. Thank
you. But you were doing the strongest
work because you had the strongest
trust. Thank you. No one needs to
experience that
pain. Particularly with the idea of
childbirth and anything associated with
it, dolphin energy is also being of
strong assistance in alleviating your
pain.
Thank you. Sure.
How did the dolphins feel about being at
sea world?
[Music] They
They
recognize the nature basically of the
captivity. But at the same time, on some
level they are willing to participate in
that if that is what it will take to
blend your two societies
together. They are loving enough to do
that. Now, it is our suggestion and many
of you have already started this upon
your planet that you can begin to build
theaters of interaction that are in your
oceans where they can come and go
freely. They will come because they want
to. They will interact with you. You do
not have to hold them captive to have
those interactions. But even if they are
captive, they recognize that they are
providing you a service, an opportunity
to get to know them, to get to know each
other so that you can feel each other.
You follow me? Yes. Thank you. So while
they may prefer not to be captive in the
overall sense, they are willing to do it
to assist you in learning to love
yourselves by loving them, by learning
how to play with them. All of you have
openstanding invitations to go and play
with dolphins in your ocean. physically
they will come to
you because it is time to blend the two
alien societies upon your planet into
one society as it used to
be. Right now, one of the strongest
things that is going on is that many of
your children, especially those before
what you call the age of three of your
years, and many of the young
dolphins are actually sharing bodies in
their dream state. astrally back and
forth, back and forth, back and forth,
slipping in and out, getting used to
once again the idea of living lives as
either species upon your planet, which
you have done with
both. So the children now, the human
children, the dolphin children are
slipping into each other's body because
you are both the same type of
soul. You follow me?
Does that assist you? Well, thank you
very much. You and then you. Um, is that
why the uh on the news a baby dolphin
walked into in destroy I think it was in
San Francisco? Yes. Is that it has
something to do with the idea now of
showing you the level of energy that is
the strongest the idea of the level that
is coming to you interacting with you
and it will meet you on your own terms
if you will not meet it on it. It will
come to you as it has. Um do you sense a
a stronger convergence or equal um in
February 13th of
88? There is some preparation on the
idea of February. But also once again do
not forget that of every year especially
between now and your year 1990 one of
the strongest dates will be your March
15th as it always is.
Can you explain why? That is simply
indicative of the vibratory pattern of
going to another accelerated level. Many
of you already recognize this. You call
the eyes of
Mar. It is simply a recognition of a
connection to conscious, subconscious,
and unconscious aspects of yourself. the
making of assessments of those portions
of yourself, the integration of what you
are ready to integrate and the stepping
up to a new level from that point
forward. It is a very natural cycle of
vibratory overlap in your society. So
basically as we all accelerate um we're
doing this in leaps and bounds as more
people become more accelerated. Yes, it
is geometric logarithmic.
The idea is that there will be highly
compacted acceleration by your year
1,990 which will allow there to be more
conductivity, more conduciveness to
allowing more blatant interactions
between your civilization and the
civilizations within the association of
worlds. Okay, I have one more question.
Okay, I have one more question.
Hey, can you uh explain the difference
between this uh transformational age and
other transformational ages that have um
come upon our planet? I mean,
astrologically, we're actually entering
the age of Aquarius, which undoubtedly
we've done before since that's based on
the wall in a sense. But now you have
experienced high
degrees of compacted negativity whereas
you had not before. So you are coming
into this transformation with a high
degree of accelerated energy. Okay. So
we're coming out of the loop. Yes. Okay.
You are now exiting the cycle of
negativity at a highly accelerated rate
faster than you ever have before.
It is as we have
used before the idea of the rubber band
analogy. As we have said, transformation
is not the product of mediocrity. And
you can look at the idea of all the
negativity you have experienced as
having a rubber band that you have
pulled very very very far back into the
negative. When you let go, just think
how far and fast it's going to go into
the positive.
That is the main difference between all
the other cycles and this one because
you are coming out of a highly
compressed cycle of negativity which is
going to shoot you very abruptly into a
very expanded cycle of integrity. Okay.
So I what I'm seeing then I've figured
out is the conclusion of a cycle of
February which in preparation for
another new um beginning of March a
subcycle if you wish. All right. Thank
you. And also your energy is strong
enough now to allow this cycle of
integration to be the last
cycle. In approximately 2 to 3,000 of
your years, you will no longer need to
be physical as a race at
all. and you will leave your
earth and allow others who may wish to
have similar experiences to what you
have experienced to come in and use the
planetary vibration.
Thank you, Jack. Good evening, Bashar.
Good evening, Bashar. Uh just recently I
became a hospice volunteer and I got my
first hospice patient and uh I felt that
the things that I had learned and coming
uh and listening to you and so on that I
was ready for questions and uh I was
talking with this f my first patient and
she said I'm on prayer chains across the
country and I don't understand why some
people are healed and I I have not been.
And looking at this lady who may be in
the latter stages of her physical
existence here and she has what she
perceives to be cancer of the liver and
pancreas and
colon. She has been schooled in the
conventional traditional ways of
religion and so on. So I didn't know
what to say. When that happens again, I
want to be ready. Oh, I up to you.
What What uh can you enlighten me as to
what I could pay say to someone who has
been traditionally uh I I can't say to
someone. You might have chosen that.
Well, you can say it. They don't have to
believe it.
Maybe they'll say, "What do you mean?"
I'm sure they will. Then you can explain
it. Again, not that they have to believe
it. The only thing you can really do to
be of best service to anyone is create a
reflection of what you believe in that
sense is most true for you and say this
is what I believe. Now you may have your
own belief and I believe your belief is
just as
valid and let them begin to explore
first of all by allowing yourself to
share what your belief is so they can at
least have the opportunity to consider
whether they may choose to believe like
you or not. I see. So just go ahead and
say it. Say the most natural thing there
is for you to say. Then you will be
being of best service.
All right. Thank you. Oh, thank you very
much. You I had an interesting experience the
You I had an interesting experience the
other day with my brother. All right. We
were driving down the freeway and I
looked up and I saw what I consider to
be whatever UFO or someone else. And I
thought anything that is unidentified is
a UF. Well, I consider it to be a
IFO. Ano?
Identify flying object. And define
And define
describe. It
was it was a flash in the
cloud and it was kind of a a
yellowish filter kind of color and it's
something I've never seen before. unlike
anything before.
Could you see any definitive shape
or just a flash? No, it was just a flash
and like time of day.
Um, it was about 3:00
about 3:00
date in your counting.
Okay, I'm trying to date. Um
within a day or two we'll be fine. About
two weeks ago.
Our perception at this
time not a spacecraft
because my curiosity was that as soon as
I pointed it out to my brother see it
anymore. Yes. And he didn't see it. Yes.
I was always curious as to why that was
and simply because of what you call
aberrations of light.
Now you can if you wish follow what we
call our rule of
thumb. It is a very simple rule. It is
designed to remove all the wondering and
the mystery from this
idea. If it isn't
absolutely beyond a shadow of a doubt
obviously a
spacecraft then it isn't even if it
is because the whole idea is why spend
time wondering.
Now it may have piqu your curiosity and
in peing your curiosity the
synchronicity of that event may tie into
other things that may have to do with
extraterrestrial connections and so
forth and that may be where you are
picking up the flavor. But you can use
many typical objects in your own reality
to instigate that curiosity and then
allow you to pick up the flavor that may
allow you to think it's an
extraterrestrial craft when it wasn't.
But it was perhaps the catalyst to spur
you in a certain direction to start
looking in different ways. You follow
it. That's the flavor you're picking up.
Okay. But it was a very in your terms
ordinary plan.
Okay. Does that serve?
You venue. One, two.
Um, I'd like to talk about the dolphin
and music. All right. You go right
ahead. I'll pay attention.
I'd like you to talk with me about Oh,
all right.
Um, I was introduced to the to the idea
of Speak up. Speak up. Speak up. I was
introduced to the idea of the Sumarians,
I believe it is, that um, Sumerians.
Sumerians. Okay. That interacted with
dolphins and whales. Okay. And did this
and energy from Sirius. Okay.
as represented by what you
call anis their deity which you call acuman
anis their deity which you call acuman
hakish which is not a literal
translation of serious energy but it is
an interpretation many other
civilizations upon your planet will
interpret serious energy in the same way
half human half is because of the nature
of the fact that serious energy exist in
an energy sea because of their
connection to dolphin consciousness many
of you in those ancient interactions
simply assume they were literally
amphibious but also you sense that they
were in a sense humanform like
yourselves and so you blend the two
ideas together I find it very intriguing
so I feel that I was maybe a part of
these interactions at that time very
strongly so as a matter of fact it is
our perception very strongly that you
were in one of called royal courts
could you expand on that I I don't do
that you were in your terminology ology,
a child, as royalty, and you had very
much experience and spent many wonderful
hours of enjoyment talking to the
astronomers of the time, discussing the
stars and the connections and the
energies and the deities and the gods as
you defined them back then. It
fascinated you to no end. Was music a
part of that? It is always a part of the
royal upbringing, and it was always
taught to be harmonious with all aspects
of science and religion.
What time frame is that?
There are a
few. Some of it is in what you would
call your
[Music]
1300. Some of it is also BC many times
BC as you call
it 56
BC. But you have paid many visits in
many tangential ways to that particular
area. And so my dreams about dolphins and
And so my dreams about dolphins and
whales is um it's connected there, but
it's also connected to the present, of
course, because that's what's going on,
the blending of those two societies,
yours and theirs. Um I've been having a
lot of fun recently with music. Um there
was a lot of tension at first about
getting up and doing it, so I felt that,
well, this doesn't excite me because
it's too scary.
And I got kind of confused at that
point, but I've worked through that now
because I forced myself into a situation
where I had to decide. Yes. Sometimes
you can tell the things that really
actually excite you the most because
they do scare you the most. Yeah, that's
a good point. That's simply because of
the way you have created your society to
be. And sometimes that's the only way to
tell. the thing that you are most afraid
of doing is very often the thing that
represents what you really need to do to
be really who you are. And a lot of
times um during interactions like this
and when I'm feeling real high um I have
this um sense in my throat of opening
and clearing. Yeah. Very good. The
chakras. Yeah. And it is for you to put
forth the expression of the vibrational
tones of music and harmony. Wonderful.
Yes, it is. Thank you very much. Thank
you. Number two,
why is it necessary for your society to
use spacecraft? Thank you. First of all,
it's fun.
Secondly, secondly, do not in your terms
elevate us beyond the idea of the
evolutionary pattern in which we also
exist. We are not all that dissimilar
from you. The idea is that there are
civilizations that do not need that kind
of accutrament. They simply project
themselves in your terms mentally. And
in a sense, that's what we do when we
use spacecraft as well. But it simply is
representative of the phase of evolution
we are
in. In the same sense that you use what
you call your automobile to get around.
Even though in using an automobile,
you're also projecting yourself with
your consciousness and creating the
illusion of an automobile. You don't
need an automobile
either. But the idea simply is also that
it serves many other functions.
Maintaining the level of understanding
we have even though that is changing for
us also assists us in dealing with
civilizations that still look to the
physical symbols to understand what is
going on. So the level upon which we
exist, the utilization of spacecraft
makes it easier also for you to
understand what we are talking about
because you can relate to us more easily
in many ways in general as a society
that is used to using objects. But it is
also an indication of the state of our
own evolution. As a society, we are just
beginning to use the idea that we do not
need spacecraft. But spacecraft still
exists as a remnant idea in our society.
And so we will still use them. We are
still to some degree physiological like
you. Even though we are a different
dimension, a different density
vibration, but we in a sense went
through similar ideas to you. Not the
same, but similar ideas of physiological
evolution. And we have invented the idea
of spacecraft in the way we have in much
the same way that you are inventing
spacecraft. So it is simply that in our
stage of evolution we have that device
just as you have your car, your train,
your plane and so forth. You follow me?
Does that answer the question? And also
one more time, it's
fun. You will in time get an opportunity
to see some of them and perhaps you will
enjoy them as much as we do for some of
them are quite
large as I just wanted to suggest a
break when you're ready.
Then you may
all take a short break because you are
ready now. And we will resume contact in
approximately 15 of your minutes.
I'll say continue. You then you Couple
questions. Hi. Um, first one I've been
wanting to ask the three channelings and
by coincidence it happens that at the
last channeling someone else asked
ident. It happens that at the last channeling
It happens that at the last channeling
someone else asked identically the same
question but it's an individual thing.
So I read it. Um, I feel a connection to
the channel. Can you tell me what that
is? Is that past life or something else?
Some of it is path association. Some of
it not necessarily in the exact linear
way. You might
think some of it is an association by
similar vibration, similar endeavors. One
moment. Much of it has been by what you
simply call
acquaintance through many different
lifetimes. Yes. and general agreement of similar
Yes. and general agreement of similar
vibrational principles
but in different ways.
Will that do? Yes.
Thank you. You mentioned once that
malachite can have a lot to do with body
temperature regulation. Yes. How would
you use it to stabilize body
temperature? Would you wear it on a
certain chakra?
You can pass it
over your third eye
area. Sometimes your solar plexus area,
sometimes down the spine can have
regulating effects. Sometimes just
holding it in
hand. But again also simply the
imagination of that particular idea the
vibration that it represents can also
have the same effect without in your
terms the physical object present. You
follow me. Yeah. It is the idea the
vibration that it represents the field.
Yes. That will create the change the
difference and it can be different for
different individuals depending upon
their specific vibrational signature
frequency. Okay. So that's over. Yes. Uh
third question is back in the 1800s
there were two individuals um who
were keys to the development of our
present electrical technology. Speak up.
Speak up. They were Nikolai Tesla and
James Cork Maxwell and um and their work
was so original to be it was a
rediscovery of understandings your
civilization had long ago in that sense
original for your time. Yes. Well, it's
so out of context with everything else
that was happening at that time. It's
like it was almost inspired or perhaps
it was inspired but it's okay very
profound and because a literal
recognition of what the electromagnetic
field is and a very natural way to tap
into that source. It is the same
principles that we utilize in our
spacecraft. Right. I always felt sort of
intuitively that the work they did was
uh actually the key to causing
uh or the key to other changes as well
as the technology that has evolved from
it. Yes, the realizations in and of
themselves were indicative of level
shifts in the collective consciousness
of your planet.
What I think what I'm trying to ask you
is the original work they did, did it
cause um did it make other specific
changes in our society or our
consciousness? Of course, all things are
interconnected. All things. It
accelerated to some degree what is going
on now. the ability of the general
society in which you exist to express a
desire to explore its connection to all
levels of consciousness. It had that
effect because it literally in that
sense electrified a large portion of
your consciousness.
uh because of dramatic changes. Yeah.
And also because some of the specific
energy that was being used literally had
a direct effect upon your
electromagnetic mentality just because
of some of the devices that were being
utilized and invented by those
individuals. Could you be more specific
on that? The idea is specifically of
what you call Tesla's generating wave
station. That which took advantage of
the natural cycle of your Earth's
vibration, 7 and 1/2 cycles per second,
tapped into a frequency of the crystal
in Earth that actually caused
reverberations in the mental field of
every individual living on your planet.
I understood you never fully completed
that. Not fully. No, but yet it was
used. But it did have some effect. Yes.
Um I have one further question. Are you
familiar with the term biological
personality defi? As I understand it, it's a u
defi? As I understand it, it's a u
consciousness that goes that is
associated with physical body body
consciousness and it
and it
uh let's see it's it seems to be
transmitted pass from one generation to
another like it stays on the earth
plane. Yes. And connects the individual
to the energy of the earth. Yes. In a
sense. Yes. Okay. Um I'm wondering how
technically how does that work? Does it
interconnect with the etheric body? Yes,
it does. It interconnects through all
different levels of your consciousness
that are attached to what you call the
reincarnational karmic cycle of your
particular planet, your particular
overall frequency.
It is the general theme consciousness,
the general cycle consciousness that
carries with it the wave front of your
biological evolution determined by the
directions in which your consciousness
flows at any given
moment. It actually has the ability to
unlock the genetic structure in certain
directions and cause what you call
mutations. Well, now are we talking about something
Well, now are we talking about something
that is a part of the individual's
consciousness or is it something that it
is a part of the collective
consciousness and therefore a part of
every individual within it? Ah, so it it
is inherited in a physical
sense. It is a template in a
non-physical sense that creates the
apparency of physical inheritance.
Okay? Do you understand?
Do you understand?
I have the idea which is I don't fully
understand. If you wish, it is a
branching program that sometimes shifts when you
program that sometimes shifts when you
change the whole idea, the collective
idea of yourself and then causes
spontaneous mutation to take place
within the individual body consciousness
to accommodate the bodily forms that are
necessary to survive within the energy
that has
been newly created. I see it. It
contains all the possibilities. Yes. the
template. Yeah. Um my question, the
other part of my question is how can I
um relate to that, interact with that in
a way that is mutually beneficial rather
than uh being in conflict with it at times.
uh being in conflict with it at times.
Experiment with electromagnetism. You
have in and of yourself many similar
approaches to the ideas of individuals
such as you have mentioned Tesla,
Maxwell, Faraday. You have had experience in
Faraday. You have had experience in
these realms. Explore it further and
really understand the vibrational pals
of
electromagnetism that can cause
different types of crystallization take
place within your bodily form. So the
template and your mentality is created
from the electromagnetic field. You can
redefine that. Experiment with it.
Thank you very much. Well, thank you.
Yeah, sure.
Um, what about last summer I asked you
about where my father is. He had died in
1968. You said speak up, speak up, speak
up. You said at that time that uh you
had given me enough information and that
you told me that he was hanging out with
other musicians with and that is what he
is. Um, but a couple things are coming
up. One, I did say hanging out. [Music]
[Music]
Okay. You are rubbing off on me.
He would really have enjoyed you, but I
think he enjoys you anyway. Thank you.
Okay. Um my dad it's it's I have a lot of
Um my dad it's it's I have a lot of
nostalgic things that go on about my
father particularly when I hear uh
certain music and it's just about all
kinds of music from 1970 back because he
played uh all kinds of music. So often
today I could hear a song and and it
reconnects you into that vibration
totally and very very constant. It is
also very very present. Yeah. Um and and
sometimes like today I've become very
tearful. Uh we can there's a lot of
pain. Why? Well, it feels like there's a
lot of
unresolved things. We didn't get a
chance to say certain things. I did not
get a chance. Then say them
now. When you are tapped into that
vibrational frequency, resolve them.
What are you waiting for?
I don't know. So what I end up doing is
just feeling the sadness and then I
don't Well, perhaps you do not really
believe you are connected.
[Music] Okay. Some what something that is is
Okay. Some what something that is is
happening and
connecting connected is um I grew up in
a extended Italian family with 19 first
cousins and the last of those cousins is
getting married in August. And also how
are you feeling nostalgic I guess? Yeah.
Yes. So much so that I do want to uh go
to New York and be at the wedding. Oh,
right. Have a good night. Thank you. And
I feel that the wedding a lot of my very
elderly aunts and uncles all of whom
grew up my parents and my aunts and
uncles all grew up together from around
age 12 and 13. All right. Um I feel like
it's a journey to learn more about my
father. Can be. Yes. To some degree. You
may discover some things that you here
to did not understand. Mhm. And that it
will particularly the information will
be given to me particularly by two
uncles uh who he was very close to in
their youth. Um perhaps also a female
where you least expect it.
[Music] Okay. Okay.
[Music]
Uh okay. And it doesn't it doesn't feel
like there's really any question other
than that I want to keep confirming to myself
that I want to keep confirming to myself
that this is an important event that I
want to be there. It is an event.
You have it in your imagination now.
Yes. Yes. Then you are there now. And
the more you understand that that is
real now, the easier it will be for you
to attract the
physiological representational
circumstances to allow it to manifest to
match the picture and the vibration you
are creating that you are there now.
You are at the wedding now.
Literally let your physical reality fall
into place.
to bring you the circumstances that will
allow you to manifest
physicalize what you know now
exists because you say
so all right well um what's happening
right now is that I am there and I do
hear his music
yes so it is all in the present it is
all alive right Now you are in
connection. Now sometimes the releasing that you are
Now sometimes the releasing that you are
feeling is your way of resolving what
you believe is not being resolved. You
are centering within the vibration that
represents his signature energy. And by
centering, even if you are doing it
through tears, you are
resolving what you think wasn't
resolved. Mhm. Understand? Yes, I do.
Because it's
um if the signature of the music is very
loud and clear. Um then assume that it
is
resolving otherwise the signature would
not be that strong. You are in
synchronous harmony. To be able to
perceive the signature that strongly it
means you're resolved.
Now, if you choose to continue to
believe that you're
not, you can enjoy that process, too.
That's all right. It is up to you.
Completely up to you.
No, I I choose the sense of resolvement
because I feel also
that if I stay connected to that idea,
Yeah. that there's another and I feel
like my dad has been telling me this
that there's another level for me to go
to now. But that I have to be very
clear. Well, do me a favor. Will you
do as I do?
[Music] Well,
Well,
well, no, no, no. Like Like
this well.
13. That's all [Music] right. Ha.
Repeat after me. Ha. Haha. Haha.
Well, well, well, well, well, well,
well. Well, well, well, well, well. What
do you know? What do you know? Here I
am. Here I am. Always. Always. Where I
belong. Where I belong.
Unconditional love unconditional love is
mine to create. is mine to create. Mind
to behold. Mind to behold. Mine to
experience. Mine to experience. I feel
like I'm getting mad. mad.
Good.
Good. Do not think that just because you
attend a wedding that you are not being
married as
well. You are marrying more of yourself.
I got it. Thank you very much. Thank you
very much. You may kiss yourself.
Allow the new dream gates and dream
doorways within you now to send you a
flood of new light. New life.
All right, I will. Pleasant dreams. Yes.
Thank you.
How do I overcome my fear? Which one?
I feel at the present time a very short
situation. I feel I am being offered
something of magnificence, but I can't
let go of of what? Fear of what? Label
it the unknown. Fear of the
unknown. If you don't know what it is,
why are you afraid of it?
How do you know it's not positive?
Oh, then why are you afraid of it? Why
are you afraid of it? If you know it's
positive, what is there to fear?
Ability. You just told me that you
recognize you are going through
transformational changes. Yeah.
You don't sound too sure. All right.
You in a sense just told me that you
perceive that there is energy and ideas
that you would be very excited about
doing. Yes. Do you understand that your
ability to perceive it to conceive of it
is the same thing as your ability to
manifest it? No. Do you understand the
connection? They are one and the same.
Two sides of the same coin. No such
thing as one-sided coins. If you have
the ability to conceive of it, that
shows you you have the ability to
manifest it or you would never have been
able to conceive
it because the universe does not have
pointless and extraneous creation. There
is no such thing as a person who has the
ability to conceive of something they
cannot do. Understand? So if you see something
do. Understand? So if you see something
that really excites you because you can
perceive it, it says you have the
ability to manifest it. Otherwise, you
would have conceived of something else.
It's that easy. Does that help you?
I have another question. Oh, all right.
I have a fear of having a child. A fear
of having a child.
Why do you think it will interfere with
something?
I have a picture that I made a
commitment some time ago to bring some
yes seeing to understand the planet that
it wouldn't be in normal physical
form if it's real in a sense it is real
continue so what of it
I don't know what to do about it how
about just continue your life and let
everything fall into
Because when you get to be the person
that is representative of the agreement,
it will all feel natural by definition.
By then, you don't have to worry about
it. Now, if you're not the person yet
that will be the person that will
fulfill the agreement, then why are you
worried about it when it's not
you? Let yourself grow and become that
you. And then when you are that you, it
will feel natural and you won't be
worried about it. So don't worry about
it now because it's not you yet. And
when you become that you, you won't
worry about it because it's natural. Understand? natural. Understand?
[Music]
As you say, sufficient unto the day is
the life therein. Be who you are now.
You don't have to worry about who you're
going to be when you are that person.
You will naturally be that person and
everything that that person is all about
will feel the things that that person
needs to feel and they will feel quite
correct at that time.
Well, thank you very much. Just one
moment.
Give it anywhere from 3 to seven of your
years. All right. There's many many
things that you will be doing before
then. Many
things. Many
things. Thank you.
Sure. You
all the metaphysical books say that
we're here on this earth. It's a
classroom and we're learning lessons.
Everywhere is a classroom. Everywhere.
And I want to know why. Who created this
game? You did.
All of you did. Together. You agreed to
be where you are. We've agreed that we
will live live as, you know, human
beings on this earth. That's
plain and simple. That's it. Your game.
You can change it in any way, shape, or
form you desire to. It is not locked.
Seth talks the Seth material talks about
um that all that is wanted to know
itself and therefore created people. All
that is will experience itself in all
the ways there is to experience itself.
And what you call people, well, at least
your version is one of those ways,
right? And so that's what we're doing is
just experiencing ourselves as the
creative energy. Yes. In this particular
modality, just as we are experiencing
ourselves as the infinite creator in our
particular modality and the dolphin
creator, other creatures. Yes.
Okay. Thank you. Well, thank you very
much for your choice. and your
willingness to be of service in the time
and place you chose to be. It makes a
difference. Thank you. Well, thank you.
Yes.
All right. You then female. Yeah. I just
want to share a little synchronicity. Go
right ahead. Okay. Do speak up. All
right. I uh rented a VCR to um rent.
It's a toughy for you. I know that. But
uh we're doing a
we're doing a uh you dealt with this
eons ago. We uh we're doing uh a session
of the uh intensive workshop tomorrow.
And I I wanted a smaller uh VCR, so I
rented one. And at the same time, uh, we
said, "Well, let's rent a movie while
we're in the store." And I thought,
"Well, do I want a movie that's kind of
silly or something after this wonderful
channeling?" I thought, "Well, maybe
I'll get something that's close to it or
about the same thing." And after what
we're talking about, experiencing the
all of everything, I thought it was very
appropo that the movie that I just
happened to grab was All of Me.
Oh my goodness. Isn't that
great? That's it. Thank you very much.
Oh, I had her question. Um, I am not
surprised about my mother. Kind of two things
about my mother. Kind of two things
question. She died all the way. She died
in 1970 of stroke. I was diagnosed as
paralyic before that and she was in that
state about 5 years prior to her death.
All right. Um I would like to know how
she is now. They are both doing fine.
I am not making a joke for it is an
ultimate cosmic form of humor that the
particular experience that individual
had that you call paranoid schizophrenia
has allow the oversoul to split itself
into more than one incarnation this time
to experience the bipolar realities that
were in that sense contained within one
body before. Again,
before. Again,
an over soul can have as many bodies as
it likes in any time frame. And an
individual that in this case has
experienced in one body the idea of
schizophrenia as we have perceived it in
this particular round of incarnation has
allowed itself not to reincarnate as a
single individual but as more than one.
to experience the differences that were
being experienced within one body now in
different bodies to play out the idea
that was begun in the one body as a
split. Is that counterparts? Yes, it is called
Is that counterparts? Yes, it is called
counterparts. So they are fine and in
our perception reincarnated
well as more than one
person identities now as more than one
person. Yes. Well at the time she was uh
totally miserable. Yes. At the time
angry and resentful. Yes. Did not have
to be. So that's how you would explain.
Oh, there are many ways to create that
apparency on the surface. That is simply
one of them and that is simply the case
we perceive here. Okay. Thank you. Thank
you. One moment. Yes. Um I have another
question. In 1970 I went to Stonehenge.
Um and it was while people were still
allowed to walk around among the stones.
It was a very very nice experience. And
I hit England. It was around Christmas
time. Did it hurt?
No. Oh, what? They were having
a sick
day. I told you I was unconscious for
three days.
Part of it is reliving the plague.
Uhhuh. You have assimilated much in those three
You have assimilated much in those three
days. I had a feeling I did. I was with
an English friend and they were giving
me uh aspirin and codine. It made all my
joints swell really badly.
You have a familiarity with that area.
You have been in that sense familiar
with what you call druidic rights.
Yes. My other question that has to do
with Stonehenge is Sidonia and
Stonehenge are considered magnetic
vortices. Yes. And they're positive.
Yes. Are there any other on the earth
and there? Well, there are many.
That is a very strong one. Yes. Under
what you call England on the aisle of
man. Very strong.
Where else? Many many almost at every
axis point of the meridians of the lay
lines of your
planet. But there are some that
fluctuate in stronger formats. The one
in what you call your Bermuda area is a
very strong one. But it fluctuates
randomly because of certain attachments
to adalantian technology as
well. What you call the great pyramid in
Giza is a very strong one. That is why
it was built
there. Understand? Mhm. It takes
advantage of the energy in that
vortex for the rights of initiation that
were performed within its structure.
There are many in what you call all
portions of your
planet. There are some very large ones
in what you would call the major chakra
points. Again, your Mount Chasta, your
Hawaii, your Mount
Fuji point in
Peru area you call
Baja, very strong in the northern
area you call Yucatan. Very
strong. There are many, many, many.
Will that do? Yes. Thank you very much.
of fighting very
I want to ask about star people I've
been reading a lot about star the star
star seed as you are all in a sense star
people as we have said none of you are
original to your planet but the
reference being made to star people are
simply individuals who are awakening to
the fact that you all have connections
elsewhere. And if they waken to it very
strongly, they may then exhibit some of
the strong traits of those connections
more than other individuals may if that
is simply not their orientation. Is it
important for them to come to
consciousness at this time? To some
degree may not be completely resolved
with aspects of the femininity within
you. Two, it can allow some aid and
assistance in the blending of the idea
of femininity and masculinity even in
the present
light. Three, it can connect you to
certain extraterrestrial connections
that may vibrate along that wavelength
and allow you the fullness of conscious
awakening into your own higher self as
you call
it. Do these and many other things that
can also connect you very strongly to
what you call the naturehood of your
earth. Okay. Does will that give me will that
Okay. Does will that give me will that
amplify healing powers? Yes, it can.
Especially if you believe it can
especially if you prefer to use that
particular methodology. However,
remember once you begin to truly
integrate your imagination will kick in
and offer you different suggestions that
may seem more exciting, more enticing.
follow them because
the of the integration that has been
created through the utilization of the
older tool and the tool might change.
All right. Right now, I'm feeling a
strong urge to go to Sedona. Bye-bye.
Okay. Have a good time. Follow the urge.
It is there for a reason. Okay. And
you're not going to tell her the reason
it is. It is a very highly magnetic
area, a vortex that connects into all
levels of dimensionality to allow you to
integrate whatever you choose to get out
of it. It's a very strongly conductive
magnetic area that can align you. Okay,
just a line.
and align you. Okay, just align my um
there may be some specific encounters
you will have with different individuals
who also live in that area that might
represent reflections of different
pieces of yourself that you are pulling
together as well. Thank you.
One moment. There is also a very strong
moment. There is also a very strong
connection there for a specific past
life idea with regard to being in what
you call your Native American culture
and your relationship to the earth
itself. Okay. Yes. Thank you. Yes.
Yes. I'd like to talk with you about an
automobile collision I was in about 5
days ago. Oh, right. Some things
happened during the collision that I
have not experienced before. So
um when the collision happened, I
realized that I it was like the other
person came from out of nowhere. It was
like they were invisible. Like I hadn't
seen the girl behind the car. And after
I went to get out of my car um to go and
check on her, as I was standing there
with people, I felt like I was
invisible. And as I was looking at
myself, I felt um that I was getting
acquainted with my body that I hadn't
seen it before. In a sense, yes, you
were also recreating yourself in and you
will shift your consciousness up and
down the stream, the fabric, the
framework of all these probable
realities. You will fade in and out of
one or another and allow yourself to
realize the true malleability the
focusness of your consciousness can
have. So yes, in it you were fading in
and out and you created an intersection
with another aspect, another reflection
of your consciousness to show you that
where you focus your concentration along
more than one line three-dimensionally
will create solid
reality. Everything else that seems to
be invisible to you contains all other
reality. 99% of all other reality is
invisible to you. Where you focus your
concentration is where it solidifies.
Um also um at the scene of the accident
um well we were taken by ambulance to
the hospital and I had the same reaction
there where I would be talking to the
doctor and the nurse and I would um have
the same thing where it's like they
didn't see me or I wasn't there. And
then for the next uh few days
um basically I felt like I was getting
uh reacquainted with my whole
surrounding but real disconnected
from the head. Let me tell you
something. All of you all the probable
earths already exist.
Changes that seem to take place in your
world are changes because you are
shifting into another probable
reality, another
earth. You understand?
Could you expand a little bit on that?
Every idea of each and every earth that
overlaps every other earth and exists in
a different frequency
band is representative of a particular
difference in an idea you might have
from one idea to
another. Let's put it this way very
simply. You have the earth right now you
are familiar with.
There is another earth that is identical
in every way, shape and form except
perhaps you are sitting over
there. That one difference is the only
difference on that earth. Then another
earth perhaps has two differences. Then
three, four, five, an infinite number
for every dimension for every world.
The changes you see in what you think
are the one earth in which you exist is
actually you taking yourself up and down
the bandwidths of the frequencies of
different
programs. So you are now becoming
consciously aware that changes in your
mind actually change the frequency that
you are on and create your focus on
another parallel earth. You are now
becoming consciously aware that you
actually do automatically make an
adjustment to that new
earth. Understand? You are beginning to
realize the true malleability of your
physical world and beginning to realize
that physical reality is a dream.
Literally a dream. And you have to
invent it and do invent it every moment
of time that you create to exist.
You are inventing it over and over again
so quickly that you have been able to
forget you are doing it. You have
allowed it to become
subconscious. But every moment you
experience the ability for your hand in
a sense to move from here to here is
similar to the analogy you call
animation where there are a million in
between motions representing a million in
motions representing a million in
between Earths. in different states of
one now eternal
moment. The earth of this now, the earth
of this now, the earth of this now. We
have just gone through millions of
earths literally. So rapid is the frequency of
literally. So rapid is the frequency of
the creation of reality as you do it.
Do you understand? Yes, I do. And uh
also one of the things that was amazing
to me at the time was that when I was
standing outside of the car, I would
look at my body and I didn't have any
scratches or cuts. Everything seemed
perfect. And I would look at my car and
it was total. And I was amazed at how
that could be. It could be if you are
not exactly in the same reality. If you
are out of
faith because then the reality of the
car in that sense, the old reality has
nothing to do with the new reality. you
are as we said only when you focus on
the three linear
dimensions do things become truly solid.
So it showed you that in a sense a part
of the interaction that you had was
focused and phased in an old reality and
a part of it in a new reality wherein in
a sense the accident did not take place
because you showed no result of an
accident. Right? It was like she was
really injured and I was Yes. Like I
wasn't even there. Yes.
You cocreated that for each other to
learn the things you each respectively
needed to learn. And I never saw her at
all. I had no recollection of seeing her
appear on the scene. In a very real
sense, she wasn't there until she needed
to
be understand. Yes, I do. Many times,
many of you will experience this on
different levels. Now sometimes when you
are looking for something and you don't
see it in a sense you can say yes
because you create this to be a part of
the idea of the reality you may be in it
could be a quote unquote trick of the
light. You may simply have not been
paying attention and that is why you did
not see it. But many times many of you
know the thing you were looking for was
not there because there is nowhere else
it could have been because it wasn't
behind anything. It simply wasn't there.
And then all of a sudden, you turn
around and there it
is. When that really represents a phase
shift, it really wasn't there. You
simply had loosened your definition of
your reality to not contain that, to not
need to manifest that. When you really
needed to redefine it, you redefined it
into your reality, shifted yourself to
that station, and then you could
perceive it. It is similar to what you
call again the radio or television
analogy in your society. You know all
the programs are all there all at once.
The only one you perceive is the one
your dial is tuned to. However, but they
are all
there. Understand? Yeah. What is
invisible to you is simply at that
moment not of your
frequency. Plainly, right? Okay. And um
yes. Um did it go to another frequency?
I guess so.
Um turn the dial
back. Click. Click.
Something about it. The the scene of the
accident. Dad. Dad.
I'm I can't remember. This isn't what I
was going to say, but this is before
what I was going to say. All right.
Driving. I know. Yes.
Driving just about to where we we
crashed. I kind of felt like I was
floating like through a cloud in a
sense. Yes. I remember that feeling and
I was kind of denying it, but it it was
there. Yes. that was happening. Yes, you
are actually physicalizing the
experience of quote unquote tunneling
through the different frequencies
interdimensionally. That limbo state,
that floating state is an indication of
unlocking from one reality so that you
can observe all the probable ways the
realities can manifest and then choose
the one that is most representative of
the vibration you are in the limbo
state. That's why many of you now in
this transformational age are undergoing
the idea of
confusion, disorientation, disillusionment.
It is why many of you feel like you're
floating in a limbo undecided state
because you are unlocking from your
previous reality, your previous concepts
and you are floating in that in between
stage that allows you to see the
spectrum of all the probable realities
you can choose and then choose one. It
was also now I remember what I want to
say. It was right at the time that we
collided that I I hit my head also. And
that's right after I hit my head. It was
like I was separate from the body that I
was walking around in. Yes. Or like I
was new to the body. Yes. That's when
that occurred. You created a little bit
of an ascension into yourself.
You feels good. Your energy. Yeah. In a
sense, I haven't felt um especially at
the whole thing. I didn't feel any
emotion in a very real way. The old you
actually died. That's right. And you are
a new beginning. The you you are now.
Happy birthday. Thank you. Like you.
Thank you. For sure.
You decide among yourselves.
Okay. Thank you. Boldness.
Um about 12 or 14 years ago, we were
traveling in Baja at night and a
spaceship called
followers. I'd say about 500 ft above us
and finally we had to stop and we got
out and we all laid down and went to
sleep right on the I mean it was like
right on the surface. What happened?
Many of you in having the communications
you desire to have as a result of the
agreements you have made will in that
sense need to become unconscious to
allow the communication to take place on
all the levels that it needs to because
many of your presuppositions in your
conscious mind will in your terms get in
the way.
You can be assisted in remembering if
you wish by choosing individuals who can
in your terms regress you. It will come
out bit by bit at whatever rate you are
comfortable in letting it out. But it
is, I will remind you, part and parcel
of many similar ideas that are going on
all over your world at this time because
it is an opportunity to blend and
integrate and balance the old negative
fears within you. transform them into
joy and ecstasy and equality. That is
the basic as you say once again bottom
line. Okay. I've been experiencing all these
Okay. I've been experiencing all these
things you've been discussing for quite
a while now. Yes. And I keep thinking
what am I supposed to be doing? Where am
I supposed to be going? What excites you
the most?
All right. Keep it simple. Keep it simple.
right. Keep it simple. Keep it simple.
What excite you for your
part? Sir, you
I don't have to me what happened to my
left leg here about 17 years ago. It's
kind of slow moving. Did you in your
terminology have it medically analyzed?
I did. And they told me three different
ways that I had I couldn't believe that.
All right. And then they told me that
due to an accident I had thrown out of a
car and that possibly could mean I had
chiropractors work on it. All right. And
it seems to be getting a little bit
better, but I want to get better faster.
All right. You are as we have already
right. You are as we have already
suggested made of energy. The exercise
that we have already given you can be of
some assistance to you. I felt that when
you were saying, yes, let yourself dive
deeply into that energy state and
redefine yourself completely as an
electrical matrix. Sometimes what you
call fluoride crystals can aid and
accelerate this idea especially with
regard to the neuronic pathways and
neural links in your body.
It is simply conducive to the specific
vibration of the neural
sheets that protect and balance and
nurture your nervous system and can
promote an accelerated healing within
it. Regeneration sheets.
Yes. The idea
also can be to allow yourself to
envision in any particular
area a concentration of the liquid blue
in a jellyike
form. See it
infused into the
leg and becoming the material out of
which new crystals of all type bone,
skin, muscle, nerve will form out of
this homogeneous blue
jelly. Let it regrow, become flexible,
new from inside out. inside out. All
reality is created from inside out, not
outside in. That can be of some assistance, too.
in. That can be of some assistance, too.
I will do. Could you tell me when I'm
going to be moving, I'm going to sell my
house? That's up to you. Okay. Thank
you. Ask yourself if you really, really,
really want to sell the house and why.
And you will understand your reasons for
doing what you are doing. And you will
understand what you will attract.
Sometimes things that do not seem to
happen may be also because you may be
holding yourself back from doing
something that will actually initiate
what needs to be done. Are you hesitant
in any way, shape, or form about selling
the house? Not really. No. What will you
do when you sell it? Whatever comes in
my path to be able to do, I'll do it.
What do you want to do? Sell it. Why?
Cuz they're moving up north to
Washington State of Canada. All right.
Why? Cuz I feel like it'll be a better life
Cuz I feel like it'll be a better life
for us. All
right. Are you truly in your terms
acting like you are moving? Yes. All of
you. Yes. All right. Then move.
Do you need to
wait? Then don't.
Perhaps you are only creating an
illusion of attachment to something you
do not need to be attached to. Perhaps
you think it is holding you back and it
isn't. And perhaps that's why in your
terms it's not
selling. Perhaps if you simply act upon
what you know with your intuition is
what you're all about, you will then
have made a statement that you do not
need that symbol and it will sell.
Well, thank you
for you,
I have um I went to um Speak up. What
was that thing we went to? No, no, no.
That's lower. Speak louder.
Don't speak up.
Um self-empowerment workshop. Yes. And
when I went to uh my place of uh perfect
peace. Yes.
Um the first place I was was in there
was a man there and then there was a
bird. Yes. Um I know the person was the
person that's in my uh physical life
right now. All right. I have
subsequently had dreams about this
person in me. All right. Um another time
it was also a birth and he was there.
Yes. And the last time
um everybody was congratulating us
because we were going to get married and
I was pregnant. All right.
Um I'd like to know the significance of
this person. Could you tell me more
about this person or No. Have had many
lives together. You are a part all of
you and many others that you know of one
particular type of family and you have
interacted and shared and interchangeed
many different roles at many different
times. Remember that the whole idea now
that many of you are understanding upon
your planet is that you are all married
to each other. You don't have to think
of the idea of relationships in that
sense as being mutually exclusive of
each other but in fact they are mutually
enhancing. understand. I I do understand that. Um I
understand. I I do understand that. Um I
I feel some
you are in the middle of a process we
cannot fully
interrupt. There is not a lot of
information we can share because you are
right at the point of unraveling or
unwrapping if you will a present.
Yeah, that's what I thought. I swear I
didn't think I was going to ask the
question cuz I didn't think I was going
to be doing it cuz I didn't think I was
ready. That is an answer. Yes, the
answer is that you are doing just fine.
Trust it. You are getting the messages
in the way that you need to get them and
you by
essence by feeling in a sense know their
significance. You are very familiar with
each other.
Yeah. So enjoy
and and also um we were talking about
earlier. Is there something that I can
do that can
um
oh a step that I can make or something
to
um um physically get into uh somehow
interrelating my um psychic abilities
with my um engineering abilities. I have
a little conflict there because one is
of such a physical nature and the other
one is of such a um personal nature.
Psychic abilities are of in a sense a
physical nature too except that your
science does not define it as so. Simply
your science chooses to measure the idea
of psychic functioning by yard sticks
that have no business being used to
measure it. As we have already said
everything is vibration. And when your
scientists begin to understand that
consciousness needs to be included in
their equations, they will understand
how to prove what they seem to be unable
to prove. Now, with regard to the idea
of psychic functioning, they are simply
not allowing themselves to quote unquote
test the ability within the framework
that will give it the best opportunity
to show them that it exists. They are
attempting to measure it along
frameworks that have nothing to do with
that particular phenomenon. If you start
once again to understand that it is more
closely connected to the emotional
aspect of you and uses energy in that
way, then it will be seen to cause very
strong fluctuations in the
electromagnetic field and can be picked
up and can be repeated as many times as
they care to. But they must test it in
the laboratory in which it belongs,
which is the laboratory of spontaneous
life, not the sterilized idea of
absolutely structured
experiments because it is an emotionally
based, emotionally activated presence.
It can
be blended with the idea of many aspects
of your science. But the idea is first
and foremost consciousness must be
allowed to be a part of the
equation otherwise there is no
limit. It must be understood that what
scientists think is pragmatic
electricity solid material is simply
expressions of
consciousness plain and simple.
So you can blend them and because you
have the idea that you desire to blend
them then in a sense already within you
they are blended. All you have to do is
express it in whatever way seems to
occur to your imagination most fluidly
and most
excitingly that you can let us say
invent your own definitional
parameters by which both can be
measured. But you see the idea of
dragging someone into a sterile
laboratory and hooking them up to many
machines and saying, "All right,
malfunction psychically is quite
analogous to dragging them into a
sterile laboratory surrounded by a bunch
of people they do not know, do not
relate to, have no feelings for in that
sense. Hooking them up to machines and
saying, "All right, on the count of
three, fall in love with
me. Oh, you did not do it. Therefore,
scratch love. it doesn't
exist. You see, they will get more than
enough repeatability if they will
observe the manifestation of psychic
functioning within its natural
laboratory life because there are many rules to
life because there are many rules to
psychic functioning. Primary is it
always will take the path of least
resistance just like electricity.
So in other words, if somebody says,
"Hey, what did I have for breakfast
today?" Well, in the overall
event, that person already knows the
answer. So why should psychic ability
even begin to function when the path of
least resistance has already been
fulfilled? The answer is known by the
person asking the question.
That knowledge in and of itself can
short circuit the ability of anyone who
chooses to function psychically from
discovering the answer unless rule
number two they have an overwhelming
desire or need to know that must also be
present. So if someone asks you a
question and you cannot function
psychically for them that does not mean
that psychic functioning does not exist.
It simply may mean that you're not
interested in finding out who's going to
do what on the such and such date of
such and such month. You don't care. So,
you do not have the overwhelming desire
or need to tap into that flow of energy
to see what the most likely probable
reality is. And remember, there is no
such thing as a prediction of the
future. Any such prediction is a sensing
that is made of the energy that is most
likely to manifest at the time the
prediction is made. An awareness of that
prediction can change the energy. Out
goes the prediction. It becomes obsolete
just like that. And that's the third
rule. Understand? So there are laws
quote unquote that can be very
scientifically listed and labeled and
oriented. But simply that is those laws
that must be used to see the
repeatability and provability that they
desire to see. You have to use the
measuring stick that is relative to the
thing you are
measuring. So enjoy your exploration.
Thank you.
You and then you
me or her. Yes, you. Um, thank you. I'd
like to pursue our our previous
conversation a little bit further
regarding a little bit. Yes. regarding
uh using electromagnetic fields to get
better in contact with the physical
consciousness. Pulsing them at the earth
vibration of 7 and 1/2 cycles per
second can aid and assist in bodily
alignment. Yes. Are there any other
frequencies? 10 cycles. Okay. Seven.
Three, these will put you into the
various contacts with different levels
of your collective consciousness. Is
that is is it no accident that those
numbers correspond to common brain
frequencies? No accident. Okay. Um
alpha, theta, delta, that's the whole
idea. For instance, one delta might be
very specific
approximately three is delta one and in
a sense you are approaching death.
Deep delta invokes what you call astral
projection. Okay. Uh I was actually when I asked the
Okay. Uh I was actually when I asked the
question I was thinking also in terms of
paraphric specifically 27 kilos. Does
that have the particular
23 to 27 can put you in touch with the
vibrational frequency of all
synchronicity standing waves so that
your life literally can become an
ecstatic explosion of sequential events
seeming coincidentally to tie in and
connect to everything you are doing in
life. 23 to 27 instant enlightenment,
instant synchronicity, instant
recognition. In that sense, yes, it can
be. Of course, it will still depend upon
the belief systems that are inherent
within you. It will not overwhelm those.
Yes. Any others you care to share at
this time?
33. The transformational frequency that
can shift you through gates of
dimensionality. That is a very strong
one. Very strong.
That will do for now. Thank you very
much. Thank you very much. Yes. Completely well.
Completely well.
In what way do you imagine that you are
not completely well? Um I'm a cancer
patient. All right. What are you
learning about that about having created
that idea? What are you learning about
yourself? A lot of things. All right.
Are you willing to integrate them within
you and understand that you have created
this idea for a
reason or do you feel like a victim?
Um, I think I feel both ways. One way or
the other. When you feel one, you are
that reality. When you feel another way,
you are that reality. You are not both
at the same time. Well, I don't feel
that I caused my own cancer. I never
wanted to be. I understand that it may
not be a conscious realization and we
are not saying that when you choose your
reality. You expressly actually say I
want cancer but the idea can come from
many different source beliefs within
you. Denials of certain other things or
desires for certain other things may
bring about once again as we have said
an effect that represents the path of
least resistance in discovering the
things you want to learn. Now if you
have been brought up to think of the
idea of disease as one way to do that
then you may simply create it even
though that's not your absolutely
conscious intention but for some reason
in some way from some direction you must
understand that you have created it
because no one else can. So but it could
be a subconscious. Oh yes, absolutely.
And very often it is because you all
know none of you directly or at least
not very many of you consciously want
dizzy. And what sort of lesson do we
learn from putting ourselves through
suffering? Perhaps the simplest lesson of all that
Perhaps the simplest lesson of all that
you no longer have to suffer
anymore simply because you don't prefer
it. Sometimes many of you will create
disease because you will not allow
yourself any other way of learning that
you don't have to suffer because you
will then compound the idea to such an
extreme that it scares you and sometimes
fright is the only way you will allow
yourself to live in the moment. If you
will not allow yourself to live in the
moment through joy and ecstasy, then you
will be very clever and polarize
yourself so that you will force yourself
to live in the moment through fear. Now
if you understand that that may be one
of the reasons, then you can let go of
the mechanism you are using a little bit
more. If you acknowledge first of all
that it there must be a reason, then you
can begin to explore what those reasons
are. Remember, you cannot transform what
you do not own. So even if it was
created by a subconscious or unconscious
belief, it's still a part of you. You
have to acknowledge it. If you really
want to be able to change it, you have
to know you were in control of it to
begin with, even if you didn't know it.
The only way you can control anything is
by knowing you are always in control of
it. Do you have any idea why?
We are already discussing some of these
ideas, but you can illuminate the
situation a little bit further by
expressly coming up with some of the
specific things you have learned about
yourself by having that disease. What
have you learned?
Many many things. How has it changed
your life? What has it allowed you to
see that you may not have seen had you
not created the disease? It's made me a
lot closer to people. All right. It's
made me um a lot more happy with who I
am. Has it allowed you to truly learn to
live in the moment? Yeah. All right. Now
if you understand that these are reason
enough then you can say all right step
one I acknowledge that I created it
perhaps for the very reason of
discovering these
things. Now that I know that that may be
why I created it. I now acknowledge that
I will be able to understand these
things without the need of a negative
symbol. I will now be willing to explore
these things and live in the moment and
discover all that I need to discover in
a positive way. I no longer need to
force myself to face these things. I am
now willing of my own free will to be
ready to face anything that will come up
within me. I will not continue to judge
myself or others. I will learn that I am
one with all. I will choose a life of
ecstasy. I will choose to believe there
is absolutely nothing I could ever
discover about myself that cannot be
applied in a positive way.
Therefore, if there is nothing about
myself that I
fear, I do not need to be forced to face
these aspects of myself of my own
valition. I will face them. So, I don't
need the disease to force me to face
them. And when you make that
acknowledgement and begin to act
accordingly, you can begin to release
the disease.
Plain and
simple. Do you believe it? Yeah. Can it
be that simple for
you? Can you feel the energy, the
temperature change within you when you
consider the ideas we have shared?
Then allow yourself to understand that
that temperature change is indicative of
a frequency change and a frequency
change is indicative of a reality
change. And therefore you are changing
as quickly or as slowly as you care to.
It is up to you. Now perhaps also if
there is something in your life that
excites you that you are not doing by
doing it you will align with your
centered vibration which by definition
cannot contain disease. The more willing
you are to allow energy to flow through
you in a way that represents who you are
at your highest level of vibrational
energy, then no energy can stick around
in you, block up and bottle up within
you and create the idea of
disarmony, disordance,
disordance,
disease. Are you doing in your life the
things that excite you the most? No.
Then do them.
And you will heal
yourself by being fully who you are.
Remember like pain all
disease comes from
resistance. Disease is resistance to your own
Disease is resistance to your own
ecstasy. Don't fight it. Be who you are
and let the energy flow. Then it won't
block up and become
stagnant. Understand? Yeah.
Does that assist you very much? Live
with a full boldness of life and you
will not create the symbols of
death. Plain and
simple. It will make a difference. And
there are energies in your dream
realities dive in assistance that also
will send you their
unconditional love. Unconditional
love. Treat yourself with the same
respect. You
deserve ecstasy. Why? Because you say
so. May I ask you a
question? Well, thank you very much.
Did you have to do anything special in
order to deserve to exist or do you
simply exist?
I think I sort of have a feeling of
guilt. All right. Guilt can eat away at
you like
cancer. Cancer can be symbolic of guilt.
Self invalidation. If you invalidate
yourself, you start to cancel cancer
yourself out.
What should you be guilty of?
All right, then. Do not create the idea
of
guilt. Love. You deserve it. Why
not? Once again, did you have to do
anything special to deserve to exist? Or
do you exist?
I just exist. You know you just exist,
don't you?
Then why not take it for granted that if
the infinite creation believes you
deserve existence, you can treat
yourself with the same degree of
unconditional respect and
love. You don't have to do anything
special to deserve to exist in the way
you wish to. And you don't have to
create guilt. Do you know
what? Many of you think that hate is the
opposite of love. It isn't. It's a
polarity expression.
But guilt is the true opposite of love
because love is absolute deservability,
worthiness, validity, equality. Guilt is
the lack of all those things. Hate still
implies some deservability
somewhere. Understand? So guilt is the exact
Understand? So guilt is the exact
opposite of love. And if you have cut
yourself off in that sense from the love
prime vibration of creation, you start
to
disintegrate. That's what cancer
is. You are always deserving of the flow
of infinite creation. The way you plug
yourself back in, not that you ever
really truly unplug yourself, but you
can think that you have and create that
illusion. Because you are an eternal being. You
Because you are an eternal being. You
know you are infinite and no matter in
what way, shape or form you choose to
exist, you will always exist because you
exist now. No one ever really dies. You
just change
form. So first and foremost, back off
the idea that physical life is the only
expression of life there is. If you
exist now, you always will and you
always have because existence is eternal
now. But allow yourself to dissolve the
But allow yourself to dissolve the
illusion that you are not connected to
infinite creation. Know you deserve all
the love you can
imagine. Infinite creation thinks you do
or it wouldn't have created you. Plug
yourself back into that source and you
will find that energy flowing through
you. And if you use it to do what
excites you the most, you will then be
flowing and sparkling like a solid
crystallin gem. And when you are that
centered and that representative of
living life, no disease can exist within you.
life, no disease can exist within you.
It is not possible.
Does that assist you
exciting dream life and life dream to
you? Remember life is a dream. And once
again, you cannot change what you do not
own. So own it all because you do own it
all. All of it. All of it. All of it.
And when you allow everything, the
positive and the negative, to be
equal, then not any one has any more
power than the other. They're all in the
same level. And then that means it's
easy to choose which one you prefer
because you're not reaching beyond your
reach to get it. You don't have to pull
something up from the depths. It's all
equal, all neutral. Remember this all of
you. All situations and all
circumstances are
fundamentally neutral, empty, blank,
devoid of meaning. Nothing means
anything. You supply the meaning based
upon what you have been taught to
believe it means. The meaning you supply
to a neutral circumstance utterly
determines the effect you get out of it.
Action reaction. Positive meaning in,
positive effect out, negative meaning
in, negative effect
out. Simple
mechanics. So do not automatically
assign a negative meaning just because
your society teaches you to say, "Oh, I
have cancer. That's bad.
for you. It isn't because you decide
what it means because you created it
because you own it. Yes. Thank you for
your suggestion of your definition that
you think it's negative. I choose to
believe it is there for a positive
reason because I choose to believe I am
a positive being. Therefore, all
situations will have a positive effect
on my life. And the quicker I realize
that, you may say to yourself, the
quicker I can dispense with the original
symbol I created to show me to bring me
the opportunity to realize what I am
realizing. Is this sinking
in? You know what else?
I love you.
Thank you for being bold and strong
enough to know you are strong enough to
create that symbol for yourself to work
with. For anyone who chooses that type
of a symbol is doing it out of strength,
not out of weakness, because you know
it's going to drive you very far, very
fast. And that means you know you're
strong enough to do
it. Understand?
So focus on the strength, not the
weakness, because you created it out of
your power, not out of your lack of it. At this
At this
time, allow us once again to extend to
each and every one of you individually
and collectively our utmost
appreciation in allowing us to
experience the unique facets of the
multi-dimensional crystal of all that is
that each and every one of you are.
Shine like the gem that