evening of your time. As you create time
to
exist, allow us to begin this
interaction, this evening of your time
with the idea which may be entitled
[Music] communication. Now, in these
communication. Now, in these
interactions, in these cocreated events,
we have discussed many times the idea of
the identification of the vibration that
is necessary in order for these
interactions to occur. We have discussed
the idea that every being, every
consciousness is a frequency and in
order to be able to communicate with
another being with another consciousness
or that which you would colloquially
refer to as another being or another
consciousness, you must be somewhere
within the range of frequencies that is
similar to the frequency they are
operating on or you cannot even perceive
each other within the idea that you have
created there to three different
universes. You have therefore created
these different universes to be
different by the fact that they are
operating on different frequencies.
Everything is made out of the same one
energy. But different frequencies of
that energy create what you perceive to
be from your point of view different
universes, different realms, different
levels of existence and expressions of
consciousness. So in order for these
interactions to
happen between as you say one level and
another level, there must be some form of
level, there must be some form of
identification, some form of
recognition, some matching of patterns
between the two ideas. So that some
common ground as you say is laid, some
common foundation, some cohesive
atmosphere in which both ideas can
intermesh, interact and link to form a
common understanding of perception and if you
understanding of perception and if you
wish procedure to these communications.
Now we have discussed that this
identification or at least one of the
strongest ways to manifest this
identification is simply through the
opaces of what you call unconditional
love because love what you call love is
quote unquote the prime substance of
creation. It is the energy out of which
all is manifested. When we speak of the
idea of love, we may refer to this idea
from many different points of view and
approach it from many different
directions. But
fundamentally, as always, just as a
reminder, we have perceived that from
time to time, many of you will hear this
word love and you will think we are
discussing some old nice and wonderful
philosophy, some nice way it would be to
exist, some perhaps preferential
attitude, but it is more than that. It
is these, but it is more than that. When
we are discussing the idea of
unconditional love, we are actually
speaking of it as if it is a material, a
substance, a tangible thing because to
us it is. Everything that you call solid
matter, everything that you call energy
and radiant light is love. A version of
the material you call love. It is the
prime core, the prime energy, the prime
etheric substance out of which
everything is crystallized, solidified,
including what you call non-physical
energy. It is a primal substance far
more basic than even what you would call
energy in its most basic form. Because
what you call energy is still your
translation in physical terms. your
ability to interact in physical terms
with that prime substance which I will
not simply call energy since that may be
in your terms
confusing. It is existence
itself. The very if you wish fabric, the
very structure, the very idea of
existence itself, the pulse, the
frequency of creation itself is love.
Therefore, if you wish to bridge any
differences that you have created there
to be between one realm and another, one
dimension and another, the easiest way
to do that is through the door of
unconditional love. Because that
frequency, that vibration in a sense is
the only thing that is common to all
dimensions. because it is what all
dimensions and all beings in those
dimensions are fundamentally made out
of. No matter how they choose to express
it, no matter what limitations they
choose to put on it, it all can be
melted back down into the primal
substance called love.
So the easiest way for any of you to
create communication among yourself to
truly understand each other and be
willing to recognize that each and every
one of you is simply a different point
of view a different crystallization of
the same substance of love. The sooner
you are willing to use that
unconditional love to open yourself in
that way, the quicker you will be able
to understand even what may seem to be
the most radical differences and
perspectives and points of view upon
your planet. You may not necessarily
agree or prefer to manifest in your own
life another's point of view, but you
will understand it. And understanding is
the key. For when you can
understand why all have the point of
view that they do, how that point of
view originated, what particular
originated, what particular
specifications someone may be creating
to define that point of view, you can
always get at the root of meaning, the
meaning you have placed into the
creations in your life. And when you get
at the root of meaning, the root of
definition, then you can unlock those
definitions if it serves you to do so.
You can exchange and trade and examine
these definitions for the tools that
they are.
For because of what you have created
your society to be, many of the
definitions you originally created to
represent certain perspectives have
become locked into the circumstances
themselves. And that's why many of you
think that now the situations that occur
in your life come with built-in meaning
when they actually originally had no
built-in meaning at all. when they are
neutral and blank to begin with. Only
because you have
restricted the ability to recognize the
tool for what it is. Do you assume that
there can be no understanding that you
cannot meet eye to eye that you cannot
in that way agree to
agree to
disagree in loving ways? It can be done.
Each and every one of you could create a
completely different preferential
experiential reality from anyone
else. That does not mean you have to
have war. It does not mean you have to
have pain. It does not mean you have to
have disease just because you prefer
this and they prefer that.
If you begin to recognize that the crux
and the seed of all
communication is in first of all knowing
that everyone else is simply another
point of
view equal to you. And if you are
willing to examine the wise and the
wherefors of that point of view through
love, then any point of view can be changed,
then any point of view can be changed,
can be altered, can be integrated with
any other point of view in a way that
allows each to gain the effect each
desires from that
interaction. Regardless of what anyone
brings into an interaction with
you, whatever your preferences are will
determine what effect you get out of
it. But you can still allow the
interaction. Because only by being open
to all forms of
communication, do you then give yourself
the ability to assess what you are and
what you are not. But also then and only
then do you create the ability to live
in peace with all other points of view.
And only then do you create the ability
to surround yourself and fill your
world, the world you prefer with the
reflections and the experiences that are
representative of the point of view you
prefer most strongly in your life. Therefore,
Therefore,
fundamentally, the why of why we
communicate with you is simply because
we love you. And the how of how we
communicate with you in this way is also
because we love you. That is always the
why and the how of any communication
that takes place. Remember that when you
find yourself perhaps disagreeing with
someone, the fact the very fact that you
can even perceive their point of view at
all means on some level you are
identifying with them. Proceed from that
point of view and anything you would
call a discrepancy will clear itself up
if you trust that on some fundamental
level you are simply different
expressions of the same thing. the same
one thing. Does your left eye argue with
thing. Does your left eye argue with
your
right? It takes both to give you the
depth of vision that allows you to
experience the three-dimensionality of
your
world. We thank
you. And at this timing, in exchange for
the gift of your willingness to share
with us the love that you are, I ask you
now, how may I serve you? Hi, Bashar.
And to you, good night. First, I just
want to say that um my life just keeps
getting simpler and simpler. Oh, no.
And and the simpler it gets, um the
better it gets. Oh, all right. And I
just want to thank you for your
assistance. Oh, thank you for allowing
us to reflect the joy that we simply
found within you. Um, in my new
simplicity, um, in a rather unusual way, I find that
um, in a rather unusual way, I find that
I'm going to be traveling to England.
All right. In the spring. All right. And
it feels very significant to me. All
right. It feels that there are, I'm
sure, ancient ties. All right. Yeah.
[Music] and also possibly some type of
and also possibly some type of
communication involved. I'm sure I will
meet people there. That will be, you
know, exciting. Oh, and that goes
without saying. Yeah, there are exciting
individuals all over your planet.
Yeah. And I'm wondering if you can maybe
give me a couple of
England. You can recapture some of your
nature connection, but in terms you
would have at one time
called incantational. It has to do with
incantational. It has to do with
connections that
you represent by the term magic or
druidic ritual or practice. In that
sense, it is a retracing of the steps,
an unrolling of the scrolls that you are
familiar with in ancient times. It is a
reathering together of past law. A
recognizing as I said of the old
chapters in an old book of your life
just to cause an integration, a
reassessment so you can understand now
the difference between the way you
traveled the road then and the way you
are traveling the road now. Because now
it is far simpler as you have said not
so much ritual is required. So now in
wrapping yourself in the energy vortex
the magnetic vortex of that area in this
light you will be able to see how what
you did back then was much the same
thing but it was cloaked and wrapped in
ritual whereas now it can stand in the
light of day. You follow it? Yes. It is
a very strong strong area
electromagnetically especially for the
idea of ancient Atalantian time after
what you would call the destruction.
I almost got the feeling of um
electromagnetic lay
that is the vortex the magnetic vortex.
There are many around your world. And
again, several areas in your England are
very magnetically conducted, especially
the area that is outlined by the
structure you call your Stonehenge and
many of the other areas that support
those types of foundation. And once
again, one of the strongest areas in
that
entire place on your planet is what you
call the aisle of man. Now, you do not
necessarily have to go there.
And it is not necessarily directly tied
into some of the energies you will be
discovering, but simply it is a magnetic
vortex that does feed the area and adds
to the overall magnetism of that
particular area. Especially once again
with what you call moon
recognition. It is our perception that
this would be something you could get in
touch with very simply this night of
your time. Since it is your night of a
full moon, you will find similar connections
moon, you will find similar connections
to the idea of what you would call lunar
energy. The polarized light of the lunar
energy of your moon in your England area
and many things that have been for a
long time subterranean will rise within
you into the light of your new dawn of
consciousness and awareness so that they
need not be cloaked in ritual and
secrecy anymore. And you can see the
difference between the then and the now.
And that will give you by comparing the
two an insight as to the way and the
direction that you can take it in what
you call your future.
Understand? Yes, I do. Well, thank you.
Um, I just said, will this also have
anything to do with my creat?
Not as strongly now. That may happen in
other places. There will always be some
blending, but
this is more strongly in the direction
of other connections first. When those
foundations are laid, then perhaps it
will accelerate more in some of the
Plleadian directions later.
Thank you very But friend, you sharing.
I love you, Shark. And to you, good
night. For the past 20 years, I have been
For the past 20 years, I have been
healing the physical body. I've had one
death experience, five near-death
experience. How exciting. Yes, indeed. I
What have you learned? I have learned
that I commit each moment to living. All
right. And I want to know if I am overlooking
And I want to know if I am overlooking
anything at this point in assisting what
I call the final healing of my physical
body. Are you doing what excites you the
most in life? Yes, I am. All right,
then. Are you being of service in that
way to others by doing what excites you
the most? Yes, I am. All right, then.
Are you having a good time? Indeed, I
am. All right, then. Continue to live in
the moment as you have learned to do.
There is nothing else that really is
required. Thank you very much. Well, I have
Thank you very much. Well, I have
nothing to do with it. Thank you.
The more you live in the moment, the
more you can function as a reflective
example and a symbol for the idea of the
blending of the physical and the
non-physical reality. For in many cases,
that is what the idea of the near-death
experiences communicated to you where
you were in touch with what you call the
non-physical side. And now by learning
to live in the moment is where you
create the crucible in which the
physical and the non-physical merge,
join and become one dream.
We thank you.
Sure.
And do you good day? How are you?
Perfect. And you all right? Oh, all
right. I have a question for my sister
Tom. Yay. And
uh I guess for about 6 months now she's
been having it's a body thing. Yeah. A
body thing.
She's been having convulsions
and electricity, you know. Okay. And um
a short circuiting of what you call the
neuronic pathway.
Yeah. Well, anyway, her question is she wants
Well, anyway, her question is she wants
to know cuz the doctors she she has a
lot of belief in the doctors, okay, and
they can't find what she's got. So,
she's been passing about 20,000 tests
now, and she just wants to know if you
could spot the uh source in the body
that doesn't function like she would like it
doesn't function like she would like it
to.
How are her dreams? I don't know. I
don't live with her and I don't know
much. Can you ask? Yeah, I can ask her
for sure. There may be much in the way
of information that is coming through in
the dreams that she is not processing
physically. Okay? She may be blocking
some of the information. She may be
fearing what some of the information
represents. She may be causing her own
short circuit to prevent that
information from being understood
consciously. Yeah, she does a lot of um
she has a lot of fear, I guess. Yes. So,
you want me to ask her? That is the only
thing that can be done at this time.
Then what? to allow her to examine the
reasons for why she would be afraid of
that information of the fact that that
information would show her the power
that she has to do what it is she wants
to do.
I don't know is going to like that.
There is no other way we can be of
existence except to recommend that idea.
Great. Thanks. Well, thank you very
much. Bye-bye. Bye-bye.
Shutting. Hello. And to you, good day.
Uh my question is is somewhat similar as
the preceding uh 15 days ago or so. Uh
my mother was diagnosed as having
cancer. All right. And cancer of the
breast and particularly malignant kind
of cancer. Uh she was operated on a few
days ago and they took up they removed
her breast. All right. and um it had
spread since the lymph nodes and so now
the doctors are looking at various
chemotherapy treatments and things like
that. All right. And uh I was wondering
if you could speak to that whole issue
and I'd be very interested and thankful
for any now the idea will always once
again manifest down to the strongest
belief that the individual has and
obviously in what you are referring to
us now in this case the individual has
been brought up with many ideas and
instilled with many beliefs throughout
the childhood and the adulthood of the
individual that may be difficult for
that individual to change. It may be
that that individual will only allow
themselves to go along certain belief
patterns. However, there are many other
However, there are many other
methodologies which can be made
available to individuals upon your
planet that may be more representative
of what an individual may be willing to
do in terms of changing their belief.
And there are some individuals present
this night of your time who have had
similar experiences of late as you say
and can perhaps share some of their
experiences with you in the ability to
transform what you call disease even of
that nature into something that no
longer is manifested in a negative way.
But more often than not a lot of these
ideas of disease and particularly what
you would call cancer have to do with
the ideas that have been ingrained and
fed into individuals in your society all
their lives. And now in dealing with
certain ideas that are coming to the
surface, in not knowing how to process
them, many times they will allow these
ideas to eat away at them through the
idea of invalidations and guilt and
frustration and all sorts of negative
emotional patterns that they have been
fed all their lives. They may know no
other way to process the information
other than deteriorating themselves to a
non-physical state. It does not have to
be that way. It never has to be that
way. But whatever the strongest belief
in the individual is will determine how
easy and or difficult it is for that
individual to transform the idea in a
positive way. If an
individual absolutely can, as you say,
get a handle on why they would believe
they would have to experience the
disease to learn what it is they need to
learn. Then they can learn that
information in other ways and they don't
have to experience it in a negative way.
That's what if they can that's their
choice. That's one of the things that's
been happening. It's been something like
that. It's uh been very
transformational. Yes. For everyone
involved. It's brought a lot of love
presence. Many times an individual will
do that more so even for the individual
around them than for anything they
really need to learn. And they may
simply allow that to be what you call
their last gift before they translate
into non-physical reality when in many
times they will function as spirit
guides for a while for the immediate
family as you say still physically
remaining. It may be that this is the
pattern this individual is setting up.
It may not serve them to circumvent it.
However, once again, the more willing
any individual who is learning something
from it is to get the information and
learn the lessons in a positive way, the
less need there is for the manifestation
in such a limiting, painful and negative
way. She seems very uh willing uh to
way. Our strongest suggestion, however,
simply because of the belief, systems,
and habit patterns that have been
ingrained in that individual, would be
to research out some of the other
methodologies that may be available to
individuals on your planet that you may
simply not be aware of simply because
one particular culture will
disavow the efficiency of a method that
they do not believe in. There are many
ideas of electromagnetism and
electricity and even many other
substances that may be of assistance in
alleviating the negative manifestation
in that individual. And once again,
there are individuals present this
evening of your time who can give you
some suggestions for experiences they
have had that may point you in
directions that will serve you. Thank
you very much. Frank
is and and
and always always always as our
suggestion simply not we are telling you
what to do but always as a suggestion do
not see the individual as
weak. See them as strong. See them as
having had the strength to choose
something so limiting because it takes
strength to do that. So support them.
Send them love. Send them energy. See
the blue white light of the
electromagnetic field in which you are
all immersed beaming to that individual.
See them glowing with radiance.
Reinforce the positive state of their
image, not the negative one. Understand?
Yes. Thank you. Thank you. Shutting
strawberry seed. Oh, perfect.
Thank you. Time to report. It's been
many weeks since we were together as we
count time to be. Yes. As you remember,
my mom was in the hospital with uh a
condition. Yes. You proceeded to give a
very uh poetic and uh beautiful uh
rendition of what was about to occur
there. And I got on a
plane a day
later. The next day I became extremely
pissed with you. All right. Very great
experience. My father called in a heavy
emotional condition stating that the
first thing he said that was that mom is
finished. What? Making me think she had
died for a moment there. Then it was
discovered the exploratory surgery was
done. Cancer was found through our
entire system according to the surgeon.
Right. All through the stomach and all
through the system. Oh. What? I was on a
plane two hours later.
uh worked with a family, handled the
emotional, helped them transform the
emotional conditions they were in and
then met the mom the next day. They had
her hooked up with all kinds of tubes
coming out of her nose and stomach and
so we went through some wonderful
emotional experiences and uh began to
check into power of choice and and uh I
checked into the toolbox that the uh
medical people have which is primarily
chemo and radiation. die. None of them
were willing to use any of those. They
basically said go home and die. All
right. And uh so I had already
formulated a you know various types of
sharings that could occur based on
whether she chose to uh transcend from
this physical or not. Yes. And we went
over that in some detail. Had a
wonderful in-depth emotional experience.
Very good. Made the choice to
uh heal the body. Looked at why for what
reasons? What excitements? What are you
going to do with it? Why heal it? What
for? How you going to use it? Yes. Yes.
That sort of thing. Yes. Yeah. I had a
lot of fun with that one. Oh. And then
uh you know, she decided that well,
we'll clear the junk out of the body,
make a healthy body so that she could
share with her family, which was her
range of excitement that excited her
most. And so, and so we began to develop
the various methods. I began to research
all over the place. uh communicate with
the doctors and uh study their belief
systems and the rigidity and limitation
which they had designed so extremely
well. Yes, we mastered limitation in
that area and uh as I had in a few areas also
area and uh as I had in a few areas also
but began to look at the whole gamut
approach. Good evening
Good evening
Mich. Uh recently I've been doing some
research on a film that has to do with
the dangers of nuclear reactors. And the
more research I do, it almost becomes
staggering to me the the amount of
danger that's present in these things.
And I was wondering if you could just
say something about that.
You may find within what you call the
next 30 of your years that you will have
switched primarily to relying upon
various forms of the generation and
focusing and amplification of
electromagnetic energy for your power
source. Having realized not so much even
just the idea of what you might call the
physiological danger but also the degree
of complexity involved in those
particular mechanisms which is totally
unnecessary to arrive at the levels of
power you require to do anything at all
you wish. The electromagnetic field
around your planet can supply it all. It
is our perception therefore that we
sense this shift taking place within
your recognition as a consciousness
approximately within the next 30 of your
years of counting. Also, as we have
already said, there may be substances
which will appear within the next decade
or two, which will be of a plastic-like
nature, a polymerlike nature, which when
rendered into sheets, actually will have
the property of absorbing what you would
call radioactive particles, thus forming
material out of which you can create
cases to encapsulate what you call
radioactive material, now rendering them
in your terminology harmless.
This is our perception of your energy as
it stands now and seems in the time
track we are reading to be the most
likely way you will manifest your
approach to this particular idea of
power generation. Does that suffice as
an answer for you? Yes, it does. Thank
you. Thank you very much.
I wish her good day to you.
Um, I haven't really thought about my
question because Well, that is all
right. I kind of felt that I should know
what I'm going to ask when I get when I
get here. That is all right. You may
discuss if you wish some idea. That is,
as you say, germaine to you. You do not
need a question to interact with us. In
fact, the more willing you are to create
your questions to be statements of
conviction, the more you will express
your equality with us. Do you have
anything you simply wish to discuss that
delights you beyond anything else? Yes,
go ahead.
Um, there is a possibility in the very
near future for me to form like a
partnership with uh two people. All
right. How exciting will it be to do
something that you are excited about? I
really love to do that. Oh, all right.
Have a good time.
I'm kind of
um not sure. I mean what the purpose of
what we're going to be doing really
excites me. No. All right. Do you then
trust that if this is the thing that
excites you that you are attracting all
the necessary circumstances and
relationships that will enhance the
overall idea or are you sewing doubt
into the process? Exactly. I'm I'm very
certain about the project. I'm in doubt
about the relationships. One moment. Now
we would desire to discuss and examine
the very idea you have just
mentioned. Listen to what you have said.
I have no doubt about the project. I am
in doubt about the
process. Why do you create a difference
between the two? The end is the means.
The means is the end. If you really
understand without a shadow of a doubt
that the project itself represents what
excites you the most and you understand
that the process in getting there, that
the steps in getting there are not
separate from the project but are a part
of the project. Then allow those steps,
whatever they may be, whatever
relationships they may be to be infused
with the certainty of the project
itself. So that you will then have not a
shadow of a doubt that whatever the
steps are that will represent how you
achieve the overall project. The steps
will be extensions of the already
successfully existing project. And you
don't have to wonder if the steps that
are happening are the appropriate steps
to get you to the project you want. If
you do not segregate the steps from the
project itself, you will then allow only
those circumstances that are
representative of the project to occur
in your life. Understand?
Yes. No. Maybe. No, I do understand. And
that's I mean at one level I do
understand. Oh, one moment. One moment.
Here we go again. At one level I
understand it. But on Oh, let's say this
level I don't. Why are you creating there to
I don't. Why are you creating there to
be the idea and the definition that you
have more than one level to understand
it on? Why not simply assume you
understand it on every level you need to
in the way you need to? Why even assume
you have different levels? Why not just
know you do in fact understand it? Do
you really believe in the idea that
excites you? Yes. Then why would you
assume that there would be circumstances
in your life that would have nothing to
do with your ability to do that idea?
Why would you assume you could attract
relationships that would not allow you
to do that idea? You can you can attract
those relationships but only if you
doubt that the process is not a part of
the project.
Okay. The way I see it is yes
the relationships I'm attracting it's
not that they're not going to allow me
to do the project but yeah but what but
but but but meaning there is an
exception right I mean it's like the
project can happen but I may I don't
know maybe some of the people involved
may have a hard time
whatever it is the project is to you
will mean you won't what If you are
clear about what the project is to you,
whether anyone else that is involved has
a hard time or not, you won't.
Well, maybe I'm the one perhaps. But
simply all we are saying is that sit
back and recognize whether you have
attracted the relationships you have
attracted out of doubt or whether you
have attracted them as extensions of
your faith in what excites you. If you
have attracted them out of the doubt
that the process is not a part of the
project, then they may not represent the
idea of the completion of the project.
Get in touch with the definitions on
which you have attracted the
relationships. If you know beyond a
shadow of a doubt that what it is that
excites you the most cannot be anything
but accomplished, then you will also
understand that whomever you attract
into the process will on some level
somehow enhance the whole procedure and
not in your terms delay
it. Understand? Anything that they would
Understand? Anything that they would
choose to have as a difficult time will
not affect your ability to not have a
difficult time. And if an individual
that you have attracted truly isn't the
vibration of the project, they will go
their way. Unless you have attracted
them because you have doubts about the
process, because you have doubts about
your ability to attract the appropriate
process that is a representation of the
project itself. If that is what the
relationship is based on, then there may
be difficulties. But if you understand
that the project, the idea that excites
you is simply sending tendrils out to
you, if you wish to look at it this way,
from the future. And that these tendrils
will be extensions of the project and
will only be the type of tendrils and
relationships that will be indicative of
your ability to do the project. Then you
will see clearly that what you attract
with that faith and with that clarity
will only be tendrils that will lead you
to the project and not away from it. Is
this making any sense to you?
I'm not very sure because the
relationships came before the project.
The idea of the project came afterwards.
So So it's not that I had this project
in mind and then I attracted the right
or it doesn't have to be one before the
other. cause and effect are not
necessarily linear.
Okay. The idea simply is that if the
project is now the most exciting thing,
then assume that the relationships are
details of the project. When the project
did not exist in your mind, then perhaps
the most exciting thing was the
relationship and that was then the
strongest intention and everything else
in your life was a subordinate detail to
that. Now if the existence of the
relationship has thus created a project
which really is to you the most exciting
thing then those relationships are now
details of the project and they are
extensions of it. So trust it if that is
really how it manifested for you if you
recognize it in that way. Understand?
Mhm. Is this making sense to you?
Yeah. I mean, where is your hesitation?
I I don't want to tell you because
you're going to say you're I'm kind of
viewing myself in different levels and I
shouldn't, but I am. Oh, I'm not saying
you shouldn't. I'm saying you don't have
to. Correct. What are you defining to be
the different levels on which you
understand this? Let us clarify the
definition together.
My if I can put it a name like my higher
self or my intuition or my heart yes is
in that project your heart is in the
project right and so what does this mean
to you but like if I start think about
it yes so my analytical mind and
sometimes my emotions or my fears are
what make me hesitate all right and I know
make me hesitate all right and I know
that those are le let's say my heart
it's senior to all those things but I
can just all right ignore it then oh I'm
not telling you to ignore it the idea
then is if that is what you are doing
and you know your heart is there then
focus on the heart and learn what you
need to learn from anything that appears
to be a hesitation in your life or a
fear find out why it's there because if
it is there and you know it's there
because your heart is focused on the
project then whatever fears you are
discovering are things you need to
examine to integrate them within
yourself to become more of the person
who will be the person that is
representative of the one who will do
the project. Those things are there for you
project. Those things are there for you
to discover as parts of the being you
created yourself to be. If there are
levels then the reason you are
discovering them is so that you can
reintegrate them into one idea. So that
they don't have to remain as separate
levels. Whatever fears, whatever
hesitations, whatever analysis you
discover within the process is there for
you to learn
from to learn in a positive way to find
out what it is about this event that is
happening. This fear that you are
creating, this emotional reaction that
you are experiencing. What is it about
this that
belongs in the process of this project?
Because it does belong there obviously
to show you a portion of yourself. You
need to see to integrate it within you
so you can be the person who will be the
person who does the
project. Understand? Mhm. Is this making
sense now? Yeah. Trust your process is
all I am saying.
Yeah, I get that. I have
been trying to trust my process all the
time and that's the point that I do have
a hard time sometimes. Well, that's all
right. If you are having a hard time,
the first step into transforming it into
an easy time is to recognize that you
are choosing to believe it has to be a
hard time. So as soon as you understand,
all right, all right, I'm having a hard
time. That means I am choosing to
believe I need to have a hard time. Why
would I choose
that? What if I have a fun time knowing
I have chosen to have a hard time? What
if I enjoy the idea that I was clever
enough to create the idea of difficulty?
What if I pick that whole definition
apart and scatter it into the wind? What
if I play with the definition of
difficulty? What if I really examine it?
If I'm going to be analytical, why not
go all the way and have it on all
levels? Why not analyze my analysis?
Why not pick it all apart until going
full circle, there's nothing left to
analyze? [Music]
[Music]
What about that approach? Sounds fun.
Sounds fun. All right, then. Maybe
that's your way because remember
everything is a circle in that sense.
And
sometimes the way out is
up. The way out is
in. If you go far enough in one
direction, you'll come back to your
starting point. Perhaps you can handle
your fear that way, your analysis that
way. Don't reject it. If that's what you're
Don't reject it. If that's what you're
doing and you find that it's difficult
to change it, then that's your clue. Go
further into it and then you will
shatter the
illusion. Running from it still means
the reflection is still coming from that
mirror. Trying to back away from it
means that you can still see that
reflection of
fear. If that keeps happening when you
move this way, then move this way. Go
through it. Break it apart. Crash
through the illusion in the mirror and
then it will be
gone. Understand?
Mhm. Does that serve you? Yes. Yes, it
does. All right. Pleasant dreams. Thank
you. Thank you very much.
Good day, Bashar. Andrew, you good day.
Oh, or good evening, whichever it is.
I'm not I'm never sure. All right. Maybe
you should take a look outside. Well, I
know what it is here. I don't know what
it is on. Well, it is various times
around different portions of the planet,
isn't it? Just like yours. What is it
where you are now in my craft in orbit?
It is daylight. Ah, then good day. Thank
you. That is why I've been saying good
day. Just checking. Thank you. I have a short
Just checking. Thank you. I have a short
sharing and then a question. Short
sharing. Yes. I took a little visit to
the spaceship today. Here, can you hear
me? Um
Okay. I was playing the tape from last
week this morning. And I lay down on the
rug in the sun and closed my eyes and
took that trip again to your ship, the
Solar Wind. I love that name. It excites
me. All right. And in the middle of
that, the first time I heard it, I loved it.
the first time I heard it, I loved it.
It has such a vation. Continue. So, I
was lying there um visiting your ship
and I felt my little cat come actually
he's he's rather large and he came over
and he lay down beside me and got as
close to me as he could and I felt that
he was there with me on the ship sharing
that experience. I was very touched. I
got the feeling that he wanted to be
there too. Anyway, I thought I would
share that with you. Thank you. Also, my
question now is about um I talked
to an entity through a channel last
Monday night from
uh Atlantis that said who who gave his
name as
Aron and said he is a light crystal
master from Atlantis. And since I have a
very strong Atlantean connection, I ask
about that. And he had something to say about
that. And he had something to say about
a group that I used to belong to or
participate in. Seven of
in. Seven of
13. What does that mean?
13 is the transformational number as
many of you know, especially when it
comes to the idea of bringing to the
surface many of the things you have
suppressed or placed in your unconscious
or subconscious self. And therefore in
your society very often is represented
in a fearful quote unquote superstitious
way. 13 is the transformational number
especially the door between physical and
non-physical reality. Seven of 13 to some degree is a
reality. Seven of 13 to some degree is a
recognition of the accomplishment or the
awareness of having created harmony with
the idea of transformation.
I like that.
Can you say anything more about that
particular lifetime or lifetimes or
connections with Atlantis?
Only that there is strong connection as
you already know to interaction with
dolphin consciousness then as well as
now. Yes, I do know. Will that serve
him? I guess it'll have
I guess it'll have
to. Close mouth sometimes for sure.
especially with those quote unquote that
know better.
All right, I accept that. Remember this,
for I will give you a
hint. The easiest way to allow me to
carry on like a
chatterbox is to make statements rather
than ask questions.
Yes, I do know that. When you have the
conviction to state what you believe is
true for you, then we may comment. We
may function as a guide to steer here
and there and discuss in open ways the
various aspects that you have awakened
to in your own recognitions of self. But
the more you ask, the smaller the mouth
becomes. The more you share as an equal
what you feel moves you as an energy,
the more excited we get and the more we
desire to discuss it with you as an
equal. That's your hint.
That's not a hint. That is a revelation.
Oh, all right. We thank you very much.
Thank you very much. And next time I
want to talk to you about orca energy.
Oh, all right. I will pay wrapped
attention and Japan. All right. Thank
you. Thank you.
Sharing Shakashini.
Shakashimi. Shakashimi. 13. 13. Yes. I'm
13 tonight. Oh. All right. Happy
birthday. Thank you. Thank you.
Uh, a couple of weeks ago we talked
about being a thousand times more
excited. Thousand times. Yes. And you
want to talk about a million times
tonight? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. All
right. All right. All right. All right.
Uh, my experience of being a thousand
times more
excited now and growingly is feeling
more and more a thousand times more at
peace. Yes.
The idea once again, as we have said, is
that when you are infinitely accelerated
and everywhere at once, it feels like
you're standing perfectly still. Because
you're everywhere. It's lovely.
everywhere. It's lovely.
Yes. Thank you. You're welcome. Thank
you, Sherry.
Hello, Ashar. Good day to you.
Um in reading your new metaphysics
handbook, I I was looking to these five
levels of uh
energies starting from existence, then
knowing beliefs, belief, emotion, and
thought mentality. Uh I always thought
that mentality was senior to emotions.
There are a few different semantic
definitions to this idea. To some
degree, it is. When we say thought, we
are actually talking about the
analytical framework that more often
than not many of you think of as your
thought process. The one that is the
last stage before you create a
perception of the physical reality. We
are not talking about mentality as a
whole. We are simply referring to the
idea of thought itself. The mentality to
some degree you are referring to is more
connected to the belief knowing
state understand more or less it is
simply a different definition a
different semantic of the idea. All
right. In in the in the way you organize
these levels, they are seniority. I mean
beliefs comes before emotion, emotional
and then mentality, right? Thoughts.
Thoughts. Yes. Thoughts. Okay. Classical
thoughts. The way you think in physical
terms. Now I've been having this
difficulty in relating to belief
systems. Yes. Uh for me equates a lot to
mentality to to thoughts. Well, that is
what we have said. Mentality. Yes.
Because mentality is the primal
intersection of your consciousness with
the electromagnetic field of your
planet. It is the first physical
introduction. Mentality is created when
you as a consciousness interact with or
as what you call a physical dimension.
But thoughts, the way they process out
are the last phase of mentality. The
type of mentality you are talking about
is
also the idea the overall idea which
fractionates down into belief, emotion
and thoughts in the classical sense.
Understand? In other words, mentality is
the same as awareness itself.
Okay? And then it fractionates down into
the beliefs, the emotions and the
thoughts. So in this case what you are
calling mentality is actually more akin
to the knowingness stage of our
definition. All right. If if you really
want to change uh the reality you are
experiencing you have to go and change
your belief system basically. Basically
yeah okay now how do you do that? Do you
have a recipe uh to work with? Because
you see for me uh belief system are like
energy statements. Yes, they are. All
right. But for for me it's difficult to
get to that energy statement. That's a
belief. Uh okay. Why do you believe it
is difficult? Well, because I can relate
more to my thoughts. I can I can I can
uh Oh, one moment. One moment. One
moment. You can work it from any of the
three directions if you really want to.
If that works for you, you can change an
emotion and change your reality and
change your beliefs and thoughts. You
can change your thoughts and change your
emotions and your beliefs. You can
change your beliefs and change your
emotions and change your thoughts. You
can work it from any direction. If one
of them seems more workable to you as a
direction, then simply come from that
direction. You do not necessarily have
to in the classical sense use the actual
belief state first. You can work it
quote unquote backwards. Thank you very
much. Oh, thank you. The [Applause] [Applause]
sharing one
moment before we continue let us give
one more brief analogy to the idea of
belief, emotion and thought. Remember
you can use the analogy of a prism. It
is a threesided prism.
If you change any of the sides, the
belief, the emotion, the thought, that
alters how the white light of your
mentality or your knowingness comes
through the prism and determines what
kind of spectrum, the physical reality
you create. So you can change any of the
sides and it will change the spectrum.
Thank you. Continue.
That's encouraging what you just said.
Oh, thank you. Um, it's nice meeting
you, Bashar. and you as well. Thank you.
We thank you for co-creating this
interaction. Do proceed. Um I recently
started a business and Oh, how exciting.
Yes, it is. Um I know that I've created
this before. Oh, what? And
um want to Not in the same way, of
course. Okay. Not in the same way. And
and believe I'll probably be creating it
again. Um, again when
you mean in a future life? Yes. Well,
all right. But you're living this life
now. Okay. Let's focus on this one. I've
been experiencing a lot of deja vu. And
that's what Very good. Exciting. It
means you are becoming consciously aware
of your non-physical
consciousness. You are blending the two
levels of physicality and
non-physicality of the physical dream
and the non-physical dream. More often
than not, although it can be many, aja
vu is when in your dream reality, you
have created a particular scenario that
you wish to play out in your physical
reality, but don't want to know you
created that scenario until you have
spontaneously played it through. After
you play it through, you can remember
you created in your dream reality first
and you have the memory you call deja vu
or the overlap of the physical and the
non-physical. When you are literally
consciously existing in what you call
physical and non-physical plains
simultaneously or let's say when you are
aware of the fact that you already exist
in physical and non-physical planes
simultaneously. That's a deja vu. Mhm.
Not only is it already something you
have seen in your dream state, it is a
form of what you might call
doubledimensional vision. Okay. Is it
viewing a simultaneous existence? Yes.
Okay. In your terminology, it would seem
as if it has already happened. Yes.
Because you in your linear terms already
planned it out in your dream. But yes,
it is still simultaneous. That is why it
is absolutely double vision. Mhm.
Um, I wanted to ask your feelings about
what you see in the future with respect
to this business. Well, does it excite
you? Very much. Well, what do you see?
It is your business. I I have been
seeing lately resistance on my part. Ah,
does that excite you? No. All right. Why
do you have resistance to what do you
have resistance?
Success. Why? Fear of what?
Success. Why? What is your definition of success?
Why? What is your definition of success?
Let's clarify. What do you imagine will
be success to you? Receiving. Receiving.
You don't like to
receive. Do you like to give?
They're both the same, aren't they? I I
appear the I feel that I do like to give
and that it's easier to give than
receive. And yet I see them both as
being opposite sides of the co of the
same coin. Well, basically, but they're
not even really opposites in that sense.
Mhm. Now, you say you have for now more
of a propensity to give than to be able
to receive yet. Exactly. All right. But
do you understand that allowing others
to give is one of the greatest gifts you
can give?
Yes. Does that tie them together for
you? It helps me a great deal because
when you allow others to give to you,
then you are allowing them to reflect
your own abundance. Mhm. You are
allowing them to serve. Would you not
want them to be just as fulfilled as you
are? Yes, I would. Then let them give.
You deserve it. And so do they. Does
that help? Yes, a great deal. Thank you
very much. Thank you. Thank you. Thank
you. Thank you. Loving, loving, loving
heart. Thank you. Thank you. Shutting.
Good evening. Good day to you.
A week ago, I was in Washington DC, not
even contemplating coming to California.
Oh, surprise, surprise.
Indeed. And I didn't know that you
existed in body or out of body until
yesterday. Ah, I exist in my own body.
Yes, indeed. And I'm delighted to have the
indeed. And I'm delighted to have the
opportunity to share some of your
thoughts this evening. Always delighted
to share your own.
Yes. I believe that
uh the label that's placed on people who
are quote mentally ill, okay, is an
erroneous label. It is misleading to
some degree. Yes. That psychosis is
merely another state of consciousness.
Basically, when it becomes in your
definitional sense, negative is
generally when it becomes a closed loop,
feeding itself perhaps in a negative
spiral simply because those individuals
have never been taught that the
different levels of dimensionality they
originally perceived were something they
could communicate back and apply to the
society in which they exist. because the
society rejects their visions. They
close themselves off and become locked
in that self-fulfilling spiral. That's
the only thing that creates it to be a
negative idea. And unfortunately, our
society uh
views people who have been in
institutions or whether they well
whatever their length of stay might be.
Yes. And we're very prejudiced to for
people that have been in the middle. But
that is changing. Your definitions are
changing. Yes. Your ability to even
discuss this shows that to be so. Sure.
Well, and the fact that uh you know I
was in that state six years ago myself.
Well, how exciting. It
was very What did you learn? Yes. I I
think so. You know, I learned that
um that I Well, my peers were based upon
the fact that my mother had been a
schizophrenic and labeled such and my
father an alcoholic. Right. And so you
got lost in the labels. And I after well
it took me about 45 years to create the
condition uh so that I could experience
it myself. Oh all right.
And at that time I was uh functioning as
a school principal and so two years
later when I was so recovered uh you
know I went on public record about it.
This was in uh Northern Virginia. Yay.
And that helped me to get an early
retirement from the school
system. Oh. All right. I hadn't planned
that but that's okay. Okay. So now I
spend a great deal of my time and
resources in working as a volunteer with
schizophrenic or manic depressives.
Well, thank you. Yes. And while here in
California, I was introduced just uh
yesterday and today to u crystal bowls
that I understand that this channel gave
the formula for. Not completely. No.
Okay. We simply assisted to some degree,
made certain recommendations, certain
guidances, but the idea arose from
within your own society. Okay. However
that may be, it's occurred to me that
that they the sound vibrations. Oh, yes.
Yes. Yes. And may be of great assistance
in helping to uh rebalance, regground,
whatever termology you want to use.
people who are still
who are still
unst and I wonder if you would have any
other u what well you know what to do
you know when you feel the core that
hits you that strikes you can allow any
individual to pick the one that strikes
them the strongest that's the one that's
representative of their signature
vibration the core vibration allow them
to identify with it to match its
frequency and they will bring themselves
elves back to center. Immerse them in
that sound, in loving laughter and
light. They will center themselves.
Immerse them in that atmosphere. It will
create what you call a field around them
that will then unlock them from the
other realities they have been locked
into and give them the time and the
opportunity to reassess where they are
and what they wish to plug into once
they center themselves.
people who
are in halfway houses, adult homes or
whatever that uh are I think suffering
partially from incorrect nutrition, lack
of exercise,
lack of caring etc. Yeah. Do you think
it's essential to change that
environment before introducing
uh the sound vibrations as a way to help
them balance? Well, not necessarily. It
will depend upon the individual. Go with
your intuition and your instinct. Each
individual will be different because
they have a different belief system
about what will work first and what will
work next. Trust your instinct with
every individual. It will always help to
do as many of them simultaneously as you
can to create as many changes in as many
of the quote unquote negative
environments as you can into whatever
you think is more representative of a
centered and balanced vibration. Let me
be sure all I'm not quite certain I
understood. You say do as many of them
as you can. Are you speaking of in other
words what you call nutrition what you
call your living environment what you
call light color yeah I just wasn't
clear if you were talking about
individuals as many of them as
individuals or the pro that too that's
up to you that it could work with
several not necessarily one well let me
put it this way if you sit yourself down
in a particular room with an individual
who in your terminology is eating
something beneficial to their belief
system and you are playing your bowl for
them, all well and good. If you are
sitting down on a stage and playing your
bowl for 10,000 individuals, all sitting
there nibbling something that they find
beneficial to their belief system as a
concert, all well and good. Whatever
level you wish to operate on, it's up to
you. Do you see
Do you see
uh hypnotherapy
andor energy disposition things are
tools. Yes. With
integrity, use anything you believe is
representative of your desire to be of
service. And that means you will do it
in a positive way. They are all tools.
Yes, I accept that. Do you do are there
other tools that I am not your
imagination that I'm not consciously
aware? is your imagination.
When they need to be made aware to you,
they will be. Whatever you are aware of
now, work with that. As soon as you
start working with what you have, you
will create the momentum that will
generate inspiration within you and you
will get
more. Understand? Yeah. It's like I
really am on the edge of the uh the pool
and I haven't dove in. They will all
always be on the edge of another pool.
Yes, jump in. Yes, there will always be
another place to jump.
Use what you have. And that is what
allows there to be the space for more
tools to come in. Certainly. Although
paradoxically you may find that the
tools will get simpler and simpler and
fewer and fewer and you will be working
more directly with just energy energy
energy identification directly
communication communication which is the
title of this interaction. I believe
that I personally am clear enough to do
this work now without
uh undo influence or interference by my
own ego. All right. Then have a
wonderful time and we thank you for your
willingness to be of service in the way
you have chosen to. And we thank you for
sticking to your principle.
And thank you. And I must say that uh
it's a joy to interact with you. Uh I've
been accustomed to working with uh
people such such as yourself but who did
not allow their sense of humor to come
forth as you do and I've enjoyed this
evening very much. We cannot help but
always find ourselves laughing over our
interactions with all of you.
We thank you for allowing us to express
and for returning our joy sharing.
Hello Bashar. Hello wizard.
I am here to extend uh some more
communication at the wizard level. Yeah.
And uh I don't know what to say about
it. Well say it away wizardwood. Uh,
Haro. All right. Uh, trying to put into
effect some of the things that you've
been discussing. Try try try try try.
Yes. As I was doing. Yes. I was thinking
of levitating in wizard fashion. So,
here we go. [Music]
Are you having a good time? Yeah.
Where do you wish to take this?
Well, part of me has levitated and part
of me is still on the ground. I see.
50/50 proposition. Well, it's almost
that way. Um the last time um we
interacted at this level I felt very
good during it and afterward and this is
the main reason for my being here again.
And it's been some time since we've
interacted full wizard level and I would
welcome some input from you at this time
about this
process. What is in a sense levitation
but
enlightenment but acceleration but
ascension of all the vibration of the
entire vibration that you
are. Although do remember that for the
purpose of many of your interactions
with many other individuals to awaken
their wizard, you will appear to remain
firmly grounded. So they will take you
grounded. So they will take you
seriously.
[Laughter]
You follow along? Yes, I do. I follow
along. Oh, thank you. Does this serve
you? Yes, it does. Good to see you
again, wizard. Thank you for your
laughter and your light. And thank
you at this
timing. We extend once again to each and
every one of
you our unconditional love and we thank
you for allowing us to communicate in
our own way this idea to you. We remind
you your way is just as beautiful. We
thank you for allowing it to be
experienced by all of
us. Loving
dreams. We are the sharing that
continues forever. Good day.
At any given moment, do what excites you
the most with full integrity and full
trust. That's all it takes. Because as
we have already discussed previously,
now whatever is going on now is the most
important thing in your life or
something else would be happening.
Whatever it is that's going on now is
the most important thing. Be excited
about that. Learn from it. Use the
moment fully.
Allow yourself with integrity to act to
act on any opportunity that presents
itself to you at any given moment that
represents the most exciting thing you
could be doing. Just take it a step at a
time. We are not saying you have to come
up with something that when you think of
it, you find trumpets blaring and
lightning flashing. That can happen for
anything really. But the whole idea is
to simply recognize when this
interaction is finished, whatever it is
you decide at this moment with integrity
will be the most exciting thing you want
to do, do it. It will lead you into the
circumstances to give you the capability
to do the next most exciting thing that
will come along and the next one and the
next one, the more expanded ones.
Because excitement is a thread and it
leads to all other excitement and it is
an upward spiral that increases the
opportunity to experience even more
excitement if you think you can stand
it. I will which many of you don't think you
I will which many of you don't think you
can.
So all we are saying is do what excites
you right now. Okay. On that I have a
two-part question. And one I just
realized um what does not excite me and
what seems to be very monstrous in my
life is monstrous. Yes. Is re is um
organization. Organization. Organizing yourself so
Organization. Organizing yourself so
that you can do the things that excite
you. A but you see if you really are
doing something that excites you what
you call discipline comes automatically
because you want to do it. And because
you really want to do it, you will
automatically see whatever structure is
necessary to allow you to do it most
effortlessly. And you will then simply
put that into play. Because as your own
world says, a labor of love is no labor
at all. The idea of organization and
discipline do not have to be rigidized
and limiting ideas. No. When you do
something you really love to do, you
automatically want to do it in a way.
You automatically draw yourself to doing
it in a way that allows it to fall
automatically in place and it
self-organizes. When you truly do what
excites you, you will simply find
yourself drawn to the circumstances that
need to happen in the next proper order.
Well, sometimes there are little things
that you need to do that don't excite
you. Understand there is always always
Understand there is always always
always a way to create what you really
need in an exciting way. Always. And if
you do not think there is, then that's
the limitation of your definition. No, I
understand what you're saying. All
right. Okay. I'm just thinking about all
the little organizing things I have to
do. You want to do, not have to do. You
see how you are defining it. If you say
I have to do it, it becomes drudgery. If
you understand that you will want to do
the ones that are representative of what
excites you, then it will be exciting.
And you will only find the ones that
excite you that need doing. The ones
then that don't excite you won't really
need doing. But the ones that really allow
doing. But the ones that really allow
you to organize it in the way you want
to in an exciting way will be done in a
similar exciting fashion. You may also
be assuming that certain styles of
organization are necessary when they may
not be. Many times a spontaneous action
will in and of itself eliminate quote
unquote whole reams of organization that
may be necessary to another person that
is taking it step by step in a very
rigidized way. You may simply arrive at
a conclusion and do away with the need
for all sorts of preliminary
organization going on to the next step
automatically. But whatever truly needs
to be there to help organize the idea if
you really know you are doing the most
exciting thing you could be doing then
everything that goes with it will also
be exciting and whatever it is you need
to do will come to you in an exciting
way. So you will want to do it because
even the process will be exciting. Look
at it in a childlike way with childlike
fascination. There are no boring
situations only bored minds.
Okay. Agreed. Now, if I want to do what
excites me and right now I find that
what excites me is sharing what I am
with other people. then do in this
energy I would I would ask your help in
I'm looking for employment now and
everything that I've come across um is
not in that what do you see yourself doing
in that what do you see yourself doing
that you would really enjoy doing what
picture do you have of yourself that you
can see that would then allow you to
appear happy in that picture as you are
interacting with other people basically
working in metaphysics andor helping
people in any particular Okay.
To be happier or to see that there are
possibilities. Yes. But do you mean
simply that the method that will be
happiest for you will simply be to talk
to them or will it involve something
else? Is the talking sufficient
at this point? Um I think it would have
to be sufficient. Oh, one moment now.
One moment. Not have to be. What really
is the full picture that you are not
sharing? What do you really see yourself
doing? I am talking for now in playing
this game with me. Don't include your
judgments or invalidations of the
picture based on what you think you can
and cannot do. Just give me the whole
picture. What do you really see yourself
doing that you know would be very
exciting? How do you see yourself doing
it? The picture is to give people their
The picture is to give people their
power. And what do you see yourself
doing? How do you see yourself doing
that? Describe the full picture. Use all
your senses. I'm okay. I am like you
said to the lady before me, see the end
result. That's what I'm seeing. Then
describe it to me.
What do you see as the end result?
That is the end result. Give me a
description of the person. Yes. of
everything. You are now finished
interacting with an individual or you
are interacting with an individual.
Describe where you are. Describe what
you feel, what you see, what you hear,
what you taste, what you smell, the
colors around you, the location on your
planet. What day is it? What kind of day
is it? It's Thursday and the sun is
shining. All right. Okay. Where are you?
New Mexico. All right. Is that a guess?
No, that's what I'm sensing. Thank you.
Okay. And describe the interaction that
you are having or have just had. What is
the result of this interaction? [Music]
[Music]
Don't think about it. Just describe it.
Um, it's a healing process where I'm
giving energy and love, light, wisdom.
Yes. How? How? Physically describe
it. Are you talking? Are you touching?
Are you painting? Are you writing? How?
Physically describe it. Um, touching,
talking.
Yes. Yes. Yes. You find this exciting?
Yes. All right. Then get into it. Sound
like you're excited about it. You don't.
Yeah. At this Okay. At this moment, it
seems like it's something I haven't
reached yet.
Why? Just because you haven't done it
before, not in this lifetime. So what?
If you can imagine it, that's who you
are right now. If you will allow
yourself to believe that's who you are,
if you really can allow yourself, and
here's the crux, to believe that what
you can imagine you want to be is who
you are now, you will then have a
completely different outlook. and the
completely different outlook will
attract to your site the different
opportunities that will allow you to
take advantage of them to lead you in
those directions. The only reason you
are not seeing the path clearly is
because you don't believe you actually
are that person yet. Correct.
Oh, you know what time it is now. It's
time for Threshold of
believability. One of my favorite
interactions. Are you ready to play?
Yes. All right. Do I have all the necessary
All right. Do I have all the necessary
parts? Absolutely. Okay. Beyond a shadow
of a doubt. Now, this image of yourself.
Oh, first of all, let me ask you, will
you be honest with me in your answers?
Yes. Thank
you. Will you be honest with yourself?
Yes. All All
[Music]
right. Have the image again of the you
you want to be. Have you got it? Yes.
All right. Now, I will ask you a series
of questions. Do not think about the
answer. Just answer yes or no. All
right. Yes.
This person you say you want to be with
all the abilities and all the
skills doing the thing you say you want
to do that you believe would be very
exciting and be very rewarding. this
person. Do you believe really believe
honestly believe beyond a shadow of a
doubt without a second thought that
within what you call 40 of your years
you will be that person before 40 of
your years are up somewhere between now
and 40 years will you have already
become that person?
Yes. All right. I just made that
decision. All right. Now, do you really
believe beyond a shadow of a doubt that
somewhere between now and 30 of your
years hence that will be enough time for
you to become that person?
Yes, you're sure now I'm working on it.
Working on it. Then you're hesitating
right now.
As soon as you start
hesitating, as soon as you do not
believe, as soon as you are not sure
that that's enough time to become that
person, that's your first indication of
exactly how long it will take. The
hesitation was because the original
answer was no, but I want but I want to
do that. I feel Why was the original
answer no?
Then then thank you for being honest.
Why do you think it will require more
than 40 years to become the person you
want to be to do those things you see
that you really want to do? Probably the
basis because it took me 40 years to to
get to this point. Ah, that's Don't you
believe in acceleration? Yes. This year
has been an acceleration. Then must it
take 40 years? No. All right. Must it
take 30 years? No. I realize it could
happen in an instant if if you could
believe that that it is so correct. As
soon as you understand the following
simple idea, if you have the ability to
idea, if you have the ability to
conceive of it, that's who you are right
then and there. All you have to do is
start relating to it. Be that energy
because the moment you conceive of it,
the moment you create it, that's you.
Okay. A couple all you have to do is
start acting like it. a couple of days
ago or a week ago, whatever it was. Yes.
I I felt that I am more than I can that
I am so much more than I am now. And I
want to be that. But you are. And the
easiest way to be that is when you have
a recognition that you are that much
more is to start acting like whatever
degree of that much more you can act
like and to not hold back on yourself
because you are waiting to be that
person. Be that person now. whatever
degree of it you can be now and it will
make it happen that much more quickly to
be the fuller extent. But do remember
you will never stop growing. You will
never become absolutely finished and
done. Are you going to wait until you're
Are you going to wait until you're
absolutely finished and done before you
start? You'll never start. No, I have
started. I know that. Oh, very good.
Yeah. Then why not continue in whatever
way you really really want to in
whatever way it really excites you to
continue. There will always be more to
discover. There will always be more to
learn. Just by fully being whatever you
can imagine you want to be now, that
doesn't mean you'll use it all up all at
once. It doesn't mean there won't be any
more to be. Okay. But I was asking you
in in your,
for lack of a better term, overview, am
I looking in the wrong area of the city?
Is there a better area? Is there just
why did you give me the location that
you did? Because I'm questioning that
about 5 minutes ago I started thinking
about that. And what did you think? I
thought I would ask you why did you say
the location to begin with?
It's kind of a little um yes dry for
lack of a better term. And do you find
that attractive?
No, but I hadn't thought about it really
before. All right. But what is it you
found attractive enough about it to say
its name? Why did you picture yourself being
name? Why did you picture yourself being
in that type of an environment in the
scenario I asked you to create? Oh, that
was in and I don't know. That's what
came. All right. Well, how does it feel
when you think about that area? It feels
good. It feels good. Why? Because I'm
supposed to be there. I guess it's
perhaps. Yes. That's your best clue.
Mhm. And if you give yourself the
opportunity in creating a vision of who
you want to be, if you give yourself an
opportunity to actually see a literal
environment that you know exists and
that really strikes a chord within you,
then what are you doing where you are?
Go to where that environment is because
obviously you are giving yourself the
understanding that that's a more
conducive and reflective and
representative environment for who it is
you say you want to be. So why not
surround yourself with all the
accutrants of the things that represent
who you really want to be rather than
continuing to surround yourself with the
accutrants of a person you don't want to
be? Makes sense to me. Well, thank you.
Makes sense to me. Well, thank you.
Makes sense to me, too. I ask one more
thing. I have this little stone someone
gave me, and I'm just curious what it's
good for. Purpose.
Someone else will help you with that.
Okay. We thank you very much. Thank you.
At this timing, you may all enjoy a
short break. We'll resume contact in
approximately 10 of your minutes. [Applause] Continue. Good evening,
Good evening,
Mich. Uh, recently I've been doing some
research on a film that has to do with
the dangers of nuclear reactors. And the
more research I do, it almost becomes
staggering to me the the amount of
danger that's present in these things.
And I was wondering if you could just
say something about
that. You may find within what you call
the next 30 of your years that you will
have switched primarily to relying upon
various forms of the generation and
focusing and amplification of
electromagnetic energy for your power
source. having realized not so much even
just the idea of what you might call the
physiological danger but also the degree
of complexity involved in those
particular mechanisms which is totally
unnecessary to arrive at the levels of
power you require to do anything at all
you wish the electromagnetic field
around your planet can supply it all. It
is our perception therefore that we
sense this shift taking place within
your recognition as a consciousness
approximately within the next 30 of your
years of counting. Also, as we have
already said, there may be substances
which will appear within the next decade
or two which will be of a plasticlike
nature, a polymerlike nature, which when
rendered into sheets actually will have
the property of absorbing what you would
call radioactive particles, thus forming
material out of which you can create
cases to encapsulate what you call
radioactive material now rendering them
in your terminology harmless.
This is our perception of your energy as
it stands now and seems in the time
track we are reading to be the most
likely way you will manifest your
approach to this particular idea of
power generation. Does that suffice as
an answer for you? Yes, it does. Thank
you. Thank you very much Charing.
Hi. Good day to you.
Um, I haven't really thought about my
question because Well, that is all
right. I kind of felt that I should know
what I'm going to ask when I get when I
get here. That is all right. You may
discuss if you wish some idea that is,
as you say, germaine to you. You do not
need a question to interact with us. In
fact, the more willing you are to create
your questions to be statements of
conviction, the more you will express
your equality with us. Do you have
anything you simply wish to discuss that
delights you beyond anything else? Yes.
Go ahead.
[Music] Um, there is a possibility in the very
Um, there is a possibility in the very
near future for me to form like a
partnership with two people. Well, all
right. How exciting will it be to do
something that you are excited about? I
really love to do that. Oh, all
right. Have a good time.
I'm kind of
um not sure. I mean what the purpose of
what we're going to be doing really
excites me. No. All right. Do you then
trust that if this is the thing that
excites you that you are attracting all
the necessary circumstances and
relationships that will enhance the
overall idea or are you sewing doubt
into the process? Exactly. I'm I'm very
certain about the project. I'm in doubt
about the relationships. One moment. Now
we would desire to discuss and examine
the very idea you have just
mentioned. Listen to what you have said.
I have no doubt about the project. I am
in doubt about the
process. Why do you create a difference
between the two? The end is the means.
The means is the end. If you really
understand without a shadow of a doubt
that the project itself represents what
excites you the most and you understand
that the process in getting there, that
the steps in getting there are not
separate from the project but are a part
of the project. Then allow those steps
whatever they may be, whatever
relationships they may be to be infused
with the certainty of the project
itself. So that you will then have not a
shadow of a doubt that whatever the
steps are that will represent how you
achieve the overall project, the steps
will be extensions of the already
successfully existing project. And you
don't have to wonder if the steps that
are happening are the appropriate steps
to get you to the project you want. If
you do not segregate the steps from the
project itself, you will then allow only
those circumstances that are
representative of the project to occur
in your life. Understand?
Yes. No. Maybe. No, I do understand. And
I mean at one level I do understand. Oh,
one moment. One moment. Here we go
again. At one level I understand it. But
on Oh, let's say this level I don't. Why
are you creating there to be the idea
and the definition that you have more
than one level to understand it on? Why
not simply assume you understand it on
every level you need to in the way you
need to? Why even assume you have
different levels? Why not just know you
do in fact understand it? Do you really
believe in the idea that excites you?
Yes. Then why would you assume that
there would be circumstances in your
life that would have nothing to do with
your ability to do that idea? Why would
you assume you could attract
relationships that would not allow you
to do that idea? You can you can attract
those relationships but only if you
doubt that the process is not a part of
the project. Okay. Okay. The way I see
it is, yes,
the relationships I'm attracting, it's
not that they're not going to allow me
to do the project, but yeah, but what
but but but but meaning there is an
exception, right? I mean, it's like the
project can happen, but I may I don't
know maybe some of the people involved
may have a hard time.
Whatever it is the project is to you
will mean you won't. What if you are
clear about what the project is to you
whether anyone else that is involved has
a hard time or not you won't.
Well, maybe I'm the one perhaps. But
simply all we are saying is that sit
back and recognize whether you have
attracted the relationships you have
attracted out of doubt or whether you
have attracted them as extensions of
your faith in what excites you. If you
have attracted them out of the doubt
that the process is not a part of the
project, then they may not represent the
idea of the completion of the project.
Get in touch with the definitions on
which you have attracted the
relationships. If you know beyond a
shadow of a doubt that what it is that
excites you the most cannot be anything
but accomplished, then you will also
understand that whomever you attract
into the process will on some level
somehow enhance the whole procedure and
not in your terms delay
it. Understand? Anything that they would
Understand? Anything that they would
choose to have as a difficult time will
not affect your ability to not have a
difficult time. And if an individual
that you have attracted truly isn't the
vibration of the project, they will go
their way. Unless you have attracted
them because you have doubts about the
process. Because you have doubts about
your ability to attract the appropriate
process that is a representation of the
project itself. If that is what the
relationship is based on, then there may
be difficulties. But if you understand
that the project, the idea that excites
you is
simply sending tendrils out to you, if
you wish to look at it this way, from
the future. And that these tendrils will
be extensions of the project and will
only be the type of tendrils and
relationships that will be indicative of
your ability to do the project. Then you
will see clearly that what you attract
with that faith and with that clarity
will only be tendrils that will lead you
to the project and not away from it. Is
this making any sense to you?
I'm not very sure because the
relationships came before the project.
The idea of the project came afterwards.
So So it's not that I had this project
in mind and then I attracted the right.
It doesn't have to be one before the
other. cause and effect are not
necessarily linear. Okay, the idea simply is is that
linear. Okay, the idea simply is is that
if the project is now the most exciting
thing, then assume that the
relationships are details of the
project. When the project did not exist
in your mind, then perhaps the most
exciting thing was the relationship and
that was then the strongest intention
and everything else in your life was a
subordinate detail to that. Now if the
existence of the relationship has thus
created a project which really is to you
the most exciting thing then those
relationships are now details of the
project and they are extensions of it.
So trust it if that is really how it
manifested for you if you recognize it
in that way. Understand? Mhm. Is this
making sense to you?
Yeah. I mean where is your hesitation?
I I don't want to tell you because
you're going to say you're I'm kind of
viewing myself in different levels and I
shouldn't but I am. Oh, I'm not saying
you shouldn't. I'm saying you don't have
to. Correct. What are you defining to be
the different levels on which you
understand this? Let us clarify the
definitions and work them through
together. My if I can put it a name like
my higher self or my intuition or my
heart. Yes.
is in that project. Your heart is in the
project, right? And so what does this
mean to you? But like if I start think
about it. Yes. So my analytical mind and
sometimes my emotions or my fears are
what make me hesitate. All right. And I
know that those are let's say my heart
it's senior to all those things. But I
can't just All right. Ignore it then.
Oh, I'm not telling you to ignore it.
The idea then is if that is what you are
doing and you know your heart is there
then focus on the heart and learn what
you need to learn from anything that
appears to be a hesitation in your life
or a fear. Find out why it's there.
Because if it is there and you know it's
there because your heart is focused on
the project then whatever fears you are
discovering are things you need to
examine to integrate them within
yourself to become more of the person
who will be the person that is
representative of the one who will do
the project. Those things are there for
you to discover as parts of the being
you created yourself to be. If there are
levels, then the reason you are
discovering them is so that you can
reintegrate them into one idea. So that
they don't have to remain as separate
levels. Whatever fears, whatever
hesitations, whatever analysis you
discover within the process is there for
you to learn
from to learn in a positive way to find
out what it is about this event that is
happening, this fear that you are
creating, this emotional reaction that
you are experiencing. What is it about
this that
belongs in the process of this project?
Because it does belong there. Obviously
to show you a portion of yourself, you
need to see to integrate it within you
so you can be the person who will be the
person who does the
project. Understand? Mhm. Is this making
sense now? Yeah. Trust your process is
all I am saying.
Yeah, I get that. I have
been trying to trust my process all the
time and that's the point that I do have
a hard time sometimes. Well, that's all
right. If you are having a hard time,
the first step into transforming it into
an easy time is to recognize that you
are choosing to believe it has to be a
hard time. So, as soon as you
understand, all right, all right, I'm
having a hard time. That means I am
choosing to believe I need to have a
hard time. Why would I choose that? What
if I have a fun time knowing I have
chosen to have a hard time?
What if I enjoy the idea that I was
clever enough to create the idea of
difficulty? What if I pick that whole
definition apart and scattered into the
wind? What if I play with the definition
of difficulty? What if I really examine
it? If I'm going to be analytical, why
not go all the way and have it on all
levels? Why not analyze my
analysis? Why not pick it all apart
until going full circle, there's nothing
left to analyze?
What about that approach? Sounds fun.
Sounds fun. All right, then. Maybe
that's your way. Because remember,
everything is a circle in that sense.
And
sometimes the way out is
up. The way out is
in. If you go far enough in one
direction, you'll come back to your
starting point. Perhaps you can handle
your fear that way. your analysis that
way. Don't reject it. If that's what
you're doing and you find that it's
difficult to change it, then that's your
clue. Go further into it and then you
will shatter the
illusion. Running from it still means
the reflection is still coming from that
mirror. Trying to back away from it
means that you can still see that
reflection of fear.
If that keeps happening when you move
this way, then move this way. Go through
it. Break it apart. Crash through the
illusion in the mirror and then it will
be
gone. Understand?
Mhm. Does that serve you? Yes. Yes, it
does. All right. Pleasant dreams. Thank
you. Thank you very
much. Sharing.
Good day, Bashar. time to you. Good day.
Oh, or good evening, whichever it is.
I'm not I'm never sure. All
right. Maybe you should take a look
outside. Well, I know what it is here. I
It is on. Well, it is various times
around different portions of the planet,
isn't it? Just like yours. What is it
where you are now in my craft in orbit?
It is daylight. Ah, then good day. Thank
you. That is why I have been saying good
day. Just checking. Thank you. I have a short
Just checking. Thank you. I have a short
sharing and then a question. Short
sharing. Yes. I took a little visit to
the spaceship today.
Here. Can you hear me? Oh, okay. I was
playing the tape from last week this
morning. And I lay down on the rug in
the sun and closed my eyes and took that
trip again to your ship, the Solar Wind.
I love that name. It excites me. All
right. And in the middle of that, the
ship likes it, too.
The first time I heard it, I loved it.
It has such a vibration.
Continue. So, I was lying there um
visiting your ship and I felt my little
cat come actually he's he's rather large
and he came over and he lay down beside
me and got as close to me as he could
and I felt that he was there with me on
the ship sharing that experience. I was
very touched. I got the feeling that he
wanted to be there too. Anyway, I
thought I would share that with you.
Thank you. Also, my question now is
about um I talked
to an entity through a channel last
Monday night from
uh Atlantis who said who who gave his
name as
Aron and said he is a light crystal
master from Atlantis. And since I have a
very strong Atlantan connection, I ask
about that. and he had something to say about
that. and he had something to say about
a group that I used to belong to or
participate in. Seven of
in. Seven of
13. What does that
mean? 13 is the transformational number
as many of you know, especially when it
comes to the idea of bringing to the
surface many of the things you have
suppressed or placed in your unconscious
or subconscious self. And therefore in
your society very often is represented
in a fearful quote unquote superstitious
way. 13 is the transformational number,
especially the door between physical and
non-physical reality. Seven of 13 to some degree is a
reality. Seven of 13 to some degree is a
recognition of the accomplishment or the
awareness of having created harmony with
the idea of transformation.
I like that.
Can you say anything more about that
particular lifetime or lifetimes or
connections with Atlantis?
Only that there is strong connection as
you already know to interaction with
dolphin consciousness then as well as
now. Yes, I do know. Will that serve
you? I guess it'll have to. You're close
I guess it'll have to. You're close
mouth sometimes for sure. especially
with those quote unquote that know
better. All right, I accept that. Remember this,
All right, I accept that. Remember this,
for I will give you a
hint. The easiest way to allow me to
carry on like a
chatterbox is to make statements rather
than ask questions.
Yes, I do know that. When you have the
conviction to state what you believe is
true for you, then we may comment. We
may function as a guide to steer here
and there and discuss in open ways the
various aspects that you have awakened
to in your own recognitions of self. But
the more you ask, the smaller the mouth
becomes. The more you share as an equal
what you feel moves you as an energy,
the more excited we get and the more we
desire to discuss it with you as an
equal. That's your hint.
That's your hint.
That's not a hint. That is a revelation.
Oh, all right. We thank you very much.
Thank you very much. And next time I
want to talk to you about orca energy.
Oh, all right. I will pay wrapped
attention and Japan. All right. Thank
you. Thank you,
Shering. Shakashini.
Shakashimi. Shakashimi. 13. 13. Yes. I'm
13 tonight. Oh, all right. Happy
birthday. Thank you.
Uh, a couple of weeks ago we talked
about being a thousand times more
excited. Thousand times. Yes. And you
want to talk about a million times than
I? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. All right. All
right. All right. All right. All right.
Uh, my experience of being a thousand
times more
excited now and growingly is feeling
more and more a thousand times more at
peace. Yes.
The idea once again, as we have said, is
that when you are infinitely accelerated
and everywhere at once, it feels like
you're standing perfectly still. Because
you're everywhere. It smells like
everywhere. It smells like
Yes. Thank you. You're welcome. Thank
you.
Shutting. Hello, sir. Goodbye to you.
Um, in reading your new metaphysics
handbook, I I was looking to this five
levels of uh
energies starting from existence, then
knowing knowing, belief, emotion and
thought. Yes. Uh, I always thought that
mentality was senior to emotions. There
are a few different semantic definitions
to this idea. To some degree it is when
we say thought, we are actually talking
about the analytical framework that more
often than not many of you think of as
your thought process. The one that is
the last stage before you create a
perception of the physical reality. We
are not talking about mentality as a
whole. We are simply referring to the
idea of thought itself. The mentality to
some degree you are referring to is more
connected to the belief knowing
state understand more or less it is
simply a different definition a
different semantic of the idea. All
right in in the in the way you organize
these levels they are seniority I mean
beliefs comes before emotions and
emotional and then mentality right
thoughts. thoughts. Yes, thoughts. Okay.
Classical thoughts. The way you think in
physical terms. Now, I've been having
this difficulty in relating to belief
systems. Yes. Uh for me equates a lot to
mentality to to thoughts. Well, that is
what we have said. Mentality. Yes.
Because mentality is the primal
intersection of your consciousness with
the electromagnetic field of your
planet. It is the first physical
introduction. Mentality is created when
you as a consciousness interact with or
as what you call a physical dimension.
But thoughts the way they process out
are the last phase of mentality. The
type of mentality you are talking about
is
also the idea the overall idea which
fractionates down into belief, emotion
and thoughts in the classical sense.
Understand? In other words, mentality is
the same as awareness itself.
Okay? And then it fractionates down into
the beliefs, the emotions and the
thoughts. So in this case, what you are
calling mentality is actually more akin
to the knowingness stage of our
definition. All right. If if you really
want to change uh the reality you are
experiencing, you have to go and change
your belief system basically. Basically.
Yes. Okay. Now how do you do that? Do
you have a recipe uh to work with?
Because you see yes for me uh belief
system are like energy statements. Yes
they are. All right. But for for me it's
difficult to get to that energy
statements. That's a belief. Uh okay.
Why do you believe it is difficult? Well
because I can relate more to my
thoughts. I can I can I can uh Oh, one
moment. One moment. One moment. You can
work it from any of the three directions
if you really want to. If that works for
you, you can change an emotion and
change your reality and change your
beliefs and thoughts. You can change
your thoughts and change your emotions
and your beliefs. You can change your
beliefs and change your emotions and
change your thoughts. You can work it
from any direction. If one of them seems
more workable to you as a direction,
then simply come from that direction.
You do not necessarily have to in the
classical sense use the actual belief
state first. You can work it quote
unquote backwards. Thank you very much.
Oh, thank you. Merry one
Merry one
moment before we continue. Let us give
one more brief analogy to the idea of
belief, emotion and thought. Remember,
you can use the analogy of a prism. It
is a three-sided
prism. If you change any of the sides,
the belief, the emotion, the thought,
that alters how the white light of your
mentality or your knowingness comes
through the prism and determines what
kind of spectrum, the physical reality
you create. So, you can change any of
the sides and it will change the
spectrum. Thank you. continue.
Thank you. continue.
That's encouraging what you just said.
Well, thank you. Um, it's nice meeting
you, Bashar. And you as well. Thank you.
We thank you for co-creating this
interaction. Do proceed. Um, I recently
started a business and Oh, how exciting.
Yes, it is. Um, I know that I've created
this before. All right. and
um want to not in the same way, of
course. Okay. Not in the same way. And
and believe I'll probably be creating it
again. Um again, when?
You mean in a future life? Yes. Oh, all
right. But you're living this life now.
Okay. Let's focus on this one. I've been
experiencing a lot of deja vu. And
that's what Very good. Exciting.
It means you are becoming consciously
aware of your non-physical
consciousness. You are blending the two
levels of physicality and
non-physicality of the physical dream
and the non-physical dream. More often
than not, although it can be many, many
things, deja vu is when in your dream
reality, you have created a particular
scenario that you wish to play out in
your physical reality, but don't want to
know you created that scenario until you
have spontaneously played it through.
After you play it through, you can
remember you created in your dream
reality first and you have the memory
you call deja vu or the overlap of the
physical and the non-physical. When you
are literally consciously existing in
what you call physical and non-physical
plains simultaneously or let's say when
you are aware of the fact that you
already exist in physical and
non-physical plains simultaneously.
That's a dja vu. Mhm. Not only is it
already something you have seen in your
dream state, it is a form of what you
might call doubledimensional vision.
Okay. Is it viewing a simultaneous
existence? Yes. Okay. In your
terminology, it would seem as if it has
already happened. Yes. Because you in
your linear terms already planned it out
in your dream. But yes, it is still
simultaneous. That is why it is
absolutely double vision. Mhm.
Um, I wanted to ask your feelings about
what you see in the future with respect
to this business. Well, does it excite
you? Very much. Well, what do you see?
It is your business. I I've been seeing
lately resistance on my part. Ah, does
that excite you? No. All right. Why do
you have resistance to what do you have
resistance? Success. Why? Fear of what?
Success. Why? Fear of what?
Success.
Why? What is your definition of success?
Let's clarify. What do you imagine will
be success to you? Receiving. Receiving.
You don't like to
receive. Do you like to give?
They're both the same, aren't they? In a
sense. I I appear the I feel that I do
like to give and that it's easier to
give than receive. And yet I see them
both as being opposite sides of the co
of the same coin. Well, basically, but
they're not even really opposites in
that sense. Now, you say you have for
now more of a propensity to give than to
be able to receive yet. Exactly. All
right. But do you understand that
allowing others to give is one of the
greatest gifts you can give?
Yes. Does that tie them together for
you? It helps me a great deal because
when you allow others to give to you,
then you are allowing them to reflect
your own abundance. Mhm. You are
allowing them to serve. Would you not
want them to be just as fulfilled as you
are? Yes, I would. Then let them give.
You deserve it. And so do
they. Does that help? Yes, a great deal.
Thank you very much. Thank you. Thank
you. Thank you. Thank you. loving loving
loving heart. Thank you. Thank you.
Shutting.
Good evening. Good day to
you. A week ago, I was in Washington DC,
not even contemplating coming to
California. Oh, surprise surprise.
Indeed. And I didn't know that you
existed in body or out of body until
yesterday. Ah, I exist in my own body.
Yes, indeed. And I'm delighted to have the
indeed. And I'm delighted to have the
opportunity to share some of your
thoughts this evening. Always delighted
to share your own.
Yes. I believe that
uh the label that's placed on people who
are quote mentally ill. Yes. Is an
erroneous label. It is misleading to
some degree. Yes. That psychosis is
merely another state of consciousness.
Basically, when it becomes in your
definitional sense negative is generally
when it becomes a closed loop feeding
itself perhaps in a negative spiral
simply because those individuals have
never been taught that the different
levels of dimensionality they originally
perceived were something they could
communicate back and apply to the
society in which they exist. because the
society rejects their visions. They
close themselves off and become locked
in that self-fulfilling spiral. That's
the only thing that creates it to be a
negative idea. And unfortunately, our
society uh
views people who have been in
institutions or whether they well
whatever their length of stay might be.
Thanks. And we're very prejudiced for
people that have been institution. Yes.
But that is changing. Your definitions
are changing. Yes. Your ability to even
discuss this shows that to be so. Sure.
Well, and the fact that uh you know I
was in that state six years ago myself.
Oh, how exciting it
was. Very. What did you learn? Yes. I I
think so. You know, I learned that
um that I Well, my peers were based upon
the fact that my mother had been a
schizophrenic and label such and my
father an alcoholic. All right. And so
you got lost in the labels. Then I have
to well it took me about 45 years to
create the condition uh so that I could
experience it myself. Oh all right.
And at that time I was uh functioning as
a school principal and so two years
later when I was so recovered uh you
know I went on public record about it.
This was in Northern Virginia. Yes. And
that helped me to get an early
retirement from the school system.
Oh all right. I hadn't planned that but
that's okay. Yes. So now I spend a great
deal of my time and resources in working
as a volunteer with schizophrenics for
manic depressives. Oh thank you. Yes.
And while here in California I was
introduced just uh yesterday and today
to uh crystal bowls that I understand
that this channel gave the formula for.
Not completely. No. Okay. We simply
assisted to some degree, made certain
recommendations, certain guidances, but
the idea arose from within your own
society. Okay. However that may be, it's
occurred to me that that they the sound
vibrations. Oh yes. Yes. Yes. and may be
of great assistance in helping to uh
rebalance, regground whatever term you
use people
who are still unbalanced. Yes.
And I wonder if you would have any other
uh what Oh, you know what to do. You
know when you feel the cord that hits
you that strikes you, you can allow any
individual to pick the one that strikes
them the strongest. That's the one
that's representative of their signature
vibration, the core vibration. Allow
them to begin to identify with it to
match its frequency and they will bring
themselves back to center. Immerse them
in that sound, in loving laughter and
light. They will center themselves.
Immerse them in that atmosphere. It will
create what you call a field around them
that will then unlock them from the
other realities they have been locked
into and give them the time and the
opportunity to reassess where they are
and what they wish to plug into once
they center themselves.
people who
are in halfway houses, adult homes or
whatever that uh are I think suffering
partially from incorrect nutrition, lack
of exercise,
lack of caring etc. Yes. Do you think
it's essential to change that
environment before introducing
uh the sound vibrations as a way to help
them balance? Well, not necessarily. It
will depend upon the individual. Go with
your intuition and your instinct. Each
individual will be different because
they have a different belief system
about what will work first and what will
work next. Trust your instinct with
every individual. It will always help to
do as many of them simultaneously as you
can to create as many changes in as many
of the quote unquote negative
environments as you can into whatever
you think is more representative of a
centered and balanced vibration.
All I'm not quite certain I understood
you say do as many of them as you can.
Are you speaking of in other words what
you call nutrition what you call your
living environment what you call light
color yeah I just wasn't clear if you
were talking about individuals as many
of them as individuals or the pro that
too that's up to you that it could work
with several not necessarily one well
let me put it this way if you sit
yourself down in a particular room with
an individual who in your terminology is
eating something beneficial to their
belief system and you are playing your
bowl for them, all well and good. If you
are sitting down on a stage and playing
your bowl for 10,000 individuals all
sitting there nibbling something that
they find beneficial to their belief
system as a concert, all well and good.
Whatever level you wish to operate on,
it's up to you.
Do you see
uh hypnotherapy and or in all of these
things are tools? Yes. With
integrity use anything you believe is
representative of your desire to be of
service and that means you will do it in
a positive way. They are all tools. Yes,
I accept that. Do you do I are there
other tools that I am not? Use your
imagination that I'm not consciously
aware. Use your imagination.
When they need to be made aware to you,
they will be whatever you are aware of.
Now, work with that. As soon as you
start working with what you have, you
will create the momentum that will
generate inspiration within you and you
will get
more. Understand? Yeah. It's like I
really am on the edge of the uh the pool
and I haven't dove in. You will all
always be on the edge of another pool.
Yes, jump in. Yes, there will always be
another place to jump.
Use what you have and that is what
allows there to be the space for more
tools to come in. Certainly. Although
paradoxically you may find that the
tools will get simpler and simpler and
fewer and fewer and you will be working
more directly with just energy energy
energy identification directly
communication communication which is the
title of this interaction. I believe
that I personally am clear enough to do
this work now without
uh undo influence or interference by my
own ego. All right, then. Have a
wonderful time. And we thank you for
your willingness to be of service in the
way you have chosen to. And we thank you
for sticking to your
principle. And thank you. And I must say
that uh it's a joy to interact with you.
Uh I've been accustomed to working with
uh people such such as yourself, but who
did not allow their sense of humor to
come forth as you do. and I've enjoyed
this evening very well. We cannot help
but always find ourselves laughing over
our interactions with all of you.
We thank you for allowing us to express
and for returning our joy sharing.
Hello Bashar. Hello
wizard. I am here to extend uh some more
communication at the wizard level. Yes.
And uh I don't know what to say about
it. Well, say it away, Wizardwood.
Uh Haro. All right. Uh trying to put
into effect some of the things that
you've been discussing. Try try try try.
Yes. As I was doing. Yes. Yes. Yes. I
was thinking of levitating in wizard
fashion. So here we go. [Music]
[Music]
Are you having a good time? Yeah.
[Laughter]
Where do you wish to take this?
Well, part of me has levitated and part
of me is still on the ground. by see
50/50 proposition. Well, it's almost
that way. Um the last time um we
interacted at this level, I felt very
good during it and afterward and was the
main reason for my being here again.
It's been some time since we've
interacted all wizard level and I would
welcome some input from you at this time
about this process.
What is in a sense levitation but
enlightenment but acceleration but
ascension of all the vibration of the
entire vibration that you
are. Although do remember that for the
purpose of many of your interactions
with many other individuals to awaken
their wizard, you will appear to remain
firmly grounded. So they will take you
grounded. So they will take you
seriously.
You follow along? Yes, I do. I flow
along. Thank you. Does this serve you?
Yes, it does. Good to see you again,
Wizard. Thank you for your laughter and
your light. And thank
you at this timing.
We extend once again to each and every
one of
you our unconditional love and we thank
you for allowing us to communicate in
our own way this idea to you. We remind
you your way is just as beautiful. We
thank you for allowing it to be
experienced by all of us.
loving
dreams. We are the sharing that
continues forever. Good day.
forever. Good day.
[Applause]
How did it go? Thank you.
Thank you all for being here tonight.
Yes. Thank you.