Allow us to
begin this interaction this evening of
your time with the
entitlement foreign
relations. The idea we'll have to
do with our interactions with all of
you. Your interactions with all of us
all the
beings within what we have termed the
association of
worlds. feel this
way. We are
perhaps as foreign as relations could
get. Now the idea of our contacting you
in this way to some degree we have
explained from time to time our reasons
our methodology a brief as you say
methodology a brief as you say
encapsulization of this information
maybe in order to bring ourselves up to
date we mean that we have interacted
with many other civilizations going
through transformations those civilizations
transformations those civilizations
that are in stages of
development that have not yet allowed
them to perhaps realize that they could
interact with other civilizations in an
open way. We will then establish
way. We will then establish
communications in the way that you are
perceiving now more or less more often
than not.
recognize that
biological light is the most efficient transmitter
light is the most efficient transmitter
and
receiver. And
so that is why there is the
communication through beings such as
yourself that you have termed channel to
some degree an appropriate
terminology. The idea is not that we
cannot communicate with you along your
radio, television devices. We could to
some degree, but not until there is
degree, but not until there is
established a rapport of
understanding through the methodology
you call channeling or biological
reception because that is what allows
changes to occur in the mentality of the
society and that is what makes it
possible for the frequencies upon which
even your mechanical radio devices are
constru instructed to be able to receive
our communications. For as we have
described from time to time, each and
every different civilization is on a
different frequency of energy. And if
those frequencies are not matched, at
least brought within a certain range of
compatibility, then no matter how long
we send information along what would be
called our level of radio frequency,
your level of radio devices would never
pick them
up. They would still operate in
different dimensions of
existence and they would be completely
invisible to each other. So first
changes in the idea system in the
perspective system in the belief system
of the society must come about in order
for your radio devices to be able to
even perceive the idea of transmissions
that we could send.
However, the idea even more than that
for the lack of likelihood of
communicating in that way is simply
that the majority of civilizations we
interact with do not communicate through
what you call radio
frequencies. Several civilizations from
time to time will go through that stage
of their technological evolution, but
many will not. And even when you do go
through as your planet is now that stage
of technological evolution of what you
call radio
communication, it is not always done the
same in different
civilizations. And even if it is, that
stage of your technological evolution
usually does not last that long. for
very quickly in terms of history do you
pass through the radio stage and go on
to other levels other sources of energy
other utilizations of energy for your
communication systems. So even those civilizations
systems. So even those civilizations
that may have been relatively close to
you as you
say cosmically speaking in distance who
may have used radio communication at one
stage in their evolution technologically
They are either in your terms
still so far away that their radio
communications that have radiated out
from their planet have not reached you
yet or many of them have already passed
you by before you had the ability to
listen because it is a very short phase
of their particular history or
evolution. In a sense as we have said
before right now your world is
functioning in a radio desert. There are
no radio messages in that sense on their
way to your
planet because that technology is not
that often
used and not always in that way when it
is. If a society to begin with chose as
you say to cable their electromagnetic
frequencies or tight beam their
electromagnetic communications, it would
not radiate from their planet to any
distinguishable degree that you could
pick up anyway.
So even some of the societies that have
utilized it have done it in such a way
that they do not leak radio
emissions not the way that your society
does. Therefore the idea more often than
not in our experience is that societies
will eventually come to understand that
biological life are the most efficient
transmitters and
receivers and the mentality of
individuals will be tapped and touched
first. This again as I've said forms the double
This again as I've said forms the double
purpose of not only creating a
communication but assisting in the
altering of the consciousness of that
particular society to allow that society
to allow it within themselves to become
more acceptable to communicate with
other civilizations. And again it is done
civilizations. And again it is done
unobtrusively because we do have in
complete and total effect one of the
ideas that many of your science fiction
writers have thought they invented but
in a sense we're simply picking up upon
and that is simply called the
non-inference directive. The idea that
any new civilization that is in an
evolutionary stage where it does not
necessarily express an absolute
conscious recognition that there are
other civilizations it could communicate
with is left
alone. The idea of our existence is not
forced upon them. Until such time as
they exhibit the willingness to
communicate in that way. Until their
entire society understands that they can
communicate in a loving way, not in a
way that will in that sense destructure
their society in a negative way causing
chaos as you say and panic.
or the disassemblement of their society
through fear, doubt,
self-doubt that we might be something
greater than you that might undermine
your own abilities to believe in
yourselves. This we cannot do and that
is why we remain unobtrusive to this
point. Now and then there can be and
have been isolated contacts in certain
ways. Testing the waters as you say to
see what level of belief system still
exists, what level of fear still exists
in your society. Testing individuals
here and there to see whether it is now
truly more conducive for your world and
our worlds to interact face to face as
equals in blatant ways. And as we have
indicated, these times are approaching.
Within what you call the next two to
three decades, this can be a relatively
common thing. But right now, by many of
your own admissions, in the general
cross-section of your society, you do
not want such widespread interaction,
for your society is not structured in
your terms to handle it.
It would cause an, in our estimation of
your energy in general, a
destructurization of a negative sort,
where there would still be fear and
panic, where there would still be the
beliefs that your reality is not in your
hands. And many of you, far too many of
you, would still be more than willing to
give over your power to us. We do not
want to thank you.
We have enough of our own. All that we
need to live the lives we have chosen to
live in communicating this way and
establishing foreign relations with you.
That is our primary goal.
Do understand that in all the
interactions we have shared with you, we
have been more than willing and quite
ecstatic to experience and express the
interchange of love and to be of
assistance in reflecting back to you
what you already know about the power
you have to create the lives you want to
create. But do understand it is not in
that way our
mission to really in a sense provide
this information.
The idea is to simply establish
relations and to that effect is what has
been done. Our methodology is the
methodology that has been chosen from
hundreds thousands of interactions that
have taken place during the past
hundreds and thousands of your years
with many different civilizations within
the association.
And to us it is what you would call the
tried and trueue
method. The reflection to each of you of
your own power so that each of you
individually and collectively can make
the decision as to whether or not you
want to interact with us as a society.
That is completely up to
you. Should you decide no, we will be on
our way. It is our perception that you
are deciding yes. And so we hang
around but not as your saviors. You do
not need saviors. We are not here to
rescue you. We are here to play with
you, to share with you, to love you, and
to remind you that you are equals within
creation to all beings that have been
created by the infinite.
All of this so that our societies in
combining may expand and become
familiar, maintaining our individuality
but not being so foreign to each
other. Once again, we thank you for
these opportunities to establish
relations in this way for it once again
allows us to see that many more ways
that the infinite has of expressing
itself through the creation that it is.
In return for this gift, your
willingness to function as
representatives of your world and
allowing me to function as a
representative of our collective worlds
of the association, I ask you now, how
may I serve you?
[Music] Hello, Bashar. And do you die? I'm Joel.
Hello, Bashar. And do you die? I'm Joel.
All right. And uh in uh in connection
with your uh with your uh comments about
uh relationships, I've never met a
person from another planet. So I have a
million questions, but uh basically uh
I'm curious to know about your the
social organization of your planet. How
are you all organized? I will be brief
because this information already does
exist to some extent on many of the
interaction tapes that we have made with
you. However, the idea simply is that we
are a spontaneous civilization. Now, we
have elevated what you call trust to an
art form in a positive sense. The idea
simply being that we no longer need what
you would call a government as such, a
political system as such, an economic
system as such because we interact
directly with each other individually
and in groups more in the format now
that you would call a network. In a
sense, it is our perception that your
government in Thai, what you call your
governments upon your planet will take
on more of the aspects of what you now
call networks where you will facilitate
networks where you will facilitate
individuals in contacting other
individuals, those that have services,
those that have needs. The idea of our
association is not so much a government
nor exactly what you might call a
federation for that still implies to
some degree a governmental structure
similar to the one you know. The idea is
that it is a networking body, a serving
body that puts intelligence in line and
in touch with other intelligence that
matches spontaneously need for need,
service for service. And that is much
the way our society interacts. We have
the need for a medium of exchange
because every individual that has a
service automatically attracts every
individual that needs that service and
every individual that needs that service
that is attracted automatically brings
with them a service that the first
individual needs. Everything is run by
what you would call synchronicity
coincidence because that is the way life
works because life is a holographic
matrix wherein everything is connected
to everything else automatically. When
your attitude knows that when when you
focus on that particular structure then
that's the way you experience life and
you do not need what might be called a
reference structure in order to organize
things. Things organize themselves and
the government becomes one that serves
rather than rules allowing the flow to
take place. At any given moment, as we
have said, our population is exploring
in spacecraft and interacting with other
civilizations and exploring many aspects
of the universe. Very few of us remain
on the surface of our planet at any
given time. Our planet is very green and
you say parklike in your language. There
are no large builtup structures upon our
world, no large cities as upon yours.
The idea for us is not necessary since
the spacecraft in which we live many
times are the cities themselves, many of
them being many miles of your counting
in length and holding what you may call
tens of thousands of
individuals. There are only
approximately 200 million in your
counting of our permanent population.
Anyway, our numbers are far lower than
yours. The remainder of our population
are those beings that simply, as you
say, come and go. that are not a
permanent member of our society.
Sometimes individuals popping in and
out, taking for the moment our corporeal
form to experience our particular
civilization and then flashing back into
energy and sometimes simply other beings
from other societies who choose to spend
some time upon the surface of our planet
interacting with many different members
both of our species and of
others. This is in general the idea of
our lifestyle. It is very spontaneous,
very joyful, very ecstatic. We are
always exploring, always learning,
always growing, always having a good
time. Our bodies briefly are of 5 ft,
heights average as you count, white
whitish gray skin coloration, very wide
upturned eyes. Males have no hair,
females have
hair. Will this do? It sounds uh sounds
interesting. Uh but there is more
information available on many of the
tapes that we have already made with
you. What about the non-conformist? Is
there uh is there such a thing? Everyone
is a
non-conformist. And because everyone is
allowed to be the fullest individual
they can be, then we have great unity.
Does that agree with the with the one
mind concept? Yes. Understand that it is
a misunderstanding in your society that
one mind means a blandness of
individuality. The idea just like the
person you are is that when each and
every one of your consciousness parts
when each and every one of your
personality parts is as strong and equal
to every other part it can be then you
function as a whole being. And so like
it is in a society when every individual
is the strongest individual they can be
then you have unity for everyone is
equally validated for the individual
they are and therefore paradoxically
everyone supports the totality of all
the other individuals that exist and
supports the idea of each and every
being being the strongest individual
they can be. So unconditional love is
the key that allows us to function as
one mind and at the same time allows us
to operate as distinct and variegated
individuals. Understand? So there's no
disagreement among there are always
different points of view but the
different points of view do not in your
terms impede from the general flow of
our positive
progress. There is never disagreement in
the sense that it holds things up.
There can be different points of view,
different approaches. But you see, to
us, they're all valid. So if three
individuals have three different points
of view and three different approaches,
we do them
all. Or if they finally allow themselves
by trying them all, as I use your term
for now, trying to simply come to the
understanding that what one individual
or another individual did perhaps is not
as efficient as what the third
individual came up with. Then in
recognizing that the other two will
probably align themselves with the third
one. Again everything is done
spontaneously in a very obvious and
conscious and willing manner. There is
no need for argument as you call it
because all points of view are valid and
we can learn from all of
them. Understand? Mhm. Does this assist
you? Yes. Well, thank you very much for
your point of view and your sharing. One
question for person.
Thank you. Well, thank you Charing. Good
day, Bashan. And to you, good day. Uh,
I'm curious about Esanians. Um, what you
do for kicks, what kind of entertainment
you have. Again, we have many different
forms of expression. Some of them are
similar to your own. There is in your
terms art, there is in your
terms. There are many different ideas,
some similar, some very diverse from
your own. We are always exploring and
learning many different endeavors, many
different expressions. I in that sense in your
expressions. I in that sense in your
classic vernacular would be considered a
pilot, an engineer, a
sculptor, and as you say, a
diplomat. These are the things that
excite me. Everyone does what excites
them the most with full integrity.
Beyond that, it is unlimited.
Do you I'm sorry. Continue.
So continue.
Do you have um an entertainment system
such as television or films the way we
do here? No. There was something similar
in what you call times past. Now our
society is in your terms mostly
telepathic. Information is simply sent
as you say from mind to mind. There are
to some degree within the spacecraft
recording devices, but these are
completely what you would call pneumonic
and are accessed directly by mentality
into the computers. The images simply
unfold in our mind. They do not have to
appear on what you would call a screen.
Understand? So there's no central uh
place that sends out these entertainment
or other images to individuals that you
could tune into. There is one
representative place always on every
planet of the association that can
function in this way. But there is also
a chamber on every large city ship that
functions in a similar fashion.
And who creates these
images? Every individual does. I mean
that would if you have 200 million
people on your planet alone that would
be a lot of um frequencies. Well, not
every image is processed nor does it
need to be. The idea will simply be,
however, that if an individual has a
specific desire for a particular access,
they will be able to get
it. Remember that all individuals,
including your own on your own planet,
have access to all knowledge, especially
that knowledge that pertains most
directly to your
world. It is generally referred to as
aashic records. Understand?
It is a storehouse of knowledge of the
infinite. We simply have to some degree
a modified mechanical representative of
that idea. It is a network once again of
idea. It is a network once again of
energy.
Terrific. But it is not
confusing. It overlaps. But any
individual who creates themselves to be
a particular frequency will only access
the particular information that is
aligned with that particular frequency.
They will not interfere with anyone
else's ability to access what
information they
need. Understand? It is holographic in
that sense.
Does that make sense to you? It's
falling into place. All right. Does that
serve you? It does. Thank you very much.
Well, thank you very much. Allow it to
begin this interaction, this evening of
your time with the
entitlement foreign relations.
The idea we'll have to
do with our interactions with all of
you, your interactions with all of us,
all the
being within what we have termed the
association of
worlds. In this
way, we are
perhaps as foreign as relations could
get. Now the idea of our contacting you
in this way to some degree we have
explained from time to time our reasons
our methodology a brief as you say
methodology a brief as you say
encapsulization of this information
maybe in order to bring ourselves up to
date we mean that we have interacted
with many other civilizations going
through transformations those civilizations
transformations those civilizations
that are in stages of
development that have not yet allowed
them to perhaps realize that they could
interact with other civilizations in an
open way. We will then establish
way. We will then establish
communications in the way that you are
perceiving now. more or less, more often
than not, recognize that
not, recognize that
biological
life is the most efficient transmitter
and receiver. And
receiver. And
so that is why there is the
communication through beings such as
yourself that you have termed channel to
some degree and appropriate terminology.
The idea is not that we cannot
communicate with you along
your radio, television devices.
We could to some
degree, but not until there is
established a rapport of
understanding through the methodology
you call channeling or biological
reception because that is what allows
changes to occur in the mentality of the
society and that is what makes it
possible for the frequencies upon which
even your mechanical radio devices are
constructed to be able to receive our
communication. For as I have described
from time to time, each and every
different civilization is on a different
frequency of energy. And if those
frequencies are not matched, at least
brought within a certain range of
compatibility, then no matter how long
we send information along what would be
called our level of radio frequency,
your level of radio devices would never
pick them
up. They would still operate in
different dimensions of
existence and they would be completely
invisible to each other. So first
changes in the idea system in the
perspective system in the belief system
of the society must come about in order
for your radio devices to be able to
even perceive the idea of transmissions
that we could send.
However, the idea even more than that
for the lack of likelihood of
communicating in that way is simply
that the majority of civilizations we
interact with do not communicate through
what you call radio
frequencies. Several civilizations from
time to time will go through that stage
of their technological evolution, but
many will not. And even when you do go
through as your planet is now that stage
of technological evolution of what you
call radio
communication, it is not always done the
same in different
civilizations. And even if it is, that
stage of your technological evolution
usually does not last that long. for
very quickly in terms of history do you
pass through the radio stage and go on
to other levels other sources of energy
other utilizations of energy for your
communication systems. So even those civilizations
systems. So even those civilizations
that may have been relatively close to
you as you
say cosmically speaking in distance who
may have used radio communication at one
stage in their evolution technologically
They are either in your terms
still so far
away that their radio communications
that have radiated out from their planet
have not reached you yet or many of them
have already passed you by before you
had the ability to
listen because it is a very short phase
of their particular history or
evolution. In a sense as we have said
before right now your world is
functioning in a radio desert. There are
no radio messages in that sense on their
way to your
planet because that technology is not
that often
used and not always in that way when it
is. If a society to begin with chose as
you say to cable their electromagnetic
frequencies or tight beam their
electromagnetic communications, it would
not radiate from their planet to any
distinguishable degree that you could
pick up anyway.
So even some of the societies that have
utilized it have done it in such a way
that they do not leak radio
emissions not the way that your society
does. Therefore the idea more often than
not in our experience is that societies
will eventually come to understand that
biological life are the most efficient
transmitters and
receivers and the mentality of
individuals will be tapped and touched
first. This again as I've said forms the double
This again as I've said forms the double
purpose of not only creating a
communication but assisting in the
altering of the consciousness of that
particular society to allow that society
to allow it within themselves to become
more acceptable to communicate with
other civilizations. And again, it is done
civilizations. And again, it is done
unobtrusively because we do have in
complete and total effect one of the
ideas that many of your science fiction
writers have thought they invented but
in a sense we're simply picking up upon
and that is simply called the
non-inference directive. The idea that
any new civilization that is in an
evolutionary stage where it does not
necessarily express an absolute
conscious recognition that there are
other civilizations it could communicate
with is left alone.
The idea of our existence is not forced
upon them until such time as they
exhibit the willingness to communicate
in that way. Until their entire society
understands that they can communicate in
a loving way, not in a way that will in
that sense destructure their society in
a negative way causing chaos as you say
and panic or the disassemblement of their
panic or the disassemblement of their
society through fear, doubt,
self-doubt that we might be something
greater than you that might undermine
your own abilities to believe in
yourselves. This we cannot do and that
is why we remain unobtrusive to this
point. Now and then there can be and
have been isolated contacts in certain
ways testing the waters as you say to
see what level of belief system still
exists. What level of fear still exists
in your society? testing individuals
here and there to see whether it is now
truly more conducive for your world and
our worlds to interact face to face as
equals in blatant ways. And as we have
indicated, these times are approaching
within what you call the next two to
three decades. This can be a relatively
common thing. But right now, by many of
your own admissions, in the general
cross-section of your society, you do
not want such widespread interaction,
for your society is not structured in
your terms to handle it. It would cause
an, in our estimation of your energy in
general, a destructurization of a
negative sort, where there would still
be fear and panic, where there would
still be the
beliefs that your reality is not in your
hands. And many of you, far too many of
you, would still be more than willing to
give over your power to us. We do not
want it. Thank
you. We have enough of our own. All that
we need to live the lives we have chosen
to live in communicating this way and
establishing foreign relations with you.
That is our primary goal.
Do understand that in all the
interactions we have shared with you, we
have been more than willing and quite
ecstatic to experience and express the
interchange of love and to be of
assistance in reflecting back to you
what you already know about the power
you have to create the lives you want to
create. But do understand it is not in
that way our
mission to really in a sense provide
this information.
The idea is to simply establish
relations and to that effect is what has
been done. Our methodology is the
methodology that has been chosen from
hundreds thousands of interactions that
have taken place during the past
hundreds and thousands of your years
with many different civilizations within
the association.
And to us it is what you would call the
tried and true
method. The reflection to each of you of
your own power so that each of you
individually and collectively can make
the decision as to whether or not you
want to interact with us as a society.
That is completely up to
you. Should you decide no, we will be on
our way. It is our perception that you
are deciding yes. And so we hang
around but not as your saviors. You do
not need saviors. We are not here to
rescue you. We are here to play with
you, to share with you, to love you, and
to remind you that you are equals within
creation to all beings that have been
created by the infinite.
All of this so that our societies in
combining may
expand and become familiar, maintaining
our individuality but not being so
foreign to each
other. Once again, we thank you for
these opportunities to establish
relations in this way for it once again
allows us to see that many more ways
that the infinite has of expressing
itself through the creation that it is.
In return for this gift, your
willingness to function as
representatives of your world and
allowing me to function as a
representative of our collective worlds
of the association, I ask you now, how
may I serve you?
[Music] Hello, Bashar. And to
Hello, Bashar. And to
you, I'm Joe. All right. And uh in uh in
connection with your uh with your uh
comments about uh relationships, yes,
I've never met a person from another
planet. So I have a million questions,
but uh basically uh I'm curious to know
about your the social organization of
your planet. How are you all organized?
I will be brief because this information
already does exist to some extent on
many of the interaction tapes that we
have made with you. However, the idea
simply is that we are a spontaneous
civilization. Now, we have elevated what
you call trust to an art form in a
positive sense. The idea simply being
that we no longer need what you would
call a government as such, a political
system as such, an economic system as
such because we interact directly with
each other individually and in groups
more in the format now that you would
call a network. In a sense, it is our
perception that your government in time,
what you call your governments upon your
planet will take on more of the aspects
of what you now call
networks where you will facilitate
individuals in contacting other
individuals, those that have services,
those that have needs. The idea of our
association is not so much a government
nor exactly what you might call a
federation for that still implies to
some degree a governmental structure
similar to the one you know. The idea is
that it is a networking body, a serving
body that puts intelligence in line and
in touch with other intelligence that
matches spontaneously need for need,
service for service. And that is much
the way our society interacts. We have
no need for a medium of exchange because
every individual that has a service
automatically attracts every individual
that needs that service and every
individual that needs that service that
is attracted automatically brings up
them a service that the first individual
needs. Everything is run by what you
would call synchronicity,
coincidence because that is the way life
works. Because life is a holographic
matrix wherein everything is connected
to everything else automatically. When
your attitude knows that when when you
focus on that particular structure then
that's the way you experience life and
you do not need what might be called
irreference structure in order to
organize things. Th things organize
themselves and the government becomes
one that serves rather than rules
allowing the flow to take place. At any
given moment, as we have said, our
population is exploring in spacecraft
and interacting with other civilizations
and exploring many aspects of the
universe. Very few of us remain on the
surface of our planet at any given time.
Our planet is very green and you say
park-like in your language. There are no
large builtup structures upon our world,
no large cities as upon yours. The idea
for us is not necessary since the
spacecraft in which we live many times
are the cities themselves, many of them
being many miles of your counting in
length and holding what you may call
tens of thousands of
individuals. There are only
approximately 200 million in your
counting of our permanent population.
Anyway, our numbers are far lower than
yours. The remainder of our population
are those beings that simply, as you
say, come and go. that are not a
permanent member of our society.
Sometimes individuals popping in and
out, taking for the moment our corporeal
form to experience our particular
civilization and then flashing back into
energy and sometimes simply other beings
from other societies who choose to spend
some time upon the surface of our planet
interacting with many different members
both of our species and of
others. This is in general the idea of
our lifestyle. It is very spontaneous,
very joyful, very ecstatic. We are
always exploring, always learning,
always growing, always having a good
growing, always having a good
time. Our bodies briefly are of 5 ft
heights average as you count, white
whitish gray skin coloration, very wide
upturned eyes. Males have no hair,
females have
hair. Will this do? It sounds uh sounds
interesting. Uh but there is more
information available on many of the
tapes that we have already made with
you. What about the non-conformist? Is
there uh is there such a thing? Everyone
is a
non-conformist. And because everyone is
allowed to be the fullest individual
they can be, then we have great unity.
Does that agree with the with the a one
mind concept? Yes. Understand that it is
a misunderstanding in your society that
one mind means a blandness of
individuality. The idea just like the
person you are is that when each and
every one of your consciousness parts
when each and every one of your
personality parts is as strong and equal
to every other part it can be then you
function as a whole being. And so like
it is in a society when every individual
is the strongest individual they can be
then you have unity for everyone is
equally validated for the individual
they are and therefore paradoxically
everyone supports the totality of all
the other individuals that exist and
supports the idea of each and every
being being the strongest individual
they can be. So unconditional love is
the key that allows us to function as
one mind and at the same time allows us
to operate as distinct and variegated
individuals. Understood? So there's no
disagreement among there are always
different points of view but the
different points of view do not in your
terms impede from the general flow of
our positive
progress. There is never disagreement in
the sense that it holds things up.
There can be different points of view,
different approaches, but you see to us
they're all valid. So if three
individuals have three different points
of view and three different approaches,
we do them all.
Or if they finally allow themselves by
trying them all, as I use your term for
now, trying to simply come to the
understanding that what one individual
or another individual did perhaps is not
as efficient as what the third
individual came up with. Then in
recognizing that the other two will
probably align themselves with the third
one. Again, everything is done
spontaneously in a very obvious and
conscious and willing manner. There is
no need for argument as you call it
because all points of view are valid and
we can learn from all of them.
Understand? Mhm. Does this assist you?
Yes. Well, thank you very much for your
point of view and your sharing. One
question for person.
Thank you. Well, thank you. Sharing.
Good day, Van. And to you, good day. Uh,
I'm curious about um what you do for
kicks. What kind of entertainment you
have? Again, we have many different
forms of expression. Some of them are
similar to your own. There is in your
terms art. There is in your terms music.
There are many different ideas, some
similar, some very diverse from your
own. We are always exploring and
learning. Many different endeavors, many
different expressions. I in that sense in your
expressions. I in that sense in your
classic vernacular would be considered a
pilot, an engineer, a sculptor.
And as you say, a
diplomat. These are the things that
excite me. Everyone does what excites
them the most with full integrity.
Beyond that, it is unlimited.
Do you? So, I'm sorry. Continue.
So, continue.
Do you have um an entertainment system
such as television or films the way we
do here? No. There was something similar
in what you call times past. Now our
society is in your terms mostly
telepathic information is simply sent as
you say from mind to mind. There are to
some degree within the spacecraft
recording devices but these are
completely what you would call
pneummonic and are accessed directly by
mentality into the computers. The images
simply unfold in our mind. They do not
have to appear on what you would call a
screen. Understand? So there's no
central uh place that sends out these
entertainment or other images to
individuals and that you could tune
into. There is one representative place
always on every planet of the
association that can function in this
way. But there is also a chamber on
every large citizens in a similar
fashion. And who creates these
And who creates these
images? Every individual does. I mean
that would if you have 200 million
people on your planet alone that would
be a lot of um frequencies. Well, not
every image is processed, nor does it
need to be. The idea will simply be,
however, that if an individual has a
specific desire for a particular access,
they will be able to get
it. Remember that all individuals,
including your own, on your own planet,
have access to all knowledge, especially
that knowledge that pertains most
directly to your
world. It is generally referred to as
aashic records. Understand? Uhhuh. It is
the storehouse of knowledge of the
infinite. We simply have to some degree
a modified mechanical representative of
that idea. It is a network once again of
idea. It is a network once again of
energy.
Terrific. But it is not
confusing. It overlaps. But any
individual who creates themselves to be
a particular frequency will only access
the particular information that is
aligned with that particular frequency.
They will not interfere with anyone
else's ability to access what
information they
need. Understand? It is holographic in
that sense. Does that make sense to you? It's
sense. Does that make sense to you? It's
falling into place. All right. Does that
serve you? It does. Thank you very much.
Well, thank you very much. Sharing.
Hello, Vishar. And are you a good day?
Um, I feel very strange in my life right
now. You know, how
exciting. exciting to feel strange in
your life. Do you know what the Twilight
Zone is?
[Music] Um,
Um,
I'm I'm having an operation tomorrow.
We've talked about it. It's not a
dangerous one. All right. And I'm
experiencing some fear that I don't
think is necessarily related to it. I
noticed that in my life I seem to have
completed most of the major things in my
life. I just uh separated from my
husband. Yes. My best friend um who I've
been in touch with many times a day for
many years has decided to live in
another country. No. Another close
friend that's been living with me has
just left tonight and on and on and on.
Think the the building that I live in
that I own is just empty. The tenants
are all gone. All you live there for
years. Time for a change then. And yeah,
it seems that I'm uh ending some this
facet of my life. All right. Are you
beginning another one? Well, that's my
question. I certainly hope so. Hope you
doubt it. Well, I have a little bit of
fear since I'm facing an operation in
the morning and and looking at
everything completing in my life
tonight. It's a I feel a little strange.
Well, all right.
I wonder if you can uh shed some light
on what's happening in my life now in
terms of these completions and the
Is there still something you want to do
in life? Yes. Oh, yeah. Lots of things I
want to do such as well one thing that I
want to do is have a satisfying
relationship.
All right why and I want to have
children a family I want to um be a
world diplomat. You and I have discussed
this. Oh yes a world diplomat. I I have
a lot of more books that I Hen do you
think that you can use what you call
this operation as a turning point as a
operation as a turning point as a
passing point as a
gateway that will allow you in a sense
in one
sense to allow the old you to
die and the new you to be born. Can you
change your energy in this operation?
Can you use it as a neutral gear to
elevate yourself to a different level?
To reconstruct yourself entirely, not
only physiologically but as a
physiologically but as a
person? Can you emerge from this
operation, this neutral, this twilight
zone as a new person?
I wondered if I was in the process of
doing that and that's why everything
seems to be completing. Yes. Well, I
wonder if it is that obvious.
Well, not everything is completing. It's
not. It feels very strange, Rash. I um
unusual synchronicity. So many things
completing. Oh, no, no, no, no. Not
unusual at all. Well, maybe for you.
Synchronicity is all there
is. Everything is always happening in
conjunction with everything else. When
you start to see that, that means you're
lining up. That means you are placing
yourself in alignment with the natural
flow of things. That means you are in
your own terms coming into that space
that allows you to truly see what you
are doing in a conscious fashion rather
than an unconscious fashion. You are
seeing the framework of creation at
work. Everything interconnecting with
everything else. All the timing exactly
where it needs to be. You are now seeing
the waves of change. That's what you're
seeing. So flow with it. Again, it is not truly
So flow with it. Again, it is not truly
an ending. It is a transformation.
Old cycles may be changing. Yes, you can
call it a completion of certain ideas,
but it is always, it must always be, no
matter on what level it is, it must
always be the beginning of other ones.
Always. Because you cannot be, as you
already know, created nor destroyed. You
can only change. So no matter what level
you do it on, it's always going to be a
transformation from one level to another
level. If you recognize that there are
ideas, as we have discussed, that still
represent who you are, then trust that
these kinds of transitions that you give
yourself in life that you attract into
your life, these limbo states, these
neutral states, this shifting of your
gears is for the very purpose of
allowing yourself to shift that gear in
the way that is most comfortable for
you. Since it is most comfortable for
you to do it as a society still in an
unconscious state, hence the
operation. It is one way for you to feel
that your power is being flowed through
other individuals and back to you and
that they are flicking all the necessary
switches for the next
phase. But it is your power. You are
shedding the light. You are closing down
the old cycle and awakening the new. But
you are doing it through beings who are
willing to be of service to you, those
that will do the
operation. There will be operations
taking place on more than just the
physical level. And you will be holding the
level. And you will be holding the
sharpest
knife. And you will be creating the
greatest changes. Mhm. Even though you
may not now be conscious of it, you are
beginning to be conscious of it. That is
your recognition. And after you come out of
recognition. And after you come out of
the operation, you will not be the same
person. You know that. Yes. Literally
not the same person.
So relax.
You are changing yourself in the ways
you know you need to to be who you say
it excites you the most to be.
So have a good time. Thank you. Well,
thank you. No accident. I'm having it on
the 13th which is the transformational
number. Transformational gate. Yeah. No
accident at all. You know what you're
doing. You know it's a very powerful
time of coming together of facing all
the different ideas that you are all
about. That's why the idea of the 13
number has always been so frightening to
many of you because it forces you to
face all the things within yourself that
many of you have not been willing to
face because it is the opening up of all
the things you have been taught to
fear. But you know you're strong enough
to process it into positive
transformational energy so it doesn't
faze you. Have fun. Thank you Bashar. All my
you. Have fun. Thank you Bashar. All my
love to you and all of our unconditional
love to you for being so bold. Shing,
the last time that I was here, I heard
you say that your strongest fear becomes
your strongest desire many times. The
idea, simply put, is that whatever your
strongest fear is, if it is more
overwhelming than your strongest joy,
will usually activate the negative
blueprint belief patterns within your
mind. Emotion, emotion, energy, motion
is the
activator. Therefore, if your strongest
emotion is one of fear, you will usually
attract the idea of all the negative
representations of that emotion.
I've thought about that every day uh
since you said that. Um, have you been
having a good time? Uh, yeah. I do what
excites me.
Uh, my life is about being of service
right now because, uh, I don't know what
else to do. Um, what else is there?
The thing that excites you the most is
what will allow you to be of best
service. Uh, my strongest fear I had
Uh, my strongest fear I had
uh I'm a sober alcoholic
and my entire contradiction.
Contradiction. All right. I heard Well,
I'm a person who doesn't drink anymore.
Oh, all right. Uh, then you are not
alcoholic. I don't know how that I understand the
I don't know how that I understand the
nomenclature that is used in your
society that an individual once this is
always that right but the idea is as we
have in that sense explained from our
point of view that if you truly become
another person you really don't have the
same history literally
that's too scary for me to even conceive
why um it's up to you I will not force
you to conceive of it but I am curious
why is that so
Uh
because I've been told that if I drink
that I'm going to die and my inner voice
is always telling me that I'm not an
alcoholic and that's not what we are
saying like work through this stuff and
become another person. One moment. One
moment. That's not what we are saying.
We are not saying that if you recognize
the idea that you are another person
that you have to contain the urge to
drink at all.
If you really are a person who no longer
needs that particular idea or that tool
or that outside
expression, you simply will not have the
urge to drink.
H understand. I haven't had that yet.
All right. I mean the obsession has been
relieved. But it's it's like a fantasy
there all the time pretty much. Fantasy.
Fantasy. Yeah. Um uh the what I want
what did I want to say? I wanted to say
that uh before that I quit drinking I
always had this natural knowing ever
since I was a child that I was always
going to be alone like alone in the
sense of like unmarried with other
children and that it was pretty
comfortable for me because my love
affair was with drugs and alcohol and
other obsessions. So now that uh I don't
have that, it's pretty much like turned
into a fear. Duh. You know, and other
people fulfill that
aloneeness, that feeling of aloneeness
with other, you know, like men and
women. Anyway, I just have this feeling
like once again allow us to remind you
and share with you something that one of
you shared with us. A very astute
perception that comes from your own
planet. Do not be surprised.
The idea simply is as this individual
suggested that you can pronounce the
word alone or you can pronounce it all
one. It is up to you understand that in
a sense you are alone because you are
the creator of your reality. You are the
one expression of the infinite within it
and in that sense there is only you
within that universe. However, you are
at the same time all one with all other
expressions. You are never
disassociated. You are never
disconnected. It is always both, not
just one or the other. Mhm. You are
always your own idea, your own complete
autonomous expression. And at the same
time, you are interconnected with
everything. Everything.
Everything.
Everything. Everywhere. Everyone.
Therefore, how you choose to look at
your connection
will utterly determine the feelings you
have about it. Once again, remember
perspective determines the reaction you
get. If you have a negative feeling, if
you have a fearful feeling, it's because
you are feeding into your perspective
negative definitions. I'm alone.
But if you understand that you can feed
in positive definitions, I'm all
one, then you will not have a negative
fear reaction. Mhm. Because a fear and
all emotions are only reactions to what
you believe to be true. They do not
exist of their own accord until you feed
them a definition that creates them to
react within you. That's the only way
you can feel that type of an idea to
create a definition first that feeds the
feeling and fans it into the flames of
your emotionality. So if you find yourself in
emotionality. So if you find yourself in
fear, then you are feeding in negative
definitions. If you don't prefer to,
don't rewrite the definitions in a
positive way. Rewrite them in the way
you prefer to represent yourself and
then feed that into your perspective of
life and that will determine utterly
what kind of emotions you feel from that
point forward. Understand? Mhm. The idea again
forward. Understand? Mhm. The idea again
simply is to really understand that
however it is you define yourself at any
given moment is literally truly really
the person you are at that moment.
You are not the old person struggling to
be different. You are a different
person. Literally. Yes. Yes. Yes. We know. We
Literally. Yes. Yes. Yes. We know. We
know. We know. Your faces look the same.
Right. Exactly. So what? That's just
outer appearance. And you know what you
say about the cover of things. They are
only covers. They are only
representational symbols.
Although once again do remember that the
more you really know you have changed
the more different you actually start
appearing to other people literally
physically because you do make the
change. It just takes you a little time
to physically show it because your
description and definition of physical
reality is that things take time to
shift physically. As we have said, we do
know of civilizations where when they
make a decision and change the person
that they are, their outer appearance
changes instantly. They are recognized by their
instantly. They are recognized by their
energy, not by their
face. But understand it is still no
different. If you really make a change
in your belief, in your emotion, in your
thoughts, you have changed the basic
structure of the persona. You are the
artificial construct. You are as a
personality. Personality is just a
projection of the consciousness of the
idea you are being at this moment.
Change any factor, any variable within
that equation, you are literally a
different person. If you are literally a
different person, you don't have the
same history. You don't have the same
past. You don't have the same
future. Literally, I am not speaking
figuratively. I am not speaking
philosophically. I am talking mechanics,
physics. You are not the same person.
You're not the same person now you were
two of your minutes ago.
Literally, the idea, the
notion of continuity is your
invention. It's your illusion. It's your
projection. It serves you, but it's
still your creation. The only reason you
experience continuity between the you
you are now and the you you used to be
is because that's the way you've been
taught to think. Because the definition
of your physical reality contains linear
time. I was this before. I am this now.
I will be this later.
But in a sense, even though it's the
same consciousness, the same overall I
as the person you are, it's not the same
you. So when the person you are says, I
was this before, well, I do not mean to
be derogatory, but that's a
lie. It's not
so. The you are now is whoever you
define yourself to be now and has really
not much to do with whoever you defined
yourself to be some time
ago. You can learn to live in the moment
that fully and you can learn that you
can be whatever you wish to be at that
moment and that anything you have ever
been therefore will not be tied to you
and whatever you define yourself to be
will be the only feelings you
have. Understand? Yes, I do. Is this
assisting you? Yes, it is. Well, thank
you very much. Thanks.
Pleasant dreams to you. And to you,
dream a sweet dream. I am doing so right
now. [Music] [Music]
Before we
continue, after your
break, I will to some degree discuss a
little more clearly the whole notion of
how it is in this state. we do in fact
perceive you and how in fact we do exist
relative to your dimensional
frequency. Continue.
Good evening, Bash. And to you. Good
day. Good day. Um I have a special
question. Oh, special question. Everyone
listen up.
In three in 3 weeks time I'm going to
experience a wonderful occasion in my
life. Oh, all right. What would that be?
Do you care to share? Sure. I'm getting
married. Oh, all right. Um, there's one
person that uh I'd like to be there on
that day and that person will not be
able to because she passed away many
years ago. So, I'd like to know whether
she will be there with me in spirit and
if so, how will I be connected? How long
ago in your terms of time? The term of
passage? About 10 years? Name of the deceased?
About 10 years? Name of the deceased?
Yes. Valerie. Full. Name? Valerie
Kennington, methodology of
death.
Cancer. One moment.
In a sense, the music of the spirit will
be there. The essence of the
consciousness will be there, but in a
larger form than you are used to
thinking of that individual
as it will not be confined to the
individuality it used to be. The essence
of the energy will be there. But the
aspect as you would understand it that
you are used to thinking of as Valerie
has already
incarnated. I shall say in your terms
reincarnated. However, the essence of
the oversoul, a projection of the spirit
will be there because simply you have
requested it. It takes nothing more than
that. As soon as you tune in to anyone
with your thoughts, you are in link and
whatever aspect needs to be
representative of that particular
reflection of the soul will be present
with you. Even if they have in your
linear terms of time
reincarnated, an aspect of their over
soul will be
present. Understand?
Yes. Is this making sense to you? Yes,
it does make sense because I've been
touched quite a few times in the past.
Now, there is also another individual
involved that might, let us say, and I
do not necessarily mean this to be
literal, that might be more considered
what you would call a grandmother energy
that is connected to that person you
have called Valerie and also to you and
to many other
individuals. To some degree, that has
been functioning as a spirit guide. this
grandmother energy and it is an aspect
of the soul that you knew Valerie to
be but it is not as confined or specific
as just the idea of
Valerie but it is an aspect of that
energy and it will be present even as it
is present now
that that doesn't surprise me all right
thank you very much thank you very much
and happy Okay,
shooting. Hello, Bashar. How are you? Good day.
Hello, Bashar. How are you? Good day.
I'm very excited to be speaking with
you. Always excited to speak with any of
you. I um I have a question about a
relationship that I was in and obviously
I'm still in. I feel
very I know it only changes. I I um I as
much as I try to get away from this
person, try try try try. Um he seems to
pop up at um pop pop up appear. Okay,
the most unlikely places. Oh, unlikely.
Unlikely. And uh I don't seem to be able to
And uh I don't seem to be able to
resolve and let go of that that
connection with him because I I seem to
fall right back into the same pattern.
And um we did share an awful lot. We had
a music project together and we still
have a a wealth of material that um I'm
not sure what to do with it. Do with at
the time. All right. Present time. So
I'm wondering if maybe I had a past life
connection. Yes. Yes. That's a given
with almost all of you. Anyone you are
physically close to, emotionally close
to in any life, you have had usually
many other lies with before. That's a
given. I guess I need to know whether
I'm supposed to let go of this person or
or if I'm supposed to visualize the
person. Does the definition does the
definition of the relationship serve the
definition you now believe yourself to
be? Yes or no? Uh what do you mean? Does
the as you define yourself, does that
idea, the definition of that
relationship fit? Well, obviously it
doesn't because I'm trying to pull away.
Why? Um I feel like
Um I feel like
I cannot fully express myself to this
individual. I I feel like um the
communication is blocked between us.
Well, one moment. One moment. Key
question. Have you on your own behalf
fully expressed yourself to this
individual? Are you simply saying that
that individual does not receive the
full expression? I believe. Have you
actually stopped yourself from fully
expressing yourself to the individual
because of your assumption they won't
receive it? No, I don't think so. I've
I've really um tried to um not try I've
I've really tried to express I've I've
expressed you
my desire for us to get some counseling
because there's obviously something very
strong between us and he's just not
really ready for that or all right then
be in the
relationship in whatever way it seems to
be m you may need to reflect to do the
things that will allow you to see the
fullness of your expression reflected
back. So I should just accept the fact
that we are not in communication and but
you are in communication and then simply
the idea is that if you have a
particular preference of how to express
yourself and you believe you are
actually doing that with integrity and
you're not getting a particular response
that is reflective of that expression
then you are in that relationship
perhaps to allow that individual to
learn the things they need to learn and
you are learning what you need to learn
out of it. But you do not have to in
your terminology assume for this is the
only thing creating the appearency of
the repetitive pattern. You do not have
to assume that you cannot attract other
relationships that can simultaneously
reflect whatever portion of yourself you
are willing to express to the fullest.
Okay. Understand? Yeah. So in the
meantime, what do I do with this body of
material music that we've written
together? Do I That's up to you. go on
on my own or try to Do you believe that
that individual would have some sort of
objection to you applying this idea in
whatever way you want to? I I've gotten
the indication that he might. Yeah. Then
let it go and create your own a I've
done that, but it doesn't seem to be in
the as good a form. It's not as good a
demo as the stuff that we did together
because of course it's start I'm
starting over in a way. So what what do
you mean of course? Well, I'm uh are you
in your own estimation complete without
him? Yes, I believe that. Well,
then it's going to be equal. It may be
different, but it is equal in its power
and its ability. I believe that, too.
I've just recently had to sort of take
over the responsibility of doing it all
myself. And it's it's a little
frightening at first, but um well, cuz
you I'm in a man's business that um I I
come I come up against a lot of um a lot
of
um obstacles I see. in terms of the only
ones you come up against. Or you may
recognize that many of them exist, but
the only ones you actually come up
against are the ones you buy.
Understand? Of course I do. All right,
then don't buy them. You may still
recognize them, but your path will go
through them, around them, over them,
under them. Okay. So, I should just just
stick my music out there and and no
matter what they say, just keep putting
it out. Do you believe you are creating
it to the fullest expressive ability of
your integrity and joy? Indeed. Well,
then need I say more? It is worth
putting out. Put it out. Let those that
will be reflective of a positive
response be attracted to you by the fact
that you are willing to have the
conviction to put it out. If you don't
put it out, how can you attract someone
who can hear your vibration? Well, I
get, you know, I get all these stories
like it's too off on guard. It's not
Well, those are stories, are they not?
They are stories. Well, what story do
you want to buy into? They're all
stories. They're all valid, but they're
all stories. They're all equal. Every
one of them has equal potential to be
realized in your life. Create the story
you prefer. Buy into that one. Okay, I
will. It's up to you. Your story is just
as valid as anyone's, is it not? Yes, it
is. Then tell a story and let others
hear it. I will. Thank you. Thank you.
[Music] [Applause]
[Applause]
Let it be obvious.
Hello. Uh hello. My name is Jerry. This
is my first experience. This is my first
experience with you. Yes. Um, my
daughter has recently started to
channel. Oh, all right. And, um, I have
some concerns and I'd like to know what
how it's going to affect her life and
mine and I need some help in in
recognizing. Well, can you answer a few
questions for me? I'll try. You don't
have to try. Thank you. I will. Thank
you.
Does she understand that fundamentally
channeling is really simply allowing the
full expression of the self to come
through in a trusted and loving way that
it is simply a creative expression to
begin with and does not have to involve
what you might classically call another
entity. I believe she does. All right. It can it
I believe she does. All right. It can it
can be a connection as such because
everyone is connected to everyone
else. Does she
believe and have a desire to do this
because of wishing to be of service in a
positive way? I would believe so. All
right. Does she believe that she will be
able to handle it?
Yes. All right. Does she believe that
there really is anything to fear in the
endeavor?
I can't answer that. All right. Does she
believe she is in control?
I I believe she believes she is becoming
in control.
Becoming one little secret you can
remind her. You're always in control.
Even if you create a scenario in which
it seems you're out of control, you're
creating that. So you're still in
control of it. And that is when an
individual as you say clicks into the
understanding that they always have been
in control. Then they can consciously
know they are in
control. Any agreement that has been
made between her and any other
consciousness will always be
representative of whatever pace she is
willing to move at. Nothing will be
pushed. nothing for that would not serve
the purpose. If the channel themselves
is pushed beyond what they believe to be
their capacity then they are not being allowed
capacity then they are not being allowed
to be the fullest individual they want
to be and therefore that does not serve
in a positive way the idea of the
connection. So she will never be pushed
faster than she can handle. You
understand? The control is always in her
hand. If she says stop, it stops. If she
says go, it goes. If she says go slow,
it goes slow. Oh, she says go fast. It
goes fast. She is in the driver's seat
completely. I believe she experienced
that what you just said. Then all you
really have to do is understand that the
only reason there would ever be concern
in the fearful sense is simply due to
the idea of doubting that your original
intention is not a under your control
under your conscious commandment and
that b somehow it might express a mind
of its own which it cannot do.
If that individual understands that they
made an agreement to be of service in
that way, all they will attract is a
positive vibration. And if that is their
frequency, that's all they will
experience. The idea of
fearing, of being negatively concerned
that something might creep in in and of
itself provides the
doorway for a negative
attraction. Understand? Yes. So the idea
is to trust. Trust that the original
intention was made with integrity. Trust
that the desire to be of service is
reflective of the understanding that
there is a positive connection and then
let it come through in a positive way.
Always understanding that she is under
control and has absolute final say as to
exactly how fast and far it goes.
Otherwise, it would not serve the
positive purpose because the channel is
also to be
served. The whole idea is not to give up
your life. The idea is not servitude.
life. The idea is not servitude.
The idea is to learn and integrate and
become equal to the idea because all
that is being reflected in any
channeling to each and every individual
that experiences the channeling is that
all of you are channels and all of you
are self-empowered and all of you have
the same abilities that you may see
expressed through any other channel. We
are functioning as a
mirror. You are the reflection.
Understand? Yes. So wish her pleasant
dreams and exciting life and also
express our thanks.
Does that serve you? Yes. Thank you.
Thank you very
much. One moment. One
moment. There will be some surprises in
the sense of an expansion of awareness
of what the energy is she is in contact
with within what you call the next 3
days to 3 weeks of your time within the
dream state. Sharing.
Sharing.
Hi, Bashar. And you good day. I have two
burning questions and they're quick. Can
I answer both of them? Burning question.
Well, they better be quick.
Don't want to hold on to them too
long. All right. Hurry up. The first
one. The first one. Um there's there's
an Indian folklore that I've heard that
says that crystals are the brain cells
of the planet. And since we're taking
out so many crystals out of the planet,
are we literally taking out brain cells
of our well to some degree there is
merit to this idea in the sense that if
you were to go into what you might call
a battery and remove some of its cells,
you might impair the efficiency of the
battery to
conduct to some degree. Yes.
Although because more and more of you
are beginning to recognize that you are
your own master
crystals, then pretty soon it will not
be necessary for the idea to experience
and express any but a
few utilizations of externalized tools
in the crystallin form. It is not a
serious idea at this point as you say.
It is not a serious depletion, but the
idea does have merit in the sense that
the crystals being naturally embedded in
your planet do conduct energy in a
specific way and they are located in a
specific area for a certain reason to
act as amplifiers and reflectors to the
energy that you are as a mentality to
remove them to some
degree can quote unquote impair the
efficiency of the
transceiver. But the idea is that you
can blend and balance these ideas out
through yourselves being the master
crystals being connected and grounded to
your planet crystal. Understand? Yes, I
do. So in time it will be such that you
will more often than not perhaps choose
a few crystals to represent the whole
idea and allow all the others to remain
where they lie.
Understand? Yes. Thank you. The other
question is you haven't talked for a
long time about the triad asani. Yes.
Earth and Sirius. Is there any new input
that you could add to that idea? Next
week of your time, a dialogue on Sirius.
Thank you. Thank you.
Shing. Hi Bashar. And a good day.
Hi Bashar. And a good day.
Um, first I want to say thanks to my
friend Ken because all of a sudden I
realized I had this question that I
wanted to ask so bad and my name wasn't
on the list and he came up and said,
"You can have my place." Oh. And things
like that keep happening. Oh, lovely.
Yes. Um, when I was uh I think about 5 years
Um, when I was uh I think about 5 years
old, I had an imaginary friend named
Gary and my parents used to tell me
about it. And they used to tease me and
my relatives and they'd always say,
"Make room in this chair because Gary
has to sit there." And I don't remember
really. I don't remember um the person.
I remember them teasing me, but I don't
remember the friend. And I just met
someone named Gary that when he told me
his name, all of a sudden I remembered
that. And I feel very strongly attracted
to this person. He's really attracted to
me. And so I just wonder if that had
And so I just wonder if that had
anything to do with my imaginary. Oh
yes. Because the idea is as a children
you still consciously recognize that you
are setting up
relationships for the life you have been
born into and you are in communication
very often as children when you have not
yet created the barriers to such
communication that very often you do as
adults and so you are in touch with the
individuals you have made agreements to
interact with in that physical life very
often. Yes. And many other connections
are understood by you as children that
you do not allow yourselves to remember
as adults. Although this is changing now
and that's why I don't remember when I
was young. Like I can't remember what he
looked like. Well, because you were
teased out of it.
Oh, understand? Well, how can I how can
I remember that? Why not? I mean, how
how can I can I remember what that was
like back then? Well, do you need you
now that the individual is
physiologically in your life?
I guess
one moment. One
moment. You can now from this point
forward cocreate interactive dreams with each
cocreate interactive dreams with each
other to quote unquote
recapture the original
communication. Understand?
Not exactly. had it. Have you ever had
what is simply called a common dream
with someone else where you have
dialogue with them in your dream and
have them remember the same dream? No,
not that I can remember. Well, you can
now. Your expression of affinity for each
Your expression of affinity for each
other, your love in that way for each
other can create you to operate on a
similar enough frequency so that it can
even extend into what you call your
dream realities. And you can interact
and you can recall everything you need
to recall about the dialogues you have
had in the past. But all of that will
come out in the interactions you have in
the relationship anyway. Oh, understand?
Uh-huh. Well, that was kind of what I
was wondering is because there's like
this really strong attraction between
us. Yes. This seems really silly, maybe
you would say. But but it he doesn't
ever call me. So,
and but like the other day, I ran into
him in a completely different city right
at the store. You are connected
synchronistically cuz that was I was really I was really
cuz that was I was really I was really
um driving myself crazy with that one.
How come he doesn't ever call me and uh
I guess I don't need to.
That may change, but obviously not at
this point. The idea is to simply
understand you are connected obviously
to recognize that connection and utilize
it in whatever way you really want to
know that you are in communication and
that you have been for years and years
and years and years and years for lives
and lives and lives and lives that you
have not been out of touch.
Understand? Yes. So open up to the idea
of dream communication and see what you
get. and he doesn't he isn't um doesn't
have these kind of beliefs about what
we're talking about and everything yet.
In the dream reality, you all know the
same things. No matter what the persona
things. No matter what the persona
limits itself to believe, in the dream
reality, you are all on the same level
and all free and have all the same basic
beliefs. That is why we are suggesting
that you can have the dream dialogue
first. set it up in the dream dialogue
even as you did when you were a child
and it can then manifest as you say leak
into your physical reality. The more you
talk in your sleep, the more you will
talk in your awake state, so to speak.
Well, that sounds fun.
Then see what it does for you. And so he
really is my imaginary friend Gary. My
little Well, not imaginary. No.
[Laughter] Imaginary
Gary. Understand that your imagination
is always
real. There are times when what you get
in your imagination may be more
representative of other dimensions of
reality that are not immediately
applicable to your dimension of reality,
but it is no less real. Understand? Mhm.
Everything you imagine is real
somewhere, somehow, somewhere because
you cannot imagine non-existence.
You are always tapping into some level
of reality. The doorway is what your
imagination is. The gateway to all
realities, all dimensions. They are all
real, even if they're not immediately
applicable in your
dimension. Understand? Mhm. But in the
case of forming agreements with other
individuals to be born in this physical
life, very often the idea of what you
call your imaginary friends of childhood
are many of the individuals you have
made such agreements with to meet as you
say later on in life and many times are
actually indications of interactive
communication with beings that are still
on what you call the spirit
realm and even sometimes communication
with some of us.
So even though he's a year younger than
me, um we were still communicating just
like our consciousness. Understand again
on the level of consciousness, you are
all infinite and eternal. You're all the
same age.
Okay? And a child knows this
instinctively. Remember that when you're
communicating on that level, you're not
children. Understand? Mhm. Does this
assist you? Yeah. All right, then.
Pleasant dreams. Okay. Thanks. Thank
you. Within 72 of your
hours, you will receive some interesting
information. Sh.
Hi, Bashar. And you good day. Good day.
This is only my second time here. So
although it's still my first, right?
Although I've never really heard you
speak very often, I feel like I've
been told much of what you've said.
There are many avenues through which the
information is being shared with your
planet now.
Right. And as a child, I believed that I
was already communicating with someone
on another planet and another imaginary
friend. I see. Right. And
um in that
communication and that education that I
started receiving as a very young child,
I was most interested and drawn
to looking at the relationships on this
planet and interreationships between us.
To me that seemed like that was my
teaching or that was my lesson and
that's what what I wanted to relate back
to the others to like report and even as
a child I remembered like going to
report to them about you know this is
very interesting humans are are very
interesting creatures and let me just I
have said that quite often
and I seem to have do that quite quite
often. Yes. So, and so my lesson now
though, and what I'm trying to get
clarity on is a particular relationship
that that I am in right now. And what I
was wondering
was what is it that Jamie and I are
supposed to learn so that we can be
together? One
moment. Any clarity for any relationship
can always be answered by the following
question.
What are you learning right now about
yourself by being in the relationship?
That's why you're in it. That's what you
need to learn. Well,
but what is it that we need to learn so
that we can What are you learning now
about yourself by being in the relationship?
yourself by being in the relationship?
That's what you need to learn.
M it will change what you learn. But the
idea simply is that at any given moment,
whatever you are learning about yourself
now that you can apply into the growth
of the idea and the definition that you
are is why you're in the relationship.
Any particular way you might choose to
express that idea of what you are
learning is up to you. Choose whichever
way excites you the most. Whatever it is
in life that does excite you the most is
what you are here to
do. Understand?
Yes, I suppose I was I'm looking for
some clarity perhaps
and perhaps I was curious as to what it
was that we've experienced together
before that might give some clarity as
to what we're experiencing. I understand
what you are saying and it is a valid
way to research yourself. But understand
that every individual has all the
ingredients necessary in their kit to do
whatever it is they need to do in the
present life by simply understanding who
they are in the
present. You can research the idea of
your past all you wish and it can
provide some illumination.
However, all the illumination can come
from the present if you are simply
willing to learn whatever it is you are
learning in the present in the
relationship and apply it in your
present life in whatever way it excites
you the most to apply it now. It will
serve the same
idea. We are usually reluctant to take
you back into the idea of focusing on
the past since so many of you in our
perception do believe that what you are
capable of doing now is utterly
contingent upon what you did do in the
past and that's not so. What you're
capable of doing now is what you're
capable of imagining you can do now.
Regardless of what you have done, what
you have done may allow you to
experience a flavoring of certain ideas.
It can enhance, we are not saying it
will not, it can enhance the
understanding of who you are in the
present, but you don't have to rely upon
that knowledge in order to be able to do
what you really want to do. An easy way,
however, to bring that up to light is to
simply ask yourself with your own
intuition and instinct, is there any
particular era in your history to which
you are more attracted than any
other? Yes. No.
When you think of yourself and that
other individual and you feel the energy
that both of you are together and then
take that
energy, feel the
energy. Where do you believe that energy
would feel most comfortable if you were
to project it into any particular epic
in your
past? Where does your curiosity attract
you? Do you want me to answer that or
can I just think about? I mean, but yes,
it would assist in the conversation.
Well, the actual era doesn't interest
me. It's then where's the lessons?
Are you attracted to any particular
Atlantis? I suppose. All right. All
right. But many of you in fact all of
you have been in Atlantis. France.
All right. I I'm not really there's many
many many many. Yes, there is. And
that's why you do not necessarily need
to pinpoint the idea of the past because
there is many pinpoint the idea of your
present. What are you learning about
yourself by being in the relationship?
How can you apply what you are learning
towards the expression of doing what it
excites you the most to do? That's the
purpose of your relationship and the
purpose of your life. this life to do to
the fullest the thing with full
integrity it excites you the most to do
and all relationships that you attract
in your life are for the purpose of you
getting out of those relationships
whatever it is you need to learn about
yourself in order to do that and to be
of service to the other individual or
individuals in that relationship to
allow them to learn what they need to
learn about themselves in order to do
that for themselves to express
themselves to the fullest that's the
purpose of your life
understand Mhm. Is this making sense?
Yes. Although I'm very clear about that.
So I'm just wondering why there's so
much confusion around the issue. What is
the confusion? And remember that
confusion is not necessarily negative.
It is confusion. Well, it's a it's a
confusion that keeps us from really
being together. In what way?
In what way? Of being together? Yes.
of being a team, a partnership team of
being being able to be together more and
to grow
together more. All right. But if you use
what you have now, that is what will
make room for something else to come in.
A change in that one or the influx of
something else.
Don't wait for the particular changes
you think you need to see before you are
willing to express the fullness of the
relationship that you have
now. Express the fullness you have now.
And that will create the momentum that
will allow it to change and accelerate.
Understand? Yes. Are you sure? Mhm.
Don't wait for what you might call the
ideal state.
be an expression of the fullness of the
relationship now
because if you wait for the ideal state
you will be waiting forever
because it will always change. It will
always grow. It will always move in
different directions and you will always
have the ability to create another
assumption of a new ideal state that you
are waiting to have happen before you
are willing to act in the expressiveness
of the relationship as it
is. Put out what you already have
learned. When you use what you have
learned, the relationship will see ah
she's using what we're giving her, so
we'll give her
more. If you're waiting around, nothing
more comes because you haven't used what
you've already
learned. You haven't expressed the
fullness of the relationship that you
are yourself
yet. Understand?
Yes. Is this making some sense to you?
Yes. Thank you. Well, thank you very
much. Thank you very much.
Shing.
Hi, Desai. And good day to you.
Um, you mentioned before how many of us
the people that we're close with that
we've shared past lives and my fiance
Dave and I have always felt that we have
shared. All right. Thank you very much.
And I was wondering if um we've been
very curious to know at what time in
what period in the past what kind of
relationship we had. You tell me. I
don't know. Yes, you do.
Have you had any dreams about it? No.
Dayd dreams? Sure. Well, tell me.
Not specifically. I mean, I thought
maybe don't invalidate it. Tell
don't invalidate it. Tell
me. Follow your
heart. Daydream now. Right now. But it's
more I feel daydream now.
Okay. It would be in Israel.
Israel. Why? How does it feel? Can you
describe it to me? Close.
Any further definition? Natural.
Natural. Any particular time frame?
Any particular time frame?
Biblical. All right. Any particular
biblical time frame since that seems to
cover quite a bit of time. Um when
Um when
the temple existed in when the temple
existed in um 70 BC maybe AD 70 AD 69
all right
67 68
69 how many changes did you go through
in what you call your year 67 68 69 of
your present counting
I don't No, I
don't understand.
In your terminology, were you
physical during what you call your year
1,967? Yes.
Yes.
What changes did you go
through in those three years?
I don't understand what you mean. In
this life,
do you remember any experiences that
would indicate a great change at that
time? No. In your estimation, in your
counting, what was your physiological
age at the time?
I can just guess that perhaps
1967. Oh, this Oh, this year. Oh, I'm
Oh, this Oh, this year. Oh, I'm
sorry. Um, I was Five.
Five.
All right. Then for your years five,
six, and seven, what were your
experiences in life? Happy. Yes. And and
did you have any particular attraction
to any particular things during that
time? Good family life. Good family life. All
Good family life. Good family life. All
right. And And nothing in particular.
Does anything else stand out for those
three years? No. 5 6 7
ask your family. Uh-huh. And see if it
ties in to the idea of your connection
to Israel. Now, that will be something
for you to explore in your own timing.
Mhm. But continue with your daydream for
now, if you
will. What kind of life did you live?
Now we are talking about the other 67,
68 and
69. Do you see a picture of yourselves
in your daydream? Farm life. Farm life.
All right. Spiritual, religious,
family life. Yes. Children.
All right. Anything else? No.
Do you feel some form of strength of
connection to this individual through
that particular feeling then? Yes. You
feel contempt uh in that way with each
other. Uh-huh.
Do you find that you are therefore
focusing on the idea of the creation of
a similar daydream in the present life?
similar daydream of family life. Yes.
How does that feel?
It feels um that's what I want to
happen. Do you feel stable when you
think of the earth? Yes. Do you feel
close to the earth in that way? I think
so. Are you under the perception that
you are building your own temple in that
sense? Yes.
Are you capable of interacting
physiologically with your mother? Yes.
Interact and ask about the
idea of some of your focus between your
years in present life of five, six and
seven and see if anything comes up. All
right? But again do understand on a general
But again do understand on a general
level it is not always that paramount
that you tap into the idea of the past
life situations. You have all had
hundreds thousands of past lives as you count
thousands of past lives as you count
time. The idea is to focus on your
energy now. Right? Anything that needs
to come up will come up. And do
understand this. You are always having
bleedth through from other lives anyway.
But the usual way you will experience
the bleedth through not only from other
lives but other dimensions will be in a
way that you recognize as having to do
with the life you're living now. So you
may not recognize it as a bleed through
because it will always come in the form
that serves you in the life you're
living now. But a lot of the information
and a lot of the attractions and
curiosities and fascinations and ideas
that you have in this life are also
bleedthroughs and crossovers from your
experiences in many other lives. because
all your lives are going on
simultaneously right
now. Your idea of linear time is your
convention. But is it is it possible to find out
But is it is it possible to find out
specifically or is that basically
irrelevant? It is.
Everything has significance. Uhhuh. One
way is to simply once again go into your
daydream and understand that your
imagination is real. Uh-huh. And trust
the images you get. Even if they are in
your terms symbolic, they will still
carry with them the feeling that you can
assimilate into your being and that is
what will serve you. Sometimes you can
have very as you say literal images but
not always does the literal image really
serve the essence because many times the
literal image of a life then doesn't
really fit into the literal images of
the life
now. Understand? Mhm. But always
symbolically it will fit. In essence it
will fit. So take the essence. That is
our strongest suggestion. All right.
Understand? Yes, I do. Thank you. And
enjoy your life. I will. Well, thank
you. Thank you.
Thank you for being so down to earth.
Hi, Bushar. Thank you. Good day. Um, I
have a question. Oh, all right. Real
important. Oh, real important. Um, I'm
supposed to be going on a
journey to take a visit to a mother ship
and Lord Mona came to me with some
information and I hate to use the word
fear but I want to go so badly. I hate
to use the word
fear but you can use the word hate. All
right.
What I'd like to know is I feel hesitant
yes on going even though I want to go.
One moment.
The terminology as we perceive it from
our dimension of
experience maca is representative of a
level of consciousness. It is not
absolutely tied into one singular
being and it is a symbol for you to home
in on as an energy beacon.
The invitation in that sense doesn't
literally come from one singular being.
It is an energy vibration to allow you
to align and fix in home in on your
ability to expand your consciousness to
the point where you can
perceive yourself in connection with
what you call those city ships, those
mother ships. What is there to fear in
your estimation? What definitions do you
contain within you that would allow you
to generate the idea you are hating to
call fear?
I'm afraid that I won't come back.
Oh, no. No. I know that that's that
that's not going to happen, but is there
some insight that you could give me on
why they want so badly for me to go
because it's all happened in the last I
would say month. The idea is not that
they so badly want it. The idea is that
you are simply becoming so sensitized to
your timing that you are experiencing
their knowingness of the timing in a way
that makes them seem anxious. They're
not anxious at all. They trust the
timing. It is simply that you aren't
getting the full brunt in a very short
period of time of their absolute
recognition of the agreements that you
made. It is not that they are pushing
you. It is simply that the energy is
that strong of their awareness of the
agreements you have made.
understand. Mhm. Go at your own timing.
Whenever you feel comfortable, they will
always be there. They will always be
there. They're not hurrying you up. It
is only the ideas and the definitions of
your own society, quote unquote, the one
you have been born into this time, that
is creating what you are perceiving to
be anxiety on their
part. But they are in no rush. They
trust the timing. It is simply that the
intensity of their focus is being
translated by you as
anxiety because that is the way many of
you translate that degree of
intensity. Understand? Mhm.
So I think that ought to do it. All
right. Do understand this. Always always
you can create a little well I'll call
it for now a test as to your
returnability.
And that is once again simply that if
you really really really really as you
say really really
really have created it to be time for
you to go. You can always test it out by
lying down, closing your eyes, taking
three deep
breaths, and saying to yourself, "All
right, I really am done. I can now go on
to another level. I'm done with
everything I agree to do by being born
into the physical Earth at this time.
and I really am finished. Close your
eyes, breathe easily, and wait 3
minutes. If at the end of 3 minutes you
can open your eyes, you're not going
anywhere.
Can I tell you something? So, if you
wish, you can do that a few times first
and then understand you can participate
in any kind of a journey you wish to. If
you are simply clear about the
understanding that you chose to be born
on earth to perform a service and that
the information you will learn in those
linkages will give you the ability in a
sense and expand your ability to perform
the original service. Then you will
understand in all reality and in all
likelihood you will actually be that
much more strongly connected to the idea
of the earth because you will become so
much more involved in your willingness
to be of service in that way.
Understand? Mhm. And of course,
paradoxically, the more willing you are
to live in the moment and be of service
in that way by doing what excites you
the most, the more free you are to
actually go anywhere.
Doesn't that serve you? Yeah, that's
perfect. Thank you. All right. Then
simply whatever your translation of, let
us say the mocka frequency is home in on
it and be at home not only there but
where you are. For that is the whole
idea to create your earth to be a
representation of what you are now
remembering have been other homes for
all of you. It is not to run away to go
home. It is to create earth to be your
version of that home so that you can
meet us
halfway. Heaven on
earth. Understand? Does that assist you?
Yes. Thank you. Well, thank you very
much. Pleasant dreams to you and
pleasant projections.
Shedding. Hello, Bashar. Good. Good day.
Good day. I'm confused and I'm hoping
you can sh How exciting. Isn't it fun?
Yes. I love it. State of unlocking, a
limbo state in which you can decide what
is true for you now. Yes. Of late, my
passions have been uh toward
understanding Earth's development in
connecting with other entities, other
life forms, other souls, if you will. Uh
I have felt deep down inside truly that
as beings create their own ability to
connect with other beings that they will
be peaceful and that that connection
will be of the heart. Well, yes.
Especially if you begin to recognize
that as you connect more and more, as
you say, solidly with other beings, you
start to realize that all you're doing
is connecting with reflections of
yourself. Anyway,
the confusion comes in the belief that
all perspectives are real, all
perspectives are true, all perspectives
are valid, and none greater than any
other. Yes. And that there truly are not
peaceful perspectives. And that my
beliefs that out in the connection is
going to be peaceful is only as valid as
that. One moment. One
moment. There is on a fundamental level
positive integrative and negative
segregative energy. So all perspectives will be
energy. So all perspectives will be
based in one of the two. And in that
sense on the very fundamental level you
can say there are peaceful perspectives
and unpieaceful perspectives because
they are all entrenched in either the
idea of accelerating a positive and
integrated point of view or a negative
and segregative point of view. They are
all equal. They are all valid in that
sense. But that doesn't mean you still
cannot have a preference for either an
integrative direction or a segregative
direction. Understand? Yes. I'm
confused, however, at the sense that
there may be uh a planet with a life
system that has developed with a warlike
mentality that can enter into this. You
mean such as your own? Such as our own.
Absolutely. Absolutely. who enters into
space um with with the intentions of of
conquering. I understand. But do
understand something else. Individuals
with that intention do not really get
very far.
And the idea is also that your energy as
a world now has changed sufficiently so
that even if there should be close at
hand another civilization that had
similar intentions, they would be
hardressed to even find you now because
your vibration is a little bit too
different than a society that would
actually push themselves into space with
a completely warlike intention. The idea
also is that traveling in space is
actually traveling
within. And true quote unquote I will
say for now space
travel is not the idea of what your
technology is right now where in a sense
you are sliding around on the surface of
space. When you actually understand how to, as
When you actually understand how to, as
you say, breach through the barriers of
space and time itself, that requires a
very highly integrated attitude. And a
highly integrated attitude makes it very
unlikely that you will be of a warlike
nature. Otherwise, you will not get very
far or even if you make the attempt at
all, you are liable to find yourself
quite dispersed at the other
end. Understand? So the idea of warlike
planets in conquering modes can and has
happened, but they are usually relegated
to certain levels of dimensionality. And
many times that means that they actually
have to even be in physical proximity to
each other. Understand? Yes. In our
other. Understand? Yes. In our
perception.