we have an announcement from Margot
chandley please I just want you all to know that
please I just want you all to know that
the book new metaphysics by Bashar and
the association is now bound and in
actual cover and signed by Daryl
cover and signed by Daryl
personally and these are the limited
editions he did he sat out in my car and
signed 60 of them
so I just want to know anyone who who's
interested in in having one of these
limited editions please come and see me
at the table during the break okay
thanks why uh before we start I'd like
to thank all of you for coming tonight
and remind everyone once again uh
particularly for those who might be new
that what we like to do simply because
of the amount of people that are in
these sessions to give every one an
opportunity to come up to the microphone
and ask what they want to ask in the
line uh attempt to consolidate your
question or whatever you want to talk
about down to the single most important
idea and ask one question if Bashar
carries it a little further by all means
go with him but attempt to keep it to
one idea one thought and just so we can
get as many people as possible who would
like a chance to interact up to the
microphone this evening and uh
theoretically that'll also help you
focus in on exactly what it is you
really want to talk about what's really
important to you in this particular
interaction so uh do that and uh again
thanks for coming all of you have a good
time and I'll see you later
all right I'll say how are you all this
evening of your time as you create time
to
exist allow us to begin this interaction
this evening of your time with a
suggestion if you wish a
m and if you wish a favor all
right the favor I will ask and what can
be considered in a sense a modotto of
any interaction we have with
you will be
to
please please please please
please do not
believe anything I say just because I said
anything I say just because I said
it
understand this is all about
self-empowerment it is all about your
recognition of your ability to create
the lives you wish to create we are more
than willing to function as Reflections
to serve you to share with you to love
you to interact with you to play with
you but remember that we are all you and
us teachers and Learners equals in that
way we all have our own
perspectives and we simply function as
Mir to reflect once again to you the things
to reflect once again to you the things
you already know within you to show you
to allow you to be aware of things
within you that you can then decide are
what you prefer ideas perspectives
methodologies in Life or you can decide
you do not prefer them it is up to
you this evening of your time let us
discuss and this can be your
and this can be your
entitlement intuition and
intellect for many of you being such a
polarized Society have considered these
Concepts to be something that have
nothing to do with one
another as many polarities are created
in your Society very often you have
forgotten that they both must come from
a single Source at the center that has
created both polarities so Instinct Instinct
intuition and
intellect reason yes they are polarities they are
reason yes they are polarities they are
dichotomies it seems in your Society but
they are actually simply variations or
if you wish degrees of the same
consciousness of the same energy like
anything is
is
Intuition or what may call Instinct as
you recognize it in what you call the
animal kingdom is the same type of energy the
kingdom is the same type of energy the
same type of Consciousness that you
utilize when you allow yourself to
become self-aware in an analytical
intellectual reasoning focused idea it
is the same Consciousness the animals in
a sense are self-aware it is simply that
they do not have the degree of
Persona focus in the same way that you
do it can be said that Consciousness in
its natural homogeneous State when it is
all that
is under those
degrees of focus of self-limitation of
self compaction the animal level of
compaction the animal level of
Consciousness represents to some degree
one level of compaction but the
analytical the intellect ual Focus
represents a higher degree of compassion
that is all that is the only difference
between intellectual and
Instinct this is one of the reasons why
in having created the polarity in your
Society of scientific
thought and belief on faith while you
have created such a polarity and
sometimes such a war between these two
ideas for each side
fears the other side for what it
believes to be an absolute opposite of
the way it chooses to function and it
fears to incorporate blend and balance
the other side for fear that they will
lose what perspective they have rather
than recognizing they will simply gain
an opportunity to blend and balance that
perspective with another aspect of the
same Consciousness it is not truly
opposite in the sense that it has
nothing to do with the way you might
think or you might feel your scientists
in that sense have simply been hesitant
to rely on instinct or intuition because
when you begin to do that you soften the
focus of your persona and it does quote
unquote not allow for as high degree a
concentration of compaction of analysis
intellectualization rationalization and the like but in no
rationalization and the like but in no
way shape or form does it mean that
intuition is an invalid way to access
information and those that are more in
your terms instinctive do not have to
fear they will become trapped in a
quagmire of tunnel vision if they simply
are willing to adopt aspects of blending
in
reason and
intellectuality these ideas can be
Blended can be
balanced one is simply an extension to a
higher degree of the other but it is all
one conscious
this is one of the reasons we have
discussed many times why in a sense
animal Consciousness is an extension of
you and in a sense you are an extension
of it you are reflections of each other
what you call Instinct and intellect are
simply different degrees of the same
Consciousness different
applications if you
will you can blend and balance these
things and it will not be at the cost of
your reason nor will it be at the cost
of your intuition you will have both
both will be applied when and where they
are needed both are natural in that
sense natural to anything that considers
itself to be a sensient
being it is one of the things that is
representative of the blending and the
balancing going on in your
transformational age you are never now after what you
age you are never now after what you
have been through going to become
absolutely 100 100%
instinctive you are not going to become
100% intellectual in blending both you will
intellectual in blending both you will
be able to apply where necessary and
when necessary all attributes remember
that fourth density is the integration
of everything you have ever been not the
exclusion of it it is the integration of
all of it and the use of all of it when
and where it applies in perfect timing
in total trust with absolute
Clarity of reason and insight in both
senses of the term you all follow
along so the idea of any interaction
with us whether you choose to use
Intuition or intellect in interacting
with us allow us to remind
us allow us to remind
you that the idea is of
balance not the idea or or another has
to overcome the other way but of
balance of
allowance of
trust of
integration at this timing allow us to
extend once again to each and every one
of you
our utmost appreciation in your
willingness to co-create this
interaction to allow us to share and
drink deeply of the Consciousness that
you are
uniquely to give us an appreciation of
the differences and the diversity you
have created yourself to be and simply
to have fun with you to share to play to
love to grow together as equals in our
own ways
for this gift I ask you now how may I
serve youw yours
are it does not belong to
me thank you
shutting good evening Bashar to you and
to you uh three months ago um you shared
some guidance with me about singing I'd
asked you about singing and how I could
go about bringing that excitement into
my life and you told me to just do it to
sing and incorporating that and with
being present in the moment so that
opportunity confine me yes to act like a
singer so you will have the light of a
singer yeah exactly I have started
singing professionally thank and I sang
with Steven H CPR last Sunday night at
the closing of the um Crystal Congress
did you have a good time I had a ball it
was incredible it was wonderful and then
the next then Monday I sang for um the
soundtrack of six videos the soundtrack
no stopping you now no with Neville r
and i channeled mermaids and it was like
and dolphins and it was so wonderful and
I I just wanted to share that excitement
with you and thank you thank you for no
longer waiting to be who you knew you
were and are yeah I was Wonder thank you
thank you you are welcome and my
question is do you have any information
about a mineral uh by the name of
sugilite and would you share that with
me it is in your terms connected
obviously to the crown vibration in that
way understand violet light yes and
because many of these things are now
gaining predominance in your Society
because you are now becoming aware of it
because it seems new to you it is simply
a synchronistic indication of the areas
that you are now moving towards in terms
of light vibration The Violet Crown area
you are all accelerating up it can be as
a trigger as a tool as a symbol very
conducive for many individuals to put
them in touch with those aspects that
represent their astral selves in that
way and perhaps allow there to be more
release in the sense more blending in
the sense of the non-physical and the
physical Realms more communication so
that becomes more natural for you to
understand there really is no difference
between them that you can blend them
together it can be used in that way it
is one way some of it also has to do and
will perhaps evoke in some of you
connections into what you may
colloquially call quote unquote now I do
not mean this in the sense to elevate
anyone judgmentally above anyone else
but to connections of royalty that all
of you have had in that way lineages in
that sense the
recognition of the idea of royalty in
the meaning that you all have that Inner
Glow the higher light that you are all a
royal lineage when you choose to believe
yourselves to be that you all can have
the perspective of the Violet Ray that
allows you to penetrate and see through
the dimensions that interconnect your
world to all other worlds that
understanding that was had in Egyptian
times and Atlantean times and sometimes
in what you would call your Renaissance
period where there was a strong
attachment to the idea and why not only
because of the scarcity of die for that
is no accident purple became the Royal
color understand yes does that assist
you yes very much thank you very much
thank you there are a few more things
you may discover on your own and there
will be a few more things that other
individuals who are working from a
different perspective now will start to
release as ideas that that mineral can
be used for within your Society within
the next year of time there will be more
understandings more
applications some of it has also in
small amounts a very
pacifying aspect as it to some degree
can represent a higher vibration of the
rose quartz you follow me yes so it can
be a very deepening and a very passioned
enriching of the heart vibration for
some individuals sometimes it may invoke
individuals sometimes it may invoke
memories of the
use of blood in your Society or what
blood symbolizes that deep rich
idea of the Violet that allows you to
know you're on the verge on a threshold
of a
transformation understand yes New Life
blood in that Way New Life blood good
thank you kindly thank you
sharting greetings Pasar and you goodbye
uh may I ask a question about some
things that were discussed last week ask
all right uh you were discussing the
overso and showed a wonderful Matrix of
all past lives and how it all goes about
my question is if we had made a certain
Soul judgment for ourselves before
incarnating guys can we talk to the
overso and can and change it to some
degree yes you have a great degree of
flexibility within the original ideas or
agreements you have made they are not as
restrictive as you think and A change is
not necessarily a change of the Primal
agreement but simply a change within it
a change to do something in a different
way still fulfilling the agreement
rather than the old way you used to
fulfill the agreement you understand yes
so those changes can occur even within
the agreement they do not have to be
looked at as needing to change the
entire overall agreement because the
majority of the agreements you make
before you are physical are General and
not always very specific oh I okay
understand yes General themes you agree
to play out but you have the ability to
decide and change at any time in your
life how you play those themes out that
doesn't affect the other Matrix of all
the other lives and Incarnation yes to
some degree it does any change will in
that sense affect it any change in you
in the present changes your past and
your future but that doesn't mean that
it's a cancellation of the original
agreement it simply means it can be a
continuation of the original agreement
in a new way understand yes does that
serve you yes thank you well thank you
very much Shing hi Bashar hi uh I'm going to
much Shing hi Bashar hi uh I'm going to
ask two questions because a friend of
mine could not come back this week she
was on The Leftovers so I have question
leftovers all
right um okay her question is in regards
to can you give us some insight as to
why and the wherefore of the uh death of
the dolphins on the East Coast what that
is as to some degree it still ties in
with some of the magnetic fluctuations
that are going on upon your planet the
Dolphins can be just as easily confused
as many of you with some of the
fluctuations that are going on
understand yes they guide themselves
along electromagnetic lines and
sometimes shift in those electromagnetic
lines will divert them from the
direction they actually prefer to go
into thinking that they are heading that
way when they are not in other words it
confuses their magnetic sensing devices
to some degree but an overall reason to
still interact with your Humanity in any
way shape or form they can Will Allow
some of them to choose ways that may
seem drastic to you but will bring to
your awareness the fact that they exist
and will allow you to stretch your
hearts out to them so that in that
stretch even if for what seems to be a
negative reason there will be contact
which can then be transformed into
positive interaction you follow me yes
but what what is the symbolism what are
they trying to get us to understand on a
fundamental sense that you are one
society that you need to interact with
them that you are two alien species on
one planet they are sensient beings like
you humans are not the only aliens on
Earth aliens to us that is Dolphin
satation whale that is the second alien
species upon Earth you have been
segregated for a very long time it is
time now to blend and B and become one
Society interacting helping each other
sharing with each other playing with
each other to become the one world that
will allow you to interact with other
whole integrated worlds that's the
fundamental reason for the interactions
Now understand yeah I just don't to see
what the death how that is going to
incorporate people to to play more the
idea is that certain individuals in your
Society are only enticed when others are
in your terms in
trouble understand yes sometimes s what
you call tragedy is the only way to
reach some of your hearts and so they
will be willing to do
that understand yes uhhuh does that
serve you yes yes uh and my question is
uh I've been going through a lot of uh
disorientation how exciting yeah right
in time with everyone else who is
disorienting from their old reality and
orienting toward a new one what reality
do you prefer to orient to in an
orientated one that's as soon as you
make a choice you will Orient into it as
soon as you make a choice and act on it
are you doing what excites you the most
in line uh yes somewhat yes someone well
I I thought that perhaps um with you
having the hotline uh me yes well you
have one to you know I know but there's
some interference on my line obviously
obviously it is not obvious at all to me
oh well then I guess I'm just not
getting the messages uh clearly to to
assist in my getting out of uh I the
upheaval that I seem to be going through
with decisions and activities in my life
there doesn't seem to be a sense of
direction are you doing at any given
moment the thing that excites you the
most that you're capable of doing at
that moment or are you waiting for
something better to come along before
you act well
are you invalidating the things that
excite you in the moment because they
seem in that sense frivolous and not
connected to the things you think you
want to do on the
surface well I seem to have an Mo of
doing too much in life at times so I'm
trying to pull back from that and allow
more what do you want to do what is the
thing that excites you the most and are
you doing all these other things because
you don't believe you can do the thing
that excites you and you feel you have
to do a lot of busy work in order to get
yourself to a point where you can do the
thing that excites
you does something excite yes what is it
okay there's a move that I want to do to
the to the west side of town all right
okay and there seems to be a lot of
activity that's getting me nowhere with
that why do you want to move because I
don't like where I'm living all right
what do you want to do in life what
excites you besides the idea of the
you besides the idea of the
move well my career excites me well
thank you which excites you more the
career or the move well the career well
then why are you focused on the move
which is only one of the details that
will fall into place automatically when
you act upon the thing that excites you
the most well you see that's what I
don't have a lot of trust in because I
don't see how my pursuing of my career
is going to bring that about why
not just I just don't don't see it that
way why
not may I ask you a question question
sure would you like to see it that way
sure then see it that
way okay believing is
okay believing is
seeing not the other way around you have
to believe it before you will see it but
if you believe it you will see it I
guarantee it well isn't there any kind
of even mini manifestations that can
happen along the way to give the faith
of yes in a sense there are but again
they also take believing is seeing you
have to take the first step before you
see a change in scenery mhm otherwise if
you don't move nothing will change
around you apparently you will stay
quote unquote where you have always been
until you take the first step but I am
changing my belief system all right okay
but you have already expressed a
reluctance to trust that you can change
it as quickly as you wish to not
believing or not willing to believe that
if you simply act upon what excites you
the most that all the other details will
take care of themselves automatically to
allow you to continue to do what excites
you the most if doing what excites you
the most
requires that you be in a living
situation that allows you to be happier
than where you are now then it will
automatically have to be attracted into
your life otherwise you won't be able to
do what excites you the most and that
won't happen that way act upon whatever
you are capable of acting on in what
excites you the most and all the details
and circumstances and situations and
relationships that have to be there to
support you in what excite to you the
most will come to you and then all you
have to do is act on them when they come
because you'll recognize them when they
come and it won't be a difficult
decision understand yeah I guess I was
just sensing some blockage and I thought
you might be able to but blockage is
only unwillingness to move in the
direction that is actually most obvious
MH that is all a blockage is it is lack
of trust that's it mhm that is all a
blockage is none of you ever have any
real blocks it is simply a lack of
willingness to believe that what you
really know is what you really
know plain and simple you are more
willing to complicate it and say Well
there must be something here I'm missing
it can't be that easy it can't be that
simple it can't work together it can't
dovetail in one thing doesn't fit into
another it doesn't appear to be
connected I can't do this and
automatically have that why not why not
why not all these things that you are saying
not all these things that you are saying
are merely assumptions they are merely
beliefs you have been taught they have
no more fundamental reality or solidity
than anything else you can decide what
system of interconnected creative
reality you prefer to believe in and
that's the one that will work for you
all beliefs all beliefs generate their
own self-perpetuating systems of support
that's why they are all true they're all
real they all work it is simply that
when individuals upon your planet in the
past have found that one particular
system works for them they create the
assumption that therefore that's the
only system that works forgetting
completely that before they found that
system another system worked for them
just as
well and realizing then that all systems
work when you believe in them you can
then appreciate the fact that different
systems are simply different expressions
of the same one all that is manifesting
itself in all the different ways that it
can so when you define definitions
so when you define definitions
definitions definitions when you define
the system you prefer and act like you
believe it will work just as validly as
any other system you have lived in that
you have created it will work for you
just as strongly as any other system and
you don't have to say well the other
systems haven't worked for me yes they
have because what you get with a
negative belief is a negative working
system so when you say well I don't
believe I'm capable of this or I believe
this will not happen that's what you get
something that does not work that does
not happen you get an absolute 100%
reflection of what you believe in most
strongly so when you change your belief
you will change the apparatus the
mechanism by which you create your
reality and you will get that feedback I
guarantee it yes I know it's a matter of
trust but if you know it's a matter of
trust then simply saying it's a matter
of trust and not acting as if you
believe that then is simply an
excuse because if you know you have a
habit it's no longer a habit it's just
an
excuse understand I guess I guess what
is not clear um well I guess I am
changing my belief system and I still
don't see the manifestation there of
don't put an expectation in the way you
think you ought to see it let it come in
a way that it will come along the path
of least resistance because you don't
necessarily have the analytical ability
to understand all the ways that it could
come M and when you focus on the one way
you think it should come you shut all
the other doors through which it might
come quicker MH understand open up
that's what trust is all about saying
all right all right this is what I
believe I need but this is what really
excites me so if I act upon what really
excites me in any way shape or form that
I can I will trust that all all the
other circumstances that I really need to be
circumstances that I really need to be
allowed to continue to act upon what
excites me the most in highest ecstasy
will fall into place make themselves
obvious and then I will simply act upon
them when they occur even if they are
not what I originally expected don't you
want some surprise in your life sure I
have surprises every day all right let
them be positive Surprises by allowing
yourself to recognize that if you simply
move in the direction of what excites
you the most all the ingredients will
fall into place to allow you to continue
in that same
direction understand it does work it's a
simple mechanism but you'll have to
trust it believe in it and act upon it
before you will allow yourself to see it
work but it will work I guarantee it
there are no exceptions not even you
okay okay thank you thank you
[Applause] one moment remember that for many of you
one moment remember that for many of you
in exploring what your beliefs are that
is also as you say critical to use the
situations you are creating to get in
touch with what you believe that created
the situation you are in and allow
yourself to understand whether or not it
is an issue of believing that you
deserve that things can change for many
of these things you have hidden in your
unconscious and subconscious sell you
have created the UNC conscious and
subconscious self to hide these things
within so whatever process you are going
through now it is giving you the time to
discover all the things within yourself
so that you can then have a complete
enough definition of what you are doing
so that then if you don't prefer it you
will have a complete enough definition
to change into one that you do
prefer continue hello bishar andto you uh since
continue hello bishar andto you uh since
we choose our lives and and who we're
going to have agreements with basically
yes I was wondering why you chose to
live in essani and if you could tell us
about some of your past lives it is very
much
fun one of my past lives is the physical
channel before you now and the reason I
chose that the only life I've ever had
on your planet was to do the
facilitations we are doing now so I
would have a model of an understanding
of your Society through the experience
of my past life upon your world
otherwise you would be far too alien for
me to understand and I would have no way
of relating to you in the way that I
am other past lives have been on
essani other lives have been on other
civilizations other worlds some of which
you may call Sirus and other
connections the ones on nasani are not
unlike what you would call your historic
Panorama of
lives in ancient times and so on and so
forth with different degrees of levels
of technology and Society
and so on you understand mhm is there
something specific you wish to know
other than the fact that where I am now
is obviously where I choose to be so I
can be of service in the way I am being
of service because that's what I want to
do I'm I'm interested in how life
differs on as soci to here do you have
families the same way that we do not
exactly no to us the idea is that every
single member of our society is quote
unquote not in the same way you mean it
married to every other member of our
society We Are One family and in a sense
we consider you to be a part of our
family as well even though some of you
may not the idea simply is that we do
not recognize the same degree of
separations we are telepathic in that
way and the children are the children of
all the adults are the parents of all
even though the children recognize what
you would call their biological parents
and vice versa but anywhere the child
winds up they are with the parent they
need to be with to learn the things they
need to learn to be who they chose to be
in our society to be of service in the
way they chose to be of service that is
how our family operates in absolute
trust in absolute spontaneity in
absolute Joy understand yes it's kind of what
Joy understand yes it's kind of what
we've termed a communal Utopia here that
we've tried to achieve in certain areas
it is what you are transforming into but
it is not what you would colloquially
call a naive state of existence as some
individuals have termed your so-called
Utopia it is simply absolute trust and
in absolute trust it is absolute
workability because everyone knows that
everyone is there to be of service and
therefore all have what they really need
because all are willing to supply what
everyone else needs and in turn they are
supported by the whole that is what your
Society is transforming into to some
degree and that is why your vibration is
now enough like our vibration to allow
us to be able to interact with you and
reflect these things to
you if you were not close to that
vibration we could not interact with you
in the way we are interacting with you
now understand yes I do does that serve you
understand yes I do does that serve you
it does thank you very much well thank
you very
much Shing hello Bashar hello um my
father asked me to read a book called
Holy Blood Holy Grail and it's a story
that they well it's information that
they've just found that could possibly
be a connection between um Jesus and
Mary Magdalene in that they were married
and had children not in the sense that
you understand it not in our perception
not that way no okay and so they did not
have children and they are not
culminating their line in Pierre
plantard in uh France then not directly
as you understand it no okay not
literally there is some symbology to
this that in your terms is true but not
literally in that sense it is a part of
the overall play that is still going on
and what you call Magdalene is one of
the aspects of Christ Consciousness as
was what you call Mary which was
actually in your terms a manif estation
of the Christ Consciousness the feminine
aspect of the Christ Consciousness that
gave birth to itself as a male and was
she was she actually a woman that lived
and was was both both Mary yes both
mares both okay and this book talks
about Pier plantar being the uh King who
who will come again in terms of
governing but not ruling understand that
the Christ Consciousness will not
manifest in a singular individual the
second coming in any form is the
Awakening of the Christ Consciousness
the collective identity within all of
you and how does that to the harmonic
convergence that's that is the idea that
allows you to recognize the overlap of
the old cycle and the new cycle it is
the ability to be in the limbo state to
choose which realities you prefer to
harmonically align with upon your planet
to allow your reality to become that
which you prefer it to be in peace life
love and harmony and the idea is
symbolic of the Turning Point the
fulcrum point in which you are all
beginning to wake up as aspect of the
Christ Consciousness which is the
combined consciousness of all of
you understand differ individuals will
feel it in different ways and some that
are simply used to talking in colloquial
terms in colloquial symbology may feel
that they need to be special about it
when they feel that Awakening within
themselves and sometimes the ego
structure can still get in the way not
even consciously but the idea simply is
that there is no need to interpret it in
the old symbology it is not a
manifestation in a single individual it
is the manifestation and The Awakening
within all of you understand yes does
that serve you um yes and the reason why
he asked me to read it was he lives in
Jordan and um there's as you know a lot
of upheaval in that area are and the
book very much pertains to um the the
problems in Jerusalem and between the
Arabic and the Jews there is going to be
a high concentration of transformation
in that area in approximately as we read
your energy now your year
1,997 and after that point there will be
much what you would call confusion for a
few years until it is recognized that
the idea of the things that are going on
and the interactions that are going on
there now are represent
each and every one equally of different
aspects of the Christ Consciousness and
no one of them is more correct than
another so in other words if we live
together as you do um where you are yes
in then we have then reached that if we
can finally live together yes in a whole
it is a simple thing to do when you
understand that there is no one way that
is more correct than any other way they
are all manifestations of the one idea
and if there were only one way there
would only be one person one point of
view understand yes they seem to do that
in Africa then in the in the um some not
all some some of the communal tribes
some thanks very much oh thank you very
much Happy
blending Shing hi Bashar hi it's
wonderful to be here again oh than you I
was given four pages of automatic wri W
in all right and uh how does it feel to
you feels very familiar all right and it
looks is it something you might have
written yourself uh possibly all right I
would like to have it translated and
where it comes from and uh what exactly
it says maybe maybe
is this from
within either three of your weeks or
three of your months ago three weeks all
right
in your present location or from another
location upon your planet Santa
Barbara actually Oxnard excuse
me to some
degree for now will you be willing to
accept that it is Association oriented
instead of being more specific yes very
much so do you understand that it is to
some degree formulas of vibratory
relationship mhm one
mhm one
moment all right here is the
key allow yourself to scan and in
scanning line up and intersect the lines
in any way shape or form you feel is
correct you will find overlapping patterns
you will find overlapping patterns
within the lines that will begin to make
more sense as
geometric information MH this geometric
information represents
tonalities light and sound that can be
used to align you very strongly with
some of your ancient and future
selves MH to allow you to truly be the
center that you can be within yourself
and learn to express Express a
continuous flow of that energy line them
up play with them pattern them see which
rows feel correct next to each other all
right and see which symbols seem to
repeat themselves in certain geometric
patterns you will feel it out it is a
little bit of a game and a little bit of
a puzzle for you but not something you
will not enjoy and all of a sudden a
pattern will hit you it will emerge see
it see it you will recognize it and the
chord that it strikes Within you will be
representative of what your signature
vibration is getting in touch with that
signature vibration will then Aid and
assist you to Center and align from
anywhere any when at any time MH that is
the basic as we perceive it fundamental
meaning of the
message it is in that sense what can be
called an
anagram of
sorts or what some individuals may call
an
Abracadabra understand yes
it is also in a sense a fragmented
mandala or what used to be called a
chant does that serve you yes one
moment some aspects of purple blue and
Rose coloration May mean something to those
coloration May mean something to those
that are musically inclined and you may
find yourself attracting some assistance
to interpret it
tonally which may also help you as
well from another individual or other
individuals mhm all right very good it
is something that actually involves more
than just yourself some comrads of a
sort of a type of a vibration of which
you are all alike so this definitely has
something to do with the harmonic
convergence it's something the harmonic
convergence of yourself yes in general
of course any harmonic convergence but
yes it is the centering tone the
signature vibration that you yourself
are understand yes it is in a sense your
name all of it is in a sense all the
variations all the directions and all
the perspectives of your name not the
name you may call yourself in physical
life but your signature vibrational
there there there is a couple I noticed
a couple of the um shapes were of a
fourth density name that I one of my
fourth density names and I picked it out
in the first page very good then you are
on as you say the right track continue
to blend it together and you will allow
it to merge and blend into the one
harmonic vibration that is your
name all right very good well thank you
very much thank
you shoting hi B hi Ron and I were each
given a packet of this I believe it's
crystalline Earth from Japan an
89-year-old Japanese man woles up to a
mountain every few months and picks it
apparent and and get throws it from the
ground apparently it was implanted into
our planet as it was evolving by another
race of beings and apparently as a form
and an expression of Consciousness it is
not something that was physiologically
done it was a seed implantation of
thought to czee and grow at the right
place at the right time and to be found
at the timing that would represent when
your world could begin to accept the
higher vibration of that particular
crystalin formation it is a seed which is now
formation it is a seed which is now
beginning to bloom and therefore is
being spread around and seeded around
your planet it is analogous to some of
the seed Transformations the Silicon
Transformations that are going on within
your bodies all of you at this time mhm
it allows you to be more receptive to
more r ified electromagnetic
[Music] waveforms how may we use it physically
waveforms how may we use it physically
besides holding it you can plant it in
the Earth around you give it a home if
you wish mhm you can plant things in it
and commune with the vibration of the
flowers that grow from it commune with
the colors the light the fragrance all
of it all your senses will attune you to
that particular particular
rare earth crystallin form what race
implanted this no no no okay not now is
there anything more you can tell me
about
it this may or may not make sense in
translating into your language for now
but there will come a time when it will
drink from the Electro magnetic
fountain drink from the electromagnetic
flow backwards in
time thank you well thank
you one moment one
moment there is a very strong dream door
that opens up with that particular idea
as well pay attention in your dream
reality this evening of your time
pay attention to the colors all
right yes good evening Bashar I'm to you
Bashar I was talking to a friend of mine
in San
Diego within this last week how exciting
it was and uh she told me of something
that happened that I thought maybe you
could clarify maybe this woman is 80
years old has known she was psychic
since she was six I all of you are well
she has known known it yes has been in
touch with the spirit world since she
was six ni has had over 20,000 people in
her home since 1974 all right two of
these people are the people who put out
the book on the pades the uh the
photographs that Billy Meyer took their
name are Lee and Brett Elders
I um this last week she had two people
coming to see her I believe in this area
and as they were driving on the freeway
a piece of metal shattered came through
their back window shattered the window
came into the car attached itself to the
car so strongly that it had to be pried
off guys when Adele called the Lee and
Brit and told them about this they told
her to to hold on to the metal to keep
it that they wanted to take it and have
it analyzed they felt it might have come
from the UFO is that a
possibility it is more something that
emanates from your own Planet but it is
a recognition of a timing of a
synchronicity in that sense it is
connected to the idea of what you may
call extraterrestrial energy but it is a
message that was delivered from within
the opes of your own
Planet through what you would call
circumstance what the high velocity and
the type of metal that it is in that
sense will have much meaning with regard
to to the connections that individuals
involved in that scenario do have to
extraterrestrial Consciousness it
doesn't come directly from what you
would call space in that sense in other
words it was a message to the people who
were driving that car yes I see okay
could I ask you one quick thing yes uh
three weeks ago when I talked to you you
told me one of the things you told me
was that I was Loosely connected to this
planet yes the week after that you told
my husband that our 20-year-old son who
is down C room was Loosely connected I
you'd explain you ought a loose
family well I knew that simply the idea
is that you have the ability to phase in
and out of your particular dimensional
Focus very
simply understand yes I think I
do you can reorient yourself to other
dimensions of reality you can feel the
energy pulses coming from them and allow
yourself to realiz to manifest
materialization from them from those
other dimensional planes other levels
you are Loosely connected slipping in
and out of
realities my husband would agree with
you all right thank you thank you very
much shoting thank you bajar for being with
shoting thank you bajar for being with
us and you for being with us uh I have
been told that I would be a channel for
an energy called the wings of Eternity
what well I'll be a channel in the sense
of like I am now or similar to Daryl
that's up to you isn't it I guess so you
guess so yeah you know
so which way do you
prefer and how are you channeling now
well I'm uh conscious of what comes
through when I do oh understand darl is
not unconscious simply does not focus on the
unconscious simply does not focus on the
words because they are too Swift in that
sense there is no analysis there is no
thought the channel is conscious but in
a very different way oh it is more as
you would call a dream state emotion
energy pictures abstract sometimes as
you say solid mhm there is awareness
there is
infusion there is intuition there is
absorption there is activity there is
excitement there is Joy it's not
unconscious by any means in that sense
no but simply the
words are not needed in much the same
way that if you Daydream of any
particular idea that excites you you
simply do not know of the activity going
on around you it is not where you are
focused do you understand right mhm if
this excites you you can do the same it
is up to you but this is the age of
remaining conscious
conscious
understand so you will be conscious in a
different way if you do not have to
become unconscious and the whole idea is
to become more fully conscious of all of
it but in a way that allows you to serve
in whatever way you wish to
understand yes I and in a way that
serves you otherwise there would be no
point so how do you wish to do it what
format that is up to you do what excites
you the most act upon it in that way let
it set itself up in that way to allow
you to be conducive to ch in whatever
way shape or form you wish
to understand yes mhm does that serve
you yes it does well thank you very
much Shing howdy cousin howdy stranger all
Shing howdy cousin howdy stranger all
right about a year ago I told you of
this um aspect of called future self
that had come to me about 15 or 16 years
ago I and I at that time was told that
it had more to do with the past
connection and at that time that was all
you could tell me this is a two-part
question so the first part of this
question is at this time is there more
you can yes good some of it is very
strongly connected to our civilization
that I can tell you
now well I just told you you did
right you have visited in that sense and
very often interacted in our particular
dimensional frequency not only with our
planet but with some others we are aware
of in our own Universal reality you have
explored foreign whyde you have now we
are not saying in what you would
consider a colloquial reincarnational
sense a direct connection but you have
had and in more than one Universe have
expressed a what you would call Marco
Polo type
idea you are in that sense an
Explorer and you usually when we
perceive your energy exploring in
different Universal realities you do not
stick to one particular thing but you
hop around from world to World absorbing
all that you can about that particular
area sliding around very slippery
fellow you are very inquisitive in that
way and your curiosity takes you far and
wide deep and
deep and
high this we can tell you now and you
have picked up a few things along the
way a few shall we say gems of
understanding gems of realization
focuses crystallizations perhaps would
be more
precise these crystallizations are
within you in the trary format of three
crystals one red one green one blue you
can focus on this idea and let them
share their light to become one white
crystal in the center that can open many
doorways of remembrance and recognition
for you very clearly
let your imagination Bloom and let the
images represent the ideas that you have
encountered and absorbed and as you may
say logged does that help
logged does that help
you yeah that that helps me a lot um
right I figur that a lot of that'll just
be like you say for me to go in yes and
connect up with that you have the tools
you have collected all the tools you
need it will work very strongly for you
if you simply Center and use it you will
get the pictures you will get the
feelings and you will know for yourself
what they mean and how you can use them
the closest thing I experienced so far
in a meditation was an image of being
alone in a kind of crystalline craft
floating through space yes very good
that in a sense is what I used to travel
with to all those different planets it
is the projection of your Consciousness
in the
form that is most representative and
conducive to allowing you to understand
the different dimensions you have
penetrated
yes that you have identified with by the
way since you have brought it up whether
you know it or not I will remind many of
you once
again that many of what you call your UFOs are
UFOs are
yourselves visiting
yourselves understand uhhuh quite so
does that serve you it does uh I would
uh in part of this just ask if um uh if
the tool that we are creating now with
the video with the future
self uh will be of assistance to others
along this yes yes yes yes yes will be
very powerful for many of them yes okay
and the last part of the question I was
going to ask you telepathically but I
didn't want to leave anybody out so the
question was and do you think you can help me
was and do you think you can help me
re uh retain more physical moisture in
this existence here I seem to uh kind of
get Dy it is to some degree a side
effect of the
crystallization of the transformation
into more silicon rather than carbon
energies allow
yourself to think of a thick Golden
Fluid and lock that into the crystallin
form
that will assist in the
moisturization of your transformation it
will give you that
buffer all right thank you thank you
very much some of you are already
familiar with that thick Golden
Light yes good day Belle and to you good
day well um something kind of pretty
incredible just happened kind of pretty
incredible all right um um it all kind
of relates let me kind of stick it all
together I had stick away I had um my
bottom right wisdom tooth removed a
couple days ago and I was in it didn't
hurt while they did it but afterwards it
hurt a lot and just coming here I was in
really excruciating pain just until
about about half hour ago I swear I can
swallow and I couldn't even swallow
thank you when I came in here this
energy is yours you have allowed us to
Simply show you a vibration that will
Elevate you integrate you beyond the
need for pain because all pain is
resistance all pain is separation you
are now flowing as one idea allowing us
to reflect to you the vibration you can
always create for yourself and do not
need to be in contact with us to create
anytime any when right my question was
about that that I know that pain was
resistance and I didn't understand why I
had um
manifested like my okay let let me tell
you this all right all right okay all my
wisdom teeth have been coming in since
the end of my 18 years which is 18
equals nine the number of completion
okay so um now they have all been coming
in without any problem whatsoever the
one that I've had trouble with was only
like was 34s of the way out and suddenly
I manifested um it being infected and
impacted my birthday is in two days and
I'll be 27 which again is 2 and seven is
nine fine to and um so the number of
completions so I was I was wondering can
you share reflect some of this with me
um what why did I why manifest
99999 right in that sense is the
vibration in and of itself of what you
would call
wisdom
okay okay okay now the fourth
level the fourth tooth okay in that
sense yeah is one that now is
transferred into a non-physical reality
and it will become more solid to you you
are in that sense chasing after it you
are moving into that vibratory
reality very quickly I see
all right did by any chance your dentist
give you any laughing
[Laughter] [Applause]
[Applause]
ass no but he gave me my tooth and and
um I remember when I left I forgotten
and I ran back upstairs cuz I felt I
needed to get it and and what popped
into my mind was that it was an offering
to me and now I thank you for the
offering oh thank you has this given you
enough to chew on for now [Laughter] [Laughter]
yeah
thanks thank you very
much for your biting
commentary One Moment One Moment think
of nine as a bell a bell a
bell think of it as a
Bell follow the
tone nine follow the
tone sharing hello Bish
hello I'd like to share with you about U
some changes I've been having after
looking at the oh oh I'd like to share
with you about um some changes I've been
having after looking at the diagrams
that you've been you were showing last
week and uh it seems like at the moment
I couldn't understand too much about it
all right but then suddenly start going
on during the week and uh then I had the
cognition about it was like a cognition
something like that
that I couldn't see time outside of me
anymore very good suddenly it wasn't
there very good and I realized it was
like you've been explained with me with
with me yes and then um that's feeling
good about it but
uh also with this change I
start having almost like a fight you
know like some something left still
after that connation and it is I realize
I still have the tendency uh almost like
to not a tendency not a tendency to run
away a choice okay not a tendency to
okay like a choice to run away from the
moment uh from myself all right and I
see like a picture you know something
almost close to something going to blend
like come together like the relative and
the absolute or the yes you know
something like that but then
something start like running around me
and and uh I kind of catch up so I want
to ask you that all right it's all right
do not be yourself do not belittle
yourself do not think less the things
you are quote unquote running from
now you would have absolutely fainted at
the sight of a long time ago now at
least you are remaining conscious and
you are integrating in a very fast way
allow yourself to recognize that things
you are integrating now and not running
from are things you might have run from
many years ago you are changing and you
are blending do not ber rate yourself if
you feel for now that you must back off
from something you simply do not want to
integrate yes if you you in that sense
invalidate yourself you will only
actually create more separation okay if
you back off then acknowledge you have
backed off all right all right I just
wanted to get a better look at it you
say okay then you will at whatever pace
is comfortable for you walk back toward
it and say all right now that I see what
you are and now that I recognize you now
I will integrate you okay never assume
that the things we discuss with any of
you end on the night the discussion
physically ends
the conversation always continues
forever in all the ways shapes and forms
that it needs
to understand yes things will leak in
when you open a door okay not until you
do though okay and another thing I got
during all this I got like the idea of
um I saw a like a blue light in there
and uh I got the idea of the Holy Holy
Ghost all right in a sense what the
meaning for the magnetic mentality of
your entire planet which is what you
have colloquially religiously called the
Holy Spirit okay the electromagnetic
mentality Consciousness the overmind of
your entire planet is what you have
called the Holy Spirit okay so that's
what I was getting in touch a little bit
yes Mass mentality Mass Spirit okay
thank you thank you very much you are
very welcome good evening Bashar
welcome good evening Bashar
yo thank you for what you said about
dolphins um some people have been asking
me about that and uh what you said Dove
failed with what I felt and also um what
I had received before about that sort of
sacrifice on their part to uh enable us
to open our hearts to them nice um
yesterday I went to se world with some
friends including Steven huitt whom you
know very well and we had a wonderful
time with the orcas and the Dolphins and
uh it was an ecstatic day Al together
well thank you I feel that connection
being made stronger and
stronger and I find it very exciting me
too I have a question for a friend of
mine in
um Sonoma I was visiting him recently
and he has developed something he calls
Photon art all right he tells me photon
is a unit of light in your language yes
yes all right these designs are um it's
a design form that delineates it is a
trary representation of a crosssection
in one dimension of a
photon understand I think I do a photon
contains the Triad the tetrahedral
principle and that is why it is
bracketed in threes and it is an
indication of the flow it is in a sense
almost what you would call an atomic
picture of light but it is a
cross-section a slice in one dimension
through a multi-dimensional phenomena
which you recognize as a
photon oh well very good because that answers
oh well very good because that answers
his the second part of his question
which is what how does it relate to the
field of
electronics um it is in a sense a
diagram of how light intersects your
dimension how it flows how
it creates what you would call
atomically its Co valent structure even
though it does not carry what you call
an atomic structure as such the diagram
is still representative of the way the
lines intersect your electromagnetic
field or as I shall say more precisely
as your electromagnetic
field okay so that's why this design uh
indicates the interlocking positive and
negative space both yes because it is
literally as you say like a Gear
interlocked with every other aspect of
what you think of as a vacuum but which
contains the infinite energy of all that
is oh he'll be very excited uh he wants
to know if you can tell him where he got
this idea was this a past life was this
from all that is that's told
him I can bring a larger one in fact I
meant to but I had to draw this from
memory it simply comes from a flash
revelation of overlapping Consciousness
within himself when he has eliminated as
you say or dissolved most of the
barriers between the different levels he
has created his Consciousness to be it
is simply a recognition that comes out
because of the way his energy his
Consciousness was patterned the
direction in which he was looking gives
him that particular image or
cross-section of your physiological
energy reality well it's a fascinating
uh design and he's used used many
different forms of it and decorated his
whole house it is one that also
indicates constant motion constant
motion yes thank you so much for sure
thank you it can in a sense if you wish
be called a light
flake that's exactly what it looks like
yes thank you thank you very much at
this time you may all enoy enjoy a short
break we will resume contact in
approximately 10 to 15 of your minutes how [Music]
I all say
continue this lady my for announcements
of cars uh this lady back here who's
parked alongside
pick up somebody at the airport so if
anybody's parked behind someone
alongside the building please go assist
her so she can make her pointment at the
airport thank you Bashar not my car
either shoting hi B
shoting hi B
I can you all hear L be
L be
bold I've been having a lot of negative
fantasies in my life that I enjoy these
fantasies and part of me is thinking
this is really a waste of time and you
st this immediately is going well you
better go ahead and enjoy them so that
you can stop and
confused with this idea
because I don't want to have this
negative future but I discovered that a
part of me does enjoy these all right
the idea does not mean that what you are
aware of within yourself has to manifest
and in particular if you allow yourself
to peruse them as they come naturally
you will then get out of them what you
wish to apply positively while at the
same time you will still be aware of the
polarity of positive and negative that
can occur within you but it will stay
with within you and will not in that
sense need to manifest if you will allow
it to be there when it needs to be there
and get out of it what you wish you can
still learn from it and apply it in a
positive way you understand just because
you are aware of it doesn't mean you
have to manifest it in fact
paradoxically the more integrated you
become the more aware you also become of
all the negativity you could manifest
that's a part of what integration is all
about more awareness of more of yourself
all of yourself and that has to include
the positive and the negative side but
just because you are more aware of it
doesn't mean that it must manifest in
fact just the opposite the more aware of
it you are the more you know what you
actually prefer to manifest and what you
do not prefer can remain in what you
call a fantasy State
understand yes no yes uh but yes but
what yes but but
um I'm going if you're still enjoying it
then aren't you going to start creating
it in what sense are you enjoy enying it
what are you enjoying out of it are you
enjoying simply certain experiences and
expressions that you can create in what
you call the non-physical sense that you
can then apply to the physical world for
if you are enjoying it that way again if
you get your enjoyment in the
non-physical sense it may not have to
manifest in the physical it still takes
an overwhelming desire in that sense to
really bring something into
manifestation or an overwhelming fear if
it is simply in your terms an enjoyment
that is on the level of what you call an
amusement an extrapolation in that way
you may simply not be giving it enough
energy to manifest fully as a physical
reality you
understand yes no
maybe I'm trying to think about it what
what it is that you said can you
describe what it is you enjoy about
it let me put it this way would you
continue to enjoy it if it manifested
physiologically no do you desire to
continue to enjoy
it in the way that it comes to you
now no I don't why
not and in what way do you enjoy
it it's it's an idea of um being
uh helpless and sort of having your life
go slowly downhill all right and I don't
know exactly what it is that's enjoyable
about it but maybe
just feeling of Letting Go and
all right can you perhaps allow yourself
let us say to say that you are exploring
different quote unquote
luxuries different opportunities
different experiences you have had
perhaps you are in that sense
reviewing some of the enjoyment you may
be having is simply that as you are
reviewing things that you have lived out
in many different lives what you are
enjoying is maybe that they're in the
past you can be enjoying that you can be
enjoying it from the perspective of the
over soul in the sense that all
experiences are valid and simply as you
review all these different things you
have already done your enjoyment comes
from the fact that you are now creating
the satisfaction that you can integrate
all these different experiences and have
a positive result in terms of the
manifestation which occurs in your
physical life now can you understand you
might be enjoying it for that
reason simply now that you are looking
at it from the perspective of what you
might call hindsight knowing that you
don't have to go through it again and so
you can relax and at your leisure review
these things and even gain the sense of
learning that you learn from them and
that may be what you are enjoying the
experience itself
itself
understand I don't think any of those
are it all right it kind of confuses me
because I think the thing that I'm
enjoying is like the feeling of Letting
Go and yes which I could see as being
both a positive and a negative thing yes
and I'm confused because I don't know if
it's positive or negative or can be
whatever you choose it to be if you know
it can be both which do you prefer to
recognize it as I prefer it as positive
but I don't want to create that
fantasy but you have just contradicted
yourself if you understand that the
Sensation that you are experiencing in
the fantasy can be viewed as a neutral
idea and manifested either as a positive
or A negative and if you prefer the
positive then no matter whether it comes
to you in your imagination as a negative
to at least put you in touch with the
feeling if you simply prefer that it
will manifest in physical reality as a
positive then that's the only way it
will manifest
manifest
understand yeah I think
so the idea in other words let's put it
this way you are creating a version of
the idea having your cake and eating it
too you are now able to create both
sides and learn from both and in a sense enjoy
and learn from both and in a sense enjoy
both the positive and the negative but
you simply quote unquote wisely choose
to keep the negative manifestation in
the non-physical side of your reality
and the positive manifestation on the
physical side so you can enjoy them both
because you allow them to manifest where
to you they are
safe understand yes so enjoying them
where they are does not mean that they
will manifest and that sense it means
that they won't because you have found
the place in which you can enjoy them
safely yes thank you understand yes does
that help you yes thank you oh thank you
very
much shedding hi Bashar it's million
hi
well things have really coming to head
here yes who I'm mine all right all of
us um I'm fin finally getting that
wonderful experience of manifesting what
I want oh finally yes right after all
these months of torture oh all
right and uh yes and it feels
exhilarating it feels different I can
understand why it wasn't that
comfortable because it was so unique
that I didn't know what it felt like and
it I kind of have to adjust myself when
I get it to allow myself to love it and
appreciate it and feel what it feels
like thank you and so part of one of
these things that are coming to a head
seems to be is a culmination of the um
the first visit that I had by the space
people in 1973 the three beings that
were the first thing that I ever asked
you about the first time I ever saw you
nice and you told me they were pleadians
and Friends of
pleadians and that I would find out in
time well this last week I have been
obsessed with zeter reticuli oh
I mean I woke up with this whole
marketing plan and I've been drawing
them and designing them and I mean I'm
just my life has become zet reticuli and
so I thought well that's exciting and
somewhere around the same time when I
had the visit by the three beings I also
had one of those straight scars on the
abdomen that I had no idea where it came
from and then I conveniently forgot
about it for 15 years until I read
whitle striber book and then channeling
class to night a whole different energy
came to me that was so strong and so
deep that it almost frightened me and I
never experienced fear in channeling
before but it was just right at the edge
yes and there was dialogue going on just
inside my head not speaking or
vocalizing this was not vocal at all
understand and I asked I said is this
are you Zeta and they said uh something
like Zeta that's something like it your
version of it oh oh H your recognition
your Recreation of the agreements and the
Recreation of the agreements and the
connections something like
it oh I have one phrase which we can
share okay and not much more at this
time okay the eyes
have the eyes I
know God
yes thank you oh thank you thank you
okay do they speak through us I mean is
this a vocal channeling thing I
understand you've said they have a hive
mentality it can be but anytime they
quote unquote push their mentality
through you to create what you perceive
to be a single Persona will require a
large amount of
them since they are in that sense much
more of what we have discussed at the
beginning of this evening the
instinctive spread out form of
Consciousness that you refer to as a
hive mentality more than the focused
personalities each of you consider
yourselves to be we are somewhere
halfway in
between aha okay um have I channeled as
aani energy you are in touch to some
degree with it you are using it as a
carrier wave oh okay oh that's great
okay that explains a lot thank you thank
you sharting hi Bashar
hi Bashar
hi uh last Tuesday we were discussing
being where you need to be whenever you
need to be there and uh since the it's a
good thing we talked about it when we
did well I was thinking since the U
group Consciousness has eased up on our
necessity for creating time since um you
might say time is the movement of energy
or the seeming movement of energy
through right yes I might say that have to
right yes I might say that have to
create space to move in do we no time
and space are actually manifestations of
the same idea which means that like we
could physically pop from here to
wherever we want and you actually do
anyway well uh when Billy was talking
about that to seasi or seasi was talking
with Billy uh she mentioned a a
coordinate uh set where he needed three
coordinates to get there and then it
broke off that it was just for Billy uh
is can you tell us how to do that we
have discussed the ID in the principle
many times it is simply that what you
call coordinates are part of the
equational variable that an object is an object
variable that an object is an object
does not exist in space location is one
of the properties of the object if you
measure all the vibratory frequencies of
a particular object in one spot move the
object to another spot it will vary by
the one variable that represents the
different location
if you can isolate that and then beam
that energy in a coherent pattern around
that object with the variable the one
different variable that represents
another coordinate location that object
will have to cease by definition where
it used to be and take up resonance in
the new vibrational coordinate that you
are influencing it with how do you
isolate that uh vibration by measuring
all the vibratory frequencies of any
particular object and isolating which is
the vibratory variable of location okay
we must be automatically equipped to do
that you are automatically equipped to
do that yes what but in terms of
translating it into your idea of
Technology no I'm thinking of just the I
mean you know first of all it will take
being absolutely Fearless okay absolutely
absolutely Fearless okay absolutely
because it will involve what you might
perceive as a momentary blanking out of
your entire ego stru Ure okay and your
ego structure will hold on very tight in
the habits you have given it to hold on
to yeah but also like in the in the um
um isolation tank I have and some
experiences I've had there I've had to
let go of that so it's but this is some
of the idea of applications of
technology that we are talking about
okay the creation of an isolation field
around you can be done with what you
call Simple meditation simp well I
realiz but what I'm saying is uh how do
you isolate what do you look at or think
about to isolate that vibration of a
different place in a sense
nothing you become the absolute limbo
state of recognizing nothing and
everything all at once and in that flash
second you will then reorient to
whatever happens to be the predominant
vibration uh of like say if I wanted to
go from here to Air's Rock yes so it
would be the predominant vibration of
Air's it would be your focus at that
time once you had created yourself to be
in the centered isolation field unlocked
from every expectation of every
direction and then simply impose one
over all the others you will instantly
translate literally translate yourself
out of the holographic matrix in that
location okay simply remember that you
are already at Air's Rock I realized
there's only here and now yes so all you
have to do is redefine yourself
and really believe it that is really all
it takes is real belief okay understand
yes now that at first may start to cause
some Sensations that some of you have
begin to feel but are not comfortable
with and that is the disassociation and
the disorientation and the
disillusionment that you may feel as you
unlock from the particular frame of
reference you are used to and have been
used to for thousands upon thousands of
years as you create create that idea so
here's another clue remember that each
and every life creates the past and the
future from the present so if you stop
associating with the idea that you have
been locked into a particular habit of
physical reality for thousands of years
you will not continue to create that
idea or Habit in the present and then
anything anywhere any when is as you say
fair game uhhuh understand yes so think
of yourself as a hologram you are
everything everywhere and all it takes
then is a shifting a very slight
shifting of focus of
perspective to truly create the other
reality around you you can also think of
it this way perhaps that you are not
going anywhere that it is coming to you
mhm that is just as literal as anything
else since you actually aren't going
anywhere at all well that's true yeah so
you can simply change the picture around
you if you wish uhhuh now one of the
main reasons a lot of you also do not
allow yourself to do this is because of
what your Society tells you that if you
lose touch with
reality you will be insane you're being
annoy no one will listen to you you will
be crazy hey I was at A's Rock only a
second ago yeah
sure understand yes so some of you
hesitate to let go for that very reason
as well simply because of what you think
other people will think about what you
think well I've been on other planets
only seconds ago why not Air's rock yeah
it simply all we are saying depends upon
how much stock you put into whether or
not anyone else needs to know you have
done it or what they think about it or
what they think about it which is much
the same thing mhm could you give me a
hint of who's sending the Transmissions
I'm picking up no thank you
thank you
shoting hi hi this is my first time me
too and um speak up speak up I've been
experiencing um several beings in our
home and so as my daughter are you
having a party yeah it's always a party
and um I was wondering why they're there
and um what do they let you know about
yourself what do you think about
yourself by being involved with
different levels of consciousness does
it feel natural to you well it doesn't
really bother me but they are
interfering with my daughter they are
not interfering with anyone someone's
belief May create the apparency of
interference what have you taught her
about the
idea well I've given her some basic
metaphysical type um learnings and stuff
like that and she's able to deal with it
a little bit more in your terminology
what is the age of the daughter the age
of what daughter she's 14 all right
individuals in your Society between what
you call typically the ages of 11 to 17
will be highly psychically connected to
many different levels of spirituality
very sensitive to it in a sense the only
reason it seems to be a bother is simply
because the individual has not focused
on who or what they really are yet and
in a sense physical and non-physical
reality can seem to be annoying to them
it is an extension of what you all
typically think of as your adolescent
stage and it simply in this case extends
into the non-physical reality as well
okay but why are they coming to us now
because it represents the timing of when
you need to grow in awareness of the
existence of other levels of
spirituality that exist within you I see
is possibly one of these um my niece
Jenna only a fragment the majority of
the Consciousness in that way is as you
would say elsewhere or let us say
focused elsewhere a fragment of it is
present in that sense but not in
totality as you understand the Persona
you call Jenna okay I understand thank
you thank you very much One Moment One
Moment Stay
Stay you you oh okay all
right a message which may make some
sense later no promises from
us for your daughter and perhaps even
for you is Kitchen bread and
you is Kitchen bread and
soup a familiar setting and a familial
setting Hef Hef Hef the kitchen and the
Hef some of the contacts and the connections
some of the contacts and the connections
in spiritual form that you are making
have to do with strong Connections in
what you would call Past Times that
revolved around the kitchen and the
Hearth bread and
soup the recreation of some of this
familiarity may make you and her feel
more at home literally with some of
these spirit
consciousnesses and allow them to feel
more at home with
you understand yes I do thank you thank
you sharing hello Bashar hello this is my
sharing hello Bashar hello this is my
first time a little nervous mine too I'm
not you know why why I'm nervous no why
I'm not oh no get because I am always
excited to explore something new
everything to me is the first time every
time I have never done this before ever
ever ever and I always know that anything I
ever and I always know that anything I
discover will always add to the over all
ecstasy and excitement that I choose to
experience in my life can be the same
for you if you wish good anything you
say will come out exactly as it needs to
share I wanted to ask you about a um
physical problem I've have been having
and um there seems to be uh more
awareness as I come through it speak up speak up
as I come through it speak up speak up
be bold and share share share so that
all may share and on top of it my mother
has experienced some extreme physical
health problems during this time and
also my husband I wonder if there was my
my my I mean everyone is like falling
apart all right maybe that's how you can
pull yourself back together in another
way yes but we we feel an Awakening of
some yes as I just said so you can pull
yourself back together in another way
now the Assumption in this sense comes
from an old Habit in your soety that
assumes that in order to pull yourself
together in the way you want to you have
to first destroy the original structure
you don't have to you can transform it
easily effortlessly lovingly gently you
can transform it dest
structurization does not have to be
destruction you don't have to fall apart
to Simply disassemble the old idea and
reassemble the new one this simply comes
from an old habit an old assumption on
the part of your
family that you have to break into
pieces in order to gather yourself back
together you don't have to break into so
many pieces to analyze each and every
one in that way you can allow yourself
to begin to function to know you are a
whole as you are you are a whole as you
are allow yourself simply to redefine
the whole idea that you are and any
pieces you choose to continue to create
yourself to be will then become a part
of that whole and redefine themselves
you are energy are you not yes as energy
you are homogeneous are you not mhm you
are one idea are you not yes but we're
all viros so
piy step so I mean are we be you're
saying that we're analyzing everything
and and that we need to get past all the
to some degree on certain what you would
call sublevels of thought the idea
simply comes from the built-in
assumptions that your Society gives you
that you have to create a breaking down
in order to build up it is what may be
called if I may right now the Phoenix
syndrome in your society that you
actually have to reduce yourself to
ashes in order to rise from them again
you can simply transform in that sense
more like what you would call the
chimera rather than the Phoenix by
recognizing the fire that exists within
you now and allow the fire to transform
you without consuming you so I didn't
have to do all this at all right no you
don't have to at all if you can imagine
the way you prefer to be and start
acting like that person you imagine then
you will be that person and have that
lifestyle and all that goes with it if
you simply assume that the person you
would like to be require some lengthy
bridge to cross in order to get there
then you will spend time on the bridge
bridge and you may create it to be quite
creaky so allow yourself to melt into
the person you wish to be now rather
than chipping away at yourself in order
to become that new
idea understand yes does that assist you
yes very much so pleasant dreams thank
you energy blue blue blue blue blue blue
okay and
green and warmth and warm
and red red
[Music]
shootting hello hello um when I was
seven and a half I used to have these
dreams about somebody coming into my
house and um trying to kill me and my
mother he'd have a knife and um he'd
throw it and I'd catch it when he tried
to throw it at my mother yes and then
we'd stand there for about three minutes
and then I'd throw it back nice and
would hit him in the arm so you know
then he you know being pain came and
call me all these nasty words all right
and we'd go at the table and we sit down
and talk yes and I knew he would try to
kill my mother again so um you know I
was telling my mother watch out watch
out watch out and then he threw the
knife at her again yes and then the cops
came in the house and I told them you
know that he was trying to kill us and
they took me away yes okay now during
this time my father was on drugs and had
an alcohol problem oh right and he had
gone to gym yeah for robbing a store
doing all these other
things what sort of relation does this
have to do thank you first of all some
of it is simply symbolically playing out
some of the ideas of what you call the
familiar plur that you have grown up
with with regard to the symbology of
your father but also literally the idea
is that you were doing an instant replay
from what you would call a past life
wherein that individual what you call
the murderer in that way was the
individual who is now your father and
you're simply replaying that incident
over and over again and when you realize
that you have taken control of the
situation and toss the knife back that
that individual will always get back
what they put out you are in his life
now again to teach him in a loving way
the ideas he did not learn in the last
life by committing the murder in that
sense of you and your mother in the
present life the idea is that as you sat
down at the table in your dream and
talked about it you both began to create
create some recognition that you could
talk it out in your dream reality and
that you are talking it out in your
dream reality to allow him to recognize
his own self-empowerment so he does not
have to act as a powerless being in that
way who must in that sense try to
dominate other individuals in physical
reality for all aggression in that sense
and all violence in that sense and all
perpetration in that sense is the result
of an individual usually believing that
they are powerless to control and create
the reality they
desire in killing you in that sense in
the past life and in agreeing to be
together again you have formed the
family unit that can allow the
individual to pass through all the
phases of lack of empowerment which is
symbolized by what you call the drug and
alcohol problem in that way early on and
to learn to love the self and love all
and know that they are in control of
their life you are working all these
things out and have been working them
out in your dream realities for quite
some time in that sense the police
taking you away is simply an indication
that you are the creator of your reality
and you agree to be in the reality that
you are in and be of assistance to that
individual to allow them to learn what
they need to learn to gain their
self-empowerment back loving that you
are to have done this it is one of the
ways you can Aid and assist an
individual who perhaps created a
negative reality in One Life to Aid and
blend and balance and assist in their
lives to recreate that blending for
themselves to do colloquially what you
would call The Balancing of their
self-created karma are you understanding
this yeah so that's why I had these
every day until they stopped for some
reason that I don't no you have ironed
out a lot of it now a lot of the
momentum in that sense is up to him you
have in that sense done your
part understand yeah unconditional love
and the remembrance that you made an
agreement to be with that individual to
be of service to them will allow things
to smooth out even more on all levels
all levels unconditional love you are
all Eternal you are all infinite this is
one play one moment moment in an
infinite series of manifestation
realities that you call different lives
but this is the life in which you can
allow all of you as a family to balance
and blend that energy to love each other
unconditionally understand yeah thank
you for your strength in in being
willing to face that individual in this
relationship in this way to be willing
to be of service to him to allow him to
regain his own power and learn to love
himself and then love all that is you
recognized it and in simply attracting
in the last life the idea of that person
to perpetrate upon you the murder you
are now willing to allow him to regain
his standing within himself by loving
him in that sense as his
daughter murderers very often do not
understand that they will be very
intimately intertwined with their
victims many times in the next
life thank you for your strength and
your love thank you allow your dream
reality now to open new doors in which
you can begin to breathe fresh air new
air new atmospheres that will point the
way to the directions of the paths you
chose to be throughout the remainder of
your life you are opening up they are
opening up relax relax love love love it
will change and transform everything
trust you are in a position of strength
and power for around you resolve
the idea that that individual needs to
resolve within
themsel thank you does that assist you
yes it does thank you Les and dreams to
you thanks there will be more in your
dream state a few words of
state a few words of
whisper
sharing hi Bashar hi it's
Joker oh excuse me switcher thank you
well I I have been um starting out my
sharings for the last few weeks with a
joke but best thing I could come up with
was why did the ssan cross the road and
that didn't go anywhere so I forget it
you all right perhaps to remember that
he was already on the other side that's
right thank
you you know I have a I have a
proposition for you B all right I think
we' make a great comedy
Team all right
so um moving into my sharing here I
would like to know more about the
harmonic convergence two parts I would
like to know if there is a
physical event that's occurring some
kind of physical alignment shift
whatever yes in a sense it is in an
energy form but the physical event is
the unification of the action upon your
world that many individuals are taking
in acting as one in harmonizing in
converging in focusing their ideas their
actions and their intentions in a
laser-like coherent fashion that
physical action on the part of all the
individuals in your planet in
participating in that party will make a
big difference in the available energy
of your entire world to accelerate into
fourth density that much more quickly
okay so in terms of the physical we're
not talking about a planetary or uh
solar um alignment or something like
that we're really talking about the
people the people yes the people uh can
you be more elaborate as to what the is
doing what we're actually it is
crystallizing you literally
crystallizing you it is unlocking you it
is the eye of the hurricane it is where
all is still and silent so that you can
pass into whatever reality you choose to
it is the threshold it is the transfer
gate it is the switching yard if you
wish you can go onto any track it is all
right Grand Central Station
that is what it is it is the point from
which you can go to any place any
time it is the limbo state it is all
realities Blended and
available so in in a sense we're
decoupling from our current reality
period and uh and choosing which reality
to recouple too okay
um gee I've got questions here I'm not
sure how how to formulate them um
perhaps into
answers hey now that's an
idea thank you well I'm just thinking in
terms of Are We creating this energy to
be coming from quote unquote outside or
is this something that we're just
generating all from with it is all from
within although there is in your terms
participation from outside as well it is
still all within in terms of your
experience of it certainly okay then
what what can you um recommend as
a u positive I'll say ideal if you're
willing to accept that term uh thing to
do that will create the most
acceleration greatest acceleration
greatest positivity for any individual
yes as each of you are doing the thing
that excites you the most be aware and
in touch consciously of the fact that
everyone involved is doing the same
thing so that while you remain as an
individual you also move as a mass mind
you follow me yes so be aware of the
fact that everyone is focused in a
similar way in their own particular
version of that idea okay then what can
what effects or what
results can we I don't want to say
expect but that's the idea what what do
we What will what will we what will we
see as a result of doing this then vast
changes in things you thought would
never change such as
habit patterns of individuals you think
are stuck in a particular way changes
within what you call your sociological
and governmental and religious
structures more acceleration
more willingness to create networks more
observation of synchronicity in your
lives and it has a
particular ability to assist in the acceleration
ability to assist in the acceleration
of ideas within what you call three
years of your time within what you call
1990 to allow there to be more blatant
manifestations of our presence as well
ah okay aside from the three-year thing
you just said it within what time
framing would you say these observations
will be made it will depend upon the
individual it can be almost immediate or
it may simply take a few months usually
you will begin to see them start leaking
into your reality within the 3-month
time frame that's great some of them
will be within 72 of your hours because
so highly accelerated and focused will a
lot of you be you will see some
instantaneous manifestations right away
again in the form of what you call
coincidence MH on many different levels
in which you didn't think coincidence
could occur all of a sudden it will be
what world am I in
yeah yeah understand this is very
exciting very exciting yes thank you
very much thank you
shoting greetings Bashar and to you I've
recently purchased a u magnetic bed pad
from Japan all right and are you having
a good time with it yes uh matter of
fact uh a number of people have used
this for some period of time have
reported almost miraculous Health
changes in their bodies all right
magnetic alignment can do much of that
for many individuals well I was
wondering from your point of view what
does how does this bed pad work and is
it in any way detrimental to any other
the members of our generally no although
again it can depend upon specific belief
systems but generally our perception is
that most individuals will allow
themselves to derive benefit as you call
it from that particular experience and
what it is doing is setting up a
magnetic field that is pulsing at a
certain rate that allows your bodily
crystallin structure atomic structure to
align with the Earth pulse 7 and 1 half
cycles per second so it puts you in an
automatic meditative state which
realigns and centers you magnet ISM can
do this and this is why we have said
that you will begin to discover as some
of you have that some of your medical
magnetic resonance imaging devices are
not only in that sense good for
diagnosis but good for the Cure as well
there's been some really great uh
changes with it I was wondering does it
have any applications for people who
have what we call AIDS it can yes any
individual who can magnetically align
and Center themselves within the blue
white electromagnetic field of your
planet in that Blended and balanced
State what might be called the idealized
blueprint State cannot by definition
contain any disease of any nature at all
so while you're laying on this pad be it
all night or just for short period of
time it' be almost like being way out in
the boonies somewhere away from all the
electromagnetic flux and no no no it
will be being we in not way out it will
be being the electromagnetic pulse or
flux itself it will be
homogenization so that no one idea
stands out no one fragment stands out no
one compartment no one portion of
yourself stands out more than any other
portion you literally become liquid
light blue electromagnetic liquid light
I can see that yes then you can
recrystallize yourself in whatever
format is most indicative of the
strongest belief system within you at
that point um I thought perhaps this was a
point um I thought perhaps this was a
modern version of an Atlantean healing
bed that I heard of yes it is oh good
thank you thank you very
much Shing hi hi this is my first time and
Shing hi hi this is my first time and
I'm enjoying myself immensely me too on
both counts I have a question um Also
regarding that magnetic Sleep Pad many
people have remarked that they have had
really different dream patterns can you
elaborate more on what how what effect
this have on people's dream reality well
the dream reality and the physical
reality are simply expressions of the
same one reality so as you CER yourself
in the balance point between both then
you are more in touch with the physical
reality as a dream and the dream reality
as real so you increase in that sense
create to be more Vivid your experiences
in the dream reality and create to be
more dreamlike your experiences in
physical reality understand mhm does that assist
reality understand mhm does that assist
you mhm I have one other kind of
associated question this thing has
dramatic um impact on people's physical body
um impact on people's physical body
almost instantaneously pain goes away
strange looking things like that seems
to me that it must be having as dramatic
an effect on people's mental spiritual
and emotional bodies of course as we
have said it is aligning the whole idea
it brings it all into one here and now
connection Point that's why everything
else becomes more Vivid because what was
formerly distant dim realizations of
some non physical reality is brought
immediately into real focus in true as
you say Living
Color understand yeah so this will help
to increase people's personal vibrations
or just Center them generally yes
although again an individual can do with
it what they wish to and if they are
focused into negativity it can
accelerate some of that generally
speaking most individuals will receive
some benefit from
it understand uhhuh and in the overall
sense even if the magnetic alignment
allows them to amplify the negative
portion of themselves that can still be
of benefit since it gives them an
opportunity to face things they need to
integrate within themselves understand
uhhuh and it can be very grounding in
that sense and allow you to really begin
to relate to the magnetic pulse of the
crystal in
Earth a couple of people that have seen
this or experienced it have absolutely
categorically just rejected it all right
why is that is that because on some
level they know they're going to have to
face something to some degree sometimes
yes it might be a little too raw of an
energy for them at this point they may
feel that they went into it without a
buffer understand uhhuh but not every
tool is for every person it is also as
simple as
that okay does that assist you yes thank
you very much thank you
sharing hello I'm Penny
hello what is my purpose and why am I
here here oh my in 25 words or less
please now we have discussed some of
this idea before and we will keep it
simple and fundamental remember that
even though you are a reincarnational
being the U you are now only has One
Life to Live do you follow me so the
main purpose of your life is to live
that life as fully as you can as the U
you are now that's it and the way you
live the life you are now as fully as
you can is to do what excites you the
most with integrity that's it it's as
simple as that do you believe it yes I
believe it can you act that way it
doesn't seem to be enough doesn't seem
to be enough well are you doing what
excites you the most well I'm healing
all right are you excited about it no
what are you excited about
doing I'm not sure well allow yourself
to scan all the probable realities you
could be doing right now are you through
certainly is living One Moment One Day
at a Time exciting for you no why
not I haven't trained myself that way
you haven't trained yourself that way
but you see it isn't a matter of
training in that sense not in the
fundamental sense it is a matter of
allowance it is a matter of trust it is
a matter of understanding that
excitement is what lets you know what
you're all about and what you chose to
be and what your purpose is in this life
the things that you find exciting the
most exciting things at any given moment
at any given moment that you are capable
of acting upon is the Fulfillment of
your purpose if you act upon them if you
don't you are denying the vibrational
Beacon called excitement that represents
the purpose you chose to live out in
this physical life so all you have to do
to fulfill your purpose is act upon
whatever really excites you the most
with integrity at any given moment you
don't have to be trained do it all you
have to be told is that it's all right
to do that if you want to you can give
yourself permission to live that way
live in the moment in full ecstasy in
full excitement if you prefer that of
course if you prefer in that sense to
trudge along you can do that too if
that's what excites you but you don't
have to I can't fa ecstasy lasting all
right but you see that's the main block
that most of you have is you simply
cannot believe that it can last probably
because you have been told that in order
for it to last you have to sustain
it it sustains itself ecstasy is the
natural vibration of creation
unconditional love is what everything is
made of you are made of unconditional
love so you don't have to sustain it all
you have to do is allow yourself to be
natural and the Ecstasy will continue
forever another difficulty many of you
have in imagining that will go on
forever is because you think in terms of
time and you think well forever that's a
long time it's not a long time because
forever is right now it's always right
now so all you have to do is experience
your ecstasy now and you will always
experience it
now thank you understand yes does that
help you yes thank you well thank you
very much will you do me a favor
certainly will you take three deep
breaths and let them
out will you
sigh and understand that you deserve
ecstasy and understand that nothing is
too simple or too good to be
true nothing you were created out of
nothing you were created out of
ecstasy this transformational age as we
have said a few times is not about being
normal it is about being
natural and ecstasy is your natural
state so all you have to do is relax
into your natural state and you will
always be ecstatic but you will always
be ecstatic now because now is the only
time that actually ever exists it's
always now you don't have to worry about
sustaining with your stamina this
ecstatic feeling for all
time that can get weighty I wouldn't
want the responsibility you are creating
time time is your creation your
projection so live in the now live in
the present you won't create as much
time and then the creation and allowance
of ecstasy will be easy because the only
time you have to think about to create
ecstasy in will always be now and
that'll be it and it'll be easy to do
because all you have to think about is
now and now and
now and before you know it Millennia
have passed through
you because you're having such a good
time living in now being who you are as
fully as you will allow yourself to be
to the best of your
ability understand yes you deserve it
thank you oh thank you I had nothing to
do with it it's just
natural exciting dreams to you vibrant
vibrant vibrant
lights very nice thank you thank you
very much at
this timing allow us to extend to each and
timing allow us to extend to each and
every one of you once
again our deepest appreciation for your
willingness to crystallize this
interaction between us next week of your
time we will
discuss the harmonic
wave and that can be the entitlement the
harmonic wave we thank you for your
wave we thank you for your
sharing and we will in that sense
interact and inter with you upon that
harmonic wave
up
unconditionally exciting and loving good
day to you all
how did it go great thank you
darl those of you those of you over here
who didn't get a chance to uh catch it
this time put your name on the list in
the order that you were setting here and
you'll be up first for the harmonic wave
next week anyone who would like a copy
of tonight's tape see the girl in The
Purple jumpsuit over here you can have
it tonight if you want a video also see
her and we'll see you in next week bring
your surfboard for the wave for