all right I'll say how are you all this
evening of your time as you create time
to
exist allow us to refresh ourselves upon
the idea and the concept of
perfection we have discussed many times
with you the idea that in your lives
very often you are taught that even when
you create the idea and the notion in
your lives of what you call a spiritual
path that the reason for this is for the
attainment and the achievement of
perfection but recognize once again as
we have shared many times our
perspective is that you will never
achieve Perfection because you are
already perfect the idea does not mean
that you will not grow not expand not
change not transform not learn something
new but it is simply an allowance a
recognition of allowance in your lives
that at any given moment the idea you
are being the reality you are expressing
the events you are experiencing are for
their own reasons perfect in
themselves this
relaxation this attitude this backing
off from yourself in that way rather
than applying so much pressure to the
idea to be more perfect is what allows
you to know that you can always become a
different type of perfection at any
given moment perhaps a more expanded
type but you will always be at any given
given moment the absolute perfect
manifestation of whatever idea you are
being at that moment your willingness to
allow that moment to be perfect in and
of itself is what paradoxically allows
you to create the next and different
perfect moment because unless you are
willing to allow whatever moment you are
experiencing to be complete in and of
itself on all levels then you are not
allowing yourself to view and perceive
all facets of that experience because if
you do not think it is perfect as it is
if you invalidate it and judge it in
that way in a negative point of view
then you yourself may be shutting off
aspects of that event of that moment
that you need to see need to be aware of
to incorporate them into the totality of
yourself so that you can get on with the
next step every moment is a stepping
stone to the next moment and if you
invalidate any stepping stone then you
yourself remove from the path you are
the ability to get to the next stepping
stone always allow each and every moment
of your lives to be perfectly valid as
they are this does not mean you must
accept that the things that are
occurring in your life are what you
quote unquote should accept or prefer
you can always prefer your life to be
the way you desire it to be but the way
to allow yourself to create it to be the
way you desire it to be is to accept
that the way it is now serves a purpose
and is a part of the path you have
created yourself to be and that what you
are learning is there for a reason your
reason that there is something within
the scenario you want to see you want to
reflect on you want to learn from and in
accepting and acknowledging the way your
life does unfold that is what gives you
the recognition of the empowerment you
have to create your life to unfold in
the dire Direction and in the manner you
most desire it to be so simply do allow
yourself to reflect at any given moment
that no matter what your choices every
scenario for what it is is a perfect
manifestation of that scenario you can
prefer Perfect Harmony and perfect
ecstasy or you can prefer perfect misery
but both are perfect expressions of the
idea you are reflecting at that moment
and when you allow it to be there for a
reason then you can extract from that
scenario what will most assist you in
reforming the idea redirecting yourself
and creating what it is you desire to
experience most in your
reality many individuals will pressure
themselves in many different ways to
strive to struggle to try to be more
perfect will set themselves goals and
ideals in that way that continually
deny the validity
they possess at that moment in that way
you deny yourself all that you truly
desire as well for if you do not believe
yourself complete in that moment then
you by your own definition insist that
you do not have the capability of
creating what it is you say you desire
to attract into your lives knowing that
you are complete perhaps focused not in
a way you prefer to be but knowing you
are complete gives you the opportunity
to know that at any given moment you
have the ability to refocus yourself in
any direction you desire you lack
nothing you have all the tools and all
the abilities you require at any given
moment to be anything you are willing
and bold enough to believe you can
Define yourself to be you all follow
along sheding
hello bash hello um I had an experience
uh with my sister Elisa we had gone to a
movie and saw kind of like a um in the
desert it looked like um a wooden kind
of structure and it drew to mind an
experience we had almost three years ago
in uh Nevada at Lake me we pulled into a
Cove and we saw this kind of a a same
type of thatch Hut type idea we were
very drawn to it and after the movie we
went home directly and dug out the
pictures because we took a lot of
pictures of it it was so unusual and she
took one picture and I took the other
and for three nights in a row we did a
33 second hold on it with intense energy
and continued to uh keep that in mind
and fall asleep uh Lisa said that she
thought it was like a Gateway and I was
wondering for each one of us what is
this symbol and and what's happening the
um the dreams in
and it does feel like it is in a sense
an
invitation it is in a sense a symbol
that you have created to know that some
of the communications and connections
that you can make in that vortex in that
Gateway in that energy Zone will be
something that you will be able to feel
quite at home with that there is the
symbol of a structure that represents to
you the idea and the Securities of Home
in that way and therefore you can know
that at any time your energy and your
excitement so lure you by all means
visit that
area and you will discover in a sense
that you can walk between doorways
walked and talk between dimensionalities
give yourself the opportunity whenever
you feel so inclined whenever you are
most excited to do so we would suggest
that you do physiologically visit once
again that area you follow me yes is up
to you but it will represent a
stabilizing Foundation as a symbol for
you to allow you to know that no matter
what occurs in that area and no matter
what type of communication you
experience you will always be firmly
grounded and rooted and anchored by the
symbol of something which is that which
you can call your home as well as you
can call any place any time anywhere any
when you follow me yes anything else um
I'll probably have to listen to this
again but is there a particular way I
can use it um upon going into the dream
state you have already initiated this
idea as you have said you are trusting
your imagination and that is the primary
key and the primary tool that will
always take you where you need to be you
have sat yourself down and centered
yourself and allowed yourself to thrust
yourself into that Dimension the picture
in that way and even your own
imagination is just as real as
physiologically being there but we
simply perceive within you that the idea
of your physiological existence in that
local may have because of your belief
system a greater impact than you are
willing to allow the picture or your
imagination to have at this point so we
are simply suggesting that if you wish
to truly enter the dream enter the
physical local as well you follow me yes
I understand thank you thank you shoting
shoting
um ask a question for a friend of a
friend friend of a
friend his name is Paul and he lives in
Wisconsin and my friend tells me that
her sense of this person is that he's
always been searching for the more in a
manner of speaking um but it's been in
kind of a state of turmoil or struggle
um because there's not so many overt
spiritual kinds of experiences to be had
in Wisconson one moment um
um
I are we feeling alive yes thank you
thank you uh a week ago this past
weekend it was my perception that there
was a general shift of the mass
Consciousness through an energy doorway
which was characterized by a great deal
of
sadness and in attempting to understand
the sadness what I got was that it was
the sadness connected with letting go of
excess baggage that we would be better
off without in a sense yes and I was
interested in your perception if that if
I was that is quite accurate there is a
stronger Gateway coming up on your March
15th date as well characterized by what
by similar Transformations it is a very
strong Collective Gateway and you may
find again that individuals will release
what they no longer need not that they
have to release it in a negative way in
the idea of loss or sadness but that is
simply a habitual way your Society still
thinks of the idea of change that you
are losing something rather than simply
changing into another representation
with the same energy but the more you
incorporate these experiences the more
gateways you walk through very soon you
will pass over that threshold wherein
each and every one of these
Transformations will be felt with
ecstasy rather than the sense of loss
because you will know beyond the shadow
of a doubt by then that you really lose
nothing that nothing ever really goes
anywhere it only
changes but you have accurately defined
the sensation thank you thank you um you
sensation thank you thank you um you
always or often anyway speak of
following our excitement yes and yet my
perception is that at least that at
certain levels of spiritual
Evolution I observe on this planet what
looks to me like people being EXC Ed or
drawn to things which are addictive or
self-destructive like being excited by
drugs or all right but do remember that
if you truly examine that energy you
will find that it is not the expression
of the energy as excitement it is the
expression of the energy as
anxiety because excitement and anxiety
as we have said are the same energy and
it may be a very fine line for many
individuals as to what they are actually
expressing but anyone that finds the
idea of needing the tool because they
believe that it is the tool that has the
power rather than themselves will
actually be expressing the energy in
terms of anxiety they may call it
excitement but it is not the true
expression of positive excitement and
knowingness it is anxiety and it is in
that sense a discounting of many
portions and an invalidation of many
portions of thems they think it is
excitement to overlook the fact of the
things they fear to face about
themselves because they think that it
will be an ordeal to face those things
and they do not want to face that so
they will pretend that the anxiety they
feel is truly excitement when it isn't
you follow me I do follow you exactly so
so that
the this is a point on which I and other
people have I've expressed confusion to
myself other people have so to
understand it clearly the the way
to the way to understand the difference
is to Simply observe what type of energy
is being utilized in the creation of
that scenario if the individuals again
are placing the power outside of
themselves then it is an act in a
negative direction if they understand
that the power is within them in that
way and that they are a part of Infinite
Creation then you will not see them in
such great expression of
need so the way for an individual to
discern for himself or herself whether
the excitement they feel is genuine
excit or anxiety is to examine whether
they are moving toward whatever it is
that seems to be producing the
excitement the area with a sense that
the power lies within them yes or
whether they're reaching out thinking
that that's going to solve everything
for them yes okay good thank you
and finally ice I'm presently for my own
Evolution concentrating on developing my
emotional body in the sense that there's
a physical body and emo body body and a
spiritual developing it well yes
okay it's my experience of myself that
through various practices I was able to
if you will develop greatly the
spiritual and the mental at the expense
or forgetting or putting
aside okay the emotional body guys now
either you're going to say but that's
impossible and it's merely the way you
were looking at it but what I'm
interested in asking you is for your
help
is for well whatever you're going to
give me back as far
as I think that I'm engaged in the
process of EX of expanding my emotional
and physical body to you think you are
or you feel you
are well I'll feel that I am engaged in
that endeavor and I was going to ask for
your for whatever thoughts you might
have all right we have just given you
one clue to assist in that yes I got
that clue anything else one other
suggestion we can perhaps suggest is to
perhaps cease to think of yourself as
separated bodies and to Simply assume
that they are all simply different
expressions of one idea so that there
will not be so much segregation between
them so that a change in anyone will be
a change in all and that you can simply
relax into the assumption that all of
them are developing quote unquote
accordingly and that will fill you with
a nice
feeling and then you will know that your
emotional body is wide awake when you
feel the feeling that you are doing just
fine I understand that but I'm also
aware that people there is an expression
that people use people involved in the
process of developing growth in
themselves and others yes the expression
that people a person is not grounded or
all right things like that that's what
I'm you are afraid of that occurring to
you I'm not AF no I'm not afraid at all
I'm interested why did you bring it up
I'm interested in in increasing the
degree to which I am grounded in this
throughout various planes of existence I
guess would be a better way of putting
may I ask you a question question sure
thank you what is your definition of the
development of the so-called emotional
body well that's what I didn't have a
clear imaginative conception of which is
what I was actually going to ask you to
help me arrive at because I thought if I
had a
clear conception imaginative conception
it would speed the process ah perhaps
what is getting in your way is the fact
that you think there needs to be a
definition at all and you're spending
time looking for something which doesn't
necessarily have to exist in your
reality no I wasn't I haven't been
spending a lot of time worrying about
the imaginative this was just anide I
did not say you were worrying about it
well I wasn't even spending any time
trying to find it I've been spending
most of my time doing things that seem
to me would be effective at if you will
developing my emotional body as opposed
to other bodies recognizing that each
one is simply a manifestation of the
same single all right but you must must
somewhere within your imagination have a
picture or a
definition of a scenario wherein you
would recognize a time a place an action
on your part that would
represent the development of the
emotional body what does that picture
look like how will you know when it is
developed being completely able
to give and receive and tolerate
tolerate oh one moment
that is quite
different quite
different if you are looking for
Toleration no no wrong choice of the
word all right it's not what I meant
it's what I said but it's not what I
meant what I was thinking of was giving
receiving and also being in the presence
of on a cross flow all different kinds
of emotions with great exuberance and
high volume so you can imagine this yes
you've just helped me do it thank you
then know as we have discussed that if
you can imagine it all you have to do is
act like the picture you imagine and you
will create the effect in your life that
is reflective of the type of life that
that type of being
has that is all you need to do act like
the picture you have created of what it
would be like to be that type of being
and you will be that type of being
follow your picture create your self
image does that assist
you yes thank you are you sure yes it
does I was wondering how one more thing
how to increase the
interconnectedness to One how can one
increase one's interconnectedness to the
all that is you can't you are as
connected as you will ever be you can
increase your awareness of your
interconnectedness by doing what we just
suggested creating an image that you
desire and prefer
and then acting like that image is true
for you like that is a real way that you
can be and then you will see that you
are interconnected by the results you
get by acting like the image you have
created by believing in it by believing
it is
real by believing that because you have
the ability to imagine it that that's
who you are and acting like
that you follow me I do thank you thank
you very much Shing please keep your
questions
come here to be enlightened on a
question that I asked not only for
myself but for some of my friends who
are here tonight all right and this
question has never been verbalized
before so I ask her forgiveness if my
word my
what my
goodness there is nothing to forgive the
way it comes out will be the perfect way
it needs to come out do share your
sharing is a gift just as it is thank
you oh thank you I come from another
time in space to be in this time in
space to fulfill a quest and a mission
I'm doing rather well yes as are all of
you I hope you what hope no need to hope
hope implies despair hope implies you
are not sure you either know or you
don't you are doing just fine I don't
know all or else I would not not ask you
to enlighten me on this one no one will
know all but everyone will know all they
need to know at any given moment to be
completely who they need to
be you know all you need to be who you
are being at any given moment oh I agree
uh let me see if I can put this right
um the mission the quest that we are on
and that I specifically am on uh is
coming to a close and uh we have
utilized the completion of the
mission uh in a mass production way I'm
a writer and a producer and my group and
I have written and produced something uh
rather valuable and
famous um which we hope will have a
wondrous effect more
hope uh you know it will make an impact
I do know it is making an impact we have
a little slight problem oh if you say so
yes I do say so all right um there is
another group and I don't know how this
group exists whether it's a group uh
Collective altered state whether it's a
group of people who sit in a house uh
thinking about us but they do uh create
situations which are detrimental
detrimental is is uh uh they can kill
they have killed they have taken parts
of our group uh they have tried to
dismantle us and our project it doesn't
work in the long run because the mission
the quest is more important than the
individual for its outcome on the planet
however two questions one who are these
beings or people where are they and what
can we do to dismantle them two um my
mate is in another place or plane and is
trying desperately to join me where is
he and what can I do what my
mind now the best I could do now thank
you it is perfect
allow me first to lay down a
foundation what will assist you the
best and in no way shape or form do I
mean this derogatorily or judgmentally
all right sure what will first assist
you the best is to from your definitions
and your perspectives of this overall
scenario remove the
melodrama remove it it doesn't
belong there is no need for you to carry
over from the
Artcraft of melodrama in which you are
involved the idea of melodrama in your
physical life
life
now we will not apply a label to that
group because in that way to define them
more solidly places them more solidly in
your reality and this we will not
do the idea is not to
dismantle them the idea is in a sense
and again we do not mean this term in a
Attack Mode understanding the idea is to
in a sense
overwhelm them with the unconditional
love trust and absolute C certainty that
the reality you believe in most strongly
is
Untouchable by anything that is not of a
similar vibration the only reason that these two
vibration the only reason that these two
ideas and these two groups have been
able to interact is because of your
inherently taught and ingrained beliefs
that you can have an opponent that can
oppose you if you simply are of the vi
atory awareness and level of the idea of
your service and your love and your
light and unconditional trust in your
beingness no being that is not of that
vibration will be able to find you let
alone touch you you follow me may I
comment back absolutely thank you um I
agree with what you're saying on a whole
and I'd also like to state that I am
that very confident person I am
invincible and I shall succeed but I
have a responsibility to others around
me to them not for them to them yes and
I cannot help to understand your
definition of melodrama when a member of
our group is shot in the head dead in
front of us uh we tend to react
emotionally to this one
moment that tendency is not natural it
is
learned and also what we are saying is
that the attraction of that
event in other words that event is the
effect of incorporating
melodrama we are not saying that
melodrama is the result of that action
we are saying that that action is the
result of the belief in the melodrama in
the belief of the good versus evil that
is melodrama because good and evil are
complet completely subjective value
judgments I didn't think I quite um said
that I was the one who was good I'm just
saying that there was we understand but
we are talking about these other
individuals as well we are not simply
speaking of you since you mentioned the
idea of the energy of the group we are
discussing the energy of the individuals
in the group and many of the belief
systems they have bought into in your
reality have ingrained within them a
habitual ritual of thinking of this idea
in terms of a struggle between light and
dark and so that's what they attract
then what is it if it is not that it is
not a struggle if you understand that
the vibration you are is simply going to
be the reality you experience then the
idea of anyone who is not of that
vibration as we have said will never be
able to find you or touch you to be able
to create a struggle you will simply be
beyond their reach fine accepting that
could you please identify this weaker
form for me this group that I am
overpowering with my great confidence we
will not label them no because that will
focus you greater into the idea of a
battle the idea is to love all
unconditionally because you are created
out of unconditional love when you do
that you will then overwhelm them in
that way as a reflection of the fact
that you are as a whole Untouchable in
destructible and if that does not work
for you to say and if that does not work
is for you to deny that you truly
believe that that is the reality you say
you believe in you do not play what if
if you play what if then you are not
willing to believe in what you say you
believe in this is 100% trust that we are
in this is 100% trust that we are
talking about here we are not talking
about what if what if implies less than
100% trust in what you say you believe
you are so how am I doing now you are
doing just fine as always but you will
always be doing fine you will always be
doing perfectly it depends on what
definition of what reality you wish to
perfectly manifest it is always up to
you but the idea in any reality on any
level of experiencing the reality you
know to be true for you and not
experiencing the effect of any other
reality that may not be in synchronistic
accord with you is to Simply know beyond
the shadow of a doubt that you are being
of service that you are being of love
that you are an expression of light and
if you simply know beyond a shadow of a
doubt that that is what you are all
about as well as all the other
individuals in your group and are not
buying into the belief systems that many
of you have been brought up in this
Society to believe in that the idea of
Good and Evil right and wrong must be a
Battle Royal then you will not
experience nor draw into your life the
need to see those manifested scenarios
because it will simply not be a part of
the idea you won't need that type of
expression of melodrama in your life if
you become caught up in that belief
system that is when you are buying into
the negative groups belief system and
that that is what makes you susceptible
in inter is what draws you together if
you simply know that they have nothing
to do with your reality and you have
nothing to do with their reality in
terms of what you are capable of
accomplishing then you will not have to
interact in that way you will not have
to interact in ways that reflect your
belief that this is going to have to be
some sort of a struggle it simply won't
happen so for you to say well what if it
does means that you are buying into that
reality and reinforcing the probability
that that will be the reality you
experience and it doesn't matter what
you have experienced with them whatever
you define yourself to be now in the
present will be what you experience now
in the present and for every present you
create regardless of any other
experience you have ever had perhaps the
experience of interacting with them is
to realize simply that there are many
negative beliefs that are held by
individuals even in what you all your
positive group and for them to recognize
that it is only those negative beliefs
that attract any other negative
individual that is it I see that we both
have very clear positive realities
Unfortunately they are not the same
thank you all right but that again is
not unfortunate for every being is what
they are by their choice and they create
the realities they experience utterly as
the product of what they have been
taught to believe is true then there is
no one truth except that the truth is
composed of all truths individuals can
express themselves in positive ways in
negative ways positive simply being
integrative negative being segregative
but an individual who simply knows that
they are integrative in that way will by
the Light by which they shine simply
show an individual who is negative that
they are a Untouchable and that b they
are giving back to the negative
individual an offering of a choice a
choice to understand that they can also
be positive or if they do not choose to
be positive they can simply go their way
for that which is negative cannot exist
within the blinding light of that which
is positive that is all there is to it
it is simple
mechanics thank you bash shooting
BHA I have a mystery that I know you'll
be able to help me with oh you know that
don't be too sure well I think you might
be able to help me with it relates to
your earlier talking about negating all
experience and it also relates to a
question I had asked you on Sunday about
Poltergeist activities to keep a long series of
activities to keep a long series of
events short it was seeing lights in the
sky in an unusual formation
uh dreams about
extraterrestrials that were for me uh
nightmares all right pains in the head
and a a year of not being very well
always constantly unwell and the the
question is about that energy was it
something that I had negated and I
should have opened up to again there are
no shs but we would recommend that if
you simply were willing to understand
that there really was nothing to fear
then would not have experienced the fear
that you did it's very fearful at time
but the idea many times of the reason
that those fears occur in your society
when you are interacting with beings
from other societies in that way no
matter on what level you are interacting
with them the reason that many of those
fears occur is because let us say and
again in no way shape or form is this
meant to be a comparative judgment that
you are any less than any other being
but the way you create yourself to be
the way you have been taught to think of
yourselves creates with you the ability
to hide and suppress many portions of
your Consciousness from yourselves and
in doing so you function on a lower
vibratory frequency very often when you
come into contact with a being that
operates on a very high vibratory
frequency because it is willing to know
itself as completely as it can then
those two frequencies when they come
together will usually create the effect
of the higher frequency in a sense
overwhelming the lower frequency and
forcing the lower frequency to rise in
Pitch in forcing the lower frequency to
raise in Pitch that will bring to the
surface all the things that you have
been keeping buried within you and
bringing those things to the surface
when you are not ready to face them can
be a very fearful experience for many of
you that is where the fear comes from
that is why also we maintain along with
all the other extraterrestrial
civilizations in general our distance
from you until you are willing to
function as an integrated society and
truly believe 100% in your own positive
manifest reality for as long as you are
able to bury things within you and
beliefs within you then you will
generate the idea of fear that will
attract these negative scenarios into
your life and it is only that fear of
yourself that you are feeling it is not
really an intrinsic fear of the
Extraterrestrial it is the fear of all
the things you have been taught to fear
in your life coming to the surface
forcing you to face these things you
follow me yeah was that an experience
that I needed at particular ular
experience I needed for myself to face
all those I understand exactly what
you're saying or was it did they what
did they want it is an experience you
agreed to because you wish to expand in
many ways and you were willing to allow
them to be of assistance to you you know
they are doing you no harm they know
that it may for now seem like an ordeal
of sorts to you but they also know that
your higher Consciousness knows it will
survive intact are they still around oh
yes can I contact them in some way now
I'm learning to some degree we would
suggest that you Avail yourself of much
of the literature that is now existent
within the interactions of other
individuals that have had similar
experiences to you where do I find one
in particular that we have referred to
is a literary work you now call
communion I have not heard of it you
will okay thank you thank you you will
see many similarities many connections
and many of your questions will be
answered by that work and I I presume
that the the weakness in my physical
body is also connected with the fears
that are releasing themselves it will
get better the tensions only the
tensions are draining you mhm thank you
oh thank you very much for being so
willing and
recognize that what you are going
through is an indication of how strong
you actually know you are come to
yes so focus on the strength not upon
what you think is a sign of weakness
okay and you will be strong thank you
thank you very much
sharing andto you um I find myself
impatient and right anxious anxious
patient um you are not enjoying life
then no I
am contradiction
if you are enjoying the life you are
living if you are enjoying every moment
whether you are going to prefer to
change that into something else or not
if you are enjoying life for what it is
then you are too busy having fun to
think that you are waiting for something
better to come along therefore you don't
need patience and therefore you will not
feel impatient the only reason you feel
impatient the only reason you feel
impatient in your lives is because you
think you need to be patient but you
don't being patient is the assumption
that you are waiting for something
better to come along and nothing better
will come along that again is a value
judgment differences will occur things
can be more expanded you can always
learn you will always change and
transform but what you are again once
again at every given moment is a perfect
manifestation of the idea you are being
and when you live your life now in a
childlike fashion fascinated curious and
enjoyful of all the things that come
into your life because you know that the
things that are in your life are there
for you for your reasons for you to
learn from you will be enjoying yourself
so much that before you know it all the
things that you were waiting for will
already be upon you because when you
live in the moment you do not create the
experience of the passage of time to as
great a degree as you do when you are
sitting around waiting for things to
happen and that is what will create the
acceleration that you desire you follow
me yes does that assist you yes do you
believe that your life as it is is worth
enjoying absolutely well thank you very
much then if you live in that childlike
way you will not notice the passage of
time so much because you will not be
creating as much time and because you
will not be creating as much time you
will become more
Timeless ageless
you will not need to age the more you
enjoy the less you
age you follow me
yes hello Bashar hello uh I was
wondering is there anybody that's
channeling um to a predominantly either
an audience of children or an audience
of
adolescence at this
point in a sense yes but it usually
occurs only when children are among
children
uhhuh uh could it occur in a more overt
fashion as we're doing here it can occur
in any way your imagination can
co-create it
mhm
um what I'm just curious in what your
opinion is on
how um but this is up to this is up to you
um but this is up to this is up to you
you will create the methodologies you
will create the attractions the basic
impact it will have is to allow into
what you call the children's lives the
ability to know that their imaginations
are representative of reality and it
will allow them to not forget as much
you follow me yes so that in that way
they will know that more and more
probabilities can be manifested in their
lives and many of them then will be able
to manifest these ideas in a more
accelerated way once again reminding
many of the
adults as to who they
are the idea of any such attraction of
course will be the product of the
co-creation with the children since they
will if they find themselves gathered
together in that type of interaction
been responsible for creating that
momentum or Direction in their lives
from the time when they were not
children prior to birth you follow me
mhm so by all means if you find yourself
following that threat if that excites
you you yourself may find the child
within you you follow me
you you follow me
um if you are willing to put it together
go ahead uh do you mean as being
channelled through me another entity
Channel Through Me or just myself
creating that I I you can create the
interaction mhm you and a sense will be
channeling but in a different way but
you can pull the interaction together
mhm if that excites you it is up to you
it will have a profound
impact on what you call that
generation for again realize that what
you are experiencing as the birth taking
place upon your planet now is not simply
just another generation it is literally
another culture altogether
already MH in your terms it is a Quantum
Leap in understanding
what age group um from what age group up
would that three mhm through
adolescence well through I guess through
forever You may wish to break it at
approximately 11 or 12 because different
things begin to occur for individuals at
that time frame I remember different
focuses of extreme psychic and
telepathic sensitivity in a different
way will Blossom at that time
mhm okay thank you very much thank you
very much for your willingness to
co-create such an
impact sharing hi masar hi this is
Jessica hey I spoke to you last week
about utar hey and um that will happen
in marching the Dolphins enjoy I will
you will expand empathically in many
ways thank you for your love thank you
for yours
sharing hello again B how hello perfect
on you perfect thank you I have two
questions all right uh a a first one is
when you are telepathically
communicating as you are with this
lovely bunch tonight lovely bunch lovely
bunch where is your instrument Daryl where is
where is your instrument Daryl where is
his Consciousness is he disembodied no
no no no no the idea of this proceeding
is not a bodily inhabitation it is the
linking of our combined consciousnesses
he is willing to allow his Consciousness
to become pliable enough to take on the
aspects of my vibratory frequency and so
represent your physiological version
using the clay of his consciousness of
my Consciousness that can be represented
in your societ
uhhuh it is a telepathic link okay thank
you b b okay you have access as we all
do to a great source of information yes
um on occasion I see you when someone
asks you a question for instance you
turn your head to the side and
you just like
that and you pause for a moment and you
seem to be plugging into some kind of
system for the information yes okay my
question is yes where are you going for
that information different places at
different times because of Our intention
we are simply automatically attracted to
whatever vibratory level we need to be
to assist us in acquiring what
information will be of best service at
that time sometimes it is dialogues with
your own higher consciousnesses
sometimes dialogue with our society
other societies others who may be
familiar with you more in a different
way than we are we plug into whatever we
need to but we find out what that is
simply because of the intention of our
vibration and it simply leads us where
we need to be led mhm is there any uh
particular information that is not
accessible to you and if so why is it
not accessible to you because it may not
fit the idea of the interaction going on
at the time it may information that will
be revealing to you something that will
in your terms interrupt your flow so to
speak in other words there may be things
you do not want to know things that in a
sense we would be revealing to you that
would take you or Rob you of the
surprises you have in store for yourself
and so we will place limitations upon
ourselves so that we will not interfere
in that sense MH you follow me oh yes I
wouldn't want to spoil the surprises
would thank you very much
we thank you oh One Moment One
Moment One
Word it is from what you call
colloquially your guides are you ready
I'm not
sure okay I'm ready I'm ready all
[Laughter] right carousel right carousel
pleasant
[Laughter]
dreams there will be in your terms but a
few moments remaining for this
interaction this evening of your time
proceed hello Bashar hello um a couple
of years ago I became acquainted with
the phenomenon of Jay-Z Knight and
ramtha yes and um I was very interested
in everything I heard and read about it
and it seems that recently everything I
hear and read about Jay-Z KN and ramtha
um is not we will not validate nor
invalidate at this time is there
anything you can if it works for you use
it if it doesn't don't
okay the next question
is
um I'm going through something now in my
life that seems contradictory oh how
exciting you are discovering the
paradoxes in your life and that means
you are now standing firmly in your
higher Consciousness because it is
within higher Consciousness that you
examine all Paradox because it is from
higher Consciousness that all Paradox
comes thank you does
that can that result in the fact that
I'm um spending more time than usual getting
um spending more time than usual getting
over a virus
to some degree yes you may be placing
yourself on hold for various reasons not
that you have to do it in a disease
oriented Manner and it is not exactly a
virus can you help me out in figuring
out what is what is going on that's
making me feel less than we can assist
you to accelerate through the process if
you will when you lay down take three
deep breaths relax and imagine yourself
turning into a sphere of blue energy
dissolving in that sphere of blue energy
and then becoming one single idea one
single thought and simply assessing
yourself seeing what you are all about
allowing yourself to examine in that
sphere in that homogenous State all
ideas all pictures all imaginations all
feelings all thoughts all beliefs that
come to you examine them as you would as
if you were standing in the library of
yourself which you will
be simply assess them notice them
acknowledge them incorporate them and
allow them to fit as they need to fit
then when you recrystallize yourself you
will recrystallize as a being that
understands more of the self that has
allowed certain keys to be turned in
certain locks and when you awaken in the
morning do not try to look for it simply
go about your business and pop pop pop
into your conscious awareness will come
the things that you will now allow to
fall into
place okay and um can you ask um my
guides if they can give me a word to
send me off uh laughing send you off
laughing yes yes
yes
ice may not seem funny now
thank you one
moment that is not all you said a word
but there are two
words Ice
Cube let it in your mind melt in the sun
melt in the sun yes the radiance of your
own Inner Light let it melt and you will
not catch
cold you follow
me pleasant dreams thank you use that in
your imagination when you drift off to
sleep let it melt into the warmth of all
that is at this timing allow us to
extend to each and every one of you our
unconditional love and appreciation once
again in your willingness to co-create
this dream that we are all now this
night of your time
you are living your own dream wake up
and dream the dream you prefer to
dream we thank you for your
gifts our energy and love to you all we
bid you a f and
f and
loving at least on our planet at this
time in the position I am in a lovely
Dawn good day
make [Applause] how'd it
go thank you all for being here
tonight brief announcements uh someone
named lost a wallet if anybody sees a
wallet laying around
anywhere um you can have audio tapes
tonight of tonights if you like and can
see the ly we can make them real fast if
you want or any other of the tapes on
the list she's got quite a few of them
here uh video tapes you see
Paul um the ask a question for a friend
of a friend a friend of a
friend his name is Paul and he lives in
Wisconsin and my friend tells me that
her sense of this person is that he's
always been searching for the more in a
manner of speaking um but it's been in
kind of a state of turmoil or struggle
um because there's not so many overt
spiritual kinds of experiences to be had
in Wisconsin one
moment not as many
channelers that does not matter each and
every being upon your planet is a
spiritual experience in him or herself the idea is
experience in him or herself the idea is
for this individual perh perhaps this is
simply a suggestion to stop looking so
hard outside and start looking within
you follow me yes if that individual
knows that they are a spiritual
experience they will know they are
connected to every other any other
spiritual experience upon your entire
world within the entire
Multiverse they can then function as
their own funnel their own channel their
own Gateway their own doorway they do
not have to strive and struggle and
search outside themselves when they
simply turn within because that is where
the totality of existence comes from
anyway you follow me
yes does that assist you is there
anything else that you can say we intend
to send him this tape any
tape any
nearby Hill and or mountain of any sort
or tall structure
can be utilized by this
individual climb it sit relax recline
upon it consider the sky in day in night
the Sun the other
stars Muse imagine day dream then climb
down and be very close to the Earth if
you wish I have this individual you lay
down upon the ground feel the connection
to the Earth after having felt the
connection to the sky and realize that
each is its own representational energy
for its own purposes and that no one way
is better than any other way and that
the idea of spiritual searches is to
recognize that all levels of reality
both that which is in your terms
heavenward and that which is also of
your Earth are equally spiritual in
nature and that physical reality is not
to be denied as something less than the
spirit world for physical reality is a
part of spirit you follow me yes
also we perceive in this individual many
strong incarnations in what you would
call your Native American culture and
this individual may find some assistance
with regard to certain Native American
individuals who may reside in that area
there may be some symbology that will
allow this individual to remember the
things that will assist him in centering
the quickest and the
easiest sorry when you say that area are
you referring to the area he's living in
now yes okay thank you of the earth is
also spiritual you follow me yes that is
the assistance we perceive we can be we
thank you thank you very much
sh hello hello it seems seems since the
beginning of the year I've had many
wonderful opportunities to be excited
job opportunities uh apartment
opportunities all right and I've been
feeling a lot of expansiveness and
taking the opportunities that excite me
oh thank you very much uh one of these
opportunities was an apartment in the
same building I live in now was offered
to me and I was supposed to move this
weekend and I was also supposed to move
a year ago and it ended up after being
packed and ready to move I didn't move
all right um maybe you have moved in
other directions well I thought that I
needed this apartment to be creative and
to expand because I've been feeling
somewhat claustrophobic all right but
again do recognize that there is a
difference between following what
excites you and allowing that to become
expectation thinking that it should
manifest there are no
shoulds you may be changing so quickly
that even when you accept an opportunity
that does come to you as the product of
your excitement that may change before
it has an opportunity to complete itself
because you are ready to go on to
something else that
quickly well my question is I was going
to move this weekend and I was all
packed and last night um I decided I
wasn't going to move because the manager
decided not to put new carpeting and
drapes in the apartment and so I
unpacked all my boxes and out of
Integrity decided decided not to take
the apartment and all day today I was
very upset and anxious feeling very
closed in doesn't sound like Integrity
to
me um I spoke to the manager this
evening and I am taking the apartment
and now I am moving in and I want to
know why I caused this struggle even
though I know I don't need to cause this
struggle well obviously at that point
you did not necessarily believe so
strongly that you did not need to or you
would not
have now allow yourself to recognize
that it perhaps it simply was a last
vestage of an idea you may have been
hanging on to the idea of
assuming that every little detail has to
be just a certain way before what you
feel needs to happen can happen but that
is not necessarily so all of the details
will take care of themselves and
whatever details are there are never
going to be anything that will impede
what truly excites you what truly
motivates you you do not have to in that
way necessarily always be so
pyun as an expression of your integrity
the idea of Integrity is to function as
an integrated whole and not necessarily
focus on a particular part you follow me
yes if you simply knew that the energy
was correct for you then you would not
have been in your terms stopped by the
idea of one particular variable which
you really know if you stop to think
about it doesn't necessarily have that
much to do with the overall energy of
your excitement but which pointed out to
you that there are still in your mind
details that can or you believe can slow
you down or impede the progress you
believe you are making you follow me the
details meaning expectations on how
things are to occur yes yes but again
once you put the energy out there and
created to be an activation all the
details take care of themselves and
whatever details are there are the
details that need to be there to
represent the energy of your excitement
not function as a symbol of interruption
in your excitement who knows what you
would have discovered in the idea well
you will find out now that you have
decided to go ahead but the idea of that
particular detail may be serving a
particular purpose and if you simply
allow yourself to trust and go into the
scenario following your excitement you
will know soon enough why that
particular detail is there and why it
has stood out to you it does not mean it
is something there to hold you back it
is there to Aid and assist you perhaps
in a very unexpected
way but that is what life is all about
Discovery and the unexpected growth and
change allow yourself to follow what
excites you do not worry about the
details in that way they will transform
in whatever way they need to after after
whatever details are there have served
their purpose if something is there it
serves a purpose you follow me yes so do
remember that when these things seem
most perplexing to you in many different
levels the idea is not to Simply look at
this and say well how does this fit into
the life I've already lived but also to
recognize that these things fit into the
life you have yet to live and so you're
not necessarily going to consciously
know why it is there until you go Full
Ahead into the experience and then you
will understand why it was the way it
was just because it is that way now
doesn't mean it is going to remain that
way you follow me yes and it may because
of the way it is now lure you into other
scenarios that you truly will find
exciting everything plays A Part nothing
is out of line nothing is in a situation
for no reason simply follow the most
overwhelming excitement
and do not allow yourself to focus on
the idea that one or two details do not
seem to be appropriate to your
excitement if they are there because you
know you are creating your reality as a
reflection of your excitement then
simply assume that the details that
don't seem to fit now must still be a
part of the exciting momentum you have
generated and that sooner or later you
will see how they do fit in you follow
me yes so enjoy and discover
you may find out within what you call
now not that you have to spend time
looking for it but you may find out
within what you call the next three
weeks to six of your
weeks why that exists in the way it does
and what you will attract because it
exists in the way it
does all right yes thank you it will
also give you an opportunity once you
accept and move into a situation for you
to know you have the empowerment to
change your
foundation you follow
me
yes thank you thank you
sharing hi bash hi um I was wonder if
you could discuss for just a moment at
aspects of fear and recognizing it and
moving through it you have trouble
recognizing fear do
you well unless it's a shark coming at
me sometimes
yes if you are having trouble
recognizing fear then perhaps you're not
as fearful as you
think what about
that that'd be lovely it what would be
it is love oh thank you do you really
believe it is
lovely yes do you understand that you
can utilize the idea of fear if and when
you should choose to create it to
understand that it is simply another way
many times out of your habits to force
yourself to face something you have not
paid attention to it brings you
completely Into the Now moment many
times not that you have to experience it
in that way but many times you will
experience the idea of fear because you
have been taught not to listen to the
things that you need to listen to when
they come to you in subtle ways so if
you ignore them and ignore them and
ignore them and ignore them then they
will become louder and louder and more
fearful and scary to get your attention
first of all so many times when you feel
the idea of great fear that is simply a
proportional indication of how much
attention getting you need when
regarding communication from yourself to
yourself so when fate s me a lesson
translate when Universe God myself
whoever thank you oh I got the right
answer thank
you you are giving yourself an
opportunity to discover another portion
of yourself that up to that moment in
your life you have either been taught to
suppress or not been willing to face or
simply not needed to look at at that
point and perhaps have been taught that
that would be something that would never
come up in your life but now it has
anything that occurs in your life in
that way is there once again for a
reason and if you are willing to accept
and acknowledge that if you have created
it to come in a fearful way that that
was simply to get your attention then
thank the fear and tell it that the next
time it delivers something to you you
will pay attention more quickly so it
will be less fearful next time and the
next time and the next time you follow
me yes I do thank you thank you very
much for your expression and willingness
of trust
that is all you need to dispel all
fear Sharon Hi hi how you doing perfect
I'm you perfect thank you fine you I've
been talking to you a lot have you been
hearing me
yes um the first thing is on Tuesday
Morning within a period of an hour I
came into contact with about four or
five or six individuals who all had car
accidents and I witnessed one myself
that morning it happened so quickly it
was one right after the other yes and I
was wondering what was going on well you
are bringing more synchronicity into
your life in a
sense it is an opportunity for you to
recognize that there truly are no
accidents for if you had taken the time
and taken the opportunity to examine
each and every one of those ideas you
would understand the inter relationship
you would understand the belief systems
of all the individuals and attracting
those events to themselves you are being
given an opportunity by yourself and in
function and in concert with your higher
self to Simply understand how all things
do connect up now it does not mean they
have to connect up that abruptly in that
way but you are going to begin to unlock
within your vision now more and more
opportunities to know that every event
is interconnected with every other event
and that they are all parts of a single
event a single momentum that you will
now have the ability to trace in many
ways you are in a sense developing well
now this is going to be extremely
colloquial in your language do not
necessarily take me literally but apply
whatever your imagination so desires you
are in a sense developing your ability
and sensitivity to be a type of well
psychic sluth for you have the ability and
sluth for you have the ability and
opportunity to increase your awareness
level and sensitivity level so that all
factors that go into playing a part in
interconnecting with other factors will
make themselves known to you quite
abruptly you will not miss them they
will get your attention very strongly
I've been avoiding that in a sense I
know you what you mean all right you are
simply also seeing the idea that the
different vehicles that individuals are
living in life are only an outward
symbol and are quite bendable in that
way they can take them where they need
to go have taken them where they need to
go and now they will redefine find some
of those vehicles in that way so they
can know there are many other ways to
travel as
well you follow me mhm yes there are no
dead ends I know that yes I know you TR that
ends I know that yes I know you TR that
um I got a call the other day from
cliff and he told me about something
that we discussed um about a project
about an idea um and I have a person in
my life who could facil itate this idea
with me and with cliff and with this
person
um I don't know what I want to ask about
it I just feel like I simply allow
yourself the
opportunity now right now this very
moment yes this
one to resonate within your
heart right
now breathing in a relaxed Manner and
deeply resonate within your heart the
absolute certainty right now of the vibration you
certainty right now of the vibration you
know you
are any vibration you are will be the
effect you extract from any Endeavor you
are know that you
know that I know that you
know that you are squarely in
synchronous harmony with the path you ch
chose to be and that any such
branchings are all quite on the main
trunk of the tree that's what I want to
talk about is the trunk
yes it's all of a sudden shifted in the
last two months not really I can see the
the connection but and I can see the
path and I've always been aware that
that's been the path on a certain level
yes um
forget it there's no point to
talking what do I want to ask M maybe
you would prefer to make a statement
rather than a question maybe now that is
actually more easy than creating a
question maybe that is what is confusing
you you know what you need to know and
if you are willing to put it in the form
of a statement rather than a question it
may now feel more natural to you
I know that I have all the resources and
all of the pieces right in front of me I
can see them right where right in me
right they're within me now will you do
me a favor sure repeat after me I sure
I you do this to me every
time I do you enjoy this yes thank you
all right I I am am all all the pieces the
right I I am am all all the pieces the
pieces you follow me yes thank you very
much oh thank you I have done
nothing I have one further question all
right this individual Julie who's
connected to the person I love very much
um has this great intensity of hatred
for me that I have rarely
encountered and I was wondering just to
get some perspective because I've
already decided how I'm going to deal
with it I'm going to deal with it with
love but I want wondered what it was
that she and I might have shared you
have been intense
Rivals you have many times fought
bitterly over another
individual well once that stands out but
also over
ideology more than the idea of
individuals can you can you give me a
sense of time period
let us simply
say that some of it might involve
clerical aspects you understand the terminology
aspects you understand the terminology
yes I
do thank you thank you it is a
sterling opportunity to reflect back the same
opportunity to reflect back the same
degree of unconditional
love that's what I've already decided s
I'm in there thank
you shouting hello
shouting hello
hello um what I'd like to ask is I'm in
a uh career position right now a career
position working yes that um I feel is
stagnating stagnating what would you rather be
stagnating what would you rather be
doing that is more
exciting I'm not sure sure but well I'll
give you a moment to ponder
it time's
up what would you rather be doing that
is more
exciting um in general in general what
would you rather be doing we are not
asking you to put qualifications upon it
we are not asking you to pick something
that fits into a category of anything
what would you rather be doing in your
life that would be more exciting
traveling all
right then your career position may be
quite a mobile
one the the current position that I'm in
uh is offering is going to to go on
hiatus all short break yes and they want
me to return do you want
to uh not really all right understand
once again and we again are not simply
speaking philosophically we are speaking
mechanically physics whatever excites you the most in
physics whatever excites you the most in
life is the sign is the signal the
excitement is the signal of the things
that represent your vibration in life at
that moment most accurately repres ENT
the vibration of the things you can do
in life most
effortlessly represent the opportunity
in life that you will be supported most
quickly by the universe within that's
what excitement is for many of you
always when you reach and create in your
lives points of Despair say oh Universe
oh Lord oh God whatever you wish to
turnament give me a
sign but you have these signs all the
time and you ignore them because you do
not believe in them because you do not
believe them to be valid excitement is
the sign whatever contains the most
excitement that's what you are the most
about you follow me yes so at any given
moment if you simply act upon the things
that excite you the most and do not act
upon the things that don't you will be
making your career moves
appropriately so so even if it appears
on the surface important Point appears
on the surface that the move you will
make has nothing to do with what you
think it
should all excitement is connected by a
single thread all of it and anything
that you are capable of acting upon will
always lead you into other scenarios
that will excite you that at this moment
you may not be capable of acting upon
but by acting upon the things you are
capable of acting upon you will gain the
experience you will need to have to be
able to act upon the other opportunities
later all excitement is a single thread
it is always
connected I see my concern is um UNC to
to
leave uh a disposition yes to uh have no
uh other job to go to
although I'm unhappy in it
presently without meaning to chastise you did you
without meaning to chastise you did you
hear anything of what we
said yes then understand we are speaking
as a total event whenever you follow
what excites you the most you will be
supported in whatever way you need to be
supported in whatever ever way you need
to be supported to allow you to continue
to be the thing that you are most being
that excites you the most all the
details will be attracted into your life
to allow you to continue to do that
exciting thing all the details all the
details you follow me yes
now do you understand the concept yes do
you believe you can live the
concept yes all right if you are willing
to recognize that it is a that simple
and that b nothing is too simple to be
true then you will know it will work and
when you believe it will work you will
see it work you will prove it to
yourself by the feedback you create by
believing that it will work to begin
with because that is what you are doing
already we are not suggesting that you
do something you are not already doing
we are simply suggesting that you put
your trust and put your faith in the
direction of things you prefer to do
rather than in the direction of things
you don't because the universe always
supports you in whatever Direction you
put your trust and if you're putting
your trust in something you don't like
to do the universe will always send you
more opportunities to do things you
don't like to
do so if you'd prefer to do something
you would enjoy then put your trust and
faith in that direction and the same
mechanism will bring you the things that
are representative of the direction you
have placed your trust within excitement
is the key that is what lets you know
what direction represents the positive
integrative accelerative expansive
fulfillment of the path you chose to be
in this life you follow me yes thank you
thank you very very much for a
stimulating and exciting
[Music] interaction
sharing hi hi I have a question my mom
died when I was six all right and um
I've always wondered where she
is individuals will experience many
different ideas
primarily stayed with you as a guide up
to and through what you would
call especially attentive through what
you would call your
13th year to 17th years you follow
year to 17th years you follow
me of your life you follow me
yeah from that point you were on your
own momentum and the IND individual in a
sense has
reincarnated you follow me yes does not
assist you yes understand that you
always still carry that portion of that
individual within you the love from that
individual always
always
always envelops you and if you anytime
you think of that individual with love
and with light
your thoughts your emotions will be felt
by the overs soul of that being
regardless of whether any fragment of
the overs Soul has reincarnated or not
and your love and thoughts can even
assist that individual even in the
physical life and in many ways your
thoughts will bleed through and may act
as a type of guide now for that
individual even as that individual acted
as your guide you follow me yes thank
you for creating such a loving
interaction you have done this for each
other many many times thank you oh thank
you
sharing hello bash hello uh I was
wondering is there anybody that's
channeling um to a predominantly hey I
spoke to you last week about utar hey
and um I also spoke to utar through
Torah last night as
um in my channeling
process um it's difficult for me to vocalize
um it's difficult for me to vocalize
actual words that is all right and last
night utar
requested that I use communication
devices and he spoke of you as a
communication device and Torah as a
communication device as to some degree
right to some degree um
um and I was receiving pictures of other
devices um did you see the three-sided
pyramidal one yes uh three-sided
pyramidal as three you may have assumed
it was four but it was three yeah I
think I did um I've been
using the T like a split
tetrahedron um as an image like using it
the way a headset would be used as an
image all right that will be of
assistance um energize it with blue
energy um also using the imagery that he
suggested last week when he spoke
through you um of the lightning bolt the and the
you um of the lightning bolt the and the
lightning rod and the lightning rod do
you know why utar is the ancient word
for both the lightning bolt and the
lightning rod no I don't know why
because our society thinks in terms of
relation ships and the two things that attract
ships and the two things that attract
each other most strongly in that way are
the same single event with the same
single label oh okay yes I see um I was
wondering if there were other kinds of devices
if there were other kinds of devices
that could accelerate my channeling
process some clear crystals Maybe of
assistance in what you would call Rod
form Rod form as six
sided okay um would it be preferable for
them to be raw or polished they can be
either if it has a slight blue tinge
that will be of assistance there is a
particular type of Crystal that also is
found in what you call the Ural area
that has a slight blue tinge this will
form a very strong link for you as a
symbol okay
um also when he is speaking of you or
Torah as a communication device yes uh
translation device
um is he talking about a blending that
goes on between you and himself and then
translate down through me to some degree
we are facilitating the energy for you
modulating it in a way that will allow
you to become comfortable with it so you
will let it through at whatever rate is
comfortable for you okay um my sensing
is that he's um slightly well he seems
sort of amphibious or that's a word that
is the idea of the serious connection
that goes along with the Triad even as
the reference you call Chip is the
connection of my higher Consciousness
and represents the same serious energy
which your Society translates as an
amphibious energy but which is not
literally so so then in addition to utar
there is another blending going on yes
because the whole Triad is there that's
why we recommend the tetrahedral
structure the three-sided
pyramided okay your planet our planet
and the planet around Sirius which we
refer to as sisin are three parts of a
collective Consciousness okay is there any other
Consciousness okay is there any other
comments that uh you could make about my
channeling process in terms of um
clearing myself as a channel and
stepping aside think about
aside think about
comets this may or may not make much
sense to you now but it is the device
that may trigger many doorways for you
when you are going to sleep this night
of your time think about
comets okay thank you very much thank
you
chatting hi Bashar hi I'm enjoying
meeting with you tremendously and you I
wanted to ask a couple of questions all
right first one the society which I came
from is even more uh closed than this
one and very discouraging in one which
society is that that's Soviet Union all
right uh by the way do you uh have any
connections or have you made any
connections with people from that
country yes anyway um it's very discouraging in
yes anyway um it's very discouraging in
one's
self-beliefs um so um I think I I feel
fortunate being open and just um just
accepting whatever you're saying and
feeling that it's true all right you do
not have to but in this way the idea is
to recognize that what you call your
Soviet Union and your United States of
America are factions of each other in
many different ways and each reflects to
the other the things that fears in the
self the
most yeah that's what I feel I I agree
with you
um uh I'm thinking of um of um yes how
does one um go about imagining himself
uh in a new situation in a new job
situation because that's what I'm that's
the process all right again it is a
matter of focusing upon what excites you
the most most first of all creating the
visualization the imagination seeing
yourself in a scenario that creates Joy
within you and then simply activating
that picture with all your heart's
desire then
relax let the details fall into place
you do not have to make them fit allow
them to fit because your energy
activation will attract the necessary
opportunities and again whether it
appears to be connected to what you
think it should be or not whether it
appears to be representative of the path
you think you would like to take if it
comes with the same degree of excitement
if it stimulates you in that way that is
your sign that whether it looks like it
or not that is the opportunity that will
lead you where you want to go no matter
what it is you follow me yes thank you
thank you um another question is uh I'm
thinking of um going back visiting my
family and right there are lots of
people which are afraid um for me they
just afraid that um I could be even
either kept there or because the whole
society is pretty
um they wouldn't um their reactions
could be very are you planning to stay
for approximately three of your months
no much much less how much about a
couple of
weeks at this time it is our perception
that if you do go and come back which
you can you may wish to go back
again in or about the area of May
thank you there are scenarios which you
can be of assistance
to that are taking place in terms
of allowing for what you might call a
leakage of information to seep into the
soil of that land so that it can be
harvested by those
people your energy will remain has
remained and you can utilize that now as
a
conduit see yourself there now see the
bridge that links you from there to
where you are see that as a crystallin
bridge that is unbreakable along that
bridge you will be able to come and
go you follow me I do thank you thank
you very much the last very short
question is uh last year but at the same
time um I had an experience which
um in the evening I met two people at
the bar which later in the same night
appeared in my dream and um they they
kind of followed me to a very um he
Heavenly um environment and and I met a
person there with a very unusual
appearance with a kind of square head
and bright deep blue eyes and that was a
dream which he reacted to me in a very
in a very loving and just um
incredibly way
he kissed me and I just wanted to know
do St yes you have your guides and they
are strongly with
you strongly with you feel them wherever
you go they are always with you feel
their joy in a way the amusement is that you
joy in a way the amusement is that you
do have the capability of slipping in
and out of realities that other people
think will hold
you there are many more doorways around
you than others may think through which
you can
slip thank you thank you very much sharing