I don't say how are you all this day of
your time as you create time to exist.
Allow us to begin this interaction, this
day of your time, with a laying down of
a few foundational concepts that will
allow perhaps more ease of communication
within this interaction that your
civilization and our civilization have
co-created today.
First of all, allow us to remind each
and every one of you that even though
you may be perceiving what you would
call a singular identity, a singular
entity in this interaction, we are in
that sense representative of hundreds,
thousands, millions in your terms of
counting of consciousness that are
representative of what you call the
association of worlds. And they have in
their own manner telepathically as you
say plugged into my consciousness for
each and any of the interactions we have
with you. So understand that while there
may be a gathering of individuals on
your side there is a gathering of
individuals on our side as well. The
idea will be as follows. That we are in
many ways extremely excited or
interested to be interacting with
members of any
civilization including your
civilization. For we can learn much in
the way of your civilization's offerings
to us by seeing through each and every
one of you individually and collectively
how you have interpreted your particular
facet of the multi-dimensional crystal
of infinite creation. We always interact
with every civilization knowing beyond a
shadow of a doubt that they are in every
way, shape, and form equal to any
civilization we are aware of. No matter
whether or not you may have labels or
terminologies for other civilizations
that you may call more advanced than
your own civilization, these things are
not only just a matter of labeling. They
are only a matter of perspective in that
way. There may be an opportunity to
realize that your civilization is
changing, is expanding, perhaps even
similarly to the ways our civilization
has expanded. But in no way, shape, or
form are our methodologies being
presented to you to allow you to think
that our methodologies are better than
the ways you might choose. We are simply
here interacting with your civilization
at this time because we have recognized
that your civilization is exploring
things and ideas and levels of
consciousness that we have explored that
have worked for us. And as you create
that exploration in your consciousness,
you radiate a particular frequency that
we have in your terms picked up upon and
we accept as an invitation in a sense to
interact with you in this way now to
reflect to you some of the ways these
ideas you are exploring have worked for
us so that if you wish to you can adapt
and adopt some of the ideas we have used
into your own reality if you find they
work for you. The reason we are doing
this is because we love you
unconditionally and experience a great
deal of joy at seeing your own creative
expressiveness come to the fullest
possible blossoming that it can. And we
again always receive benefit out of
these interactions because by
interacting with you, we get to
experience more ways that the infinite
has of creating itself to be. And this
expands our understanding of creation as
well, which allows us to know there is
always more and more and more to
explore. We would enjoy exploring these
ideas with you as equals. But do
understand we are in many ways beings
like yourselves. We do not know
everything. We know everything we need
to know to be who we are. You know
everything you need to know to be who
you are being at any given moment. And
individually and together we can
discover more. But do understand that
the fundamental as you say purpose to
these interactions is to remind you each
and every one of you that you have the
power to function as a reflection of the
infinite and to know beyond a shadow of
a doubt that all the answers you seek
are attainable through the gate and the
doorway that is your own individual
consciousness. Is all of this making
sense in your language so far? Is it
translating adequately?
The idea therefore is to perhaps keep in
mind within all of these interactions
that from time to time there may be
concepts in our society that do not let
us say translate in your language
adequately. There may be concepts in
your society that do not translate into
our society in exactly the same way. And
therefore, let us in your terminology be
aware of semantic differences in all of
the things we will discuss. Very often
it has been our experience that where
there seems to be in any discussion a
great deal of difference, there really
is no difference at all in the
fundamental point of view, but only a
difference in the way you go about
defining it. And if we can trust that we
basically all of us are coming from the
same source of infinite creation then on
some level you all have to know and we
all have to know that ultimately we are
all saying the same thing. So the idea
now will be to engage in expansion of
awareness and exploration together and
we extend to you our deepest
appreciation at allowing us to
experience the gifts of your
consciousness. And in return for this
gift, I will ask you now, how may I
serve you?
You mentioned in infinite creation. Hey,
I would like to know created by what?
And what do you refer to as infinite
creation? Infinite creation perhaps may
translate more colloally into your
language as what you typify by the word
God. We use the phrase all that is and
mean it literally in that way. Our view
of what you would call the infinite
creator, the one prime force of all
creation is to us simply everything that
exists. In other words, all that is is
literally all that is made up of all
that you experience in any dimension of
reality. Now it to our perception is
aware of itself as a singular identity
but it is also aware of itself as a
collection of all the diversity within
creation as well. It sees itself through
the polarity of being one and being
many. So to us when we refer to the idea
of infinite creation we are basically
making a reference to something similar
to the concept in your planet that you
would call God. Although perhaps our
definitions may differ a little bit. I
understand. Does that answer the
question sufficiently? Yes. Well, thank
you very much. Chilling.
Is there an afterlife and a life? Oh,
it's very active. Thank you. The idea
first of all of what you call after life
is not after life at all. It is simply a
continuation of life. But we know what
you mean by the terminology. The idea
simply is that you have created there to
be a multiplicity of levels of
non-physical experience as well as a
multiplicity of levels of physical
experience as well. Now the idea is that
when you let us say translate from a
physical to a non-physical consciousness
modality, you are then in a sense a
thought form in a world of thought form
energy. The one main difference at first
that will generally be noticed by many
of you is that there will be no longer
any time lag between what you think and
what you experience as seemingly real
because you are now one to one of
thought form in thought form energy. The
idea of the definition of what you call
physical reality contains the notions of
space and time in linear fashions and
makes it seem as if there is a time lag
between the thoughts you have and the
reality you experience. You understand
that all of this idea that we are
explaining now is founded on the
principle that each and every individual
is actually responsible for the creation
of their own experiential reality. Thus
you are creating your reality physically
but there is a gap between your
imagining of it and you're bringing it
into physical manifestation in physical
terms. In non-physical terms there is no
waiting. The second you conceive of it
that's what you see. So you can put it
this way. Usually the first thing an
individual will experience having been
translated or what you would call dying
from physical to non-physical reality
will be an atmosphere, an environment, a
scenario that is most representative of
the strongest belief systems they had
just before they died. In other words,
what they were most likely thinking they
would see when they died is probably the
first thing they will see because you
are the projectors of reality in that
sense. Now, as soon as an individual
begins to, as you say, get a handle on
the idea that their thoughts change and
all of a sudden the scenarios around
them start changing, they'll begin to
recognize that all
scenarios, all atmospheres, all
projections are representative of the
afterlife. And it can be basically
almost anything you want it to be. Now
there are levels of energy in the
afterlife. Each one being less and less
and less physicalized in its terminology
more as you would say rarified in its
concept. And so less and less likely it
becomes as you let us say graduate up
the scale that you will project your
reality in any physically symbolized
terms but you will still experience it
as being a real solid reality. Do
understand this if we may. Let us say
inject this into the conversation for a
moment. In our dialogues with many of
you, we have perceived that the majority
or at least a wide group of your society
has a particular notion about the idea
of being able to communicate with
individuals who have died. It is
altogether possible. However, many of
you have created the assumption that
when an individual dies, they have
nothing better to do than hang around
waiting for you to contact them.
They're very busy. They must acclimate
to their new surroundings. They have
assistants, what you would call guides,
that are in that sense acclimating them
to their new surroundings, filling them
in, as you say, on exactly what you can
do and how you can do it. They still
have lives to live. They still have
interests and ideas they wish to pursue.
It is simply now they are pursuing them
in different ways. So it is not really
an afterstite, but an expansion of life,
a continuation of life. It is simply a
different level, a different expression,
a different perspective of light. And in
all reality, it is really no different
than you in physical terms going from
one room in a building to another room
in a building that may simply have more
windows in it and allow you to see a
little bit farther. Now, is this a
sufficient description or is there
something specific you wish to discuss?
Yes, thank you very much.
asked um why is it that we as humans
tend to make things um so much more
complicated and more painful than
a question we have been asking for quite
some time.
The idea you simply see is that many
thousands of your years ago, your human
culture began a cycle of limitation that
brought with it something that you would
call an
unexpected effect. This unexpected
effect was the ability once you had
locked yourself into materiality from a
certain point of view, an ability to
forget that you did it to begin with and
that you could extract yourself from it
anytime you chose. It is under the
category of what in your language you
call a catch22. The idea simply is is
that a certain degree of experience of
limitation, a certain focus of
limitation automatically brings with it
an ability to forget that you created it
to begin with. So once you had locked
yourself into that cycle of limitation
and focus as a physical being, you then
had to play out the natural result of
the momentum you generated many
thousands of years ago. Now you are at
the ending of that cycle and that's why
many of you are now remembering that
there is more to your consciousness on
mass then you previously thought oh here
and there individuals in your society
were able to let us say break out of the
cycle but now on mass you are finding an
explosion of examinations of exploration
of consciousness. That is why we are
even able to have this conversation this
day of your time because you're at the
end of the old cycle of forgetting and
the beginning of the new cycle of
remembering exactly who and what you are
aspects of the infinite and that you
created the cycle of limitation to begin
with and that it was always under your
control to break free of it. But you had
forgotten that that was so. So in
placing yourself within the idea of
limitation, you created let us say an
entire mythology of now how reality
should be manifest. It now became
obvious that things had to be done in
what you would call complicated manner
requiring many detailed steps for the
accomplishment of anything. And because
in a sense you had lost your sight of
exactly how easy it was to create your
reality, you began to create all sorts
of methodologies by what you would call
trial and error that seemed to be able
to bring you somewhere close back to the
surface, but which required many various
ritualistic steps in that sense. So that
you would constantly be able to monitor
yourself, your progress, your procedure
as you went. so that you would not in
your terminology accidentally slip back
into the forgetting state. And so now at
the end of the cycle you have come up
with many different systems of approach
each of which carries its own degree of
complexity. What you are now therefore
discovering is that one of the greatest
difficulties your society has in what
you call your new age of awareness is in
really believing that something can be
worthwhile if it's simple.
The idea is very simple. The creation of
your reality is very simple. You are as
you say made in the image of God. Now
what does this mean? If God all that is
is a multi-dimensional creator then you
must be too because you are made in the
image of God. That's what it means. At
least to us that's what it means. Every
being within creation is literally an
aspect of the infinite and is always
completely responsible for the creation
of its immediate experiential reality
because you are a co-creator with the
creator. So now you are remembering that
and now you are let us say weaning
yourselves of the rituals of the
complexities. You are working your way
through at whatever pace is comfortable
for each of you individually and
collectively to a point where you can
realize that things can be very simple,
very easy and that you do not have to
endure struggling and suffering in order
to discover that you deserve to not
struggle and suffer
anymore. Understand? Is this a
sufficient description of the idea? Oh,
thank you very much. Sure.
[Music] This channel of communicating has now
This channel of communicating has now
established a recent thing or has there
been intense in the past for example
through a so-called prophet? Oh yes
thousands upon thousands upon thousands
of your years of counting understand
there was very blatant interaction with
many levels of consciousness in what you
call some of the past cultures upon your
planet. It is simply that the idea of
forgetting that is actually the most
recent thing that has happened in your
history. The idea of breaking the link
consciously is the most recent thing. So
the idea of the communications that are
going on now actually preheated the
break and are now taking up once again
on a widespread basis. Now and then
through the cycle of forgetfulness,
there were many attempts to reestablish
communication. But because of the depth
to which your society had taken its
forgetfulness, much of this proved to be
in your terms difficult. But now these
communications are being reestablished
because your own consciousness is
reawakening to the possibility that
there are other levels. You are
remembering in that sense that you are
more than what you simply appear to be
as a physical being. And so you are
stretching out, reaching out once again
for those levels of consciousness both
within yourself and within other
dimensions of existence. And as you do
so, that to us is the invitation that
you are ready to re-engage in dialogue
once again, which makes us very happy.
Does that answer the question
sufficiently? Well, I'd like to add a
little bit more. All right. And ask you
if you have any idea that what has
stimulated this new awareness off of
communication. You have played out the
cycle of negativity. There's almost
nothing left for you to experience in
that cycle. You have arrived at the end
of it. Now, let me share with you a
little, how do you say, nickname that
many of us have for your planet. In no
way, shape or form is this name meant to
be
[Music] derogatory.
derogatory.
Honest, the idea is that we have called
you the masters of
limitations. And what this basically
means is that in our experiences with
other civilizations, oh there are many
civilizations going through their own
transformation. By no means are you in
your terminology, let it say at the
bottom of your totem pole at all.
However, you are as far as our
experience tells us one of the most
highly focused and accelerated
civilizations we have ever encountered.
which means you have experienced a
greater degree of limitation in a more
rapid way than almost any other
civilization we have come across. You
have in other words done it all. There
is almost no other way you could explore
the idea of limitations you began
several thousands of years ago. You have
played it all very quickly all the way
out. You have basically satisfied
yourself. You have now in a sense
expended the cycle. And now that is why
simply because there are almost are no
other limitations to perform that you
are now waking up out of that dream into
another one because there is simply
nothing else left to
do. It had to be as we would have done
in our society for thousands of years
that we knew we would have to wait until
you had played the idea out and now you
have played it out. This life is the
life that is representative of the
transformational age has been going on
now in an accelerated fashion on your
planet for approximately 40 to 50 of
your years will continue in an
accelerated fashion for approximately 40
to 50 years lower. You are as you say
smack in the middle of the
transformational age the halfway point.
But it will be a very accelerated state
because the trer you open up into
positive ideas you begin to accelerate
geometrically. It will not take very
long for your world to transform into a
unified state because the idea in and of
itself of the exploration of limitation
means things are broken down in complex
ways. Things create a lot of complexity
and detail and you have to experience
things of steps at a time, one after the
other. But now as you begin to unify
things back together and awaken into
your integrity, your integral state,
things can speed up and can be very
accelerated. You can experience a
complete transformation within what you call no
transformation within what you call no
longer than the 100 years span we have
already described. And that acceleration
in a positive direction will take you to
a place of establishing a unification
whereas it requires tens of thousands of
years to explore all the ramifications
of the idea of limitation and
negativity. So we are at the end of the
cycle. That is why it is happening now.
Does that make sense to you? Yes. Can I
ask one more thing? Absolutely. You
don't have to ask people.
With this acceleration and awareness,
will it possibly mean that more of it or
all of it will be able to communicate
with you?
Yes. But the idea first is that your own
planet, shall I say, is more important.
The sooner you begin to establish evil
communications with each others and
begin to function as one world, then it
will be a very simple thing for you as
one world to establish very pleasant
communications with other whole worlds.
But the first step is to equalize this
communication between yourselves. Then
anything is possible. Everything is
possible. And in fact, a lot of things
become highly
probable. Does that satisfy? Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Um, you said something about God before
and I'm curious if you and your people
are familiar with Christianity to some
degree. And what do you think about the
idea that Jesus Christ is the table?
We perceive that the idea has been to
some degree
misunderstood. In the usual vernacular
of your word
semiior, this is not in our perception
what the individual who call the Christ
actually meant to call himself. The idea
is simply from our point of view, we may
begin at what you call the beginning is
that what you call the Christ
consciousness is the collective, the
combined consciousness, the positive side, the
consciousness, the positive side, the
combined consciousness of your entire
civilization. Once again, aware of
itself as a singular consciousness, but
also aware of itself as the combination
of all of your collective
consciousnesses. The idea of the manifestation in
The idea of the manifestation in
physical terms of what you call the
Christ actually happens far more often
than one. And the idea simply is that in
every endeavor, in every projection of
the Christ as a physical expression, the
idea that was being shared with your
population was that you are also all
part of the Christ. Not that in that
sense the idea of the Christ is your
savior in the sense that you have no
power to create the reality you desire
and that only it does but simply that
your power to create that reality is a
part of what it is. The idea simply is
that at the time that the information
was delivered in your society the
concepts that were understood by your
civilization then could only translate
the idea in terms of being a ruler and
being ruled. And so you created the idea
that the Christ was a savior in that
sense that would do everything for you
rather than understanding that all the
Christ is is a reflection. A reflection
to each and every one of you that you
are aspect of the Christ and have an
absolute right to create the elevation
and ascension of your own energy as a
representation of that energy. Now each
and every world, each and every
civilization has its own version of what
you call the Christ consciousness. In
our ancient remnant language which we no
longer use, the combined consciousness
of our entire world was called shakana.
Our shakana, your Christ consciousness
and the combined consciousness of all
other worlds together will form what you
call the infinite creation. So in a
sense you could say the Christ
consciousness is a shall I say miniature
version of all that is and in that sense
that's why your society has translated
it out to son of god because the
infinite is a miniature version of the
infinite. You think that's why maybe we are so
You think that's why maybe we are so
limited because um we put everything in
Christian Jesus Christ and not in
themselves. The idea simply is is that
anytime you take the power that you are
and remove it from yourself, you place a
limitation that actually denies your
very existence, what you have been
created to be. So yes, in that sense,
the definitions are what is responsible
for creating the limitation. Now the
idea to some degree of what has been
described in many of the attributes and
experiences are all valid. It is all
valid. Any tool in that sense is a valid
tool. It'll get you where you want to
go. But the idea is that your society as
we perceive it and again not mentally
has placed many labels, many definitions
which in and of themselves are really
the only thing responsible for limiting
your ability to see that you are all the
Christ. And that is what it is all
about. By the
way, one of the manifestations, the
physical manifestations of the direct
Christ consciousness that many of you
have not recognized is what you call
also your being called Mary, your mother
of Jesus, as the female polarity of the
Christ. There is always male and female in the
There is always male and female in the
collective Christ consciousness. And for
our perspective, what this basically
means in relating it to what you now
call your new age or your
transformational age is that the
so-called second coming is not any
longer the manifestation of the Christ
consciousness in a single environment.
It is the awakening of the Christ
consciousness in all of you. So that you
are literally creating heaven on earth.
That is our perception of the so-called
second come. Is this making sense in your
come. Is this making sense in your
language? Yes. That answer the question
for you? Yes. Well, thank you very much.
True. Okay. Um, what do you think of
consciousness expanding drugs that we
discovered in our
exploration? Act is that all proofs are valid.
Act is that all proofs are valid.
However, recognize that we have observed
in your society that one of the shall I
say choices, you would call it
tendencies, but I will call it choices
that your society
makes is that because they have not been
taught that they are already in touch
with their aspect of the infinite and
that the power is from within them and
they don't believe they are in control
of their lives, they will continue to
put the idea of the power into the
external tool that they discover
assuming that the tool tool has the
power to alter the state of
consciousness in the way they want to
alter it. It is all well and good to use
it as a trigger in that sense as a
catalyst to show you what realms what
dimensions you can expand into. But do
understand once you have been shown you
don't need the tool anymore. You can do
it yourself anytime you want to. The
idea of what you call addiction, it can
be the continuation of the assumption
that the power is still in the tool in
the drug and that you don't have the
power. That the drug has the power and
that you need the drug in order to
create the effect once the drug has
shown you the effects. You can create it
any time because you created it to begin
with because the drug is only a
projection of your consciousness
anyway. Is it making some sense? So the
idea fundamentally is that all tools are
fundamentally is that all tools are
basically valid. If you understand that
you are approaching the idea with your
best sense of integrity and that you are
honestly exploring for what you believe
to be a beneficial idea in that sense,
then recognize that almost anything can
be used in that way and will allow you
to key into walk into ideas that will
help you expand your consciousness.
However, always be mindful of the fine
line between believing you need it and
understanding that it is simply shown
you a door that you can now open anytime
you wish. It is if we change the
definition of where the power lies.
Yes. Oh, thank you very much.
Oh, thank you very much.
Sure. Um, you spoke of our collective
subconscious or our collective
consciousness. We have certain symbols
of feelings that are very universal in
our brains and in our imaginations. For
instance, a snake shows up as a powerful
symbol for humans the world over. Yes,
although there will be some slightly
different move from cone to culture, but
yes, it is what you call a foundational
archetypal symbol. Do we have a do we
have any universal archetypes for
instance from our collective
subconscious into your collective
subconscious? that part. Well, thank you
very much. The idea first of all beginning
much. The idea first of all beginning
with life itself will be universal to
all in some form because life is what
everything is made of. It is the
creational fabric as it were. So
manifestations ideas that are symbols of
life itself, what you may call the
stars, your son being such a one or any
manifestation of life itself in that
sense will more or less be universal.
Even civilizations that do not perceive
with the same sensory origin of sight
that you do, they will still manifest
the idea of life in some format because
they will perceive it as a vibration of
the fundamental idea of the fabric of
existence itself that will translate
everywhere. Symbols however in terms are
tricky things and again will usually be
relevant to a particular culture. We may
have similar ideas, similar concepts,
but for you, you may use one symbol and
for us we may use another. The idea to
some degree is that geometric shapes
will be somewhat universal. Now the idea
of the circle in and of itself is
actually the foundational geometric
shape behind what you call the snake.
Understand? Yes. The circle as you have
said, that which consumes its tail, that
which represents the cycle of infinity.
And in fact in your society the serpent
the idea of the snake is actually a very
ancient symbol tied in with what you
call the dragon symbol and it stands for
ancient knowledge or ancient wisdom. One
polarity of it for benefit and one
polarity of it knowledge misused in a
negative way. And also, by the way, that
dragon symbol, the serpent symbol, the
snake symbol, actually ties directly in
to many connections that all of you have
that actually are extraterrestrial in
origin. In other words, none of you are
original to your planet. None of you.
And the snake
symbolizes one particular influx of
energy at a particular point in your
history of
reincarnations that were representative
of an influx from other stellar systems.
The symbol typified the idea of the
energy at that time. A great deal of it
at that time was actually experienced as
negative and had a lot to do with some
of the complexities that were formed in
your society at that
time. Is it making some sense to you?
Yes. Could you speak more on us not
being original to the planet or
whatever? Well, yes, we can, but we will
not do so too much. Okay. Because the
idea is that it is our strongest desire
that we focus on the idea that obviously
you chose to be born on your planet for
a reason and we wish your focus to
remain in the service that you can
provide on that planet. It is quite
valid to understand the idea of your
lineage in that sense and your
extraterrestrial connection. But do
understand from my point of view you are
an alien to me. So the idea is that what
you are is valid where you are and
everything you need to live the life to
the fullest that you need to live is
right with you now. Anything you need
from anywhere else will crop up in
whatever manner you need it that will
serve you and help you be who you are
right now. Our best suggestion is in
your meditative states, go exploring
with your imagination and see what
feelings come up within that are
strongest in terms of an association or
a connection to what you might call an
extraterrestrial idea. But do understand
we have to talk in what you call your
metaphysical age of people being from
this star system and originating in that
star system. You all come from
everywhere and nowhere. And the idea
when a reference is made of someone
having an origin in a particular star
system really means that that particular
connection is for some reason due to the
definition of what this light is
standing out more abruptly than almost
any other connection. In another life,
you could be perceived to have a
completely different connection to a
completely different star system if any
connection at all.
So don't explore with your imagination
but always remember of paramount
importance is to apply the idea to what
you are doing on your planet now because
even though you have connection to
everywhere else right now you are
focused as a native of your world and
therefore that must be the most
important focus otherwise you beat
someone else.
Understand? Understand?
Yeah. Well, thank you very much.
If we are responsible for our own
reality and our reality is some kind of
pain, does it end with death? And did
your society experience death as you
did? Not similarly. We do, as you say,
translate from physiological to
non-physiological formats, but we do it
as you would say with our eyes open
constantly. And simply translate our
physical form back into energy and
continue on in a more expanded way. No,
the idea of the generation of pain in no
way, shape, or form means it must
culminate in what you call physical
death. It can always be transformed
especially now in your transformation
life where you are beginning to be aware
of the fact that pain does not have to
remain. So the idea is that in our
civilization we no longer experience the
idea of pain. Now the ideas of pain, all
pains, mental pains, spiritual pains,
emotional pains, physical pains, all
forms of what you call pain are from our
perspective the result of resistance of
your natural self. Pain is friction to
put it on a simple
terminology. Resisting the natural flow
of yourself as an aspect of the
infinite. And usually this resistance
occurs when having been brought up in
the society you have been brought up in,
you have been fed and bought into
definitions of
limitation. So that in trying to live
out these definitions that are not
necessarily representative of who you
really are, you are going against your
grain, so to speak, and going against
the grain gives you splinters.
So the idea of going against the grains
will stab at you and create the idea of
pain. In fact, pain is one of the ways
that can function as a barometer to let
you know when you are attempting to swim
upstream. It can be used in a positive
manner in that way. The idea goes hand
in hand with the concept that we have
discussed with your society many times
as
false. Excitement. Excitement.
Excitement. What is
excitement? Do any of you really have a
definition of what excitement actually
is? Mechanically
speaking, the idea as we perceive it is
as follows. If we may share our familiar
excitement, what you call the physical
sensation or the knowledge, the
knowingness of yourself that is
translated as
excitement is your physical
translation of the vibratory energy that
represents the path you chose to be at
that moment of your life.
So when something excites you more than
anything else, that excitement is there to tell
else, that excitement is there to tell
you three things.
things.
First, this is who and what you are. The
circumstance and the situation that
comes into your life at any given moment
that excites you more than any other is
letting you know this is who you are.
act on it. You see, excitement is the
sign that many of you ask for. What can
I do in life? Why am I here? What is my
purpose? What is my mission? Give me a
sign. Hey, look over here. Here's a very
exciting thing you could be doing. Don't
bother me now. I'm looking for my
purpose. I'm too busy searching for my
mission in order to have a good
time. Hey, look over here. What about
this exciting thing? Not now. I am
looking for my mission in life. But you
see, the things that come with
excitement are the answers, are the
signals, are the signposts. That's what
excitement is. It's tapping you squarely
on the shoulder saying this is what you
want to be doing right now. The reason
it excites you is because it is aligned
with the idea of who you are. That's
what excitement is. The second thing it
tells you is because it is who you are,
it will be the thing if you act on it
with trust and conviction, it will be
the thing that can be the most
effortless thing you will ever do
because it is who you are. You are
really being yourself. And so, of
course, it will be effortless. The only
time you have struggles when you're
trying to be someone you're not. Again,
fighting the flow, buying into the
definitions of what other individuals
say you ought to
be. The third thing it tells you when a
situation comes along that is more
exciting than the other is. This is the
thing that if you do it will support you
in the most abundant way to allow you to
keep doing it in a more expanded ever
spiraling expanding way.
One, excitement tells you it is you.
Two, it tells you that because it is
you, it will be an effortless creation.
Three, it tells you that because it is
you and will be an effortless creation.
You will be able to attract the
abundance you need in whatever form you
need. And understand abundance is just
more than money. What you call in your
planet money is one of the valid ways to
represent abundance. But it is not the
only way. There are many ways. So let us
add one more definition.
Abundance, the ability to do what you
need to do when you need to do it.
Period. That's all abundance is. Two
individuals, one in your terms with more
money, one in your terms with less
money. If they are both capable of doing
what they need to do when they need to
do it, they are equally abundant because
that's all that matters to them. And
that's the level they have defined
themselves to be. If someone has a more
expanded idea of what it is that excites
them, then perhaps they need more
symbols of abundance to flow into their
life to represent what it is they are.
If someone simply has an idea that is
sufficient to the symbols of abundance
that are already in his or her life,
then they will still be able to
accomplish it as smoothly, as
effortlessly, and easily as anyone else.
So the idea fundamentally is that
anytime you feel pain, you are basically
ignoring either because you have been
taught to ignore or because you do not
believe that you can deserve the ease of
creation, but you are basically ignoring
the thing that really excites you the
most. And when we say the thing that
excites you the most, we do not mean you
have to have at this particular moment
an idea of the thing that will be the
most exciting thing you will ever do in
your life. No, take it a step at a time.
At any given moment, whatever it is at
that moment, if you honestly accept all
the things you are capable of doing,
whatever it is at that moment that is
the most exciting thing you could do
that you have the capability of doing
something about, do it. It will align
you with all of the flow of creation and
life will be effortless. This is
actually what is meant in your society
by the term surrendering it. You aren't
actually giving up your power. You're
actually flowing in complete accord with
your power. But because it seems
effortless and because the world is used
to thinking in terms of things being
under your control if they require an
effort, then you don't think you're in
control when there is no effort. And so
you create this idea that you are giving
your power up to a greater force. In a
sense, yes, but not really. You're
actually taking your power, owning your
responsibility. When your life is
effortless, that means you are going
with the flow of who you have created
yourself to be specifically and what you
were created to be generally an aspect
of the infinite. Is this making some
sense to you? A great deal. So you can
always transform pain by finding out
within yourself what is the definition I
have bought into that would create the
pain to begin with. What must I believe
in order to have this pain reaction?
When you get in touch with what the
definition is, rewrite
it and then act like you believe the new
definition is now more true than the old
one. And as soon as you do, your life
will be representative of the new
definition. Because your physical
reality is always the product of what
you hold to be the strongest truth, the
strongest belief, the strongest
definition. That's why there really
isn't any the truth. There are a few
fundamentals that could be called the
basics of existence that are common for
everyone, but there aren't very many of
them. All the specifics are your
creation and the ones that seem similar
from one person to another are similar
only because you telepathically agree to
create them to be similar so you can all
play the same game. But there is no real
the truth in specific terms against
which to measure other truths for their
validity. The truth is composed of all
truths and all truths are actually real.
Any definition you have at any given
moment generate a
self-perpetuating, self- sustaining,
self-fulfilling, automatic system of
manifestation to support the definition
and make it seem as if for that moment
it is the only true thing because every
reality is real. Every perception is a
reality. Your imagination is the gate,
the library to all probable realities.
You cannot imagine
nonexistence. Whatever you imagine is on
some level, somewhere somehow somewhere
real. And there are various ones that
can be manifest in your particular
dimension. Yes, there may be some that
are not immediately applicable in your
dimension, but they are nonetheless
real. So the idea is to get a handle on
what are the definitions that have
created your experience. And if you find
that there are definitions you prefer,
maintain them. He defines our
definitions. You don't prefer change
them. That's what you have free will
for. Does this help you? Yes. Thank you.
Oh, thank you very much. Tell me. Sorry.
Yes. What is the purpose of knowing what
your connection is to another planetary
system and
[Music]
of you exist on every level there is to
exist upon right now. different lives.
What you call
reincarnation is simply your term in
linear time
references. But the idea of linear time
is your perception from within a
physical reality. All the lives, all the
existences, all the ways you do exist
all exist now. And in a sense on one
meaning of the term, they all exist here
as well.
The analogy we have used a few times is
what you call your radio analogy. You
have in your society the analogy the
device you call a radio. Now you know
that when your dial is tuned to one
particular program, you know that all
the other programs are still there at
the same time. But you only get the one
you're listening to, you're focused on
at any given moment. Let's call that
this life. Now here's your dial. now
tuned into the program of what you call
your earth's
existence. But for each and every one of
those other existences, their dial on
the setting they have it on seems to be
the only life that is going on. And all
the other ones are immaterial or
ghostlike or probable or potential life
or past or future or alternate lives.
Each life sees itself as the life being
lived. But all these things are going on
simultaneously because all of existence
exists now. And all the separations in
existence are simply different
frequencies that exist of experiencing
itself now. And it experiences all these
different ideas all at once. However,
because the definition of your
particular program involves linear time,
then you don't experience it all at
once. You experience it stretched out.
Before, now, after, beginning, middle,
end, cause, effect, negative, positive,
all these ideas are simply the result of
the definition you collectively have
created your physical reality to be. So,
the importance of any of these
connections simply is that there will
always be bleed through, shall we say,
from all of your alternate lives into
this one and vice versa. And that bleed
through will usually come in a way that
is symbolized or formalized in a way you
can apply it into this life. Otherwise,
it wouldn't make too much sense for you.
So being aware of some of the other
connections can assist you. All we do is
destress the idea that it is crucial to
know all those other connections because
every life is a complete kit and has all
it needs to live the life being lived.
If it excites you to explore these
connections, it can awaken certain
insights within you about perhaps the
reason for why you chose to be born on
earth at this time. A lot of those other
connections do tie in, especially now in
your transformational age, to why you
have chosen to have a life on Earth at
this time. Especially because a lot of
the things you will be doing on Earth at
this time will actually open you up to
blatant interactions with many of us
wherein many of you will discover your
own counterparts existing in our
societies. Understand? That's why it has
to some degree some relevance in your
life. Now, but we always like to
downplay it because the power always
starts and ends with you. Understand?
Yes. So the idea simply in terms of a
different connection to any different
life will be that each life of its own
different definition will then make
different levels of connections that are
relevant to the definition of that
life. There may be several lives that
may have what you would call the same
connection thereby creating what appears
to be a continuity of connection through
a period of time.
But each light chooses to make that
connection separately and distinctly.
And any continuity you may perceive is
only your illusion. Father, is this of
assistance? Well, thank you very much.
Churning, you said that you observed our
culture over thousands of years. I was
speaking collectively, not my society
specifically, but many of the societies
within the association of worlds have
said yes. living the life that you're
living now. Do you experience time in
the same linear dimension that we
experience it? Somewhat, but not
exactly. Our ability to communicate with
you right now in a sense shows that we
experience it somewhat differently. For
colloquially speaking, we are actually
of your future. And in a sense,
therefore, you could say we are speaking
backwards in time. But the idea is that
we do perceive to some degree because we
still have a physicality somewhat some
notions of time but they are very
pliable and malleable for us because our
society's transformation is now going
completely from physicality to
non-physicality. Understand? Yes. So
from your viewpoint you can tell what
the transformational age has
accomplished to some degree here and
there. Not everything will be apparent
to us and each and every different time
that we as you say tap into the flow we
may perceive very different things but
some general overall patterns and flows
are observable to us because of our
vantage point. Does this answer the question?
point. Does this answer the question?
Yes. Well, thank you very much.
How would you uh perceive the definition
of love to be from your perception? Find
you, find you. And this is how one does
learn to love unconditionally. I'm
guessing that you in your society, you
may have not loved unconditionally
because you use the word unconditionally
specifically. In the past, we had many
similar ideas to what your society is
going through. Not as highly focused.
But there was a time of conditionality
in the idea of our love. And now in that
sense, it is
unconditional. The idea of unconditional
love is simply that once again, love is
life. Life is love. Love is the prime
chord, the prime frequency of creation
itself. In a sense you can literally say
everything is made of love of light. It
is the same thing. It is a substantial
supportive medium of existence itself.
It is the very fabric of God. That is
what love is. That's why when you're
aligned with it, you are pulsing in
synchronous harmony with the prime
fundamental oneness of existence. That's
what that vibration is. Complete and
utter unity, alignment, synchronicity,
harmony. The idea simply is that to
allow yourself more opportunity to
experience love
unconditionally, start allowing yourself
to
perceive the infinite trust, the
infinite conviction that you have always
used to create your reality, whether it
has been positive or negative. Remember
that when we talk about using trust,
using unconditional love and using
conviction in its total form, we are not
talking about things you have never
done. We are not talking about things
you have to learn to do. All of you have
always expressed infinite trust,
ultimate conviction in the creation of
your reality. It's simply a matter of
whether you trust more in the positive
or the negative side.
So the idea of having a completely
positive flight in
manifestation is to be your choice to
buy into the positive definition or the
negative definition. It's up to you.
Unconditional love can come when you
understand that if you have the choice,
the conscious choice to choose only the
positive definitions and therefore only
experience the positive manifestations,
then what would in your reality be
worthy of placing conditions upon it?
What would you want to place conditions
upon? What would you want to control in
an externalized fashion? What would you
not trust as being a part of the
unfoldment of your life? The idea goes
hand inhand linked with the idea of
ultimate trust in a positive sense. If
you know that everything that's
happening in your life is serving a
positive reason and that you will learn
from it in a positive way, then why not
be unconditional about it? Why place
conditions on it? The only reason anyone
would place a condition on something is
if you didn't trust that it belonged in
your life. But there are no extraneous
creations and there really are no
interruptions. If something is happening
in your life, then it's happening for a
reason. Even if only to show you that
it's something that you don't want to
have happen
again. Even if only to show you that you
may have beliefs that spawn it to begin
with. And you may not want to perpetuate
those beliefs any further. That can be
used in a positive way. Your reality can
be saying, "Look, here's the pain.
Here's the result of what you have been
taught. Do you like it?" No. Yes. All
right. You decide. and then will change.
So be unconditional in that sense of
knowing that you can learn from
everything in a positive way. And if you
do choose to know you are a positively
oriented person, then even if another
individual with negative intention seeks
to interact with you, you by being a
positive filtration system, no matter
what their action will only experience a
positive result of their action.
So you can afford to be unconditionally
loving to even individuals who have
chosen to operate outside of integrity.
Because the only reason individuals
choose to operate outside of integrity
is because they have not been taught
that they are in control of their lives
and they are scared to death because
they do not feel that they are in
control. They feel they are out of
control. They feel themselves tinkling.
And what an individual does when they
feel bad is they try to take as many
people with them as they can because
they don't want to be
alone. So the idea is that the more
willing you are to express unconditional
love to everyone, then the easier it is
for you to shine as a living example of
absolute positive life that will at
least give them the best opportunity by
seeing that living example reflected
from you to choose to match your
vibration and become positive examples
themselves. Not that they have to
because everyone has free will. But
simply if you radiate at that frequency
then no matter what they choose it will
only leave you with a positive effect.
If they choose to match your frequency
then there will be more positive energy
within your surroundings. If they choose
to not match your frequency they will
not be able to stand in its light and
they will go on their way and you will
still be left with a positive
atmosphere. Understand? I should. Thank
you. Oh thank you very much. Remember
this as a prime
fundamental. No
situation, no
circumstance has built in
meaning. All situations, all
circumstance are fundamentally neutral,
empty, blank, devoid of meaning, zero.
Or as you say, zip.
The idea simply is that every
circumstance that appears in physical
terms is simply a surface image, an
empty shell, a
prop. You fill the prop with meaning
based upon what you have been taught to
believe the situation means in being
brought up in your society. When your
parents said, "If you see this, it means
that." Steer clear. Now obviously on a
fundamental level there are things that
are generally beneficial in terms of
buying into the idea of something that
if you do it may shorten your
lifespan. But the idea in specific terms
is nowhere near as limiting as many of
you think. The idea simply is to remember
think. The idea simply is to remember
that it is a very physical and
mechanical principle. You have a neutral
situation. And you have two choices of
type of meaning to apply to that neutral
situation. Positive or negative.
Whatever meaning you apply is the effect
you will get out of the situation. If
you apply a positive meaning, you'll get
a positive effect. If you apply a
negative meaning, you'll get a negative
effect. It's simple physics, simple
mechanics. That's all it is. It is
simply that a lot of your definitions
have been so strongly ingrained in many
of you that you think the situation is
coming with an automatic meaning because
you apply the meaning so quickly on what
you call an unconscious level that you
don't even realize you're doing it. You
don't even realize that the situation in
and of itself doesn't have any meaning
to begin with. An example, an analogy
that we have used a few times is called
the train station
analogy. Let us say with all the
integrity you can muster, with all the
openness and honesty, you know you are
doing your absolute best to meet a train
on time to take that train to what you
believe is a very important meeting that
will change the course of your life. So
off you go to your train station. You
arrive on your platform. You look down
the track and there goes the train.
Bye-bye. You have missed your
train now. Negative choice. Negative
choice. Oh no. This is horrible.
Terrible. Unthinkable. I have missed my train. I
Unthinkable. I have missed my train. I
will now miss my mean. My life is
ruined.
Well, now you have a couple of choices
in negativity. You can keep it to
yourself and be miserable or you can
share your misery with all sorts of
other people making their day just as
miserable as you have created
yours. So let us say then you choose the
latter and you become very angry about
the idea of having missed the train.
This is wrong. This is bad. This is
terrible. I am now going to go off and
complain to the train station about
their schedule. It's their fault. Not
mine. Not mine. And so off you go in an
absolute fur as it
says. Let's back the scenario
up. Now you arrive at the train station
all over
again. You arrive on the platform. There
goes the train. Now this is the neutral
situation. You are on the platform. The
train is moving down the track. You are
not on it. That's it.
The situation doesn't mean
anything. You are standing on a
platform. A truck is moving down the
track away from you. You're not on the
train. That's
it. Now, let's say instead of putting a
negative meaning into this neutral
circumstance, you put a positive meaning
into it. Ah, you say, I know I did all I
could to catch that train and yet I
still missed it. Therefore, there must
be a positive reason. I don't know what
it is.
My analytical mind may not be
immediately capable of fathoming why.
But I know there must be a positive
reason. Why? Because I chose to know I
am a positively oriented person.
Therefore, everything that happens in my
life must only have a positive result.
How about that? Therefore, instead of
getting angry and stomping off to go and
complain, you stand there perhaps for a
little while. You ponder, ponder,
ponder. You know you're going to miss the first
You know you're going to miss the first
meal, but perhaps you explore with
fascination and curiosity. Why would
this have happened? I wonder. I wonder.
Oh joy, an unexpected challenge to
discover. Well, you ponder long enough
so that the next train comes along. Oh
my, where's the time go? Next train is
coming along and you get on the next
train. Well, I don't know why. Why
should I get on the next train? I don't
know. I missed the meeting. Well, who
knows? Well, maybe the meeting is
starting late. I don't know. So, I'll
get on the train. And there in the train
is a friend you haven't seen for perhaps
20 of your years. And all of a sudden,
it becomes clear this friend was on
their way to see you, to actually help
you in a better way than the person you
were going to
see. Too good to be true. Oh, that's
just a coincidence. That doesn't happen
in real
life. Oh, yes, it does all the time. All
the time.
When you let
it there is negative synchronicity and
positive synchronicity. Which one you
get depends on your
orientation. When you put positive
meaning in all you get is one positive
co-incidence after another. Notice I did
not say accident
co-incident after another. When you are
negatively oriented, you miss the train
all the time and do not understand why
and keep perpetuating the idea of being
out of sync with everything because you
reinforce the idea that you don't fit.
That the things in your life don't fit.
They don't belong. This can't be
happening to me. It can't be
representative of my life. I have
nothing to do with this. I am not
responsible for creating this. The power
is out of my hand. Life is happening to
me. I'm a victim. war with
me. All these attitudes reinforce and
continue to perpetuate the negative side
of
events. [Music]
[Music]
Dr. By the way, does this answer the
question for
for
sure? I have a question.
We have a terrible disease in this
country now. AIDS, you know, incurable.
Oh, not really. Would you comment on
helping someone who die in
suicide? First of all, recognize that
one of the primary reasons that the
disees disease exists to begin with and
all disease exists to begin with once
again is a refusal to blend the
polarity. In this particular case with
the disia called AIDS, it is directly
connected to the idea of the refusal
over a long period of time of your
society to blend and balance the
masculine and feminine principle within
each and every being. It is a denial of
self intimacy in many ways. That's
denial of many different ideas that has
now perpetuated, that has now forced
your society to respond to this idea by
dropping its barriers and in your terms
being exposed, by having no immunity to
the idea now of having to face the
issues it needs to face. Individuals can
be
cured. There are a few ways, although
your society may not be ready to hear
them. One of them is
electromagnetically. With a strong
enough electromagnetic field, pulse at 7
1/2 cycles per second, the vibration of
your planet Earth, an individual
cellular structure can become aligned to
the natural vibration of your planet,
and be rendered back in its natural
state of health, no matter what the
disease. There are electrical means that
aren't even what you would call chemical
means. Although do understand that all
of these physiological cures are only
representative of a strong belief system
that an individual can be curious
because the belief system is always
first. The belief system creates the
disease. The belief system creates the
fuel. However, if an individual is
choosing that idea either from ignorance
or knowledge or fear or joy to create a
disease and
die, then there are many ways to assist
an individual in allowing them to become
through the transformation with eyes
open as we say standing tall. First of
all, it perhaps would be a benefit to
remind them that they are in fact not
ending but only changing scenarios to
allow them to begin to get in touch with
the fact that a they created what they
are going through with their power to
begin with and they are infinite. They
are eternal and they will always exist
even if they only exist in another form
than what they are used to. Perhaps of
course this will all be dependent upon
whether this individual chooses to buy
into this or not because if they don't
then there may not be much you can do to
assist them. Obviously only what they
are willing to allow you to help them
with will be of help to them if only.
But the idea simply is that you can
begin to paint a scenario of power and
joy of love that all things in that
sense physiological are transitory that
they are truly eternal beings and get
them to start feeling that expansiveness
of their eternity because if you exist
now you always have and you always will.
Existence does not become nonexistence.
This is also one of the mythologies of
your planet in a sense. And this may not
be using your language correctly, but
this may explain the principle
nonetheless. Non-existence is already
full of all the things that will never
exist. There's no room for anything that
does exist to go into it. These are the
polarities of creation. Existence,
non-existence, nothing, something. You
have to have both nothing and something
in order to have everything. If you have
nothing and only nothing, something must
exist. Something has to be created out
of the nothingness in order to complete
the concept of there being everything.
So if you are already on the side of
something, you never will go to the side
of nothingness. So that which exists
always has always will. Even though it
may change form, even your own
scientists know that energy cannot be
created nor destroyed. It can only be
transformed. So you have to begin to
ease the understanding of the
individual that they are eternal. Get
them to feel that eternity. That's one
way. Another way is to take them through
a meditation we have called the well
BLT. No, it does not stand for what you
think it stands for. It stands for blue
light technique.
and it goes something as follows. This
can aid in the alignment and the ease of
pain for any individual in your terms
suffering from a disease especially one
that is going to translate them into
non-physicality. Allow the individual in a calm and
Allow the individual in a calm and
relaxed and meditative state to take
three deep
breaths and with each and every
breath envision a red vibration of physicality.
envision a red vibration of physicality.
The second breath a green vibration of
mentality and naturehood. And the third
breath a blue energy of spirituality and
electromagnetic light.
allow themselves to drift in their
imagination and create in their
visualization any place at all that
would represent to them their place of
perfect peace wherever or whenever that
is. It doesn't matter. Whatever to them
is the place of perfect rest, perfect
peace. Let them revel in that for a moment.
Let them revel in that for a moment.
Floating lying on the grass, floating in
the water, floating in space. It does
not matter where or when. Just absorb
it, enjoy the scenario of their place of
perfect peace.
bed. suggests to them in their
meditation that while they retain an
image of the place of perfect peace,
they start to envision that their body
as it is lying there feeling either the
warmth or the coolness or whatever
sensation they desire become surrounded
by a transparent crystallin bubble of
blue electromagnetic light extending
approximately 1 2 3 ft above the head, 1
2 3 ft below the feet so that their body
is floating in the middle of a bubble of
Chris and Lewis. If they are lying on
the ground, then instruct that the
bubble should go through the ground
under their body so they are
encapsulated 360° in all directions.
Allow them to feel the energy of that
bubble and then allow them to perceive
slowly that the bubble is not empty but
is filled with blue liquid light and
that it is touching their body and that
they are slowly with every breath
breathing that liquid light in filling
up their entire body breathing it out.
All impurities
dissolving. Breathing the refreshing new
blue liquid light in to every cell.
Feeling every cell invigorated and
vitalized and breathing out all the
specks of black impurity and watching
them dissolve. And as they go through this
dissolve. And as they go through this
filtration process, continue to do so
until all they are breathing in or out
is the clear blue liquid light.
then begin to feel as if the blue liquid
light is literally soaking into their
cells, saturating through their core
until every single cell, every single
molecule, every single atom, every
single space is full of glue, liquid
light, and there's a vibration and an
invigoration, an
excitation, a buzzing of all the
crackling energy.
Then allow them to begin to see what
they have for so long considered to be
their body dissolving, changing,
becoming one with the blue liquid with a
sea until they arrive at a point where
the sphere is a homogeneous sphere with no
sphere is a homogeneous sphere with no
one portion standing out more than any
other portion. And the whole sphere is
beating, beating, beating with every
heartbeat as one. Breathing, breathing,
breathing with every breath as
one. Let them feel that peace, that joy,
that release for a moment.
Then suggest that they perceive in the
very center of the
sea a tiny bright white spot of light
that is a reflection of crystal
seed. And it grows and grow and grow and
grow becoming once again a bodily form
made out of crystallin light. white
shining crystallin light. One single
crystal transparent to the blue energy,
clear and
pure. And this is the reconstruction of
their bodily form. And it is not the
same body they had before. And it is a
new body, a new thought projection of
physical materiality. And they
are a new creation.
And allow them then to allow the bubble
to expand and expand and expand and
expand until it becomes the picture of
their place of perfect peace. And allow
them to open their eyes in their
imagination as the new body and look
around at the newly energized place of
perfect peace. And allow them then with
three deep breaths to walk that reality
in. and then open their physical eyes
and understand beyond the shadow of a
doubt that whether or not they have
decided to remain physical or not, they
now have created for
themselves an energy vibration, a
crystallin body form that will either
allow itself to be healed and remain
physical or will take them through the
translation into non-physicality with a
minimum, if any, of pain.
That's one way you can use this if you
wish and trust your imagination and your
unconditional love to come up with any
other methodology that you feel within
your heart will serve them best. Because
you are interested in doing this then by
definition obviously you also must be
able to come up with ways that will
serve them or you will not be attracted
to ask such a question.
I'd like to know why is it so hard for
um takes more energy for
one for one more energy. It
doesn't more. It doesn't. It only seems
to because of the definitions you have
been brought up to believe because you
think that hating is easier than loving.
That's the only thing that makes it seem
as if it is easier to hate than to love.
It's only the definition. There is
nothing inherent. There is nothing
intrinsic about the energy of loving and
the energy of hate that makes one truly
more difficult than another. But if you
have been said over and over and over
and over and over and over again the
idea that struggle is more
natural than not struggling. Why would
you be surprised that it's easier to
hate than it is to
love? All it is is a definition. That's
all it is. When you transform that
definition, when you say, "Well, now
wait a minute. It is my definition. It
is my belief. Whether it comes from your
experience or not doesn't make a
difference. Your experiences are the
product of your belief. And experiences
only reinforce beliefs that created the
experience to begin with.
So when you get in touch with the idea
that it is only your beliefs that makes
it seem as if it is easier to hate than
to love, you will say, well, is this
what I prefer to believe? Yes or no? No.
What do I prefer to believe? I prefer to
believe it is easier to
love. Do I really believe that? Yes, I
do. As soon as you do, it will be easier
to love. It is only your definition that
makes it seem so much more difficult.
That's all it is. And do understand
this. Hate may be a polarized expression
of love, but it actually isn't the true
opposite of love. Guilt is the true
opposite of love. Because love is
absolute worthiness. And you know what
guilt is all
about?
Noneservability. Hate still implies that
something is deserved somewhere.
So it may be a polarized expression but
it's not the true author.
Does this make some sense to you? Yes.
Does that serve? Yes. Well, thank you
very much. Sean, may I ask you about
astral projection? Yes. Can you give me
a definition of it? And is it is it like
death in Yes, because they bring it in.
Now, this may take the laying down of a
little bit of groundwork. Bear with us
if you will. All right. All right. Thank
you. Understand the following
fundamentals. I know this may seem to
some degree to be extremely opposite to
what a lot of you have been taught, but
it isn't really contradictory. It's only
once again a semantic or perceptual
difference. Your spirit does not exist
inside your body.
Your consciousness does not exist inside
your body. Your body is your spirit in
body. Your body is your spirit in
physical
terminology. Your body exists within
your consciousness, not the other way
around. But when you are focused as a
But when you are focused as a
physiological
being, let's say for now that your
consciousness is the analogy of a
bubble. All right? Let us say that when
you are focused as a physical being,
your bubble is confined as it were to
the specific local of your physical
expression. Let's just say for now
arbitrarily within your head.
When you die or when you project what
you are doing is
this your consciousness, your focal
point of consciousness which is on the
skin of the
bubble expands and becomes larger than
your body. So that your body is now at
the center of the bubble of your
consciousness. And you can look down
upon your body as if you rose from the
body and you can pop here and there and
here and there because you can in a
sense open an eye of consciousness
anywhere on the skin of the now more
expanded bubble. And in your terminology
that seems to translate as traveling
here and traveling there in the wink of
an eye. It is because your consciousness
has now
expanded to include a broader
perspective. You now include more
reality than you did before. And at the
very center of it is the most limited
and confined level what you call
physical materiality. That's why it
seems as if your spirit is thriving from
your body. In a sense, it is, but it is
more that it is a bubble of
consciousness expanding outwardly and
leaving your body at the center.
Understand? Yes. Is it making some sense
to you? Uh-huh. Can you travel through
any space and time? Absolutely. So, it's
completely limitless. Absolutely.
Because space and time are your own
definitions. In a sense, that's how our
quote unquote spacecraft travel as well.
They are projected into what you might
call astral material. And then they are
simply redefined with a vibration that
represents the space-time local we wish
them to be at. And they are reinserted
into physical materiality at whatever
local is representative of that
vibrational equation having in a sense
avoided the issue of travel
altogether. Instantaneous teleportation.
It is not really quote unquote breaking
the speed of light. It is not traveling
within your dimension at all.
Understand? Yes, I do. Um I have one
more question. for death. Am I to assume
that death is not being able to get back
into your physical body? Basically.
Exactly. Okay. Thank you.
Yes. What is a way of scripture? What is
the definition of that? And what is your
state and the words you give to us?
Could that be utilized as scripture?
What is your definition of scripture?
Sorry.
My personal definition of scripture is
any text that an individual utilizes in
relation to his ultimate concern. All
right. I'll go along with
that. It is methodology. It is
perception. It is recognition of the
self that allow the self to learn to
grow to expand. In that sense, if there
is anything within this interaction you
wish to apply in that way, by all means,
go ahead. But we are not here to assume
that what we are sharing with you must
be the only way that you can do this. It
can be considered in that sense
scripture. Although it is our preference
that it simply to be called information
since we perceive that the term
scripture in your society usually has a
religious connotation and all we are
doing is talking. We are not creating
the idea of a religion or a following.
We are simply discussing our ideas with
people and having a good time. So if you
wish to call it scriptor you may but
it's simply information that can be
applied in beneficial ways for your
positive growth and
acceleration. So will that work as a
definition for you? Yes that's fine.
Well thank you very much.
Do you see us uh killing our planet
right now? Yes but not ultimately. No
how how do you see us changing? It is
our perception at this moment that you
are basically forcing yourself into a
corner that will finally force you to
face the idea that there are in your
terms more beneficial and efficient ways
to go about things. And that it is our
perception that within what you call the
next 20 to 30 of your years as a society
in full recognition of that fact, you
will then do so and transform your world
very rapidly. Because once the
recognition is made, then the changes
can occur historically speaking almost
overnight. So it is our perception of
your energy now that within what you
call the next 50 of your years at the
outside, your society will be fully
functioning as what you would call an
equal member of the association of
worlds, a fully unified planets in love,
light, and harmony. We also have already
perceived, even though this may not be
apparent on the surface of your world
yet, that approximately what you would
call 10 of your years ago, you have made
a general collective unconscious
agreement that you will not annihilate
yourself through what you would call
nuclear means.
All of the idea of what you may now
perceive to be an acceleration of
violence on the surface of your planet
in a sense is the last vestigages of
these ideas now being brought to the
surface because in a sense now you know
it's safe to do so because all of this
is not going to lead to your
annihilation. You see we have used what
we call to describe your
world your rubber band
analogy to understand the device on your
planet you call a rubber band. Yes. Yes.
But let us assume that you have taken
this rubber band and stretched it very
very very far back into the depths of
limitation and negativity as far as you
can possibly stretch
it. Now you are on the verge of
considering exploring the positive side.
What do you think is going to happen
when you let go of that rubber band?
It's going to snap very rapidly and very
far onto the other side of positivity.
Understand? This is the threshold of
what you are standing on as a
civilization. That's why many of you may
be incredulous to understand, well, what
do you mean 50 years? That's all. We're
going to be a unified planet in only 50
years. But we spent thousands of years
getting to this point. Yes, you have.
Because you've been doing it through the
idea of limitation. Once you get the
understanding that integration is that
much more geometrically progressive and
unifying, you will understand that all
it requires is as you say the blink of
an eye to accomplish anything you want
to accomplish when you really put your
mind to it and you rearrange what you
may call your
priority. You understand? Yes. So it is
our perception that in general again
though it may not seem apparent on the
surface overall you are matching the
frequency of positive
vibration. Only for this reason can we
communicate with your world in the way
we are communicating now. If as a world
you had chosen the idea of the path of
total destruction, in all likelihood we
would not be capable of interacting with
you as we are interacting now because
our vibrations would be far too unlike
for us to be able to even find
you. Understand? Yes. Everything is a
different frequency, every dimension,
its own vibration. Vibrations that are
not alike do not even perceive each
other. So you must exhibit some degree of
So you must exhibit some degree of
similarity to our collective vibration
or we wouldn't even be having this
talk. Now do understand this as well.
And the only reason I can share this
with you now is because we perceive you
have made the decision on your own to
not annihilate
yourself. Your planet is your own. You
can do anything with it you wish to. It
is our understanding that we will never
directly interfere with the growth of
the world that to us as you would say is
sacrificed sacred. You are your own
life. You make your own decisions. We
cannot interfere. We can only interact
by your
invitation. However, to some degree, there was one
However, to some degree, there was one
exception. If you had decided in your
terminology to annihilate yourselves by
nuclear means, it would not have been
possible. Because since it is our world,
you're allowed to do whatever you wish
with it as long as you say it remains in
your own backyard.
Global nuclear annihilation would tear
as you would say holes in the
interdimensional fabric of space and
affect other civilizations that have
nothing to do with
you. That is not
allowed. But understand this as
well. Your government has been aware of
this fact for a long time and has
actually been given physical
demonstrations by many of the spacecraft
of the association that your nuclear
devices if they were to be activated
would not function. Your government is
aware of this. They know it. And now
many more of your public is beginning to
understand that your government has been
aware of our existence for quite some
time. And only now is much of this
information coming out into what you
call the public mainstream. The more you
open channels of communication, not in
an attacking way, not in an accusing
way, for your government is only what
you have created it to be. Your
government is
you. But if you open up lines of
communication in a loving way that allow
your government to know you are now
willing to take responsibility for the
information, then they can begin to
share more and more and more and more of
the idea of our existence. And not that
that is in and of itself so important
but simply that they can then allow more
awareness that you can function as a
global entity because it has been done
on other worlds and you can do it too if
you want to. So this information is
coming out more and more and again
within what you call the next 13 of your
years to 20 of your years there will be
almost not a living soul on your planet
that is not aware of our collective
existence. It will be taken for granted
by
them. Other fact, yes. No, this
will tell you very much. It is our
perception that there will
be perhaps but a little time left for
this interaction this day of your are
there any further sharings at this
point? Do continue for now if there are.
What's the difference is there between
believing and knowing? All right, thank
you. Let us put it in this particular
category or categorization if you will.
First there is existence
itself. Then the first state of
separation is selfawareness,
knowingness. When you simply know
something, when you are absolutely
aligned with what you know is your
truth. Then there is belief which
usually has to do with particular
definitions that go into the creation of
a particular format or experiential
universe. Then next comes emotions which
are reactions to things you already
believe to be true. Then there are what
you typically think of as
The infinite can experience itself and
go. Here you are. There are an infinite
number of ways and infinite number of
ways. There is no end to the growth.
There is no end to the transformation.
And the idea of going from level to
level and density to density, as far as
at least we can tell, will never never
never end.
Does this answer the question
sufficiently? Yes, thank you. Thank you
very much.
How does the Holy Spirit work in this
world? All right. Again, the idea to some
All right. Again, the idea to some
degree is that our perception of what
you call the Holy Spirit is the
collective electromagnetic mentality,
the actual energy out of which all of
your individual minds are
created. Spirit in that sense meant in
this terminology is literally a
physiological phenomena, an electrical
phenomena, an electromagnetic phenomena.
It is the literal life of your world of
your consciousness. And again the way it
works is as
follows. It is an energy sea in which
all of you as individual components are
immersed. And being immersed in that sea
when you align with it
electromagnetically by accelerating your
vibration in the ways we have discussed
excitement and so forth, service and so
forth, positivity and so forth. You then
become as you say of the spirit. And
what that basically means is you flow in
harmony with all other beings. You
telepathically link with all other
beings and know all thoughts. Because
the idea is that telepathy is actually
more precisely defined as telempathy
because it is emotionally activated by
love. When you love someone as
unconditionally as you can, you identify
with them very strongly. When you
identify with someone very strongly,
you're matching their frequency very
closely. When you match their frequency
very closely, you are translating the
spirit, the electromagnetic energy of
conscious into the same type of thought
pattern at the same time. Telepathy is
not literally reading each other's
thoughts directly in that sense as you
mean it. It is having thoughts so
similar at the same time that you simply
are on the same wavelength and you know
what each other is thinking because you
think that way too because you love
them. You identify with them. You are in
the spirit with them. You are immersed
in that energy sea of consciousness with
them. You love them. You flow with them.
you are shining within the light with
them. That is the idea of what you call
the Holy Spirit and how it moves you.
And also that's where the connotation of
speaking in tongues comes from. Speaking
in tongues is actually a reference to
telepathic communication simply that you
transcend the idea of language
altogether. It can manifest to some
degree as the idea of manifesting
different cultural dialects, but the
overall meaning of the phrase actually
has to do with being in touch with each
other telepathically. That's why if you
have observed this in your society from
time to time, individuals that you call
being in love with each other will very
often know each other's thoughts because
they identify so strongly with each
other and they are matching their
frequencies and they are literally
mirroring to each other who they
are. Understand?
Yes. No. Maybe. Yes. Does that answer
the question? Yes. Thank you very much.
Tell me. Um, I'm excited that you begin
to think about dragon because it's an
idea that's been very powerful to me. I
haven't really understood why. Could you
speak more about it and perhaps help me
to understand it means to me how I might
do that now in my life? To some degree,
we perceive that there may be some
specific avenues that we will not be
allowed to have access to because it
would interrupt your own process of
growth. But we will assist you where we
can. The idea for now is to symbolize, as far
The idea for now is to symbolize, as far
as we perceive your energy to be
concerned, the idea of the dragon to
begin with, as ancient wisdom, as that
first incarnation upon your earth, very,
very old, very ancient, very strongly
rooted not only in the earth's crystal
vibration, but in the vibrations of
other dimensions of experience, one of
which would very strongly be called or
labeled Orion energy. Now, this Orion energy is
Orion energy. Now, this Orion energy is
not necessarily an absolute reference to
the star systems that you would call
Orion, although there is a connection.
And this is something that is a
connotation of what you would call a far
distant past idea. But in times past,
there were very many
negative manifestations going on in some
stellar systems. Within these stellar
systems, there was the removal of
physical light in such a manner that it
chose to reincarnate in another stellar
system such as your own to take up the
continuation of the exploration of the
blending of that polarity. The
introduction of that collective energy
reincarnationally upon your planet a
long time ago is represented by the
symbol you call the dragon. And some of
it has to do with tying into the analogy
of what you call the fall from grace.
This is simply the idea of going from
onedimensional state of energy to a
lower vibrational state of energy and
why it is associated with the idea of
once again negativity and the dragon
being evil in that sense and
representative of fire. The idea of the
fire is simply the crucible of change
itself. The idea of the infinite light
itself to which anything can be
transformed. But the dragon is basically
But the dragon is basically
representative of a collection of
consciousness that incarnated upon your
planet some time ago to which you think
we have strong association
and a positive aspect of this. Oh,
absolutely.
Just keep coming to again the idea now
is that you are regaining a memory of
who and what you are and able to
transform the old meanings from negative
into positive association. Now you can
understand with the dragon as the
concept itself of immortality of eternal
wisdom of knowledge and the ability in
that sense to break free from the bond
of what you have called the definitional
limitations you have imposed upon
yourself perhaps if you wish as a simple
analogy go from the idea of what you
call a black dragon to a white dragon if
you wish that's one way to look at it
although we are not saying that the
colorations in of themselves necessarily
have to be representative of positive or
negativity but the idea is to Use your
imagination. And perhaps this is the
best suggestion I can give to you. If
you have some idea of what it would be
like to feel like a positively oriented,
wise and ancient dragon, then act like
one. Put all your senses into the
visualization and let it manifest in
your life in whatever way represents the
wisdom you now are tapping within
yourself. Understand? Yes. Here is the
key and we thank you for bringing this
up for this can be used as another
fundamental tool for any and all of you
and apply this anywhere you wish and
this hearkens back to what you call the
key of your
imagination. How many of you really
understand what your imagination is
for? I'm not
[Music] counting. This is a scenario as follows.
counting. This is a scenario as follows.
If there is anything in your life that
you desire to be and you don't know how
to
be, conjure up, as you say, in your mind
eye, in your visualization, in your
imagination, a picture, an image of you,
the you you would prefer to be. See
yourself either literally or
symbolically as the you you prefer to
be. Create a scenario, an atmosphere, a
vision. Then put all your senses into
it. As you say, get involved. Get into
the image. In other words, what would it
feel like to be that you? What would you
taste like? How would you smell? How
would you see? How would you hear
differently? How would you touch? How
would you feel? How would you act? What
would your attitudes be that are
different than the way you're acting
now? Get involved. Plug yourself in to
the image. Feel the energy of the
image. Feel the energy of the
difference. Feel what it would be like
on every level you can be that person.
Then if there is a situation in your
life you don't know how to handle, hand
it to that you in your imagination and
watch how that you handled it. Watch the
approach. Watch the attitude. Watch the
positive manifestations
occur. Then all you have to do is mirror
the image, mimic it, copy it, and you'll
get the same result. That's what your
imagination is
for. To create the scenario that is
representative of the vibration you
choose to be, to begin to identify.
Remember what we said about mirroring
and identification. to identify with
that vibration, to start acting like
that person. Because if that person in
your imagination is acting differently
than you're acting now, then that's an
indication of why you may not be getting
what you want to get. Act the way that
person acts and you'll get what is
representative of the lifestyle of that
person you want to be. Be that person
now and you'll have the life that goes
along with that person. Now, so if you
find that a symbol, an archetypal symbol
works for you, such as the dragon, then
examine, explore. What does it mean to
be a
dragon? What does it mean? It means
boldness. It means conviction. It means
no one can ignore you.
Now, that doesn't mean you have to be a
doctor. Doesn't mean you have to always
go around stomping and roaring to get
your point across, you know. But what it
does mean that you stand out in a
crowd. And it does mean that you have
the conviction to do what you know you
are, to act in that way, to know what
you stand for, to put it out there, to
represent it, and to not worry about the idea of
it, and to not worry about the idea of
what other people think of you. Those
are the little arrows that bounce off of
the scales of the
life. Understand? You pick up that arrow
and you pick your teeth with
it and you say, "Well, thank you for
pointing out a certain idea that I
out a certain idea that I
can put into my assessment of which way
to go. Thank you for your reflection and
your suggestions and your advice. I
value them and treasure them highly."
How many dragons do you depict guarding
treasure? The idea of knowledge,
treasure itself. The idea of application
of that knowledge, intelligence, the
razor sharp edge of the dragon's
spear. Be that
dragon. That's up to you. All right.
Thank you very much. Well, thank you
very much.
Yes. I wonder if you could share with
us how members they love the
association. some idea of the number of
civilizational scientists, monitors,
scientists, and some idea what they
like. Oh, well, a few.
The idea first of all is that now this
will be to some degree an arbitrary
perspective because there are different
levels of the association when you come
from different points of view. However,
the closest representation to what you
would call your physical dimension is as
follows. We belong to an association
that now contains approximately what you
would call
360 different
worlds. But we are
aware not that all have been contacted.
Not that all are a part of our
association or even any part of any
association. We are aware simply through
the process of scanning with our
consciousness that within this immediate
galaxy and what you would call the
neighboring four galaxies thereby
considering the local five galaxies and
this includes what you would call your
galaxy of
Andromeda. There are at least no fewer
than 67 million inhabited worlds.
But the idea is that we have contacted
almost none of them in that sense simply
because of the timing of our
interactions what it represents and
simply the timing of their interactions
what it represents. They may have their
own association. Some of them may know
of us some of them may know nothing of
us. But it is our perception that that
is a figure that is generally
representative of the local five
galactic groups in terms of the amount
of civilizations that there are to
discover that would at least have some
degree of commonality with you.
Now this does not mean that the life
forms are all of the same variety but
there are many of what you would call
humanoid in that sense because that
represents a certain level a certain
vibrational dimensional experience and
life expresses itself similarly within a
certain range of frequencies. So there
are many humanoid as you would call it
life forms. Although if I were to come
from my point of view I could say you
are
ethosaniish being that I am not exactly
like you. The idea is that you will when
you begin to explore the idea of space
in the way that we have usually come
upon again life forms that are more your
style than not simply because that's the
frequency you are used to and it is
therefore more likely that those are the
type you will encounter first. As you
expand your notion of dimensionality
then you can begin to encounter
lifestyles that are very unsimilar to
your own.
Now, it is our perception that when you
begin to explore and interact with other
worlds, much in the same way we are
interacting with you now, one of the
first civilizations you will begin to
interact with, in fact, I've actually
already began to interact with them in
your dream level, is a civilization that
is in what you would call the Barnard
Star Cluster, as you name it. on one of
those worlds as a civilization not
unlike your own but
approximately evolutionarily speaking
where you were on or about let us say
your Renaissance period technologically
speaking they are already aware of some
of the communications you have had as a
society with them on the dream level and
sometimes you actually will find that
some of you are actually channeling
through some of the members of that
society now they do not in their society
label the different names, the different
channels as different things. They see
it all as one phenomena. The word in
their language for the entire phenomena
of either dream communication or
channeling of any sort is
simply that is their term for the entire
process. They are not segregated out
into different entities. It is all the
same level to them.
In time, as you expand, you will begin
to interact with them in similar ways to
the ways we have interacted with you.
And in a sense, you can become their
UFO. And in time, you can blend and
assist them in their transformations
again in similar ways to the way we are
assisting
you. New Yorks in certain ways goes by
the label of Iraq. The eyeact have
placed upon themselves a very
fascinating limitation. Their facial
structures are almost completely bony as
you would call it and they are incapable
of expressing any emotionality on their
faces whatsoever. It must be expressed
completely in different
ways. They are of what you would call
creamy whitish yellow waxy skin
configuration. There is one very unlike your
There is one very unlike your
civilization in many ways that operates
on a completely different dimensional
plane that in your terminology would
best translate out in the one
moment. that best translates out into
the idea in your vocabulary of what you
would call the doula. Now the doula
operate in a completely non-physical
sense and yet they do have to your
perception and physicality but they are
extremely plastic in their nature in a
sense they have no real discernable
features and can take all of any form
they wish. They are of a completely
primal dimensional state. They are not
really physical as you understand it.
But one of their let us say prime
exports is a sense of
humor. They are of a very very light
vibration. Their entire world is very
simplified. You would perceive it
literally as a smooth sphere with no
surface features that do not need to
exist until they are required. Then they
are literally drawn from the surface in
that way to form many different things.
The villa themselves in that sense can
merge with the very substance of their
world in that sense being very much in a
plastic or what you would call molten
state. The way you would perceive them
physically would be through almost
nothing but primary colorations in that
sense. They would literally appear to be
very plastic like to you with no
discernable features. They can mimic
your form but that is not their natural
form. In a sense they do not really have
one except perhaps what you would call a
very flattened oblate spheroid in what
you would call a state of rest. of it
really rest. There is closer at hand some of
rest. There is closer at hand some of
the ideas of the civilizations that have
been interacting with your society of
late in this transformational age. The
idea of what you would call Plleadian
society. They are in a sense very much
like you humanish in that sense
primarily because many of you are from
the same offshoots. They are literally
your brothers, sisters and cousins. And
the split off occurred a long time ago.
Now you are rejoining many of them and
literally rejoining members of your
family. Another society will be the
society from the star cluster you call
beta reticulum and this will be what you
would call short in your terms beings of
very wide eye, very pale skin, very
enlarged head and are the ones that are
most represented in the idea of the
interactions you call the abduction
phenomena. Although if you would allow
it, we would prefer the term
[Music] detainment. Since everything that goes
detainment. Since everything that goes
on in those interactions is all from
agreement, even though members of your
society may not remember having made the
agreement, and it is all for the purpose
of serving in the transformational age,
the idea of any fear that individuals
experience in those abductions are the
fears that are simply things and ideas
that have been suppressed within their
own consciousness coming to the surface.
Nothing about the interaction itself is
fear invoking. Another civilization
would be both to some degree
semifysiological and completely
non-physiological of a civilization that
orbits the star you call Sirius. and
Sirius with our civilization of Ethosani
and your civilization of Earth form a
particular triad of consciousness of
which you would say Sirius is at the
peak and represents the further steps in
the evolution we are going through and
you are going through and which both of
us will accomplish in time. The level of
consciousness that is mostly in contact
with your world that you would call
seriously the non-physical sixth density
level of consciousness and goes by the
terminology 16.
Now, they have been in telepathic
communication with members of your
society for quite some time and are
responsible for some of the mythological
manifestations in your perception of
what you would call the amphibious gods
both in what you would call your
Sumerian cultures and in some of your
African tribal cultures and American
Indian recognition. The idea simply is is that
recognition. The idea simply is is that
because they exist in an energy
sea, you have translated them as
amphibious beings. although they do have
a semifphysical counterpart that to some
degree is physiologically amphibious.
One of the reasons for this particular
manifestation being very strongly
connected to your planet also has to do
with the fact
that as we scan your Earth, we find that
there is not one but two alien
civilizations upon your planet, land,
human and water citation, dolphin and
whales are thinking,
self-incarnating, self-aware souls like
you. They are not animals as you
classify them in that sense. So in a
sense recognize that your planet is I
shall say blessed with two civilizations
that can work side by side and learn to
love one another and grow in creativity.
They have already begun to assist you by
entering your dream states and teaching
you how to play in spontaneous ecstasy.
Go to them, share with them. They love
you. But because of their environment,
they have been in telepathic
communication with many different
civilizations off the planet for quite
some time, especially a strong
connection with the serious civilization
since they have much in common as a
consciousness and are telepathic in that
sense and exist to some degree in a
buoyant environment. Whales are to some
degree the embodiment in physical terms
of the higher consciousness of a
dolphin. You simply do not have a
physiological manifestation of your
higher consciousness because the gravity
of your world would not support it. So
it is up to you to be both the
manifestation of the individual
consciousness and the higher
consciousness itself. But usually you
relegate the higher consciousness into
non-physical terminology. Whereas the
higher consciousness of the dolphin can
manifest physically as a whale because
of the buoyant environment of your
ocean. But they are there to assist you
to love you. And when you blend that one
society, that will also make it easier
for you to interact with other whole
societies. But now look at this. Look at
the sparkle opportunity you have
created. You don't have to go anywhere
in order to interact with an alien
civilization you have one in your very
ocean. Learn to communicate with them
and they will teach you much about the
way you will be communicating with all
other civilizations that you will
encounter. There are approximately at
this time anywhere from between 17 to 20
different civilization interacting in
various ways with your civilization
assisting you in this transformational
age. But the idea will fluctuate to some
degree and again primarily the decision
is up to you and the empowerment is up
to you. Would have answered your
questions sufficiently.
Thank you very much. Shutting
it
animal. Oh yes, yes, yes. And they are
consciousness. So they are a different
type of consciousness. They are also
reincarnational beings in that sense,
but they do not create nor need to
create the analytical thought process
that you do as a self-aware reflection
of the primary crystal of infinite
creation. They are to some degree, let
it say, your creations, your projections
as a collective consciousness. They are
guides and reflections for all of you
and can always assist you in
reconnecting to the natural state of
your existence. They are telepathic
again telepathy being a very emotional
idea and vibrating in the primal sense
of love. And you can learn anything and
everything not only from what you call
animals but also through the idea of
what you call plants and mineral
consciousness. But it is all made of
consciousness and in a sense it is all a
soul the oversoul of your entire planet.
So by all means they are aware, by all
means they are of soul, by all means
they are consciousness. Is simply that
they do not have to doubt
themselves. Does that answer the
question sufficiently? Thank you very
much for them as well. We thank you.
One more question. I'm sorry. Yes. I've
been doing some telepathic communicating
with dolphins and can you give me any
guidance that would help amplify that?
Absolutely. At your fullest opportunity,
go and physically play with them in your
ocean. Learn their environment. Let them
learn yours. Really become friends in
that sense. Really interact in every way
you can. Let them rub off on you.
All right. Thank you very much. And at this
right. Thank you very much. And at this
timing, allow us to project to each and
every one of you once again our deepest
appreciation, our unconditional love,
and our ultimate ecstasy at being
granted this opportunity to interact and
share and co-create this dream time with
all of you. Remember that you are all
dreaming right now.
Wake up and live the dream you prefer to
because your physical reality is only
what you dream it to be. We thank you
for this
gift. Our love to you all. A fond and
pleasant good day. [Music]
Oh, heat, heat. [Music] Go.
All right. I'll say how are you all this
day of your time as you create time to
exist? [Music]
[Music]
Allow us to begin with an interaction on
the idea of miracles. You may use that
as your title if you wish. In this way,
recognize that what you often consider
in your civilization to be miracles. You
consider to be out of the ordinary,
above and beyond the mainstream reality
that you are used to experiencing in
your day-to-day world. But recognize
what you typically call a miracle is in
actual fact a recognition of the
fundamental workings of the universe. It
is a recognition of when reality,
physical reality, the experience of
physical reality as you have come to
know it is actually working in
synchronous harmony with all other
levels of reality. And thus a miracle is
actually representative of when the
universe is working most
naturally. Physical reality the
day-to-day events that you typically
experience that seem to be different
from what you call miraculous that in a
sense is even more of a miracle than a
typical miracle as you call it. For a
typical miracle is an indication of the
natural state of the universe when
everything works hand in hand absolutely
flawlessly and can create whatever
manifestation is indicative of the way
the minds and the hearts and the beliefs
of the individuals involved in that
circumstance wish it to be. Whereas what
you call your day-to-day life is the
product of divergence many times from
the so-called natural awareness or
natural state of creation, natural state
of reality. And in that sense, the
things that you most often take for
granted are actually the exception to
the norm. In that sense, the way you
have structured your reality, all of the
different diversifications, separations, and
diversifications, separations, and
specific endeavors that you create in
your day-to-day lives, those are the
miraculous manifestations of the
foundational energy. Your daily life is
therefore miraculous. And when you see
in your life what you normally call a
miracle, when all of the normal, what
you think of as normal activities that
go on are for a moment seemingly
suspended to allow this so-called
miracle to occur. In actual fact, what
you are seeing therefore is the very
fundamentals, the homogeneous, balanced
natural energy that everything in your
daily lives is created from. you follow
along. Therefore, recognize that your lives at
Therefore, recognize that your lives at
any given moment are made of magic, if
you will, are miraculous in that way.
And that what you typically call a
miracle is not something that is an
interruption in what you think is a
natural or normal way that life exists.
But it is actually a manifestation of
naturalness. A manifestation of the
basic root foundational energy out of
which all of the divergences in your
daily life are created. A miracle is a
calm spot. The eye of the hurricane, as
you say, wherein you allow all the
different energies, the homogeneous
energy of the foundational creation
itself to simply work in its purest
form. When you know in that state that
everything does fit in with everything
else, everything does work in life. And
a miracle is simply your willingness to
allow on all levels all at once life and
the universe to work in the way it was
designed to work. So if you wish your
life to become as you think more
miraculous and for life to become more
and more effortless expression of that
level of creativity then all you need to
do is allow your life to revert back to
its natural state to the zero rest
balance point to allow the things in
your life to be there that need to be
there rather than thinking you must make
or force or push those ideas into
creation. desire,
determination, those are tools that can
allow you to allow your reality to work.
But desire and determination do not have
to be expressed in a struggle type of
mode. Desire is the activation key that
will bring to you anything you believe
to be possible to experience in your
life. And when you allow your desire,
your excitement, which is your
indication of your connection to the
primal energy out of which all is
created, when you allow your desire to
bring those things into your life, then
your life will be effortless, will be
miraculous day to day to day. You follow
along? At this time,
At this time,
therefore, we will communicate in the
mode we call sharing.
Yes, we
have we have a documentary being filmed
tonight and we have a lady.
Welcome. Thank you very much. I have a
couple of questions. They're not exactly
on the subject you're talking on, but
does not have to be, never has to be.
All right, good. Uh, it has been
predicted by Leah that in March of 87
there will be a profound change in our
economy. Do you agree? And is this
change for the better or for the worse?
The idea of what you would call
approximately March 15th to March 17th
will be a very strong energy gate
wherein many transformations can take
place. Some aspects of what you call
your sociological structures, your
economic societies may discover
Any transformation can be experienced
and expressed in a positive and or a
negative way. Which way that manifests
depends upon the attitudes and
perspectives of the individuals
involved. So it is up to you as to how
it will manifest. But that time frame is
a very strong transformational energy
gate. Yes.
Thank you. The other question is we're
doing this documentary for public
awareness. Do you have anything to say
regarding this? First of all, but you
are also doing it because of the public
awareness that already exists. So
recognize that anything you find
manifesting in your reality not only
goes towards reinforcing the ideas that
you can do, but is also a reflection of
the ideas you have already become. So
first and foremost, what we will say is
to extend from us an appreciation and a
thank you to your civilization for being
willing to come to the point in its
conscious conception of itself wherein
it is willing to discuss these ideas and
expand in many different ways. The
exploration of your consciousness will
be discovered to be the key to any idea
you wish to understand within the living
of your life. And that fundamentally
what we will share with you is that the
only fundamental process truly necessary
for you to understand anything you wish
to understand about life is to simply
live the life you are living. And in
that true and full living and expressing
yourself according to the truness of
what you know to be representative of
the energy each and every one of you
are. You will in living that life
discover everything you need to know
about the life you are living. For again
the universe does not do extraneous and
pointless things. Everything works and
there is a reason for everything.
Explore and expand your curiosity.
Become fascinated with the interplay of
all ideas as they interact and
interrelate and you will discover that
everything is an orchestration and a
flawless one at that.
Bashar, thank you very much. We thank
you for your endeavor. We thank you for
your sharing and your willingness to
participate and create an opportunity
for others to participate in the growing
expansion of awareness of remembering
that you are all made in the image of
the infinite creator and what that means
is you are all infinite creators. We
thank you. All right,
Sharon Bashar. Hey, a couple of weeks
ago in the Times there was a article
that the scientists had found two giant
arcs arcs. Could you care to comment?
Would you care to comment on tell us a
little bit about that? We can disperse
but a little bit of information. What
you are perceiving as the
arcs are specific compactions of the
gravitational dynamic tensor fields of
the physical universe that have
undergone what you would call vast
implosive energy. You are seeing the
spin-off or cast off remnants from the
implosion of one portion of this
physical universe into and through a
gateway of another physical universe.
Thus the energies released are quite a
bit higher in magnitude than anything
you have discovered around your
localized area. For in that area
therefore you are seeing let us say to
be colloquial in your language the
breach the gate the doorway from one
universe to another and the after
effects of that implosion of the
creation of that gate a very powerful
gate. These arcs therefore are
representative of how space-time itself
has become as you say warped or twisted
representative of the motion or the
eddies or the currents now involved in
that particular doorway or gateway. You
follow me?
Thank you. Thank you. Another question.
Last week you gave us some beautiful
information on limitation. Is there
anything you'd care to tell us in
regards to denial?
Denial. Denial in this way is again the
belief, the inherent ingrained belief
that there might be something in your
life that you might come across that
would not be able to serve you. But when
you recognize that everything happens
for a reason, then you will know that
anything that happens in your life can
be used to add to the overall
understanding of yourself in a positive
way and allow you to expand and
accelerate in growth. Therefore, denial
is simply the belief in your lack of
completeness, in your lack of ability to
utilize in a positive way anything that
could occur in your life. It is a fear
that there is something within you that
is beyond your control that may get out
of hand as you say. It is only a fear.
It is only the result of the fact that
your society has been taught that you
are not in control of your life.
Therefore, you do not allow yourselves
to be aware of why the things that occur
in your life do occur. And so because
you think that to learn more about them
will actually place you in greater lack
of control, you many times will refuse
to explore them, feeling safe and secure
just where you are, not realizing that
the more you explore those things, the
more you will have to add to your
overall understanding of yourself and
the more stable you will actually
become. Does that assist you? Yes, very much.
Does that assist you? Yes, very much.
Thank you very much. Thank you.
Shouting Bashar. Hey, in working with
the uh Lazarus tape that you uh
mentioned to us some a couple of months
back, secrets of manifesting what you
want. Good uh in cleaning up the tools
to use for manifestation. I I find it uh
I find it difficult to find out what my
payoffs are and my blocks are quite
large. I wonder, if you say so. I wonder
if you can shed some light on what why
do you believe your blocks are large?
And first and foremost, what is your
definition of a block?
The denial that uh I have a payoff for a
negative uh action in my life. Denial
that you have a payoff for a negative
action. Would you clarify that, please?
Okay. I'm um exhibiting lack. And you
are exhibiting lack. Yes. I I don't have
the kind of car that I want and the
money that I want to do the things that
I want and I don't know. He says, "Find
out what your payoff is." And I can't
imagine why I want to do this. All
right. Perhaps one suggestion, only a
suggestion to allow you to discontinue
looking at it as a lack and focus on the
things you already have so that you know
you already are abundant in one way and
that you can be abundant in other ways
rather than assuming that you lack
anything. Because if you are approaching it from
Because if you are approaching it from
that end, that point of view, then you
are only reinforcing the idea that you
are not abundant, that you lack
something. Approach it from the point of
view that you already are abundant in
whatever ways you have needed to be
abundant and that you can be abundant in
other ways, more expanded ways, rather
than assuming that just because you are
not right now abundant in a particular
way means that you lack abundance at
all. You follow me? Mhm. Uh-huh. So,
examine the other end of your
tool as well. Okay. Now, it also does
not necessarily have to be that
complex. It may be as simple as you
simply have the habit of generating that
particular type of scenario. Whether or
not there is any particular quote
unquote payoff whether you actually have
an ingrained belief that you need to
suffer, you may simply be in the habit
of generating the reality the way you
are generating it. So allow yourself to
know that you are in the process of
creating new habits now and that it is
not necessarily so that you have to dig
and scrape for this deep dark secret you
are holding from yourself. Beautiful.
You follow me? Yes, I do. If it is that
difficult to find a payoff, maybe that's
an indication that there really isn't
one. I love it. Okay,
thank you. Yes, thank you. So, lighten
up upon yourself. And when you use the
tools that the tape suggests, in order
to sculpt a new reality, use a light
touch as well. It is only the novice
that applies undo pressure and very
often snaps the tool. You follow me?
Yes, I do. You do not have to dig quite
so hard. Okay. Thank you. Thank you,
Bashar. Shannon.
Hi, Bashar. Toy. Um, I I bought a little
toy today. It's a tuning fork. And um,
do you like the way it moves you? Oh,
very exciting. Very, very, very
exciting. And uh I bought a little pitch
pipe too. And just while I was sitting
here, I was thinking um if there was
different notes cuz now I'm interested
in using it to heal possibly. Okay. Then
you can simply ask any other individual
to stop you when you hit the note that
moves them. And that's the vibration you
can work with them on. You follow me?
Yeah. Whatever strikes a chord within
them will be the key that unlocks them
from the reality that they have lived in
before and will allow them to now
manifest the reality they prefer. So
simply test it out with any individual
you are interacting with. Which one do
you like? This one? This one? This one?
Oh, that one. All right. Then that will
be the key one. When you hear this,
therefore, if this is the one that truly
strikes a chord within you, you will
know that when we play this note, you
will be at your absolute most malleable,
most open, most receptive, most willing
to create the reality you desire. This
will be your support field. And a
support field, it literally will be. You
will generate the tonality. And that
tonality, the vibrations themselves will
function in much the same way as the
energy fields around our spacecraft and
will in a sense isolate that individual
from all of the reality habits that they
have previously been manifesting and
will give them the opportunity to lock
into new ideas. You follow me? Yes. It
is like suspending them in a type of
fluid, surrounding them with that sound.
Okay? So there's not one or any
different note that's good for a certain
uh the individuals will let you know for
whatever it is whatever note. Hey, every
individual is different and they are
different at different times. Can I use
this like over a body instead of just by
the ears? Okay. Oh yes. Especially over
the solar plexus. Especially.
Okay. Thank you. Thank you. Chatting.
But sure. Hey,
um I talked to you the first time I
talked to you was about headaches I was
getting. They're more consistent now.
They're about every other day. And you
said it had something to do with
gravitational shifts on the planet to
some degree. Your sensitivity to
electromagnetic shifts. Okay. I was just
curious about that. The other thing was
when I was about three, um, I was
playing with a ball in our living room
and the ball rolled under our couch and
I got our maid to get the ball for me
and while she was, I happened to look
behind me and through the curtain
appeared a figure, a very tough stop.
Okay.
Are you doing in your life what you wish
to be doing?
I think on one hand I am and on yes I'm
which is researching more into
um myself in what way uh spiritually
body wise how it all how will you use
this knowledge physically
probably to improve myself and my life
and those around me
how what methodology is most exciting to
do I don't know. I'm researching quite a
few different ones. All right. Which one
has already been most exciting to you?
Which one stands out the strongest now
so far? That has has helped me the most.
The one you wish to exemplify. The way
you wish to put into action what you
have learned. How do you wish to share
what you are learning?
What? How do you wish to be of service?
I don't know. Yes, you do. I do. Yes.
Okay. When you allow yourself to know
that you do, many of these headaches
will cease entirely.
For you are receiving communication. I
know I am. Yes. And and I'm aware that I
have been. All right. I dream all the
time. Yes. And and as a matter of fact,
I had a dream about you last night. Yes.
Going to Germany, I think it is. By the
way, do you plan to go to Germany? I
planned nothing.
Okay. Now the idea is that you are
highly receptive as we have said to
these electromagnetic pulses right and
they are being used to communicate with
you. Okay. But the idea of the headache
only comes because you are to some
degree hesitating and resisting letting
yourself express it in the way you know
would be most joyous. You are analyzing
the ways a little
bit so strongly that you are not truly
allowing yourself to give full fruition,
full embodiment and full expression to
the way you truly do desire to express
it because you want to be very careful
in your mind. You are being cautious but
to some degree you are being overly
cautious. And this resistance and this
hesitation is allowing this energy
communication to back up within you and
creating the sense of pressure.
When you are more willing to let it out,
let it through. Trust your instincts
rather than having to rely so much on
your analysis process. Then you will
allow like a valve some of the steam
out. You follow me? I think so. I'm I'm
just not certain when it
when it will be correct. There I go
again. Right. Okay.
Now. Right. Right now. Let's use your
imagination right now. Okay. Let's open
those gateways up a little bit. Don't
worry, it won't hurt.
Allow yourself now.
to imagine. Even if your conscious mind
thinks this is only a game, that's all
right. Play along. Imagine right now at
least one way. It does not have to be
the absolute idealized
ultimate end all beall way you could
ever come up with right now. Imagine one
way that you would feel happy in
expressing what you are learning. One
way that you would feel most light and
joyous in sharing and being of service
with what you are learning, one way, one
idea.
Speaking with others. All right. Are you
already doing this? Yes. To what extent?
A little. All right. When you find
individuals, in other words, who are
interested, you simply share ideas with
them. Yes.
Yes. All
right. The knowledge you are learning,
how else do you imagine it can be
applied
other than speaking with other I don't
know. That's I that's where I don't know
at this point. That's not what's arrived
yet. I don't know. All
right. When it does
arrive, how do you imagine it will
arrive? I'll know. Yes, you
I'll know. Yes, you
will. Now, is it all right for you to
know that when it happens? Yes. Is it
all right for you to not necessarily
consciously know it now?
Yes. Are you sure?
I maybe I'm at the point where it's
about ready to arrive and I and I sense
it and all right. The
regulation of the pattern to some degree
is an indication of a cohesion of a
crystallization. Okay. So yes, you are on a threshold
Okay. So yes, you are on a threshold
right now. Right.
Will you do me a favor? Okay. Oh, thank
you. Will you take three slow deep
breaths? Not fast, slow. Okay.
[Music] In so doing, did any even the most
In so doing, did any even the most
abstract type of image come to you at
all? Just me. Just you. Just me. Just you.
Just me. Just you. Just me. Just you.
Very
good. You unto
yourself are absolutely
self-contained. And all of the knowledge
you are discovering already exists
within you. All of the communication you
are having, whether or not it is connecting
having, whether or not it is connecting
to what you might typically call other
consciousness or not, also comes from
you. Allow yourself to recognize
Allow yourself to recognize
therefore that right now you are
complete. And whatever definition of
that completeness you choose to have
will determine the rate and timing in
which you will manifest your unique
expression of that
completeness. You yourself is all you
need. You yourself in that sense is all you
You yourself in that sense is all you
have but it is all you need. So in your
search in your
research allow yourself to recognize
that there was you at the beginning. And
no matter what or whom you connect up to
or with in your research, there will
only be you at the end, so to speak. the
end. And when instead of a search it
becomes an
expression, then the energy will
flow. For
research is creating an echo
inwardly and the innocent headache are a
reflection of that echo.
When you let it
out, then you will be channeling through
yourself rather than allowing it to
bottle up and channel back into
yourself, constantly
rearching for that part of yourself you
think you do not yet contain. You
contain it. When you let it out, that is
when you will discover it has been there
all along and you will no longer need to
search and research.
You follow me? Yes. You know what you
need to know when you need to know it.
Yes. And at the same time, everything
you need to know to be anything you wish
to be, you know, right now. Anything
that you can conceive of being at all
right now because you have the ability
to conceive of being that idea. Even the
slightest notion of that idea, you
contain all the tools necessary right
now to be that idea. Because having that
idea is an indication that you do have
the tools for that level already. Right.
Thank you. Thank you very much. More and
continuous pleasant dreams to you. Thank
you. And the breathing, the breathing will
And the breathing, the breathing will
also energize, balance and alleviate a
great deal of the
pressure. So breathe, meditate, breathe
slowly, fully. All right. Thank you.
Thank you guys. Good evening, Bishar.
and do you?
My question is in regards to experiences
that I have had on spaceships. All
right. Weren't they fun? Oh, they were
wonderful. Oh, thank you.
They were quite interesting. I I feel
that a time has come for me
to be more open about these experiences
and I I have come to you to ask
suggestions and directions in how to go
forth to do this.
Recognize first of all that your
willingness to do what you are doing now
and share what you are sharing now is in
and of itself a first step. For now you
are allowing yourself to let it be all
right for other individuals in your
society to know how you believe you are
connected up in this society. You follow
me? Yes. You have many many
many literature books that speak of many
different kinds of encounters,
physiological encounters, mental
encounters and so forth. The physical
channel made you aware of a new one this
evening of your time. Perhaps in reading
synchronistically of that account, it
will allow you more understanding of how
to come forth with your own. For it is
in that way written by individuals who
have that experience. And those
individuals do form connections to other
individuals that have similar
experiences and wish to explore the
entire idea.
Also, whatever it is you have learned in
these experiences, you can simply share
the information therein in a general
sense. The principles apply what you
have learned, the principles of what you
have learned in a general way to your
society by sharing the ideas in ways
that individuals in your society can
make use of so that they can get them to
work for themselves.
Whether or not you define the source or
label it is not important. The ideas,
the essence, the tools, it is what is
workable. That is what is important. So
simply whether or not you have to tell
anyone where you think the information
was learned. Share the information. Then
you will be acting as an example, a
reflection for other individuals to see
within you how this information works in
your life. so that if they choose to
believe it can work in their lives, they
can live it too. They do not necessarily
have to know where it came from in that
sense. For again, fundamentally, since
it was a cocreation, it still always
comes from you.
I see. You follow me? Yes, I do. So, put
into action in whatever way excites you
the most the information. Share that
with people. Put it into action. How you
wish to be of service in sharing this
information will be exactly the correct
way for you to share it and will be the
reason for why you were contacted. I
see. Okay. You follow me? Yes, I do. We
also thank you for playing your part in
the expansion of awareness in the
civilization into which you have chosen
to be born. Thank you. Could I have one
more question, please? That was it. That
was it. Just kidding.
You do not have to ask if you can ask.
Go ahead. I'd like to know why I'm
plagued with health problems. Plagued.
Plagued. Interesting. Experiencing.
One idea is very strongly connected to
what you might call some past life
scenarios wherein you had an inherent
weakness belief. You have carried that
inherent weakness belief into this life
to some degree. One of the main reasons
was to allow you to focus on the mental
attributes that have now brought you to
where you are and given you the ability
to form the communications you have
formed. You no longer need that as a
tool for the communications have been
fulfilled in that sense. They are now
ongoing. You are doing what you need to
do in that sense. You are on track and
therefore you can allow yourself to
realize real eyes that you can be sound
of mind and body simultaneously. And one
of the ways to realize that most
succinctly and most quickly is to
recognize that your mind and your body
truly, not really, are separate things.
I see. Now, let me share with you one
idea we have shared with many of you of
late. Whether or not this makes
mechanical sense to your outer aware
consciousness, this will sink in on one
level. And you may find that in your
dream realities or the way your life
plays itself out, you will realize a
more profound, deeper understanding of
what we are about to say than it may
appear on the surface at this
time. Listen, are you listening? Yes, I am.
Listen, are you listening? Yes, I am.
Thank
you. Consciousness does not
Consciousness does not
exist in the body.
The body exists within your
consciousness. Do you understand the
difference? Yes.
Then learn to feel the
difference. Learn to allow the
understanding of that difference to be
absolutely real for you. For if your
body exists within your consciousness,
then your body is only the product of
the ideas and the beliefs at any given
moment that you are creating your
consciousness to
be. Ask
yourself, how does having the idea of
imbalanced health serve
you? If it no longer serves you, then
recognize the only reason you may be
holding on to it is because of habit.
because of the way you have been taught
to think. Now that you have formed the
connections that you have formed, one of
the reasons for those connections is to
allow you to know that you are the
creator of your reality and that your
physical experience is the product of
what you believe to be true. And if you
have a physical experience that you no
longer need, then the only way that
physical experience can continue is if
the beliefs continue. If the beliefs
continue, it is usually only the product
that you are used to those beliefs being
the only beliefs you are familiar
with. Redefine the belief. If the idea
of ill health no longer serves you, then
allow yourself to say, "I will now
receive and I make the conscious
decision now to now receive any
information I need to receive in the
easiest possible way along the path of
least resistance." And therefore I will
not have to create scenarios in my life
that now force me to look at things that
I am refusing to look at because I will
not allow the information to come
subtly. When you do not allow the
information that comes to you to come
subtly then your body and your
consciousness will do whatever it has to
do to get you to pay attention to the
area the aspect and the fragment of
yourself that you have created the
message to come from. Many times this
will take the manifestation of
disease because then you are absolutely
beyond a shadow of a doubt focused on
the idea that you are living at that
moment. You are paying attention to the
totality of yourself. When you can pay
attention to the totality of yourself
without needing the disease, you will
not have
it. So the idea is to homogenize
yourself and recognize that body and
mind are one idea. one
idea. Do not separate them any longer.
And as strong as you find your mind to
be, your body will follow suit. You
follow me? Yes.
Now, how do you
imagine yourself to be in what you call
an idealized state? How would you
imagine you would be in what you call
perfect health?
Can you feel what it quote unquote would
be like? Yes, I do. You have a good
strong feeling of what it would be like?
Yes, I do. All right. Feel it for a
moment. Let it completely wash through
your body. Feel what it would be like to
be
absolutely perfectly in health. You do
know what it is like. So feel it.
Absolutely. Experience it. Let that
sensation sink into every cell, every
molecule, every atom, the spaces between
the atoms. Let it infuse itself in the
energy field, the electromagnetic field
that you are. You know that matter is
energy and energy is matter. Yes. Yes, I
do. Then allow yourself to think of
yourself for now. If you believe you are
an outofbalance material state, then
revert yourself back to a homogeneous
energy state where no one part has the
ability to stand out from any other
part. As soon as you allow yourself to
melt back into energy in your
imagination, then you will be realigning
the definition of yourself. You will be
defining the ideal blueprint of
yourself. And then as you allow your
body to
recristallize from that energy state,
allow it to recristallize more along the
pattern of what you are now holding to
be the idea of what it feels like to be
in perfect health. In other words, in
your imagination, imagine yourself to
become the homogeneous blue white
electromagnetic energy that your
material is created from. In your
imagination, float in that state. Be
that state. See yourself as the blue white
state. See yourself as the blue white
sphere of transparent energy. Then in
that state, impose upon that energy the
vibration of what you know it feels like
to be in perfect health. Then let your
body recristallize along the new template
recristallize along the new template
that you have imposed upon the energy
that you are. And bit by bit, as many
times as you need to do it, but
absolutely definitely bit by bit, you
will then reconstruct yourself according
to that idea that you know represents
your idealized state. You follow me?
Yes. Enjoy. Thank you. This is one of the
Enjoy. Thank you. This is one of the
ideas that we will also be taking many
of you through within the workshop that
has been announced. The idea of what you
call this workshop will be as you name
it a
self-empowerment workshop and will focus
on four primary
aspects all geared in building your own
understanding of self-creativity and
empowerment. One will be bodily
alignment. The second will be psychic
sensitivity. The third will be creativity and
The third will be creativity and
abundance. And the fourth will be the
idea of awakening and
transformation and manifestation into
your life of the idea you know you are.
These four ideas combined
together will allow you to experience in
a concentrated form. A time
frame that completely takes you out of
your typical preconceived notions of a
daytoday existence and allows you to
begin to rely upon what we have
discussed to be the miraculous
foundation of creation itself.
So these ideas we will assist you with,
go through you with in terms you call
technique and exercise and it will be in
a highly concentrated
form. But we
guarantee that your own imagination
always has the ability to give you what
you need if you are willing to rely upon
it. And at the same time, when you are
willing to let yourself transform in
these ways, changes will occur in your
life at whatever rate you are
comfortable in allowing them to
change. We thank you. Thank you. Enjoy
the meditation. Be vibratory energy for
meditation. Be vibratory energy for
everything is simply
that shedding.
Good evening Mr. Busher.
Is it from Canada?
We understand the idea is that we are
not speaking your language at all. We
are only capable of using the vocabulary
inherent. The channel is Yay. The channel not meu. Do you
understand the channel? I understand the
channel. I understand the channel speaks
English. Your language English. I am
speaking Hey, I am speaking of the
higher power. We understand. Okay. But
you also have definitions that you have
been taught. Yes, I have been taught.
Now I am speaking to you. I on oneonone.
I
I'm asking a question. Ah.
All right. I'm going to a new venture. I
promotional advertising and product placement
advertising and product placement
and entertainment industry. Guys, that's
it. Guys,
I'm asking. That's it. What is my
venture going to end up with? Or what
will I What are my
I What are my
Are you frightened? Yes. Why? I don't
know. That's all I'm asking. You are
frightened because you do not know that
you have the ability to create the
reality you desire. Yes. But recognize
that you do. And that
therefore anything at all that excites
you the most is what you will be most
successful at if you put 100% of your
trust into it. You see, excitement is
your sign. Excitement is the energy of
sign. Excitement is the energy of
creation. And therefore when you
discover something that excites you the
most that is your sign that that is the
thing in life you actually can be most
successful at. All you need to do is
trust it and act upon it and follow the
excitement at any given moment. Follow
where the excitement goes and you will
always be completely successful and
abundant. Excitement is the physical
translation of the connection to
infinite creation.
So if it excites you, do it and you will
be successful. If you find at any given
time within any venture that a certain
aspect of it no longer excites you, then
discover where the excitement does lie,
follow it. And even though it may not
seem on the surface to be connected to
what you think it should connect to, it
is the excitement within that scenario
that lets you know ultimately it is
connected. Maybe not in the way you have
been taught to think, maybe in an
unexpected route, but if you always
follow with 100% faith and trust and
unconditional love, whatever it is that
excites you the most. All things that
excite you will be able to be
accomplished in your life. Because
excitement is a thread that leads
through everything you need to do to
fully live the life you have chosen to
live. [Music]
[Music]
Shutting. Good evening, Bashar. Good
evening. I've been coming to see you for
se I've been coming to see you for
several months now and I haven't spoken
before this because I'm terrified of
speaking in front of groups. All right.
You are not alone in your society. Did
you know something? What? That
particular fear is the number one fear
in your society. I would believe it.
So you are in marvelous company.
In fact, I've created it so well that I
thought if I do not get up here and get
through this,
then I'm never going to get through this
fear. So I'm here. Oh, thank you very
much. Thank you for allowing us all of
us to be what reflects your own trust in
yourself to you. We thank you for
showering us with such a beautiful gift
as your willingness to share. For the
fear you have and the fear that any of
you would have about the idea of
speaking with other individuals or in
front of other individuals is only the
fear that what you have to say is not
worthwhile. But you are a unique facet
of infinite creation. And therefore,
because you exist, everything you have
to say is just as much an equal gift as
anything anyone has to say. So we thank
you for showering us with the gift that
you are.
Thank you. And if it wasn't for the
boldness and the courage of so many
other people that have gotten up here
and done this, then I wouldn't have been
able to listen to all the wonderful
tapes that I've listened to over the
last few months and caught up on you
last year and learned so much from all
of you. And I just want to thank you
very much. We thank you. And allow us to
remind you of one
thing. The you you used to be, you no
longer are.
Thank you. Enjoy.
Hi. Hi. My mother recently had a
contact. A voice came very clear in her
head. Alana, I am your space brother.
And she's been very upset ever since
because she doesn't know how to
establish contact. And that was the only
communication that she got. And she was
kind of nervous at the time. All right.
The nervousness therefore in a sense is
an indication of the rate that will be
let us say most conducive for the next
contact. However, not all contacts are
going to come in that
method. Understand once again that no
matter what form a guide takes, many
communications will simply play
themselves out in your physical life. In
other words, walking down your street,
overhearing a certain
conversation, seeing a printed sentence
that makes sense to you, walking up to
your bookshelf and seeing the one book
that gives you the information you now
need. Those are all forms of
communication from many different
levels. You follow me? Yes. So, simply
suggest that she stop trying to pay
attention to the way it came before and
simply get on with the living of the
life. It is as we have said the living
of the life that will allow any
individual to know everything they need
to know to continue living that life.
And the idea once again and why many of
these contacts are sporadic in that
sense is once they have been let us say
kicked into action the idea is to
realize that you do not need those
contacts to live the life. They then
lure you to looking to searching to
exploring with your curiosity so that
you discover for yourself that you have
the empowerment to continue the
acceleration and you don't need the
other individual to do it for you.
Guides are very tricky in that way. They
lure you into more of
yourself. You follow me? Yes. So allow
the individual to learn to live in the
moment. Live in the now. Enjoy the life
they are.
In living that life to the fullest,
everything they need to know, they will
find out one way or another. One way or
another. It is simply the opening of
synchronicity in their life. The opening
of the awareness that everything in life
is synchronicity. And that simply means
that everything is always in the right
place at the right time interacting with
exactly the correct individuals that
need to be interacted with to show you
at any given moment what the idea is you
believe in the
strongest. From time to time the guides
will give a small hint, a small
interjection in the most subtle of ways.
It may seem to be startling to you just
because it came in an unexpected
fashion. But allow yourself to recognize
that the momentum has been set off and
that if that individual simply allows
their life to unfold and lives it that
the momentum will carry them unairringly
to the places they need to go and if and
when they need communication in that
fashion again it will be there.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Hello Bashar. Hello. Uh first I'd like
to say uh I experience great joy and
excitement in hearing the word from you.
We experience ecstatic joy and
excitement in interacting with all of
you. Thank you. Um my question is I'd
like you to discuss an antidote or
remedy for getting for getting in the
way of the true self because of the
personality. We have already done this
to some degree. Yes. Following what
excites you the most is what allows you
to be the true self. Mhm. Okay. The
medicine, so to speak, is that simple.
All you need to do is take it.
Right.
Now, first of all, what may be quote
unquote getting in your way also is the
assumption that the personality has to
get in the
way. Personality is not who or what you
are. It is an artificial construct and
therefore it is your artificial
construct. What do you wish it to be?
Define it and that's what it will be.
Define the idea you prefer to be and you
are most excited about being at any
given moment. And the persona has
absolutely no choice but to become a
reflection a representation of the idea
you believe most strongly in you know is
you. So the idea is to control the
personality aso as opposed to the
personality controlling well in a sense
but control may lead to conflict. You do
not have to control it. In a sense it is
already under your control. It is your
creation. Mhm. You are already
controlling it. You have never lost
control. Your personality at any given
moment is absolutely always a perfect
reflection of what you believe it most
likely can be. It is always under your
control and has never been out of your
control ever.