for some point even prior to the
physical life between the person that's
going to be the channel and the energy
that's going to channel through
them. Your life contains whatever kinds
of circumstances it needs to to get you
to remember that you made the agreement
and to give you whatever skills you need
to fulfill that agreement. So how
everyone gets there of course is
different depending upon the different
kind of life that you may be living and
what type of a person that you are. For
me, the biggest turning point was about
14 years ago on two occasions within the
span of the same week with four friends
with me the first time and two friends
with me the second time. We actually had
very close physical broad daylight
sightings on Bashard spacecraft, the one
that Steve mentioned over Los Angeles.
First time about 150 ft away, second
time about 60 70 ft away.
Now, what I didn't understand at the
time, aside from being excited about
seeing what everyone was calling a UFO,
and what I have come to understand now
is that that physical sighting of the
spaceship was Bashar's way of sort of
touching me in the subconscious memory
to spur me on to start researching and
learning about the things I needed to
learn about to be able to ultimately
fulfill the agreement that I had made
prior to the physical life with him.
After the sighting happened, I began
doing more research into metaphysical
studies, UFO phenomenology and
eventually came across the whole idea
along with many other ideas of of
channeling. One day someone introduced
me to several channels who were
practicing at the time and one of the
entities coming through one of those
channels offered to teach channeling in
a specific class structure for whoever
was interested because several people
were interested. Now, even then, I took
him up on the offer not thinking that
this was something I was going to wind
up doing. I just had read all the books
I could find at the time on the subject,
and I wanted to learn more about it. So,
I figured if I went into a class, I
would see something contemporary in
action. When I was in that class under
the guidance of the other entity through
the other medium and when I was in a
receptive state because of that
guidance is when Bashar and his people
made the telepathic connection with me.
As Soon as they made the telepathic
connections, then the memory of having
made the agreement came back. Who they
were, who I was to them, why the ship
sighting had occurred, dream
conversations I had had with them that I
had totally blocked out of my mind up to
that point, all came flooding back in
that one memory. And what came with it
was their first real time telepathic
message, which was, okay, now that you
remember you made the agreement, do you
still want to fulfill the agreement?
Because it was a choice, and it always
is a choice. It's not something that's
ever forced upon you. Obviously, I said
yes. And that was just a little over
four years ago now, and I've been doing
it for the last four years. Now, Bashar
presents himself as a member of an
extraterrestrial community. There is a slight difference.
community. There is a slight difference.
It's not uncommon, but it seems to be a
little bit rare. Most of the energy or
entity or consciousnesses that are
channeled through people seem to be one
way or another disembodied
consciousness. Now, this either means
that you are channeling a portion of
your own higher self or that you are
channeling someone who has been alive
and is no longer alive or you're
channeling something that is from
another dimension altogether and doesn't
have a physical representation as we
understand it isn't life as we know it
in that way. But there is also a
category which for lack of a better term
is generally labeled
extraterrestrial which not all of which
have to have bodies as we know it but
many of which do have physical forms of
some sort. Bashar is of this type. They
actually have a physicality. They can
describe much about their civilization
to you if you care to ask them anything
about that. Um, some of the information,
not a lot, but some of it is on the blue
sheet as well. Um, and the recap of what
I have just said is on there as
well. But he does present himself as a
physicalized being from an
extraterrestrial civilization that is
not exactly like ours, but it's similar
in certain ways and dissimilar in other
ways. The one thing that I like to
stress, especially for new people, is
that even though I have my own
validations in the physical sightings
and other circumstances that have
happened in my life that help prove to
me that Bashar is who he says he is, the
one thing I like to stress is that
there's absolutely nothing within these
interactions whatsoever that insists in
any way, shape, or form that you have to
believe that Bashar is who I say he is.
I cannot prove it to you anyway. So the
whole point of the information is the
whole point of the interaction is not so
much who they are but what they're
saying. The information itself is what's
critical here. And if the information
that comes through works for you, if you
find something you can apply in your
life, then by all means use it. If you
find that it doesn't work for you,
you'll get what you need somewhere else.
But they are purposely at least for a
while remaining in the
background because one of the things
Bashar has said is that he's noticed
it's been one of the habits of our
society to sort of lock on to the
messenger and not listen to the message
at all and just sort of throw it out the
window. So they are perfectly staying in
the background for a while until we feel
equal enough to them to not raise them
or elevate them above ourselves, above
our own understandings, above our own
ability to live our life. They're here
to help us remember that we have the
ability to create the lives we want and
all the power to do that within us
already. They're doing it out of love.
They're doing it out of reflection and
also doing it in the sense uh let's say
for selfish reasons in that having us
join them as equals will expand their
association will give them more people
to interact with and will help them
learn more about the way the universe
works through us. So they're doing it
for both of those reasons and perhaps
for many others. But um he comes through
in that way and just interact with him
directly in a very informal way. Uh
again it's not important that you
believe he is who he says he is but that
you get out of the interaction whatever
it is you feel you need to get out of
it. Now the word itself Bashar is not
literally his name. They do not have
names in their society because as far as
they're concerned they're pretty much
telepathic right now in their evolution.
They have a remnant language which they
no longer really use. But he felt that
because of our the way our civilization
is that we needed a name to refer to him
by. It was a little more convenient to
call it something. And so he picked a
word from one of our own earth
languages. The word bashar is actually
Arabic and that's partly my background
which is why he chose it and it does
represent some of the connections that
he and I have. But I don't speak Arabic.
I had no idea what the word meant or
that it even was a word at all when he
chose it to represent himself by. He
gave us one meaning of it and other
people who speak Arabic have five other
meanings. It has turned out that even
though the word is not his name
literally, it does seem to refer to who
he is and what he's doing at least
symbolically. On one level, the word
means commander, which is something
similar to what he is in his society. On
other levels, the word means either
simply the man or the being. It also in
a broader sense means humanity and
perhaps the most appropriate meaning is
in Armenian the word bashar means
messenger which is basically what he's
doing. So we use that to refer to him by
its convenience. Now when he comes
through he will say something that I
guess he feels is indicative of the
collective consciousness in any
gathering and it'll help set the
foundation and unify you know all of us
together. And after he's through
talking, then he's basically going to
turn it over to you. And the way he will
do that is by saying either how may I
serve you or sharing that. His way of
saying the balls in your court,
questions, answers, anything you want to
talk about. Doesn't have to be a
question. Can be a statement or
discussion. And the way we're doing it
here is simply as you ask your question
and you're finished, then take a seat
and the next people move up and someone
else will come in line right after at
the end and keep it going that way.
Um, as was mentioned, make an attempt at
least to focus or narrow the idea down
to the single most important question or
idea you want to talk about. Um, mostly
for the purpose of allowing as many
people as possible a chance to get up
here. Now, if it seems that people start
running out of questions, which hasn't
happened yet, but if that seems to
happen, then by all means, feel free to
come up and ask another question if we
have the time. Um, but focusing that,
focusing on the single most important
issue will not only allow more people an
opportunity, it will help you really
concentrate on what's really important
to you, what you really want to talk
about. It'll also help give you an
opportunity to really pay attention to
all the other questions everyone else
asks. Because many times someone else
will ask another question that you
wanted to ask and did not get a chance
to. or you will find that even though
what they're asking may not be the
question you wanted to ask, you'll be
able to apply the answer to their
question in a way that will answer
another question that you may have had.
So everything that goes on, every
question that's asked is an important
part of the sharing we have discovered.
So it's good to pay attention to all of
it. Now, as Steve said, Bashard does not
feel that there's any such thing as a
silly or a stupid question. If there's
something you feel you really want to
talk about, talk about it. Don't hold
back because you're shy or because you
think you're going to be wasting
everyone's time or because you think
it's a mundane question. There's no such
thing. Out of some of the most ordinary
questions uh have come interactions that
have really helped every single person
in very surprising ways. So don't hold
back for that reason. Now, if there's
something you really don't want to talk
about in public, Bashar is not going to
pull teeth from you. He's not going to
pull it out of you. If you don't want to
talk about it, he'll respect that. But
all we're saying simply is don't be shy
for the reasons that you think you're
going to be wasting everyone's time. Um,
the second thing is sometimes you may
speak about
something in a way that you may not be
familiar with. The words may come out in
an unfamiliar way because what's
happening here is he's not actually
speaking our language at all. I'm in a
telepathic link up with him. My
consciousness becomes softened. It
becomes diffused. It allows his
consciousness to impress itself on my
pattern and create my consciousness to
vibrate at his frequency. What you're
getting is a model of his consciousness
made out of my energy. I'm functioning
literally like a translation device for
his thoughts. Literally like a
telephone. So sometimes when the
concepts come through the words may come
through in unusual ways or the concept
may be very new to you. If for some
reason whether you're asking the one
asking the question or not you don't
understand what Bashar is saying. The
second point is please don't let it
slide. This is your time and he wants to
know you're getting out of this all the
understanding you want to get. So if he
says something you don't get it say whoa
Bashar I don't get that. Could you
explain it another way? He'll do that to
him. Everything is the first time every
time. It's not a waste of time. He
doesn't ever feel like he's
backtracking. He wants to know that
you're understanding what he's saying.
So if you feel like you want to stop
him, stop him and get him to explain it
again and then he'll go on. Okay? Uh
that's just for you, but that's totally
in your hands, under your control. So
whatever you put out is basically what
he's going to reflect back to you. On
that note, how much more light you are
about the interaction will also be how
light he is back to you. Now, he likes
to have fun. He's always having fun
whether he seems serious to you or not.
I always experience him in the altered
state as being very full of humor.
Sometimes he will present what appears
to be a somewhat stern face because he
feels a sensing from the person asking
the question that they need to see that
kind of a response in order to take him
seriously. He never takes himself
seriously. So the humor is always there.
If you look for it, you'll always find
it and you'll always see it reflected
back. Um because he's really doing this
out of
love. Let's see. um when I am going into
the altered state what I would just like
to ask all of you and when I'm coming
out of it as well either at the break if
we have a break uh and at the end is
that there is nothing tiring nor
depleting about this for me I don't
really hear the words but I do feel the
energy I know there's an interaction
going on but it's like being lost in a
daydream for me when I come out of it
it's very energizing but for a few
moments it's very disorienting it's like
waking up in the morning and I I don't
quite know where I am. So, what I'm
asking is when I'm going in and coming
out, if you would just be quiet until
I'm actually reoriented and I'll let you
know that I'm basically refocused. Then
you can start talking. If you all start
talking all at once when he just says
goodbye, then it's like having a 100
people shouting in your ear in the
morning when you're trying to wake up
out of a deep sleep. So, just sit still
for a second. I'll let you know when I'm
back. And then you can move around and
talk. Um, am I forgetting anything? I think
Um, am I forgetting anything? I think
you got it.
Okay. Uh, all right. Once again, then
thank you very much. Uh, please enjoy
yourself cuz that's what it's all about.
And I'll see y'all
later. Oh.
Um, going into the altered state,
sometimes you'll see some bodily
reactions. None of these are painful. I
say that just because sometimes people
say it looks like it is. It's not. It's
just an automatic adjustment to the
energy. So don't worry about me. I'm
having a wonderful
time. Also for the people, especially in
the first row, there will be a volume
change. Don't be startled.
[Music]
I never usually go backwards far. I know
and if I did, I probably
wouldn't till later. There was one time
that happened in uh
I don't exactly Oh, it was in it was in
I think it was in Denver. Denver. There
was a chair. They gave me a chair with
arms on it. And during the session,
because of a movement Bashar made with
my arm, my elbow cracked on the arm of
the chair. Now, somebody all the way in
the back of the auditorium said they
heard that. I didn't feel a thing. When
I came out and we later went to dinner,
I put my arm on the table and it was
extremely sore. I was sore for like a
week thereafter. But during the trance,
I didn't feel a thing.
So, but I'll move behind. [Music]
How are you all this evening of your
time as you create time to exist?
Perfect. Are you all alive? Thank you. Allow us
Are you all alive? Thank you. Allow us
to begin this interaction this evening
of your time with the laying down of a
few foundations between us. The first
idea we would like to discuss with you
is an idea that we have begun to discuss
now with many of you and with every new
interaction we shall undertake and
participate in in your society. We will
begin with the following idea. It is in
the nature of a project that we would
enjoy involving you all of you within
and we have entitled this project the
peace quark. We have heard many discussions
quark. We have heard many discussions
upon your planet many discussions about
the idea of your desire for harmony and
love and peace in your civilization.
The idea always will go hand in hand
with the degree of conviction that each
and every one of you are willing to
exhibit in creating that peace upon your
planet. In creating it to happen and not
just sitting back and waiting for it to
happen but in creating it to have in
taking an active stand as you say in
creating the idea of peace and harmony
and creativity upon your planet in
beneficial and positive ways. So we have
designed a little project that can
assist you in moving the momentum in
that direction. The momentum of the
energy of your collective
consciousness. This project entitled the
peace clock goes as follows. Is very
simple, very simple.
each and every
day at exactly the time you call 12
midday when your sun your star is
directly overhead. Be it a day that you
call bright or a day you call cloudy
does not matter directly at midday every
day for one full minute of your time in
whatever way shape or form seems most
beneficial to you. Do a silent
meditation for world peace every single
day. Now the second part of this project
is as
follows. There will be what you would
call information written out delineating
this peace clock idea and it will be
available very soon to be dispersed
among you to take it and as you say copy
it if you wish and share with as many
individuals as you care to. For the
second part of this idea is to have by
the date you call your January 1st,
1990 every single individual on your
planet every day at 12 midday for one
minute meditating on world peace. every
single individual by that
date. This information will be provided
very shortly for any that dare to take
it and spread it and share it with all
the other individuals in any way your
creativity and your imagination so
desire. In doing this, what you are
creating is a motion, a momentum, an
electromagnetic thrust around your
planet. For we recognize that on your
world you have many different time
zones. Whenever it is noon, midday in
your time zone, if that entire shall we
say flight, 124th of your planet is
focused for one minute at midday on that
meditation of world peace and then the
next slice and the next slice all the
way around your planet around and around
and around and around day after day
after day. you will actually generate an
electromagnetic momentum that will
almost literally spin you and accelerate
you in a higher vibratory pitch. Do you
understand? For you are beings of life. You are
For you are beings of life. You are
beings of energy. You are made out of
living life. The thoughts that you have
and the way you focus those thoughts
utterly determines the nature of the
physiological reality you experience. So
this idea, this
self-chosen meditation called the peace
clock will aid and assist for all that
participate in creating a more conducive
and more literally conductive
atmosphere in your combined world energy
to make it that much more available to
you and accessible to you. that your
thoughts of peace will find fertile
ground in which to take root and grow
upward. Spreading it leaves to the light
of your joy and
love. The second idea and the
foundation that we will lay down is for
all of you to recognize that the purpose
of these interactions that we have with
you and the purpose for many of the
interactions at other levels of
consciousness as you call us are now communicating to
as you call us are now communicating to
your planet folk is as
follows. You as a civilization now are
beginning to awaken into more awareness
of a willingness to explore different
levels of consciousness. You are all
beginning to suspect that there is more
to you than just the physical
form. And that consciousness truly
expands and extends beyond what you have
for so long, many thousands of your
years, been taught to believe that the
physical world is all varied. That the
physical universe simply exists with you
or without you, and that you have really
nothing much to say about it. For you
may be in it for a while. You are told
that you may be able to affect to some
degree your immediate surroundings. But
lo and behold, in the ultimate story you
are given or have been given on your
planet. Anything you do doesn't have
much of an effect on the overall
reality. But now you are beginning to
discover this is not so. You are
beginning to realize even your own
scientists and your physicists are
beginning to
realize to
realize that your thoughts themselves
are the actual driving and creative
force behind the physical reality behind
the physical experiences each and every
one of you have. We are here to remind
you of who and what you already are. To
allow you to begin to discover and
remember more and more and more and more
of the energy of the consciousness of
the beingness that you already
are. You have many different forms of
literature upon your society.
One in particular, you have labeled your
Bible. Within that Bible, there is a
phrase that many of you are familiar
with. That phrase goes as follows. You
are made in the image of God. Now, what
does that mean? Do any of you do many of
you really understand what that means?
God. What you call God, what our
civilization calls all that is the
infinite creation is a
multi-dimensional infinite
awareness. If you are made as a
reflection of that image, then you are
multi-dimensional infinite beings as
well. The idea we are here to remind you of is
The idea we are here to remind you of is
that you are aspects of the infinite
facets of the multi-dimensional crystal
of all that is and that you can learn to
shine like the facets that you are. To
live with full conviction to live with
full joy to serve and be of service and
be served and share and love with the
fullness of your being. to allow
yourself to live as you were created to
live in ecstasy because ecstasy is what
you are made of. What you call love is
the prime vibrational frequency of
existence. When you match that frequency
as unconditionally as you can, you are
aligned with creation itself and all
things are possible through you. This is
very simple. All the things we are
discussing and will discuss with you
this night of your time may sound to
many of you or may in the past have
sounded to many of you to be oh well
nice philosophy or it's a nice way to think.
philosophy or it's a nice way to think.
Well, yes, it's a nice attitude to have.
Oh yes, I suppose it's a jolly way to
be. But what does it really have to do
with physical reality? It has everything
to do with it. Everything. Because your
thoughts actually create things and your
attitude determine which of your
thoughts positive or negative create
positive or negative things. So we are
not simply discussing what you might
call some airy philosophy. We are
discussing physics mechanics of the
creation of your physical reality. This
is done through your beliefs, your
emotions and your thought patterns.
All the ideas we will be discussing this
evening of your time will always funnel
back down to that primary foundation
that you each and every one of you
individually and collectively are the
creators of your physical experiential
reality. The
The
ideas that we shall share this day, this
evening of your time will always be for
the purpose of reminding
you that you have already been created
with the
ability innately, inherently to create
whatever reality you really
prefer. Honest.
[Music] We know and having discussed this idea
We know and having discussed this idea
many times with many of you that some of
these ideas seem too simple, too good to
be true. But that's only because that's
the way you have been taught to
think. Realize the habitual rituals that
many of you have fallen into after
thousands and thousands of your years of
limitation and negativity.
When you are told a story in your world,
that story contains pain and conflict
and struggle and strife. You say, "Oh,
very realistic
story." When you are told a story where
it says, "Finally, live happily ever
after." There are fairy tales.
There is absolutely nothing within the
creation of the universe that insists
that the story that contains the
conflict is any more real than the one
that does not. It is your choice out of
your habits to believe that pain is more
real than joy.
Now you are awakening to the fact that
you have for thousands of years lived
many lives where you have explored the
idea of limitation and suffering and
struggling and pain. You have lived
almost all the different kinds of
circumstances of limitation that can be
lived in any one particular society. You
have played all the ideas out almost to
the end of the cycle. That's why you're
beginning to wake up now into more
remembrance that you do not have to
change and grow and learn through
struggle and strife and pain. You can
change and grow and learn through joy
and ecstasy and fascination and
curiosity like a
child. All of you are born on your
planet with the total facility for
living your life in absolute joy. But
because of the way I've created your
society to be, that is often, shall we
say, drumed out of many of you by the
time you are three years of age. Yes,
that young. And you begin to buy into
the belief systems that your society
says are the belief systems you must buy
into in order to survive in this world,
kid. But now that you are growing up in many
But now that you are growing up in many
more ways than just physically, you are
now beginning to realize and awaken into
the understanding that it does not have
to be that way. Or it can be, but it
does not have to be that way. That you
deserve happiness just because you say
so, just because you can conceive of the
idea is sufficient in the eyes of
creation. You do not have to prove
anything. You do not have to deserve
happiness. You do not have to earn a
living in the negative sense of the
word. You already deserve life because
you have been given life because you
exist. Your existence is your signal
from infinite creation that you deserve.
Anything you conceive of that you
believe you can deserve. Your awareness
of that idea in of itself is sufficient
to bring it to you.
Creation holds nothing back from you.
And it never ever
has. Never. In every circumstance in your
Never. In every circumstance in your
lives, each and every one of you has
always always been
supported 100% by the
100% by the
universe. But you see, you have been
created with free will.
And if you choose to buy into negative
belief, if you choose to buy into the
idea that you can only do just so much
and it is beyond your capability to do
more, the universe supports you exactly
that far and no further. Because the
universe never gives you more than you
say you are ready to handle. How many of
you believe you're really ready to
handle? absolute infinite unending
absolute infinite unending
ecstasy. A great many of you because of
your training fear ecstasy quite a bit.
Quite a bit. Or you at least contain,
shall we say, belief systems that are
selfregulating in the sense of when you
finally do create something that in your
terms seems to be going the right way,
you say, "Well, this is jolly. How long
can this last?"
You always
cut you always cut your own selves off.
And as soon as you impose that
restriction on yourself through your
belief system, the universe says, "All
right, if that's the way you want it,
cut instantly.
instantly.
Instantly, instantly. You are that
powerful. You have always gotten
everything you believed you could get.
Or perhaps even more importantly for
many of you, everything you believed you
deserved to
get. For deservability is a big issue
with many individuals in your
civilization. I deserve the negativity
or I don't deserve the positivity.
There are many ways, many, many, many
clever, clever ways you constantly
create restrictions upon
yourself. All of this stems from the
fact that in your terms, a long time
ago, you chose as a group consciousness
to be highly highly focused into
physical materiality. What came with
that choice was the ability to forget
that you were the creators of all your
physical reality to begin with. To have
played the game of forgetting for
thousands of your years. Now you are
remembering. You are waking up blinking
your eyes and saying, "Oh, there is
something more. I am now remembering
that I began this game. I began this
cycle a long time ago. Now I'm at the
end of it. time to go on to a new cycle
of joy and remembrance and
creativity. That choice on your part,
that recognition, that awakening on your
part is why I and others like myself are
now even able to begin to communicate
with your civilization because you have
opened the invitation that allows us to
come through. We cannot and will not in
any way, shape, or form at any time ever
impose ourselves upon any civilization
that does not want the interaction, that
does not extend the invitation first by
radiating a vibrational frequency that
says they now know there might be other
consciousness, that they now know that
there might be other levels to their own
consciousness. That is an invitation
that we accept. up only to the point of
acting as a mirror for reflecting back
to you what you already know. We are not
here to live your lives for you. We are
not here to run things. We have our own
lives. We are very busy. Thank you very
much. We have no time to take the
responsibility for living your lives as
well. But we do love you and we do
desire to share with you as equals. We
do desire that your world and our worlds
shall soon one day walk as you say hand
in hand in the exploration of all that
is as we already do with many other
civilizations. You are not so very far
away. Not so very far away. It is our
perception within what you call the next
30 to 50 of your years at the outside
that the changes that are taking place
upon your planet will make it conducive
for your world to be fully involved on
equal levels with our civilization.
That is all the time it will take once
you begin exploring the idea of
integration rather than the segregation
and separation you have been exploring
for thousands of years. Once you begin
to explore integration, it doesn't take
that much time by the definition of
integration to be able to get to very
accelerated places very quickly. In
exploring limitation, in exploring
segregation and separation, that carries
with it inherently a definition of more
space, more time, more pieces, more
definitions, more things to analyze,
breaking it down into components. That's
what makes it take time to live many
lives. When you begin to integrate and
consolidate and unify, everything is
within you. You live in the moment
spontaneously and you create literally
less time. So things are accelerated.
Things happen more quickly. The whole
world ignites in an ecstatic explosion
of ecstasy and coincidence and
synchronicity. Everything tying into
everything else being interconnected and
interrelated. Always in the right place
at the right time interacting with
exactly the individuals you need to
interact with.
No accidents. There are no accidents.
Never have been, aren't, and never will
be. Coincidence is simply that
co-incidence. Your ability to open up
your inner sight and see the
interconnectedness of all things.
The reason everything is interconnected
is because everything is the same one
thing manifesting in all the
multi-dimensional simultaneous ways that
it can because that's the nature of the
creation to manifest itself in all the
ways it can and reveal itself to itself
in all the ways it can. All of
you, all of us together, all the beings
within creation are all the different ways that
creation are all the different ways that
the infinite creator has of looking at
itself, of creating itself to be within
the creation that it is.
So in these interactions, we will be
discovering the aspect you have chosen
to be of the infinite creation and how
you can perhaps more easily, more
fluidly, and more consciously express
with conviction and
trust. the aspect of infinite creation
you have chosen to be and to get the
physical results as you say
pragmatically in your
lives. We will extend to you at this
time our deepest appreciation in
allowing us to experience the gift of
your consciousness.
We thank you for choosing to function as
representatives and ambassadors of your
world. For that is what each and every
one of you are right now. For there are
many on this side listening in. We thank
you for allowing me to function as an
ambassador for all that are listening in
on this
side. Bit by bit and day by day through
these interactions we shall become
closer and closer to the time in not too
many of your years. Hence perhaps within
what you call the next decade or two
where we may interact with you blatantly
face to face in many
ways in return for your gifts of sharing
and the cocreation of this interaction.
Now I ask you how may I serve you? Hi
Bashar and you good day. Nice to be with
you again. always we enjoy interaction
with all of you.
Um I have a question that comes in two
parts. One I'd like a kind of a general
background and then I have something
that's specific to this lecture. All
right. Um when you were giving your
opening instruction remarks you're
talking about thousands of years of
negativity then you speak about like
decades and three 30 years in the future
but yet all kind simultaneous. So how
does that we are using your terminology
so you understand us clearly. Yes we
know that all lives and all realities
and all dimensions exist right now but
that to some degree in our conversations
with you would be confusing. So we use
your colloquial vernacular of talking in
time sequences because all of you are
still very adhered to the clock. And
when we say 20 years from now you
understand what we mean. To say it's all
going on right now is all very well and
good, but that does not tell you how it
fits into the time track you have
created. Understand? You will still be
physiological being for quite some time.
And you will still fall under the opaces
of a time track to some degree. Even
though you may now be loosening up that
time track and realizing that all things
actually happen at once, you will still,
as long as you are physical to some
degree, be subject to the idea, the
notion to some degree of relative
outplay of time. So we simply speak in
the colloquial terminology. So you will
understand this most clearly in terms of
how what we are talking about fits in to
your understanding of time. Does this
make sense? Kind of. Kind of. There is
nothing mysterious about it. The idea
simply is that in your dimension, you
label things in linear time. So we use
your conventional terminology so as not
to be too confusing. Okay. But how did
thousands of years of negativity
translate to all kind of simultaneously?
I mean it's all right. All right. Once
again, do you remember what we have
called the film analogy? The idea what
you call your film upon your planet. If
you take a strip of your film, it has
many different frames. Yes. Yeah. The
idea is that each and every one of those
frames can be a different moment in
time, a different year, a different
life, a different century. It doesn't
matter what you label it. Sufficient to
say that each frame represents a
calculated bit of time. And one frame
follows another. You see them all laid
out in succession. You say this is the
beginning. You arbitrarily say this is
the middle. And you arbitrarily say
that's the end. right there. This is a
cycle. Let's say for the sake of this
discussion that that film strip
represents the thousands of years of
negativity. All right. Okay.
Now, that is the physical analogy of
awareness. Everything is
compartmentalized into segregated frames
one thing at a time. However, I
understand. All right.
However, now you, the being, the true
non-physical consciousness, entity,
awareness, being that you are, the total
soul that you are, knowing that the
physical reality is only one aspect of
the total soul that you are, this total
being is now analogous to what you would
call the
projectionist looking at the strip of
film, looking from above with an
expanded point of view down onto this
nice little flat piece of film with all
of its frames nice and neat and orderly
one after another. Now, while you
project your consciousness into the
film, you only experience reality one
frame at a time. But as soon as you step
back, shall we say rise above physical
reality and adopt the point of view of
the projectionist? Well, the
projectionist looking down on the strip
of film sees all the frames at once.
They're all simultaneous. They're all
right there. The whole film, the
beginning of the film, the middle of the
film, the end of the film is all, as you
say, in the can at once. The whole film
is there. The projectionist can look at
the film backwards, can look at the film
frontwards, can start in the middle and
go in both directions. So, the
projectionist point of view, it doesn't
matter because all the frames are laid
out in front of the projectionist all
simultaneously. But for the beings, the
characters inhabiting the frames of the
film, they only perceive the story one
frame at a time in a particular linear
direction. This is the analogy of
physical reality and non-physical
reality. Non-physical reality where you
exist as a total being has the point of
view of the projectionist. When you
project an aspect of your consciousness
into physical reality, it is like
becoming one of the characters in the
film who can only understand the story
one frame at a time. Understand? Okay.
So, the projectionist knows that not
only all these frames are going on at
the same time, but there are also many
other cans of film on the rack, many
other lines, many other dimensions.
Everything is there all at once. And you
can review at your leisure anyone in any
order you wish to. It is totally out of
sequence. You don't have to see anything
in any kind of sequence at all. But as
long as you are in the film to make
sense in that particular format, you
must run it in a particular way. Does
this make some sense? Yeah. Therefore,
we know that everything is simultaneous.
All the lives are there all at once. But
in terms of applying what we are talking
about in terms of events with you, we
apply the terminology to the film strip
itself because you are living in the
strip of film as the consciousness that
is now talking to us in this way. We are
responding to the character in the film.
Okay. Understand? Okay. Does this make
sense? Yes. All right. Has that laid the
foundation for your specific question?
Yes. All right. Um, in 1961 when I
graduated college, a group of us had the
same job there. There were about 750 of
us that had the job, but about 15 of us
or so have still kept in contact. Oh,
right. We have um we have a reunion
every year and keep in contact
throughout the year. I sense that I have
known these people or that we've known
each other or know each other on a
different plane somehow. Could you give
me some information or details on this?
Well, there are many ways to understand
this idea. First of all, it is a general
given not always but generally that any
individuals you are very close to
emotionally in any way, shape or form in
one life, you have in all probable
reality had many other lives with to
begin with. That has laid a foundation
of familiarity and camaraderie as you
say between you. Secondly, not only are
you active in physical reality, but many
of you, not all of you, but many of you
are active in non-physical reality in
what you call dream states. You're all,
let's say, of a particular club that
likes to do similar things in
non-physical reality. And therefore, you
are participating at similar jobs in
your dream state as well as in your
physical state. And that creates even
more
familiarity with you into the physical
state as well. and carry on with the
momentum that is generated in the
non-physical state. Understand? Does
this assist you? Uh yeah. Can you give
me any specific details on where we've
been together before?
First, we will ask you is there any
areas that you are more attracted to
than any other? I
I
no. You mean on the planet? Yes.
time as you say, history as you say. Are
there any other lifetime, any other epic
or era in your history that you are more
attracted to than any other? The
attraction and the curiosity that any of
you feel for any particular era or epic
in your history is usually an indication
that you have had very strong lives in
that time track or you would not be so
attracted to it. I know there's it's
nothing that I know of history. It's it
feels much more futuristic than it does.
number. What's that?
It's on the board. Is that right? Mhm.
Yeah. It's like 5296 or something like
that. Is that what it is? I can tell you
here in two seconds.
It's uh 2693.
uh 2693.
What was I off? Mhm.
Unless they changed
it. Unless they changed it, which is
always possible. [Music]
that I know of history is it feels much
more futuristic than it does all right
it doesn't feel like history as I know
it on the planet All right. Future
history then. I guess so. All right.
With your imagination, do you have what
you would call a scenario of how you
might be working together in your future
that excites you?
Doesn't particularly excite me. It's
just it's just something that I I kind
of have a sense for feeling of. I I
don't I don't know what it is, though.
Are there no pictures you can give to
Well, there's like silver and there's um
forms that aren't quite like these
forms, but yet they have arms and legs
and Yes. and there's still of harmony.
Stop. Thank you.
What you are doing basically is tapping
into other dimensional realms that are
functioning to some degree as guides.
For many of you, you are recognizing
your portion of consciousness that is
connected into them and you are
recognizing that portion of your
consciousness reflected back to you
through them. They are on another
dimensional plane. They are associated
with all of you in certain ways and are
representative to some degree of being,
shall we say, the overseers of some of
the ideas that you and your group chose
to act out in your physical reality at
this time. Okay. So in a sense what you
are tapping into is now I understand
this can once again be somewhat
confusing in terms of linear time but
let me put it this way. You are tapping
into what appears to be a future
recognition in another dimensional
plane in a sense what could be
colloquially called an origin point for
all of you.
However, in understanding that that can
be regarded as an origin point, then
what you are looking at is this. Let's
say you have an existence there and you
decide while you are there that some
assistance can be given to a particular
world earth going through a particular
transformation in what would amount to
be your path.
So you decide from that point there as a
group to project yourselves into the
past and create a series of lines that
would be of assistance in helping the
transformations on your planet and
eventually would lead back to that
future time where you would once again
meet yourself in a sense understand
completing the loop. So in that sense
what you are doing is heading home so to
speak and you are seeing the references
of the individuals that are there that
represent your
guide as you are immersed in the
physical reality you have chosen to
assist. They continue on the
non-physical level to remind you who you
are, what you're all about, what choices
you have made, so that you will remain
relatively focused on the path you
originally chose simply because
immersing yourself to this degree in
this type of physical reality can make
it seem as if it is easy to divert from
your original intention. So they
function as a beacon to some degree to
keep you squarely on that track. You
understand? Yes. Does this assist you?
Yes. Well, thank you very much. Thank
you. Sh.
Hello, Bashar. And you good day.
I have a personal question here. Oh, all
right. Okay. August 1st and 2nd, I
attended a channel intensive workshop.
One moment. Can you all hear this
individual sufficient? Speak up so that
all may share also for the for the
attention. Okay. I August 1st and
second. Yes. of 87 mystery. I attended a
workshop uh channeling intensive and uh two days
uh channeling intensive and uh two days
after the workshop I was perceiving
beings of light and uh I like to know if
you can help me uh give me some
information on exactly what was going
on. Well, understand that anytime you
Well, understand that anytime you
accelerate yourself, you increase your
sensitivity to the electromagnetic
energy around you. Because different
beings on different levels are simply
energy like you are but more highly
accelerated. When you increase your
sensitivity, then you can more easily
perceive those other beings. They become
more solid to you because in a sense you
are matching their frequency. You are
existing more equally with them on the
same type of energy level. So when you
begin to match their frequency by having
accelerated yourself through the
processes you went through. Then your
senses are now able to receive their
imagery. You are able to see more things
that you could not see before. What was
invisible to you before now becomes more
visible because you are more highly
sensitized to higher vibrations of
light. You understand that? I
understand. So that answer the question
sufficiently. Uh they were more or less
what you would call guides.
Okay. Was one of them a guy that I
became aware of that went by the name of
Horus? Yes, to some degree. Okay. One
aspect of vast consciousness, not the
total aspect, but one aspect. Right.
Okay. When I'm
Yes. If I'm creating my reality totally
100%. Yes. Period. Okay, that means I'm
I'm uh I'm creating what this person is
communicating to me. Basically, you are
creating, shall we say, if this will
clarify the issue, your version of what
is being communicated from that other
consciousness. So, I can't change the
communication if I wish. Oh, absolutely.
You will always be able to hear exactly
what you really want to hear.
But does
this it just seems to me that this
individual is is an illusion and is not
there. Is there a being there? There is
a being. There is a consciousness and
yet at the same time everything you
create is your projection. It's your
creation. It's your version of anything
else. Understand this. We recognize that
there is in your terms confusion on this
point in your society. But the only
reason there is a lot of confusion is
because your society has been taught
that something must be either this or
that. One or the other. It's
both. It's this and that. It is that you
are creating it utterly totally
completely fabricating every iota and
that there is another being
communicating with you. It is both
because there is always both polarities
expressed in physical reality. It's
always both. I understand. So if this
delusion that I'm creating is real is
real. Would it have an impact on me?
Absolutely. Okay. Let's say if it's
sick, there's something wrong with it. I
want to change it. Can I? Yes.
Thank you. Why not?
Thank you. Okay.
Now remember this just as an addendum.
You cannot change anyone else's reality,
but you can always change the way you
create their reality in your reality.
Understand? No. All right. Let us back
up for a moment. Now, you cannot force a
change in someone else's reality against
their choices. You can attract
individuals into your reality who may by
allowing themselves to be attracted into
your reality match your desires closely
with their desires and cocreate a
similar change. But the idea is is that
while there may be levels in which you
can temporarily cause a suspension of
certain ideas or a change of certain
ideas in their reality, if they really
do not want that reality to maintain,
they always have the power to turn their
reality back into anything else they
want it to be. However, because you are
also creating your own reality utterly,
you can always in your reality perceive
them the way you desire to perceive them
regardless of the way they choose to
perceive themselves. So, if this
person's sick, Yeah. and they're sitting
there dying, I can perceive them as
being well and walking around doing by
perceiving them that way. Now, you do
not have to ignore what they are
choosing to go through, right? We are
not saying that you quote unquote
override what they are obviously
radiating as a message in terms of the
state they have chosen to be in. But if
you see them as strong, if you see them
as well, if you see them the way you
prefer to see them, then what you're
doing is sending them a message that
they have an opportunity to match the
frequency you are sending. And if they
want to be well, they can accept that
frequency and transform themselves.
Remember, no healer directly heals
anyone else. You send a frequency, you
send an idea, you send a suggestion, you
send a conducive atmosphere that shows
them how they can change if they choose
to. If they accept the idea of the
frequency you are sending them, then
they can match that frequency, the
perception you have of them as well and
strong. And they can then in matching
that frequency become well and strong.
But they can also refuse to match that
frequency. It's up to them as well in
the co-creation. Do remember this. There
is also to begin with a reason on your
part why you would also attract someone
in your reality that is sending you
signals of that nature. I understand.
Okay. So you can in that sense recognize
that it always serves in both
directions. Perhaps if you are willing
to be a reflective person and allow them
to know that you believe in their
strength and that they can transform any
negativity into a positivity, then you
are giving them an opportunity to decide
to change their reality, but only if
they want to. You can take it to the
point, you can take it to the point
where you regardless of what they choose
can only see them as being well. But if
you also know on what you may call a sub
or unconscious level that what you're
doing is simply totally unlocking from
their reality and creating only the
version of them you really want to see
regardless of what they're choosing then
you are not actually quote unquote
interacting with them anymore.
That was beautiful. Understand?
Understand? So because you are quote
unquote all in this together, generally
speaking, you will respond to what the
other person has also chosen to create
more or less and find what you would
call a quote unquote balance or a
compromise between the two ideas to some
degree. Understand? I understand. Does
it help? Definitely. Well, thank you
very much. Thank you, sir.
I'm excited to be here with you. Oh, we
are always excited. Good day to you.
Thanks. Um, what you were discussing
with the other individual lead into what
I wanted to discuss regarding my
daughter, an eye problem. All right. Um,
an eye situation. An eye situation.
Okay. I've been um I believe in the
concept that I can heal my body or other
other people's bodies if I want to. And
what you were explaining with this this
person about uh them co-creating the
reality of her having an eye problem.
Um, I've had difficulty of like
manifesting it just being well.
um if she's co-creating. But it's not
your eye, is it? No, it's not my eye. I
would like it to get better rather than
Well, all right. But then the way you go
about it is to first of all recognize
that that individual chose that
creation. Step number one. Yes. Remember
that you cannot change it if you don't
own it. So you have to own it first. So
you must recognize the reason for why
that individual would believe they would
have to choose that particular
manifestation. There's absolutely
nothing that says they have to, but if
they have, then allow you perhaps even
with your daughter to explore the
reasons for why it would be created that
way. Now, perhaps one of the easiest
ways to go about it, and your
imagination can come up with any other
way, if you find it easier, is to ask
yourself or to have her ask
herself, what am I learning about myself
by having created this situation in the
way I've created it? When an individual
can glean the meaning they have given to
a circumstance and when they can allow
that meaning to be delivered in another
way and the lesson to be learned in
another way, then they do not
necessarily have to use a negative
carrier to get their attention.
Understand? In physiological terms, what
is the age range of your daughter? A
little six. All right. Then this is
sufficient for the child to begin to be
self-aware about the idea of creating
her own reality. You can assist now by
allowing your child to get in touch with
what does this idea
symbolize. Start simply explore all the
different things that could be
attributable to let's say formulating a
particular idea with that particular
sensory organ. In other words, you can
ask a series of questions. Well, you can
ask what is the daughter's name?
Jessica. Jessica. Jessica. You can say
Jessica. Is there something of what is the nature
Is there something of what is the nature
of what you call the eye situation?
Well, they won't both focus at the same
time on one particular object. The
muscle is is shorter or something. So,
she can look with one eye or the other,
but not both at the same time. Oh, all
right. So, say yes. Do you
Do you
prefer when you see things with one eye
more than another? Yes or no? Do you
have an eye that makes you that allows
you to feel more than the other eye that
you are perceiving what you really want
to perceive? Right or left, left or
right? See what the answer is. From
there you can go on to understand that
what this may simply be indicative
of. And this is now in certain ways very
common upon your planet. This
defocusing is to allow the individual to
perceive both polarities, both sides,
both points of view of a single issue.
Instead of being so rigidly locked on in
the way your society says you ought to
be focused to any particular idea or
reality. Sometimes individuals will
create a splitting of their vision and
defocusing in that way. So they can only
see it from one side or the other side
and not both at the same time because
they are literally within themselves
examining one side or the other side of
an issue and do not want to be locked
into seeing the idea that the society
do not want to be locked into seeing the
idea that the society says they should
see as the blended idea. They want a new
perspective, a fresh perspective from
two completely different directions so
they can in time learn to refocus in a
way that is more representative of the
new idea they choose to see. They choose
to blend the idea into not the old idea
that society says they ought to see that
they should see that they must see.
Understand? Yes.
Realize that a lot of
momentum in terms of what especially
many young children do early in their
lives and what they create early in
their lives. Many of that ideas of
momentum are to some degree carryover
from things that they were learning
about in other lives as well. And they
bring that momentum through in this
life. And they create and generate in
this physical reality whatever they need
as a tool, as a device, as a methodology
to allow them to really begin to explore
the thing they chose to explore in the
new life. It is not something that has
to be permanent. And there are many ways
in your terminology to alleviate it. But
the only fundamental way any of these
ideas will be alleviated is to allow the
situation to serve the purpose for which
it was designed. which in the first
analysis means it is up to you to begin
to trust that what's going on is going
on for a positive reason not a negative
one. Understand? Yes. Now as soon as you
begin to approach it knowing whether you
analytically understand what that reason
is or not but knowing in your heart that
there must be a positive reason for this
manifestation. And as soon as you
approach it that way, you will allow
yourself to have more capability of
having more
insight as to what the idea is for. You
will begin to look at it from different
points of view. You will begin to assign
different meanings to that particular
situation. Your imagination will spark
you with inspiration as to what it could
mean, what it could represent in your
daughter. Understand? Yes. So then in in
constantly sharing with her and and
accelerating her awareness possibly it
would be possible for her to at any time
heal herself. Oh absolutely. Rather than
a surgery wouldn't alleviate what she's
trying to learn then in this way. Oh it
can. Now any physiological act can be
I'm not saying it is not always but a
physiological act can be one of the ways
you could attract into your life to in
your turn quote unquote change the
situation. It is one of the ways you can
change physical reality. You don't have
to do it that way. However, what we are
simply saying is that more often than
not, when a particular situation has
served its purpose, it will no longer
hang around because nothing that no
longer has a reason to hang around ever
hangs around. As soon as you have used
the tool for the reason you designed the
tool, as soon as its purpose is through,
it cannot hang around one second longer.
That's why we all would suggest to each
and every one of you that as soon as you
are willing to own the situation, that
is when you can change it most quickly.
Because when you're willing to own it
and dive into why you would have created
it, then you're willing to get out of it
the information you need more quickly.
As soon as you get the information out
of it more quickly, it no longer serves
a purpose and it can change into
something else that much quicker.
So dive into it. Explore with curiosity
and fascination and allow yourself also
to
remember that you have chosen each other
to attract each other into your life.
And therefore you can learn whatever it
is you need to learn about yourself by
her having chosen that particular
situation as well. There's always a
reflection for you in that as well as a
reflection for her. Understand? Yes. and
your reactions to her situation are also
a reflection for
her. Understand? Uh not that part simply
that it is always as you say a two-way
street. You are always both learning
from each other. A situation is created.
Everyone sees how everyone reacts and
everyone learns more about themselves
and each other and how to serve each
other better. So she learns about my
concern for her. Yes. But she also
learns about your attitudes and your
belief systems and how you choose to
handle a
situation. [Music]
[Music]
Understand? Let me give you an example.
This was related to the channel by
someone on your own planet. Now you have
what you may call a discipline or a
methodology that is called on your
planet Christian science. Are you
somewhat familiar with the idea?
Now we are not in this discussion in any
way, shape or form condoning one
particular method over any other. They
are all vowed in that way as you
discover yourself. However, this simply
relates specifically to this particular
scenario. This individual in your
terminology was quote unquote brought up
to be what you call Christian scientists
and specifically within that particular
methodology was the idea that you heal
yourself. You do not avail yourself of
what you call the medical art. You
understand? Now, this belief system,
this true quote unquote faith and
knowledge was instilled upon the female
child by the mother. You have the power
to heal yourself. No big deal. Very
easy, very exciting. The child felt the
energy, felt the conviction that was
delivered by the mother. And therefore,
when the child injured herself, would
simply say, "All right, all right. Oh,
boy. I'm going to heal it. No problem. I
have that power. And in many cases did
so. Then on one particular day, the
child injured itself perhaps what you
might call a little more severely than
usual. Came to the mother boldly with
excitement. Mother, mother, look. In a
sense, another opportunity to heal
myself. Teach me how, mother. Teach me
how. Show me that this is the same as
everything else. That I do not have to
call it out as anything different. And
the mother responded that way. Yes. Yes.
No problem. No problem. Do not worry. It
is the same idea. You will be able to
heal it.
it.
Then when the mother did not know that
the child was
looking, the mother left through a
through a
doubt. Just a look. It wasn't even a
word. But the child glanced and saw that
the mother truly doubted that due to the
severity of the injury that the child
really would have been able to
heal. And from that look alone from that
day forward the child was never able to
heal herself. Not without the assistance of
herself. Not without the assistance of
the medical artist. You understand? A
single look of doubt completely
rearranged the child's belief system and
capability. So what your child sees from you, your
So what your child sees from you, your
conviction that this serves a positive
purpose, your unfl flagging faith in her
strength, in her creativity and in your
cocreation, seeing that reflection from
you is also what the child is looking
for. Understand?
Yes. Well, thank you very much. Thank
you. Share my love with everyone there.
Already done.
Shoot.
Well, I've recently been studying a um
subject called Avatar. Yes. And uh Oh,
and good day to you as well. Thank you.
I'm very excited about it because it
helps us to do what
uh somebody like you said about creating
our own. All right. There are many
tools, many methodologies. Whatever
works for you, use it. Whatever doesn't.
Okay. What I want to know is how much
impact uh is this uh avatar going to
have on the way the world. Did you just
hear what I said? I guess not. All
right. I'll repeat it in a new way for
the first time. She said to use it. I
said whatever works for you, use it.
Whatever doesn't. The things that you believe are
doesn't. The things that you believe are
aligned with your vibration will be the
things that work for you and have the
greatest impact. The things that are not
aligned with your frequency will have no
impact on you at all. So if you find
that you have attracted yourself to a
methodology, to an approach that you
believe is in line with the vibration
you are at any particular moment and it
works for you and you get your impact
and you create your results, then use
it. And in using it, you shine as a
living example for others to be able to
share similar ideas by seeing them
reflected from you and seeing for
themselves whether the idea works for
them or not. Every tool has an infinite
amount of impact on your entire world.
But not every tool is specifically
designed to hit and match the frequency
of every individual on your planet. At
least not yet. Because you have so many
different belief systems, so many
different frequencies of understanding
and levels of comprehension upon your
planet at this time, not every tool will
hit the mass consciousness in the same
way. So we simply say that the impact
any tool will have will be
absolutely indicative of the amount of
individuals that think in similar ways
to that tool, that are of the same or
similar vibrations to that tool, and the
reason that there are many tools. now
being created is because there are many
different individuals with different
belief systems who need different tools
to have the same
impact. Much of the information, much of
the basic scenario, much of the
foundational elements are the same in a
thousand and one different tools. It is
simply that different tools work in the
same way for different individuals. So
they're all having the same type of
impact even if it's not exactly the same
tool or the same methodology across the
board. If it works for you, use it. When
it no longer works for you, use what
does. Impact is only determined by
discovering what is of your vibration
and what works immediately for the
individual you happen to be at any given
moment. And when something stops working
for you, if it stops working for you,
that doesn't mean it's wrong. That
doesn't mean it has lost its ability. It
simply means you have changed. And now
perhaps you need either a a different
tool or b not so many tools anymore at
all. And that you are willing to rely on
yourself as the prime tool for that's
the ultimate goal, the end result of all
tools to render themselves obsolete.
Understand? Thank you very much. We are
in this
interaction to put ourselves out of a
job. That is our dearest desire to have there
That is our dearest desire to have there
come on your planet a day when you do
not need us at
all. And then on that day we will be
able to interact with you as
equals sharing together on the same
level. Understand? Yeah. So does that
answer the question sufficiently? Yeah.
You answer the next question I have. So
Oh, thank you. Thank you. You're
welcome.
Hello. Oh, and good day to you. I'm here
pretty much as a messenger myself. Oh,
all right. All of you are a messenger
from my husband Ren who got this uh
function started and then had to leave.
Yes. And he wanted me to say tell you
welcome and also that even though he is
halfway across the world, he is here
with you in spirit tonight. Absolutely.
And we are with him in spirit as well.
And I have one question I feel I'm not
sure that I can say it well but um I
have taken the same training not the
same training but I've taken this the
avatar training. Okay. And um I feel
like possibly you might be able to help
me
to apply this business of doing it
myself, of being what I am capable of
doing, but am not being it. Oh, all
right. Well, I will begin to assist you
by asking you why aren't you being it?
If I knew I would be. Oh, well. All
right. Let's try a little trick, shall
we? Good. Oh, thank you.
If you don't know, if you cannot find a
reason for why you're not being what you
say you want to be, then how about
stopping assuming there is a reason.
You've lost me. Oh, all right. I'll back
up. Actually, I think what I'm what I
was trying to say is yeah, I'm not being
able to as apply
the material as well as I feel like I
should be able to do it. Well, then let
me ask you another question. Okay. Can
you describe to me through your
imagination any kind of a scenario that
would indicate how you think you ought
to be applying it? In other words, what
would you have to be doing in order to
think that you are applying it in the
way you say you want to? Oh, that's
easy. Well, tell me that. Have to be
able to function as part of all that is
rather than as a a deep body. No, no,
no, no, no, no. I mean, mental mentally,
not no. Now
Now
understand the idea is a you have chosen
to be a physical being. Yes. Yes. Well
then there is a purpose in that as well
as all the other levels you also exist
upon. Being at one with all that is means
Being at one with all that is means
being at one with all that is on any
level you have chosen to be on and
expressing that oneness in the way that
is appropriate for the level you chose
to be on. There is absolutely nothing.
This is a great myth in your society.
absolutely nothing about physical
reality that has to be thought of as
less spiritual than non-physical
reality. The idea is not to run away
from physical reality and then you will
be more spiritual. Then you'll be more
at one with the universe. The idea is to
integrate everything you are into that
one understanding. Not deny any part of
it. The idea is to live as fully as you
can on every level you exist upon, not
deny the validity of a particular level,
thinking that another level is more
spiritual and more representative of the
idea of unity. That's exactly
contradictory. I I don't think that I
made that I got my point across more one
more time.
It's not a question of
not me being or living well on this
level, but it's simply that as the young
man who was sitting here before was
talking about helping his daughter to
correct her vision.
Um, I feel like I should be able to
handle this body. Yes. Well, yes. And
with this my training, I should be able
to do it very well. And I find like that
I have areas that I'm not that capable
in such as not being able to do it. You
what? You have some specific idea.
Handle physical problems that I've had.
Give me an example. Okay. I have problem
with the back of my head and neck. Back
of your head and neck. What kind of an
experience have you had or are you had
are you having it now? It's an old
injury. An old injury. All right. Are
you having that difficulty now? To some
degree. To some degree. Describe it.
Describe the difficulty. Pain. Tension.
Pain and tension. Tension and pain. All
right. Do you know what pain is?
Um, excuse me. I've heard that on one
of, but I don't remember. All right.
I'll remind you. It is resistance to
your natural self.
Right. It's not being relaxed. Well, in a
It's not being relaxed. Well, in a
sense, it is also about going with the
flow. Now, may I ask you another
question that you may have heard on some
of the other tapes? Certainly. All
right. Are you doing in your life the
thing that excites you the most?
I've had it on hold. I've been too busy. [Music]
[Music]
Are you being fatigious? No. No.
So what you have just said to me is that
you have put what excites you the most
on hold because you are too busy to live
who you are. Um I guess I've been trying
to handle other responsibilities.
Here's the point you are missing. When
you do the thing in your life with
integrity that excite you the most to
do, all the things that are truly the
responsibilities you need to take care
of in your life will automatically come
into your life to be taken care of in an
effortless way. Because when you do the
thing in your life that excite you the
most, you are being the most you you can
be. Because the things that excite you
the most excite you the most because
they represent who you really are in
your natural state. That's what
excitement tells you. That's what the
energy of excitement lets you know. When
you do and act upon the things in your
life that excite you the most, you are
in line and in alignment with the energy
that represents the path you chose to be
in this
life. So when you say you have put your
excitement on hold because you're too
busy, you're saying you're too busy to
be who you chose to be. That is
resistance. Of course there will be
tension. Of course there will be pain.
You're not being who you are. You're
resisting yourself by putting your
excitement on hold thinking that there
are more important things than the
living of the life you chose to
live because your society has taught
you. If you're not responsible in this
way, then you are not really living your
life properly. You cannot give in to the
properly. You cannot give in to the
things that excite you because you have
responsibilities first. But understand,
when you allow yourself to flow in the
direction of what excites you the most
with integrity, everything that truly is
integrity, everything that truly is
something you are responsible for doing
in your life will bring into your life
automatically a circumstance or an
opportunity that will allow you to take
care of that responsibility flawlessly,
effortlessly, abundantly, without a
second thought. You are working it backwards.
thought. You are working it backwards.
Understand? You are focusing on the
details and allowing your overriding
intention to be
subordinate. The details are subordinate
to your overriding
intention, not the other way around.
When you allow yourself to fulfill the
overriding intention, the overriding
representation of who and what you
really know you are by knowing what
excites you and acting on
that, all the details fall into place
automatically. They all take care of
themselves or they bring to your life a
opportunity that allows you to take care
of the detail in a very effortless way.
Life works flawlessly when you let it.
And the way you can allow it to do so is
by doing the thing it excites you the
most. You see a lot of you in your
lives, you say, "Oh
creation, give me a
sign. What is my mission? What is my
purpose in
life? Why am I
here?" You get a tap on the shoulder.
Hey, look over here. Here's something
very exciting. Don't bother me. I'm
looking for my purpose in
life. Hey, over here. Here's something
that'll be a lot of fun. Not
now. I'm busy trying to be responsible,
looking for the purpose in my
life. Excitement is the answer you have
always been waiting for. It is the
signal you get from the infinite
creation. Excitement is the physical
translation of the vibratory energy that
represents the path you chose to be in
this life. That's why something does
excite you more than something else
might because it's who you are. It's
what you can do most effortlessly. And I
understand I understand I
understand. Sometimes the things that
come into your life that seem to be the
most exciting things you could do don't
seem to have anything at all on the
surface to do with the things you have
been taught you should be doing. But if
it comes with the excitement, if it is
the most exciting thing that does come
into your life, if you act on it with
trust and faith and integrity and
conviction, everything you really need
to take care of will automatically be
taken care of. Whether it seems
connected or not is not the key. You
cannot tell by the way it looks on the
surface. You tell by the feeling of
excitement it brings. Understand? Yes, I
do. Thank you very much for sharing.
Well, thank you. When you give into that
flow, all tension ceases. Yes. All of
it. You recreate yourself literally a
new in the moment. You become a
completely new person.
And that means that as a completely new
person, you have changed your future and
your past. So you don't have any more
old injuries because you don't have the
same history
anymore. Literally, it depends on how you define
Literally, it depends on how you define
yourself in the present. Now one other
thing to lay a
foundation. Many of you in asking about
the idea what is my purpose? What is my
mission in
life? And then you discover a particular
thing. Understand technically
speaking that particular thing that you
may be doing, the particular thing you
may be acting out in your life is not
literally the purpose or the mission of
your life. It is the way you have chosen
to express the purpose or the mission of
your life. The purpose or the mission of
all of your lives is the same. To live
that life to the fullest you can because
you, even though you are reincarnational
being, you have never been this you
before. You will never be this you
again. The you are now only has one life
to live. So the purpose of that life is
to live it to the fullest. The way you
do that is by doing at any given moment
the thing that feels most correct to
you, the thing that excites you the most
in that sense. The thing that really
gives you the most
peace. The way you go about it, the
specific methodology, the way you go
about it in your physical life, that's
your method for expressing the purpose.
And that can vary from moment to moment
to moment. That's up to you. How you
want to express it is up to you.
Sometimes certain methodologies may seem
to be more harmoniously aligned with
allowing you to express the purpose of
your life, the full living of your life,
the full service that you can be to
others. But however you decide is the
most exciting way, is the most centering
and balancing way, do it. It will always
lead you to exactly what you need on
every single level to allow you to
continue to be the person you really
want to be.
Understand? Yes, I do. Does this assist
you? Yes, it does. Thank you very much.
And to you, good day.
Speak up so that all may share. Okay.
Um, I'm doing what in my life where I
feel me the most. Oh, all right. Thank
you very much. It also terrifies me the
most. Sometimes it will for many of you,
but that only implies a lack of trust.
Aha. Um I I I'm a singer and I do theater and
Um I I I'm a singer and I do theater and
I I teach. Oh. All right. Teach voice.
Oh, exciting. Um and I encounter a lot
of of fear. All right. Um what do you
learn by encountering that fear? What do
you learn about yourself?
God. God. All right. [Music]
[Music]
Well, I think uh that I that I've
learned as I'm feeling right now fear
that I'm afraid to be vulnerable. Oh,
well then do me a favor. All right.
Okay. Define
vulnerability. While you are pondering
that, I'll give you a few moments. All
right. Let me remind each and every one
of you and you as well that all the fear
you face in life, all the fear you
encounter in
life is never the product of the
situation itself. It is the product of
your definition of the
situation. So define vulnerability and
you'll understand why you're afraid.
What kind of a definition do you have of
vulnerability? It has to do with being
the victim. the victim. All right. A
victim. Yes. I'm exposed.
I'm open to attack.
I can be destroyed.
Oh, scary. All
right. I'll go along with you. When you
think of it that way, when that's your
definition of vulnerability. Yes, it's
very scary. I'm not surprised you are
afraid. Now, if you are willing to exercise your
Now, if you are willing to exercise your
imagination on the other, as you say,
side of the coin, give me a positive
definition of vulnerability.
To be an open channel. To be an open
channel. All right. Very good.
Now, in being an open channel, does that
mean that you are plugging into the
power of infinite creation? Yes. And
does that mean therefore that in
plugging into the power of infinite
creation you are supported by the flow
of infinite creation? And that therefore
you know you are absolutely eternal and
absolutely infinite. Yeah. All right.
Now out of the two definitions you have
given me which one do you prefer?
All right. All right.
Now we have established that you prefer
the positive definition of
vulnerability. Now if you are willing,
will you answer another question? Oh,
thank you so much.
What definition of reality do you have that
definition of reality do you have that
would allow you to believe that it is
not simply a matter of knowing you have
made a positive choice and leaving it at
that? What definition do you carry
within you that says it is not simple to
know that you don't have to worry about
the negative definition because that's
not the definition of reality you
prefer? What definition do you have that
makes it difficult to
realize that you can simply have the
life you want because you say
so? What makes you think that the
negative definition is more likely to
occur than the positive one?
What definition of life do you have that
makes it seem as if the positive
definition is too good to be true?
You don't have to answer me now, but the
idea simply is always, always, always
when you determine what the definition
is of the life you prefer to have and
there still seems to be something that
quote unquote prevents you from having
the positive manifestation, then realize
you can always backtrack to another
definition that prevents you from
realizing that it is simply a matter of
choosing what you want and that that
will stick. Okay? because you say so.
You don't need another reason. Okay? If
you say this is what I choose, then
that's what will happen. Now, here is
the key. When you make your choice, then you
key. When you make your choice, then you
say, "All right, I prefer the positive
definition." Then when circumstances arise in your
Then when circumstances arise in your
life that you haven't crafted, if you
know you have chosen the positive
definition, don't act as if you
haven't. Don't fall back to the negative
definition. Don't say when something
happens in your life, oh no, no, no, no.
That's wrong. How did that happen? That
doesn't fit. Going back to trust all
always. But understand something and
this is where many of you have a little
bit of
misunderstanding. We are not talking
about trust as if you only use trust to
create positive things in your
life. You have all every single one of
you without
exception you have all always used
infinite [Music]
exception. You have all always used
infinite trust in everything you have
created. This is the matter of whether
you trust in positive or negative more
strongly. So, we're not talking about using trust
So, we're not talking about using trust
as if that's something new. Oh, no.
Trust. Now, I got to learn to use trust.
Oh, no. That's
difficult. No, it is not something
you're not familiar with. You've always
used trust. It is the mechanism by which
you create all the reality you
experience. It's simply a matter of what
you feed into the trust. Negative
definitions in, negative reality out.
Positive definitions in, positive
reality out. And there is no other way
to experience that. What you put out is
what you get back. That's it. That's the
way the universe is constructed.
So allow yourself to understand. And
when we say use trust, all we're
actually saying is use the same trust
you've always used to the same degree
you've always used it, but feed it with
a positive definition and know beyond a
shadow of a doubt that it will therefore
respond in the same way it always had.
It will give you back what you have
given it. Understand? And that's why you
can understand that when you make a
decision to be a positive
person, nothing else has a mind of its
own. It will not change against your
will. It can't. It can't say let's mess
with her.
She utterly believes in herself as a
positive being and utterly believes she
will have a positive manifestation.
Let's fool
her. It can't do that unless you give it
the power to play that game in your own
selfcreated unconscious
mind. But you create that with a belief.
You say, "Go ahead, fool me.
I give you power to sneak up on me and
change my mind. But that's a game you're
playing all of you because you have been
taught that you have an unconscious
mind. You
don't. You are a conscious
being. Even if you are using 90% of your
consciousness to make yourself believe
you're only using 10, you're still using
it all to play the game.
You're always a 100% conscious being.
Even when it seems like you're out of
control, you're controlling the creation
of that situation. It's up to you to
understand that you're always in
control. So once you know the choice you have
So once you know the choice you have
made then when certain circumstances
arise in your life just because they may
look the same as the circumstances that
before you would have labeled negative
don't label them negative anymore just
because they look the same appearance on
the surface means nothing. Situations do
not have builtin meaning. They are
empty, neutral, blank. You fill them up
with the meaning you believe in most
strongly. The meaning you fill them up
with is the effect you get out of them.
So when something happens in your life,
don't become the old you and say, "Oh,
this has no business being in my life."
Say, "I know I am a new person. I know I
have chosen to be a positive person.
Therefore, no matter what this looks
like, I know it's happening for a
positive reason." Look for the positive
meaning. Give it a positive meaning.
You'll get a positive effect. Even if
yes, even
if another individual who comes into
your life actually has a consciously negative
life actually has a consciously negative
intention toward you, if you have
attracted it into your life, you are
only going to get a positive result out
of
it. Because if you know you're operating
in a positive frequency, that's the only
effect you can have in your life. It is
not physically,
physically,
mechanically possible to have an effect
that you are not the vibration
of. Understand? Yeah, I think so. Does
this assist you? Yes. Are you sure?
Well, I'm sure when I listen back it
will when you listen back. I mean,
all right. I understand what you mean.
But do remember this as well. You do not
need me to create the interaction
between us. You are creating this interaction on
us. You are creating this interaction on
your end by
yourself. Anytime you feel the need to
feel the vibration of this interaction
again, create it whenever you wish. You
will tap into the level of energy that
you think we represent. But what you
will be doing is tapping into your own
version of the same level we exist upon.
And you will be having the dialogue with
yourself, which is in a sense what
you're doing right now anyway.
Does that assist you? Well, thank you
very excite me. Oh, all right. You go
right ahead. All right. I'll pay you
wrapped attention.
Um actually the the first thing that I
just wanted to do was thank you very
much for um awareing me that that I can
do what excites me and be supported by
it. You know, I I really love playing
music and I love traveling. So I I've
decided that um I'm going to be uh
supported for playing music and
traveling. Little Mr. Minister. Yeah. Um
and secondly, I wanted to talk about
something else that excites me very much
that that I have some recall of but um
not of this life since we don't have
that technology and that is flying in
spaceships, right? And I was um
wondering especially since you had
talked about some beings that will be in
that are incarnating now that are from a
quote different culture that is uh have
having some connection with our tourists
if they will be helping to bring some of
that technology out. Although do
remember that none of you are original
to your planet anyway. Right. Right. Um
but yet they will forget less and
remember more. Can we maybe expect some
of that technology to be coming through
in the the coming decades? Uh oh yes.
But do not wait for them to do it. If
you are interested in that idea, explore
it from your own point of view. For do
understand that everything is a matter
of vibration. Traveling in space is
traveling within. And much of the idea
of the quote unquote technology of our
spacecraft is very much connected to the
idea of harmonic
Uhhuh. musician. Yeah.
All right, I will do that. I've uh I
have a great appreciation for the
healing aspect of music and that's a
thing that I'm interested in. Um the
reason it's healed is because you kind
of create harmonics that are
representative of the primal flow of
existence. And when individuals are
exposed to that particular bubble or
atmosphere or vibratory frequency, they
can learn to match it. As they match it,
they then blend in and balance with the
prime harmonic of creation. And in that
state, no disease of any type can exist.
Well, that's great. I thank you very
much for the chance to interact with
you. You ready?
You ready?
Would you all like a short break or
would you like to continue?
We will allow you a short break to
decide what you want.
We will resume contact in approximately
10 of your minutes. [Music] That's not
Oh, say what did you all decide? Shall
we take a break or continue?
All right, we shall continue.
Hello, Michelle. Have a good day. Now, I
just want to say that I do believe that
we create our own reality. Oh, thank you
very much. Now, what about taking
anything that I'm doing and deciding
that that's what excites me the most?
Can I create that? Oh, yes. At any given
moment, you can understand that whatever
it is that's going on in your life right
now is the most important thing of all
or something else would be happening.
So, you can get excited about that.
First of all, being excited about what's
going on in your life at this very
moment means you are willing to be aware
that what is going on is what needs to
be going on because it serves you. Even
if what is going on in your life right
now is something that you will decide to
change. Knowing that it is the most
exciting thing right now, knowing that
it is what belongs in your life right
now means you're going to get the most
out of it. and getting the most out of
it is what's going to give you the
ability to know how to change it most
quickly and most easily into what you
prefer it to be. So even if you are
creating something right now that you
don't really prefer in your life, by
diving into it and living in it in the
moment, in the present, you will then
extract from it the knowledge and
information you need to be able to
transform it into what you really prefer
it to be more quickly than if you deny
that what's going on in your life right
now has no business being there.
You can be excited about being in the
moment about everything that's in your
life and at the same time you can simply
ask yourself at any given moment out of
all the things I could be doing out of
all the things I could be acting on
right now what is the most exciting
thing I could be doing with integrity do
it if something comes up do it moment to
moment to moment even if you have an
idea in your mind of some particular
shall we say or object that is really
the most exciting thing you can think of
to do. If you don't immediately see a
way to do it, if you don't immediately
see an avenue that would allow you to
act on it, then the same answer is the
key. Act upon whatever you are capable
of acting on with full integrity and
full excitement right now. And it will
lead you into the circumstances to give
you the ability to be able to act upon
the other thing that excited you that
you couldn't act on before because all
excitement is a thread and it leads to
all other excitement and it always
expands and it always grows in more and
more exciting ways. You follow it? Yeah.
Does that answer the question
sufficiently? Oh yeah. Oh, thank you
very much. I have one other question. Oh
all right. I hear voices when me
too all the time. Well, they don't have
they're not coming from
bodies in my mind. And what's the
difference? I don't know. I'd like to
find out. Oh, thank you. There really
isn't one. There isn't any difference.
The idea of as you say hearing voices as
you mean it anyway as you perceive you
mean it is analogous to what we were
talking about earlier to another
individual that is seeing things that
aren't there. You have increased like many of
there. You have increased like many of
you sensitivity to different vibratory
states of existence which means you will
be able to see and hear things you could
not see and hear before. You are now
being more aware not only of being more
in communication to other levels of
consciousness, but you are more aware of
being more in communication with other
levels of your own consciousness. You
are hearing your internal dialogue to
different levels you did not know you
had. You are allowing yourself to come
together by discussing with yourself who
you really want to be. And you are
sensitive to other guides and other
dimensions of consciousness that are in
that sense whispering suggestions to you
about things you could choose to be. But
the choice is up to you about what you
pay attention to. Understand? Yeah. This
is something that is far more common now
upon your planet than it ever has been.
But it has always existed. There's
always been some individuals with some
degree of sensitivity to understand you
can hear other levels of consciousness
even if they are not physical. All you
have to do is listen in the proper way.
That's all. The only reason in fact that
most of you have not been able to hear
those other things is because you have
filtered them out. Do understand one
very important thing.
Many of you have been taught to believe
that your physical
senses are windows and doorways through which
are windows and doorways through which
information floods and pours
through. Not
really. Your senses are actually more
filters than windows. They keep out
99.9% of the reality around you and
allow you to only perceive what your
belief system says you ought to be
perceiving. Your senses are not really
perceivers as much as they are
filters. So now that you are dropping
some of the old definitions of what you
ought to and ought not to be perceiving,
your filters are filtering out less. So
you are aware of more communication and
information that is going on around you
in many different levels. You
understand? This is something that is
coming far more common upon your planet
now. Okay. Thank you. Oh, thank you very
Okay. Thank you. Oh, thank you very
much. And do remember it is almost in
all cases the very same thing. The
voices you are hitting the quote unquote
I use the term very loosely imaginary
friends many of you have as children.
that are very real.
Yeah. Does this help you? Yeah. Oh,
well,
hello. Why do you say that? Um, I'm
here. Yes, you are.
Um because uh I have a great interest in
channeling because I began to channel
myself. All right. Some months ago. All
right. And so I not only bring myself
here, but I also bring my channel. You
are technically speaking the channel.
This is so I am bringing the one from my
channel. Thank you. Whose name he says
that we may call him Amorita. Oh, what?
And he sends you his greetings. Always
always returned and reflected. Yes,
indeed. Um my question to you has to do with the
Um my question to you has to do with the
fact that I myself am a healer and a
teacher in my own right and I um heal
and teach by awakening the ability to
heal themselves and teach themselves.
Yes indeed. And I find that I'm also
actively involved in this partnership
with this channel and we have uh similar
goals which is we wish to assist as many
humans as possible with becoming of
course because these things are always
made by agreement on both sides. Yes
indeed. What I want to know is do you
have anything to say to me as a channel
as a channeler um who is involved in my
own work as well as in this project. Uh
do you have any words of assistance or
guidance? only that you trust that the
more unconditionally you love and the
more willing you are to be of service in
that way, the more you will be served
and the more you will expand in all the
ways you exactly and precisely need to
act as the channeler. Don't forget you
have a life of your own as well. And
always know that no consciousness and no
entity will ever ever ever ever
ever expect that you should serve at the
expense of yourself. Yes indeed I'm
aware of these things and you do mention
love um part of my focus in my work the
heart of my work is unconditional love
and the message that I'm brings is
universal love of course and so this is
something that we resonate with
together. Can you can you give me any um
practical advice for how to continue to
develop my own life and my own work as
well as to bring through what it is that
Marita has to do here as fully as
possible? Well, you can
perhaps pay attention to what is said
through you and follow it. Ah, and
follow it. I do pay attention to this.
Do you follow it? Uh, not always. All
right. Remember that you are a physical being
Remember that you are a physical being
or have chosen to be in a physical
world. Physical action is the key. Yes.
How can I best motivate myself to
physical action?
If you truly believe that your physical
action would really bring you the
ecstasy you desired, what other
motivation would you need?
Understand? Yes, indeed. Is that
sufficient? I guess it is. Thank you
very much. Our unconditional love to you
and your willingness to be of service
and perhaps simply for all of you.
Remember again the basic definition of
any channeling is simply doing what you
really love to do. That's all it is. Any
creative expression that is performed
without doubt, without worry, in
complete positive trust.
This is my experience. Thank you for
reflecting that light and being willing
to be an obvious mirror. You're most
welcome. Thank you.
Shame. Oh. Oh, one moment. One moment.
Yes. Are you paying attention to your
dream life as well?
To a certain extent I am. Do you have
any practical suggestions for how I can
do that more or do that more clearly? Do
you have a particular, shall we say,
chord or harmonic that you could either
play and or hum to yourself that
vibrates and resonates within you in a
particularly pleasing way?
Then when you are laying down to rest
for the next, shall we say at least
three nights of your time, resonate this
harmonic to yourself, quote unquote,
lull yourself into the dream state and
see if you have not opened up a few more
doorways through which some information
can come that would be of benefit to
you. Wonderful. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Sh.
Good evening, sir. I do you good day and
I want to thank you very much. This is
certainly an exciting evening for me.
All right, speak up so that all may
share your excitement.
It's about Make them believe you are
excited.
My specific concern is about a lump
that's been growing on my hand for the
last oh year and a half or two. A lump.
A to be a lump. A lump. Yes. And I'm
concerned. I didn't want a medical
solution if I could handle it without a
medical. Did you in your terminology get
what you would call a medical diagnosis?
No. All right. Why not? I didn't want to
hear that I'd have to have surgery. Oh,
all right. Why do you not want to hear
that idea? Not that it necessarily must
play out that way, but why would you not
want to hear the idea?
I feel like I should do it. Oh, why?
Just because you hear it, why does that
mean you should do
it? While you are pondering that, allow
us to continue. You see, the idea is to
simply recognize that as a being in the
society in which you live, you may have
many ingrained belief systems that are
stronger than other belief systems. And
at least if you give yourself the
opportunity to follow what may be the
strongest belief system within you now
you can at least show yourself what
following that belief system will
reflect back to you for you to deal with
in terms of information. Then you can
decide how you will handle what your
ingrained belief system has already told
you. Then you can decide to change that
belief system. Now let me ask you this.
Therefore, in what you may call a very
candid way, be
honest. Do you think it is actually more
likely that the circumstance can be
transformed through physiological
surgery or through your own mentality? Hesitation.
mentality? Hesitation.
Be honest. I think that's where that's
where I got stuck. No. All right. Are
you saying that you believe that it is
of a greater likelihood that it can be
handled physically instead of what you
call mentally?
Well, I believe it could be removed
physically. Yes. No doubt about that.
But whether that would be the end of it,
that's what Oh, whether that would be
the end. I don't know what's inside.
Don't know what's inside. All
right. What's inside you?
What are your aspirations and your
dreams and your desires? What's inside
you? Are you at any time ever afraid to
find out what's inside
you? I didn't say that. Oh, all right.
I'm not suggesting that you are. I'm
just asking you a question.
Now, do you believe or
not that there might be things that
could be in your terminology lurking
inside you that could surprise you in
negative way?
In the love. Yes. In the love. All
right. Then perhaps shall we look at it
this way? Let's assume that there were
doubts within you at one time spread
throughout. Let's assume that you decided, "All
Let's assume that you decided, "All
right, well, I'd like to get all of
these doubts front and center where I
can see them all at
once. How about if I coales them into a
lump? How do I bring them all to the
forefront right in front of my vision
all the time? I will know by having
created that concentrated symbol that
they will not be running around
half-hazardly within me, but will always
be what I have my eye
on. Now, now, now, now. All right, there
they all are. All the doubts, all the
uncertainty in that one concentrated
place. out. Now that they're all there, how to
out. Now that they're all there, how to
transform them completely quote unquote
out of my reality?
Well, with your imagination, here is our
suggestion. with your imagination in
what you would call relaxed, open
breathing fully state of meditative
bliss. Dive into that lump with your
imagination. Probe it, examine it, x-ray
it with your imagination. Discover what
ideas or doubts might be represented by
that concentration.
Examine them one at a time. Let them
come up. Examine it. Deal with it.
Integrate it. Transform it. The next
one, the next one, the next one, and the
next one until you diminish the lump by
having examined all the reasons, all the
concentrated reasons for why it would
exist. When you have done that, you will
be deflating it, melting it, dissolving
the whole idea. Understand?
Now, if in any of those examinations you
discover that the strongest belief that
sticks with you is the idea that it is
far more easily physically taken care of
than in your terms energetically taken
care of, then trust your belief system.
As we have said, there is nothing wrong
with acting in a physical way. It is
just as valid as anything else. Do not
think yourself the poorer person because
you cannot handle it
metaphysically. Physical reality is just
as
spiritual. Yes, you are learning to
transform. Yes, you are learning that
you create your own reality. Yes, you
are learning to change things with your
awareness alone. But if you in all
honesty and your self-examination
discover that the strongest beliefs
within you still are ones that are
physically rooted, then follow them.
That is the path of least resistance.
And doing that, acknowledging that that
might be your strongest belief is
actually going with the flow of your
strongest awareness. That's truly being
honest with your belief system and
working with it, not against it.
But paradoxically, sometimes you will find
paradoxically, sometimes you will find
that simply by owning up to what you
have feared might be your strongest
belief will be in and of itself enough
to create an instantaneous
transformation. Just the owning up.
Understand? Just the facing of what you
fear to find in that revelation of
concentrated dust. Examine it. Be your
own x-ray machine. Explore and explore
and you can dissolve it. But at any
moment be honest with yourself about
your strongest belief. Own up to it and
that will cause the greatest
change. Understand the balance is change. Yes.
Understand the balance is change. Yes.
Remember this as well. And again not
meaning to say this in order to force
you to think that physical reality
somehow is something you should run away
from. But remember, physical reality is
only what you dream it to be. You are
dreaming right
now. Literally, you're all having a dream
Literally, you're all having a dream
right
now. And dream reality is
real. Physical reality, dream reality
are different aspects of the same one
existence that you are.
What you are learning to do in this
transformational age is cease to have as
much differentiation between the idea,
the notion, the definition of physical
reality, nonphysical reality.
As soon as you
dissolve that definitional
barrier, then you will begin to find
that just as you can do in your dream
reality, anything at all can be manifest
in your physical reality because it is
only a dream. The only
difference between what you call your
physical reality, your dream reality is
that the physical dream contains a
definition of
solidity. And your dream reality doesn't
have to. But your physical reality
doesn't have to
either. Understand? I do. Does this
assist you? Yes, it does. Well, thank
you. I'm a pleasant brew. Thank you.
There will also be some other assistance
given to you. Thank you. I have nothing
to do with it.
Hello. Hey, good day.
Can you tell me how I might have more
friends all the time?
all the time?
More fun all the time?
Yes.
Yes, I can. Oh, good. Of course, it's up
to you as to whether or not you create
it. I'm trying, but it works the
opposite. Trying. Don't try. Trying isn't doing
Trying. Don't try. Trying isn't doing
it. I try every day. Why try? I just
said don't
try. If you try, you're not doing. If
you do, you don't have to try. Trying is
not the doing of the thing. And all the
trying that you do is only the doing of
trying and not the doing of the thing
you say you want to do. Now, you have
heard in the conversations we have had
with other individuals, one of the
primary questions we ask many of you.
Are you at every given moment doing the
thing that excites you the most to do or
not? No. Why not? Never. Why have all
these responsibilities?
More responsibilities.
You got to be rich to do what I'm going
I beg your pardon. I need to be rich. I
beg your pardon. Rich. I beg your
pardon. You see, I am becoming more selectively
You see, I am becoming more selectively
third density deaf.
I can no longer hear things that are
simply definitions that are not a part
of my reality.
Define rich.
Let's see. A lot of cash. A lot of
cash. Why is that your definition of
being rich?
Because I will give you a little bit of
a hint.
Define abundance.
That's it.
Why? Well, because you have been taught that
Well, because you have been taught that
that's what it is.
Well, because if I had it, if I
you know, wanted to travel, do all these
interesting, fun things. Yes. I could
just do them with my family. Yes. May I
ask you a question? Yes. You're sure?
Well, thank you. Want to be sure it's
all right for me to ask you a
question? Do you know, are you aware on
any level of any individual in any
circumstances anywhere on your planet
that travels without without having a
lot of money to do so.
Oh, sure. Oh, sure. Who?
And why? And how do they do it? Well,
usually they have the time to do it. But
you're caught in the economics of making
all this abundance so that you can then
travel or you know, not just travel. I
mean, if you want to get up in the
morning and do your thing instead of
You're not answering my question.
Do you know of individuals that do the
type of traveling you say it would
expect you to do and don't need the
money to do it? No. You're not? No, I'm
not aware of them. Oh, all right. I'll
give you one suggestion. Okay. Now, I'm
not saying you have to do it this way,
but pay attention. There are individuals
that you call writers. Yes. Mhm. And
sometimes they are sent on what?
Assignments around the world.
They don't pay for a thing. They go
everywhere and are very excited about
it. They don't pay for a
thing. Now, that's one way. So, all
we're telling you is that if you're
aware that there is one way someone has
done it, there are other ways to do it.
Perhaps what is confusing you is the
following idea. That your definition of
abundance only means money.
I am not in any way, shape or form
invalidating money on your planet. It is
one of the way to represent abundance.
Only one. There are many ways to
represent abundance. Again, what may be confusing
abundance. Again, what may be confusing
is that you have not been given an
appropriate definition of the word
abundance. Would you like ours?
Are you sure? Uhhuh. Thank you. Just
checking. Abundance, as you say, stop
Abundance, as you say, stop
thought. The ability to do what you need
to do when you need to do it.
Period. Hey, he didn't say anything
about money in
there. He didn't say much of anything at
all in there. That's a very open
definition. Is that all there is to it?
What was that definition again, my sir?
Abundance. Not stop. The definition is
as follows. The
ability the
ability to do what you need to do when
you need to do it.
Period. Now, let me ask you another
question. I like asking
questions. Something I've learned from
all of you.
If someone were to come
along and say to you, you you know, I
have noticed that you do this particular
type of
thing. I need someone to do that
particular type of thing. And in
exchange for you doing that particular
type of
thing, I will support you in traveling
here and traveling there and traveling
there so that you can do your particular
type of thing here and there and
there. Doesn't that excite you? They
say, "Well, I want to travel on vacation. I
"Well, I want to travel on vacation. I
don't want to work. All
All
right, one more
time. First of
all, let's start at the beginning.
Do you have an
idea of a thing, a service, a creative
expression of any type? That is the most
exciting thing you can think of to do.
Yeah. What? Well, I like to create
things. Like what? I like to paint and
draw. Paint. Painting. Design. Nice.
These things you enjoy. Yeah.
Are these type of things the most
exciting type of things that you can
imagine doing? Is this the idea of the
expression of the pinnacle of your
creative ability?
Yeah. I mean, I would rather have that
kind of career than the ones I'm doing.
Thank you.
Therefore, if you were doing that type
of
work in some other place on your planet,
would it really seem like work or would
it really seem like a vacation?
Might seem like a vacation. Might seem
like a vacation. Work. Ah, yes, I
understand that. But you see, that's the
whole point. The only reason you are not
giving yourself an opportunity to expand
yourself in the way you say you desire
to is because you're not doing what
you're all about. Is because you are not
making your love your
career. Because you are like many
individuals on your planet have thinking
that you have to do this and you have to
do that before you can do what you
really are excited about doing. Not ever
having been taught that what really
excites you, if you do it with full
conviction, will support you in the
manner to which you wish to be
accustomed. Sounds good. Yes, it
Sounds good. Yes, it
does. And it works that simply. Are you
willing to believe it?
My husband probably wouldn't, but I
would. Could I ask you about him?
But you'll have his opinion.
So, can I ask you one other question?
Answer mine first. What was it? Are you
willing to believe it's that simple? Oh,
yes. Oh, all right. Thank you. What's
your question? On that spaceship, I
mean, can any of us or
There are appropriate timings to certain
things. Always in your dream reality.
Yes. I see flashing lights. Do you know
what that is? It will be different
things at different times. Sometimes
just an increased sensitivity to other
consciousness or other symbolic ideas
being created in your reality to refer
you to the fact that you are looking
through new doorways and seeing other
things. It will not always be a quote
unquote spacecraft as colloquially
called by your planet. I don't know what
it is. Sometimes it's so strong it just
It startles me. It's all right.
Allow you to feel like you want to do
when you experience it. I It feels like
I'll be thinking in a certain direction.
It feels like some kind of communication
or or it's like so striking. What type
of directions do you find that you're
usually thinking in when you have the
experience happen? Usually of people of
people in what way? somebody who that I
had an association with before.
All right. Sometimes I'll be thinking
about that person and and I'll have my
eyes closed and striking flashing
lights. All right. But wake me up. What
you are experiencing to some degree is
the electromagnetic interconnectedness
of all of your mass mentality. You are
recognizing your telempathic connection
to other individuals and you are seeing
in a sense the actual communication
identification vibration going on
between you. You are seeing the spark
that bridges the synaptic gap between
you and them. Can
they work is not always do they
interpret it in the same way. Not always
do they understand it physically.
sometimes will allow it to come out in
their dream state when they are more
relaxed as a consciousness.
Understand? But most importantly,
remember when something excites you more
than any other thing, it tells you three
things. One, it excites you because it
is most who you are. Two, because it is
most who you are. It is the thing you
will be able to do in life most
effortlessly. free because it is the thing you will be
free because it is the thing you will be
able to do in life most effortlessly. It
is the thing you will be able to do most
abundantly. And
remember, abundance simply means you
will have the ability to really do what
you need to do when you need to do it in
the way that represents the
level, the degree you are being the idea
you prefer to be. If you are excited
about being an artist that doesn't
really need to expand any further than
your own backyard, that's where you'll
be. If however you are very excited
about being an artist on the level where
you want impact and you want
communication and you want dispersement
of the idea of the vibration of your
sharing and your artistry and your
creativity, then that level of existence
will attract all the
opportunity coincidentally into your life. that will
coincidentally into your life. that will
allow you to go as you say hither and
thither and yawn without ever having to
plan to do so.
Let me give you an example very close to
home. The physical channel before
you understand that the physical channel
before you simply in taking up the love
of doing the channeling, the agreement
he has made with us to do these
channelings has traveled far more than
he ever thought possible within the
course of the last four years of his
life and has never planned to go
anywhere. Understand?
Understand?
Are you getting the picture? Yeah. It
automatically provides the conduit for
where you need to be to express the idea
on whatever level you're willing to
express it. The circumstances and
opportunities provide themselves and
present themselves in your life
automatically without even trying. The
details take care of themselves.
Thank you. You don't have to try. so
hard. Thank you. It is easiest to be who
you are. The only time you get tired and
the only time you have to sigh is to be
who you're not.
So relax all of you.
Hello. Hello. I wanted to ask you about
um having a man in my life. Um, are you
after me personally?
[Music] Um,
no. I I'm sorry. I don't know exactly
how to and I have a very good life, but I
to and I have a very good life, but I
would like to have a man in my life to
share it with. No, I need more. Yeah. Do
you need the relationship to be
complete? Sometimes I get very lonely. And I would
Sometimes I get very lonely. And I would
like stuff. Well,
I don't like cooking just for myself or
being home in the evenings by myself.
No, I do. Um, I'd like somebody to talk
to, someone to share my experiences
with. All right. And I I think a man
would be a very nice company.
And
um I I just would like to have one. Oh,
all right. But then why do you not
simply in that sense use their
sensitivity to attract yourselves to the
vibrational individual that you can then
simply walk up to and say, you know, I
would love to have a conversation in my
home tonight. Would you like to come
home and have a conversation?
Do you have fun or easy? But it's just
something I can do.
One more time. I said that sounds very
easy, but it's just not something I can
do. Oh, why? Um, well, first of all, I
haven't seen any men that I would like
to invite them to my house to have
conversation. Oh, I see.
Why not?
Uh, most of the men I come in contact
with are married. Are there too young or
too old? I don't meet any men that are my
old? I don't meet any men that are my
age that are single. Uh, not attached.
Not attached. Not attached to a female.
Uh, not spoken for. Um. Oh, I
understand. I'm
glad do understand that our civilization
has completely different definitions
about this idea. All right. Are
Are
you able to carry
on a comfortable and equal conversation
with the masculine half of yourself?
How do you feel about your own masculine
side? How do you feel about your own
feminine side? Um, always
I Are you comfortable with either of
those signs? Yes, I think so. Which with
with my female side? Are you comfortable
with your masculine side?
Um, probably not. Why not? What is the
definition of your masculine size?
I think probably um overbearing. Oh. Um,
demanding. Oh. And um controlling. Cool.
Is it any wonder you're not attracting a
reflection of that?
If that's your definition of the
masculine energy, why would you want to
attract that?
Um, well, up until now, I haven't wanted
to. Well, you got exactly what you
wanted then, didn't you? Yeah, change
the definitions of what your own
masculine energy is so you can attract
someone who is more reflective and
representative of your new definition
and it will be no problem at all
understand. Yeah. Is this helping you?
Always the first relationship is with
you and yourself in the polarities you
have created yourself to be. Be on equal
terms with the polarity of your own
being. clarify the definitions of what
the polarities of your own beings,
female and male, within you and that
will allow you to determine what
reflections and representations you
attract into your life at what
particular timings you attract them.
Understand? Yes, it does. Now not that
this immediately necessarily applies
exactly to you but just because you have
touched upon the subject let us lay
another foundation for some other
individuals who may be wondering about
this idea. Many of you have talked about
oh what you call you know
soulmates. When am I going to find my
soulmate? Where is
he? I know that if I could only find my
soulmate that ideal mate then everything
would be just wonderful. Until then, I
think I'll
vote. Life will not be complete without
the soulmate. Where or where is
she? But you see, many times the idea
simply is that because you create your
reality with the strongest elite, if you
do believe you are incomplete without
the other individuals, you will usually
wind up only attracting individuals to
reflect your belief in your own
incompleteness. When you know you are a
relationship under yourself, complete
that doesn't mean you won't change or
grow but complete as you are sufficient
under yourself with the idea of your
polarity. Then as you beam and radiate
on that level on that frequency then you
stand the greatest opportunity of
attracting someone to reflect that
assurance that equality that radiance
back to you as an equal also.
Now again, we are not saying this is
specific to the case,
but much of the definitions in your
society about what relationships ought
to be is what
colors your ability to allow
relationships to be what they are for.
So sometimes you may impose upon
yourself or on another person an
expectation about what you think the
relationship should appear like rather
than allowing them to happen shall we
say in a more natural
way. Sometimes those expectations in of
themselves will actually short circuit
the ability to attract an individual
because it's not actually what serves
you best in the growth patterns you have
decided to experience in your physical
life. So first of all we are not saying again
So first of all we are not saying again
it must be this
way but first of all recognize that you
can soften to some degree your
definition about how old how attached a
male needs to be to at least converse
with you as an equal. For there are many
things you might learn from other
individuals, no matter what their
situations are, that can serve you as
you can serve them in many
ways. Relaxing those definitions
sometimes is what then
allows an individual or
individual, but it does not have to be
singular, to come into your life to
represent the expansion of your
definition of what you're capable of
attracting. Understand?
Yeah. So, first step in our suggestion
as we have
discussed is to simply be in touch with
the clearest definition of your own
masculine side. However you regard that
portion of yourself is usually going to
be how that exteriorized version appears
or does not appear in your life. If you
have a definition of the masculine side
that is relatively negative, then no
matter how much you say you want to
attract a masculine representation in
your life, if that's what you really
believe it to be and it is more
overridingly that you don't want those
qualities in your life, if you believe
that those qualities must automatically
come with the man you attract, you'll
never attract one. Understand? Yes, they
do. So understand once
again blend and bow the definitions of
both the feminine and the masculine and
assume that you can attract a
representation of that blend and bow
then you win.
All right. Yes. Yes. Thank you. It is
only the fear again and the definition
that keeps anything at bay in your life.
Does this help? Yes it has. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Shane, hello. Are you good there?
Yes. I'm I wanted to know how I can lose
my weight and keep it off. I lose weight
and gain quite fat. All right. Now, we
will touch on many of the reasons, but
there's a whole number of reasons for
the creation of what you call weight,
physical weight in your reality. A
number of reasons. We will allow you in
hearing this gamut of reasons to decide
which are applicable to you. In
understanding which is applicable to
you, you can then understand the reasons
for why you have created it. And
understanding the reasons for why you
have created it, then if you want to,
you can
change. Idea number one.
Many individuals will
individuals will
assume that they in order to handle more
of the energy they are now feeling in
their lives will assume that the natural
state of their body will not be able to
handle that much energy. So they will
add mass as a buffer to be able to
handle what they perceive or label to be
extra energy. One reason.
energy. One reason.
Another sometimes is dealing with things
that the majority of your society thinks
are quote unquote
airy subjects. You will then to compensate
subjects. You will then to compensate
for their judgment of you for their
invalidation add more weight to appear
more stable and
grounded. That's another reason.
serve you sometimes because you may serve as a
you sometimes because you may serve as a
center of interaction for many different
individuals in life and they come to you
for certain kinds of benefit, certain
kinds of
service. Because of the labels your
society puts on the notion of
nurturing being that there is more than
enough to go around for everyone.
Sometimes individuals will take on a
comfortable appearance. Sometimes what
may be called a motherly nurturing
appearance in that sense by adding
weight. So that individual know I can
rest on you. I can rely on you. There's
more than enough to go around. You are a
very nurturing source. And by seeing the
extra way I am attracted to
understanding that you are functioning
in that way in being of service as a
reflection so that many people can come
to you and we will know you will not be
depleted. Third is a wonderful analogy that
Third is a wonderful analogy that
happens with your English
language. Remember that energy is math.
Math is energy. When you are doing what
excites you the most in life, you flow
the energy through you and out into the
actions of the things that excite you.
When you stop yourself from doing what
excites you, you do not flow the energy,
you wait to do what excites you. And the
more waiting you do, the more the energy
turns into mass.
When you start doing the thing it
excites you the most to do, then the
mass converts back into energy and you
stop waiting to do and start doing and
then in that sense all the waiting goes
away. That's another analogy that your
society has created for the idea of
wait. Number
five, sometimes individuals will not
want to face certain ideas and so they
can create the idea of extra mass to
hide him so that no one will be able to
him so that no one will be able to
really touch them in the center for
there will be a barrier so to speak. In
a sense it will be the filling of the
aura again with math to allow other
people to know there's no room for
anyone else.
This is almost exactly the opposite of
the other one. The nurturing one, the
one that fills the aura and let everyone
know there is more than enough to go
around. Conante. So there are many different
Conante. So there are many different
ways and even perhaps many more than we
have labeled. Allow your own imagination to
labeled. Allow your own imagination to
delve
into the reason. If any of these things
have touched the part of it, expand on
it. If they do not seem to fulfill the
notion, allow yourselves to take the cue
from the way we have examined it and
come up with your own ideas about why
you think you have created this
notion. Also, because many of you are
oriented in physiological
ways, you have created also different
notions of what you call metabolism.
Sometimes many of you need far less
sustenance in different ways than you
think you
need. Sometimes the idea of
weight will be because individuals will
in that sense consume more than they
need to to replace things they think
they don't have. So it will be one way
to try to get abundance in their life by
feeling like they have a lot of physical
materiality because they do not see it
externally in their life. They will
attempt to create it internally within
their oric field. That's another idea.
There are many many many reasons and
many more reasons for the creation of
that particular symbol in your reality
just as there are many reasons for many
of the symbols all of you created. Use
your imagination. Get into the heart,
the very center of the idea that you are
and see what makes sense to
you. Understand? Yes. Has it been of
some service?
Well, thank you very much. Thank you. At
this time, allow us to extend to each
and every one of you, our utmost
appreciation in the cocreation of this
interaction, this dream, this day, this
night, of your time, of our time. We
thank you for your sharing. We thank you
for your love. And we thank you for
allowing us to see through you that many
more ways that the infinite creation has
of creating itself to be. We enjoy you
immensely. Our love to you
unconditionally. We bid you all a fond
exciting and
loving good day. [Music]
How'd it go?
Thank you.
information or to be put on our mailing
list, please call or write
Interplanetary Connections,
Connections,
16161 Ventura Boulevard, number
314, Enino,
California 91436.
Phone number area code
818 78. [Music]