How are you all this day of your time?  one
person if only one way look
around and how there are how are to look
at the unersal a creation
would not diversity if those div you
are not one more way that the truth
could man that infin creation
could all some are
things concepts are common
to
in but ar as many them as many of you
think and they are more than many of you
think and even some what to be the
things are large numbers of people creation are agreement and
agreement and
from dimension to dimension even these
things you call the rules and laws of
reality can shift and change to some
degree.  are very few things very few
principles that are common to being in
creation basically they can be rendered
in the following format one you exist
that will be common for
everyone whatever vibration whatever
perspective whatever
frequency you put out in life will be
the vibration the perspective and the
frequency
structured on the idea of ​​reflexivity of
balance of polar positive and whatever negative
vibration you most strongly
align yourself to through your thoughts your
belief your definitions and yours
will
life that will be also common
for as principle not much is common true
forle being with creation now you on
your planet  that there are certain
things that to be common at
sar on your
this deree of commonality just because
you see it over your whole planet
sometimes has you to believe that it
must be true for everyone in the
universe this is not so it is simply
that you only have your planet so far in
your immediate memory to go by but the
idea is that even what you agree to
experience or share as a common reality
upon your has common
consensus because telepathically you are in contact
with each other all the time
and you agree that these things will be there
to represent what  may be loosely
the rules of the game  you
are but they do change what you
and some rules have changed.
some but all someevoh
belief actually generated the reality at that
time that reinforced that belief
and when enough individuals changed the
definition of their belief
hand because have
your agreement and now you have time
rememberingediscovering some the
original agreements were and now in your
present day and age are coming back into
a conscious awareness of what some of
those agreements were the agreement unal
but now you are overing things now
understand what all the agreements are that generate similarities
for all of
you a paradox is occurring in your
society you are beginning to that you
did in  fact create these agreements to
begin with and that means Now that you
are aware you created them, it means you
can change them.  You are now recognizing
much more freedom of awareness, much
more freedom of definition in your
society.  And you are beginning, at least
many of you are beginning to come to the
understanding even as some of your
scientists now are that what you have
for so long called physical reality does not
really have an empirical existence
apart from the definitions you created to be
.  In
fact, what you have so
materials that you are actually created from the
that you are actually created from the
definitions you have been t in your
society for thousands of years and when
you change those definitions you will
see changes in the experiences you have
with yoursical understand you each and
each and
you are
lallyatorsally we are noting phosy here we areing mechanics we
areingys we areing tools as you as you
can get easunle
haveer to man by you as life you have
you to
when you
think over another more to man someh
more you
are throughp  it is not under your contr when
throughp  it is not under your contr when
you believe you have strugle and suff to have
you desire then you areing more
power of the strugling and the suffering
than you are in the thing you
want these things are only
representative of the habits you have
been t of the thought patterns you have
been t for thousands of to
you but you always Iantee it
100% you can always prove to yourself
that these ideas work that you are the creator
of your reality for as soon as
you get in touch with that and start exercising
the option of your decisions
you will see the  result in your life
immediately are here
to you our we have worked us
and many others we
areou and form the association
of we perceive in the changes your
society is going through the same
potential the same recognition the same
basic ideas of realization and therefore
we have picked up upon your frequ icind
in you areate them with us you are
lerally inunction
each you and all you as each
of you and all you of your right
now and we than you forowing me tounction
as
are to us and perception of your
consciousness is a gift for through  you our
civilizations are given an
opportunity to see that many more ways that
the infinite creation has of
expressing itself with the creation it
is so you are a gift equal to us in our
eyes we simply recognize that you and we
have the ener manyuse ener
we are hereind you can use ways if
you desire to and it will be very easy
and very simple and will not require stri
strugle nor trials by fire in order to understand
that you deserveasy
just because you because you don't need
another un of course you to
up  to
you in for the gift that you have given
to us  allowing us to experi you i will
ask you how may ive
and to you
good creable are
some not all but All right.
somee and time to time for these ideas
to make at least some sense in your
language we will pull what words we are
aware of in your language and form new ideas
as you say coin new phrases to at
least give an approximation of the idea one
of these concepts we have termed the
quarity we in our ancient language conceptation you call
now while this mayine
it will at least to bring us
together around the flavor of the
concept and concept understand understand
some
differentes parallel diing
might by different from anotherion
some idea that so
you  can call one dimension one
dimension and another dimension another dimension there
must be a barrier a veil
a frequency a separation of some sort so
that you can know you have two things as
opposed to one thing understand so far this barrier this veil this if you
if you
will in
and another type of diality in other
that you may call the template that
structure and
definition to the different universes is
in and of itself a universe which we are
referring to as the quar reality
and is to some degree inhabited consed
in various ways are that
particular dimension and the perceptive
abilities within  that dimension on your
planet one of the strongest  ways that
the consciousness that is represented by
the qu reality amanult more di
more di
at their daily knowledge was able to
experience in crossing from one
dimension to another the crossing through
this barrier the quar reality
and did recogn it has its own reality
that the structure itself was its own
universal dimension but perhaps at a
different vector at a different degree
from what you typically call reality and
so they were able to open up doorways
with their mind that allow these beings
these consciousnesses within the quality play
our reality to manifest aspects of
themselves in your earth terminology
these aspects  in your earth terminology
were referred to by your American Indian
culture as theina
some cutor we
have with 100 our discovered
ways to ourselves deep into our real and
as you say straight up communication
with the levels of consciousness that exist
there even our civilization has not
yet created aread yes
than you thank
you
good about lia all right i got back from ar
that there wasuse of power theyed to
bre hum andal And that everyone on that
planet on the
earth had to die and a brown gas came
and killed everyone and that there were
certain volunteers  that stayed behind to
heal the planet.  Now you are talking
about a particular with a very long
history.  You are also talking about
something relatively late in the terms
of that history and also something that
is concurrent with what you would call Atlantis
more than Lamoria.  Although
some of it was rooted in late Lamorian ideas
as well since Atlantis was as you
would say an offshoot or a colony of
Lamoria. in around that time there was the
in around that time there was the
experience of many polar and many netive
ideas and the idea of ​​what is referred to
as the brown gas in that sense is
actually a reference to a frequency to a
vibration that actually contained and
controlled and created a type ofic gous
atmosphere that was in your terms
poisonous in that sense but it was
actually more of a psychic emanation
than something you would literally
understand a brown gas although it did
cause to some deree a physical
manifestation thated that way now this
happened late in the Lamorian cycle
Lamoria being  the landm that occupied
portions of your pacific ocean atlantus
being the landm that occupied a small
portion of what you now call your
atlantic ocean very close to the eastern
sead of your unit states of america and
along the southerly portions as well but
the idea is that from the time the alliance was created you have
now as a society manycle transwaken
I just wondering about
we were told that some us down
here in he
now now in a sense you can at
this all
in transing how to take asely 50 you mags [music]
Well, I have a lot of agreements that I
think I'd like to break and I also have
some agreements that I know I' like
to and I know that it has a lot to do
with healing this planet.  All right.  It
also has everything to do with the
following idea as we have discussed this
a few times with many of you.  This will
be a general understanding.  All of you
may into this andly lives in whatever
way you to.  The fulfillment of any
agreement you have given made requires only
the following basic that you do at any given
moment with all the integrity you
have at your disposal the thing in your
life that it excites you the most to do
because whatever it is in your life at
any moment that is the most
exciting thing you could be doing is the ulfment of
your agreement that's what
excitement is there to tell you that's
the reason you get excited about certain
things because the vibration excited with
agrecite you with integrity then you are
operating at the fullest capacity you
poss can and when you do that you will by
being you can be
of the service you can be by doing
the excit you the most to do you
will attract the individuals automatically
in your life that will be able to get
something out of the service you are
providing and that excite you to provide
and therefore will automatically as you attract
the appropriate individuals to serve be
automatically served by the
individuals you attract in exactly the
way you need to exactly precisely direk
you are not ambus philosophy we areing mechanics
this is the waysicality is  set
up is structured we are talking about
vibrational  frequenci vibrational
mechanics thank you for sharing today
and you as well for the theory of the
dream we are all sharing now together
i feel that i made the
transition into the third dimension
a
simultane that I
was on many dimensions and
experiencing many diverse emotions and
situations all at exciting is it not exciting
and interesting and
challenging the process of growth a
tremendous amount of things
as under that many
timesingly for that
isp you are given the opportunity to define those
things because however it is they
appear on the surface not
comean you now have the option toly
whatever you decide is apprate for the
person you are to sitations out my
canendously one time and minute feel
disassociated with
my whole [music ]
]
point gear as totally disassociate your
old definition for a while many of you
will find yourselves floating in this
state which may feel confusing which may feel disorienting
but that's the purpose
of it to literally disorient you from
the old definitions to give you the
opportunity to see definitions that you
can choose and apply in your  life as you
prefer to.  That's what this whole
transformational age is all about.
unlocking so that you can have your disposal
a number of opportunities you did not
before because you are now for the
first time in a long time as a
society consciously aware of that state
of unlocking you are now able to
actually perceive it for what it is and
use it for what it is in its neutral
state without automatically assuming
that just because you're disoriented this
must be negative remember that
confusion and depression and
disorientation are neutral states that are
not inherently negative unless you
define them to be negative.  Depression
is only meditation that you invalidate.
That's all it is.  It's the going into the
center of yourself to find the
answers you know are not out here, but
they are in there.  Pression is actually
more precisely defined mechanically as calm press
and when you then in that centered state
assess what it is you
want to assess detach yourself from the
old definitions attach yourself to new
definition you then expand from the
compression and come out of the
compression depression as a new person a
new being with new attitudes newives new
directions new belief newition new ener you understand
you and you
use the faster you will state the less
time will understand yes so that the
will understand yes so that the
predomin feeling and reality of the
dimension is to force us to go with
and create that the  prominent
of the transition between the third and thity
is to do that once you are
operating in what you
call it will be an automatic thing you
will take it for grant just like you take
many other things for grant you
will not have to think about it that unlocking
will be quite a natural thing
and you will recn it for what it can be recognized
in a question thank
question thank
you very much.  Remember it is all
how you define the idea.  Confusion is
simply literally in the strict meaning
of your
wordusion.  Fusion with more of yourself.
That's all it's for.  It may be
disorienting that's the purpose of disorienting
you to lerally create use
so that you
can reality you prefer which definition
you prefer and attach yourself to that
and create that around you from that
moment.  Thank
you.  Hello and good day to you.  I have a
question about your spaces.
Can you describe the technical
construction and control and guidance?  I
will be brief not want to rattle on all
day. The idea basic is that they are created out
The idea basic is that they are created out
of a few different materials but in
the following
man we create matries if you
will that are metallic and cstall in
nature. They create energy
They create energy
fields that actually represent a
dimension of existence in and of itself.
On this energy
template the crystalline hull of the
ship is literally grown.
in being grown in that particular shape
because that enery template represents a
dimension under itself and because the
metallic cstal substance the metallic cstal
matri grows only in that shaped dimension
no matter how thin the hole is
it cann take any other shap so it cannot be bent
in that sense except by what you
would call a force of equal magnitude to
the dimension in which it was created with that
with that
mat magnetic lines with the enery
template that wouldent oursion would
call integrated circ
those magnetic lines junction
directly into what you would call the
ship selfware computer which links
directly with the frequency of the
pilot therefore when the pilots activates
their mental level to a certain pitch I
say these are all loose terminologies
the ship will pick up on that pitch flow
lines of energy along those magnetic
lines and cause whatever shape or change
in the shape needs to occur in the ship
such as you say the opening of a
portal there will simply be
seingly occur with matri and will matri leaving again
no
because cstal now the basic idea of
empment is done with itself and follows
the following principle and again i  will
be very brief the idea is that we  recogn
that everything is the product of
vibration every different thing
everything you call a different object
is only different because it is a
different frequ
here and measure the way form you can
and signature pattern signature
frequency signature
equation then take that and put it here
and it again there will be one differ
the differ will be tative of theation varbration matce matce
if isolation
what you call a force field around
the ship that unlocks it from any
particular universal reality and allows
it to into the prime energy matrix then create
the vibration er by location
equatter vibrational  having innocence
dematerial and aterialized whever the
vibration defines it to be not so much
matri and civilizations have some civilizations do not require
machinery to do this at all our
civilization is on the verge of that idea.
individuals can do it automatically
biologically any but for manyations
and not necessar something that
individuals do at will although there
are civilizations that
canes this answer the
question yes thank you very much thank
you very
much and to you good how are Perfect.
Perfect.
Yes.  When we say perfect that does not
mean we do not change that does not mean we do not grow
.  It does not mean we do not
learn but to us all beings as they are
are absolutely perfect ideas
of whatever it is they are being
at that moment.
I would like to ask clarification on
cofusion.  Confusion?
Yes.  In what way do you find yourself
confused?  Well, that depends.  Yes.  Uh on
journeys to the solar wind.  Yes.  I have
enjoyed it very much.  All right, one
moment.  One moment the reference that is being
made is to one of our city ships
approximately one of your miles and
length.  The idea is that if it were to
have a name it would translate in your
language as the solar wind.  from time to
time inaction with you we have meditative
states you to
yourination on shi at different
at different
times I can be almost there and at my
computer at the same
time I I' like to know if you can
specifically tell me if there are any
agreements with counterparts of entities
there.  Yes.
[music] EV a
EV a
bit there is some assistance there is
some reflection but the majority of it
is up to you and the being you have
created yourself to be in that sense what we
mean to say is that they are not
going to write it for
you but they will give you reflective
assistance constantly you are and give you all the
constantly you are and give you all the
information you need because you on the
frequency you on you have access to the same
you on you have access to the same
information they
do that you have quite
very briefly on the last trip I
know that you did not refer to your name
you don't have names
[music] There
There
was quite was
all of us will be it like if he s me
out in a sense to some deree that is one
of the counters youing about how
I name number
if you need one is
anything you would
All right.  Why
that relationship with the cat?
will apprate
syvetyally into more dimension at the
time so if that is what serves you as a
vibration to identify that portion of
yourself then by all means that is what serves
you thank you thank you and one
final not all right uh that was a good
conv youat to
me and i would to use at
as novel
book that be possible and theat is
dayer a go ahad you not need my permission
for that it is a general
concept available to any and all of you
in that sense there is no need to toase
in whatever your consciousness
understands the concept and by all means it
you do not need my permission for
that thank you thank you hello
and to good my husband and i
have the pleasure of being introduced to
court cstal balls in
California understanding that you provided
the technology for
the idea is that we have discussed many
aspects as about it we do not provide it
directly individuals on your own planet
into their own universal source of
information we simply tailored some of
the information from our perspective
gave our point of view but did not
directly provide the
information how can they be applied to the age person
the average
What do they have?
are resonating vibrations vibrations
unlock
from some generate
analy a sonic analy
to the isolation field that we
around our spacecraft that allows us to
go into whatever dimension of space or
time we wish to they are a sonic analy
of that isolation
while you are you canination your diway you to
you to
wherever and whenever you wish and you
can make a very solid connection you can
accelerate the cellular structure of
your body elevate vibratory frequency
very rapidly by being immersed in that
sonic field that the bow generates thank
you and  use yourination you education
What might see some changes could increase insters
to want to participate
want to learn that your society is now
recognizing on certain levels to be the idea of
interactivity of participation direct participation physical action some syems other some more ancs not
necess In Atalan
times these were gathered together in
what you would call loosely a class
situation and there was a who then
on a drum of particular frequency
to
match mat match mat match mat match what
would be a regularly pulsed beat and as
everyone's heart beat began  to match mat match match
that beat they  allow themselves to
become a particular oriented state where
then scenes and scenari described to
them pictures to them that allow them to
actually identify as the things they were own
in other words for exle if they were aing vessel
in that what you might
callly hypnoticate
concept to the
underks that they constructed to the
windowing the sail to feel straining at
the mask to become the idea itself to be
lost in that day dream and then when
they emerged from that particular altered state
to simply know everything
they needed to know about the idea of
ships.  students t regul heartat was that
something that was to them to do that as
well yes and first they were given the
benefit of matching the drum the drum the drum
so this knew of being able to
learn how to match it was like a
prerequisite you had to learn before you
could go to the class or it made it much simpler
yes it was a very natural thing in
something more natural to do in a higher
dimension can
Thank you.  Thank you very much your
own in whatever way shap or formation
comes through the gate that you to be as
well.  Hello and you good I have a
question about my concept of
reincarnation.  All right.  Um, are we
always reincarnated on this planet and
this universe with these types of bodies
or does the energy move from level to
level?  It moves from level to level but
this is a linear format in which we are
discussing this idea.  Your concept
generally planet of reincarnation is a
linear one because you are used to the idea
of ​​linear time because that is your
illusion, that is your structure that is
your format for your dimension.  All the
lives ex now but you look at level to
level because you have cre the concept
of below and high before and after cause
and effect midle ending that creates the
linear format in which you typically see
reincarnation and you can as a consciousness experience it
that way but
all of these lives on all the different
levels or dimensions or civilizations in a on
all now you can use analy
and that you know on your
radio any particular program you might receive
at any given moment you know all the
programs are there all at once but
you only get the one your dial is  tuned
to at any given moment and you go from
the program you listening to a moment
ago to the program you are listening to
now to the program you will listen to in
a few moments hence But all the programs
were there all at once and you could have
taken them in any order you wish.
So to some degree recognize that this
can happen as well.  Linearly speaking it
doesn't have to be in one direction.  In
other words, you could have this life
now and after this life, you could
decide to have a life you had three
centuries ago.
Next, do you understand?
at the time
another life each frame upon you that
each frame considers to be
whole andarate from other frame and a
sense ofity one frame must prceed
arif yes yes linear anyw
in linear has been because you have
yourselves out of recognizing that you
can go anywh any you want to in
forgetting that idea you have created an
automatic return mechanism that does not
allow you to recognize even sometimes
after physical death that you have the
opportunity of going anywh anywh you
want to because You have created levels
that are very strongly attached  to the
physical belief system.  And when you
simply go into those levels after
physical death and do not rise higher
than that because you are not top that
those levels exist, then you may
automatically simply hover in that level
for a moment and then automatically
return because it is such a level close
to the physical one and you may not know there are
the levels you could go to.
Now that
you create a physical will be aware of
your option and you
option and you
can
delight than you
much very happy to be with you we are to be
with you all thank
you well one reason I like being with
you is you so polite and thank you very
[music]
Thank you very
much.  Now I have it on
you. Yes.  Well, the difference bs me.  Oh, why do
Yes.  Well, the difference bs me.  Oh, why do
you say that we created this of
limitation forgetfulness?  Yes.  Which to
me like suicide and stupidity.  Not
really. Can you tell me any um you want our
Can you tell me any um you want our
positive point of view of what you have
created?  Yes.
Exactly.  There is for what you call
Earth with the association of world a
nickname.  He is a master of
limitation.  Now this is a positive point
of view.  Yes.  For understand this, many
worlds experience various forms of
limitation, but almost no other world we have
come upon has it to the extent of the focus that
your world has.  Now listen,
this means you know you're strong enough
to do it that way.  And what it also
means is that when you allow yourself as
a society to finally integrate all that
limitation into your awareness and use
it in a positive way and use it for the
lessons you can use it for, you in a
sense on one level will be one of the
strongest civilizations in the
association of because any other
civilization from that point forward
that you may run across almost be
guaranteed to not have experienced
limitations to the degree you have and
therefore any assistance you can render
to
[laughter] [music]
on the verge of overpulation on the
verge  of starvation on the verge of a
world war no [laughter]
problem you see what we mean I don't see
the maybe not now but let me put it thatation you have
been if you look at everything you have been
both the positive and netive you
will it brought you to where you are now
if you are willing to allow even the
negative events in your past to serve
you now in a positive way you will be that
much more I enteration
because you have to some
deree a deeper appreciation through
experience of that many more ways that
infinite creation  has of manifesting
itself physical reality and even
experiences of  limitation are just as
valid as an experience as anything else
and the lessons that come from it can
always be applied in a positive [ applause] moreas are not
understand you have done it you have
experienced the limitation you have it
all out now is the idea in a posi way
and it will accelerate you greatly.  You
can use what we call the rubber band
analogy.  Understand that great
transformation is not the product of
mediocrity.  And if you consider all the
negativity and limitation of focus that
your has done like a rubber band pulled
very far back into negativity, just
imagine how far the positive side you
will go once you let
[music] go
.  In a sense it is a pendulum swing
and in a sense you are giving yourself a
buildup of energy so that when you
finally allow the r to snap loose you
will go onto the positive side that much
fther and that much faster than another civilization
might.  In other words, for
all the things you
experienced and now has under as you
say, many others may take millions of
years to process.  You have done it all
in a few thousand
years.  That's how strong you knew you
were.  That's how powerful you knew you
were. process process
will
have more quickly other
all you have chosener of
limitation to you
to exactly how powerful you actually are
Because if you are now creating a world
that desires peace and you have been
able to create that desire out of all the
negativity your world has
experienced there is nothing you cannot do nothing
yes you is one of the ways and
you have chosen it but now this is
transformational ag this is andan other
andan other
life you have for so this is you
get toly everything you have in the ecatic
and way you can so don't
invalidate your that  is a steing stone that has brought
your that  is a steing stone that has brought
you to where you are invalidate
any portion of yourself and you remove from
yourself the ability ity .
moreware netive you will become that you have
them will become more aware of negative
you could choose if you had a
mind to but once you become more aware
of them you also become more aware that
you perhaps don't prefer them and so
continue to choose more accelerated and
positive understand
yes than
you me love myself
you all about unconditional love inward
and outward thank you thank you good
again having a difficult
timeing a lot of what you're telling us
yes how can i achieve it achieve
In what do
you do?  Before you answer the question do
let me what you are hearing as the
verbal part of this communication is not the
only level you are receiving this
information on.  So the first step is to
take it for granted that whether you
seem to understand it auditorily or not
you are getting the information on
whatever level you need to get it.  Do you
understand?
much more conversation are having comes
out in your dreams when you allow it to
come out.  So first step is to relax into
the understanding that whether it seems so
or not you are absorbing whatever it
is you need to absorb even though you
may not be conscious of it at this
moment.  All
right.  Secondly
in what is not clear can you a specific
idea that we have shared the different
levels I do
n't all right.  So because understand
what we call different levels of diality are all your creations
any everything is the
same one thing and levels are
created out of that same one energy
levels in that sense are arbitrary creation
are simply perspectives and
points of view they only exist because
many individuals in your consensus
reality define that they
You don't have to think of if you are thinking
oness in a sense you are
homoging many other individuals
havearated for themselves understand you
don't have to necessarily think in the
terminology we are discussing this with
the idea is to trust that your
imagination will translate the concepts
we are saying in whatever way works best
for you that's what this is all about is meditation
it can but doing what excites you at any given
moment is one of the quickest
forms of meditation there is understand
now may I ask you a question
sure are you sure
you all are you doing in your life what excites
all are you doing in your life what excites
you the
most why not fs of what
failure.  Yes.
Why?  If what excites you the most is
really who you are, how could you fail
at being you?  You can't be anyone else.
Why would you assume that it wouldn't be
natural for you to be you
?  Because what it is that excites you
the most, excites you because it is most you that you
can be.
Do you feel that doing what excit you
the most will not allow you to have a
living that it won support you that it
might be a
struggle?  All of these things
automatically do not go hand in hand
with the definition of what excites you the
most.  What excites you the most is
most who you are is the most effortless
thing you can poss in your life and is
the thing that will bring you the
highest level of abundance to allow you to
continue to be the person that
excites you the most to be those things are provided
automatically by doing what excites
you the most so you can
understand if you are willing to that if
you are willing to have the conviction to do what excit
you the most you will
not have to fear that you will be struggl
you will
because those things excit
this is and  what you are and you
can do this easily and effortlessly in
your life.  Why else would you not allow
life.  Why else would you not allow
yourself to believe that you can do what excit
you the most and do you have a
particular idea of ​​what that might be? [music]
[music]
All right.  First of all, understand you
never really get rid of anything, but I understand what
you mean.  What you are
going to do is transform there to get rid
of anything
to the idea is to take the same ener
manifesting your life and transform it
into a positive bydefining
because understand
this no situation and no circumstance has built
in meaning they are all neutral blank
empty zero devoid of meaning you
are t to supply automatic meaning to
these neutral circumstances.  The
automatic meaning you supply determines
utterly the effect you get out of it.
Positive meaning in, positive effect
out.  Negative meaning in, negative
effect out.  Simple physics once again.
Sometimes you have been tly meanings so
quickly and so automatically, so
unconsciously that when a circumstance
occurs in your life, you not even
question the idea of ​​the meaning it
comes with.
Everyone knows that if this happens it's
bad.  Everyone knows
that you don't have to.  You don't have to
buy into that belief that
definition.  Each and every situation
that comes along in your life at any
given moment is neutral.   Give
it the definition you want to give it if you
believe if you desire that you are a positive person
if that is how you think
your why assum that anyent in life could poss be ne
even though on the surprise it may
appear to be sar to that happen in your that
you then labeled as negative and
got a negative out of just because it
looks the same on the surface.  If you
know youve changed don't give it the
same negative meaning and you won get
the same negative effect out of it.  You
will get a positive effect.  Even if
another individual comes into your life
and interacts with you in a way they
desire to be negative towards you.  If
you only know that you attract
circumstances into your life that give
you a positive result because you have
decided you are only a positively
oriented person, then no matter what
their intention is, you will only get a
positive result out of their best
efforts to produce a negative one in
your life.  Understand?
life.  Understand?
Is this ass?  Yes.  Assign the meaning you
prefer you will only attract the results that are
the vibration you believe you are
most strongly.  Decide what you are and then
strongly.  Decide what you are and then
understand that until you decide to
change that decision it will remain.  It
doesn't have a mind of own.
only you
can
so here that again seems to be needing consciously unconsciously to define
it as a negative as soon as you do
that you cann get any other but a ne out
of
it define it as a posi and you will not be
able to get any other result than the
positive one.  Understand?
When we also say do the exciting
you have awareness of a care spans and
decades.  We are talking about now in the
moment if you have such a project all
well and good focus on it. do do
it but
that works both for what you call
wide range pross careers and living in
the moment is the same and that is
simply as follows at any given moment
act upon the thing in that moment that excites
you more than any other thing
that you are most able of acting upon in that excitad Even
Even
though have nothing to do with you a
excited in appearance and very often it
won be because there are so many ways you
could get to where going that you can't
always necessarily analy create inal a
recognition synchronistically you synchronistically you
to
understand  Iantee you
100% that as soon as you act upon the
things that excite you the most with
absolute conviction and integrity that's
the lifestyle
can only you
can all your what I
can do isantee
100m will you always and always will and
are not even
you all than you than you much
I have a question
on frequencies.  Frequencies.
Yes.  Okay.  All of our effects that
happen to us in our life are really
different frequency in a sense yes.  And
all of our thoughts are
frequency is some kind of physical
particle vibration.
some physiological particles or the
effect you call physical particles willle
the different frequencies yes but
they in that sense will not be the cause
of it they will be the reflection of the
frequency of the primal energy would we
get a positive effect in our life when
we achieve a goal is similar to
algebraic addition of these frequencies
to some degree yes it can be an equation
in that will always
other side thatesqu myates a
myates a
little intu
now some people are in some people
are because few differentorsh
always always a
sing enery that is likely
manation to occur at  the time the
prediction is made
in the very second that enery can
change the rendering of the recognition
into a prediction will be enough ener
presenting are never made of the
future in the future they are made in
the present of the enery of the present
if a
particularent a great de of momentum
behind it and unlikely to change that
prediction as you [applause]
If that enter that
can diver is made
aware by pr that momentum and
they want to their mind will change
the ener dire and that you can take the
pr intuition and old  it up and out  the
window because in the pr of changed the enery
always intuition those those
havee
unlikely come those are varable
and you can in that require a
prediction from moment to moment to to up
with the
changes however The idea
however The idea
also is to recognize that there are many
ways for an individual to subjectively
interpret the information that they are
getting.  Here's an example just in terms
of the level of psychic intuition in that sense
everyone is psychic everyone
is telepathically connected but you also
have your own frame of reference your
own belief structure in which and
through which you interpret many of the
ideas you are very accurate about.
In
other let's say
individual is going to create their life situation
and dire another
picks up ener
but for the individual picking up
on the enery
the enery they feel is represented
to them in a certain way.  In other
words, if they were going to be
experiencing that dire energy, they
would interpret it in the following
way.  Would happen to them in the
following way for them to feel the same
idea.  So what they may do is put their
definition on how they think the
situation would have to come about for
them to experience the same level of
energy and they maybe make the
assumption that that individual is going to
experience it exactly in that way.  So
they make the prediction this will
happen to you and this will happen to
you.  Now the die or circumstance happens
but not in the way that was predicted
because the way that was predicted was
relevant only to the one doing the
prediction.  Understand?  It can happen
that way too in fashion.
So all we are suesting is you are all
very intuitive you are all in touch and
you are
all be aware that you are someone
else in
particular there can be many times interpretation
of the energy that is
more relevant to how you would experience the event they are
going to experience
than the way they are
actually going to experience
Now and then you can as you say hit the nail
on the head for exactly how they
are going to experience it and that is
most easily done when you have as
fewp as possible as to how individuals need to
experience the changes in their
life and  have as few as possible as to
how you need to experience the changes in
your life.
life.
Understand?  Is this clarifying the idea
to some place?  a little bit.
I'll review it on the tape because kind
of fast.  Is this would this mean that
wishful thinking could enhance a certain
uh event to occur?  Yes.  If you
understand that wishful thinking is more
than wishful thinking if you understand
as you think so you are and that concept
is firmly part of your belief structure
you will understand it isn't as you say
just wishful thinking that your attitude
and your perspective is everything and
that the idea is not just to have a nice attitude
regardless of the fact that
everything is falling apart around you.
The idea is to understand that if
everything in that sense is falling apart around
you in a negative way, it
is because of the belief systems that
you have and things falling apart around
you can be viewed in a positive or a
negative way. thinkingeview could
man you prefer one of those ways it
becomes more than what you call just
wishful thinking it becomes exactly the
thing that does manifest the reality you
get but in any event any and
any perspective attitude will go in to play part
in reinforcing the prime belief
Yes.  Allow us to each and every one of
you that even though some these ideas
may not apply immediately into your
life, it is no accident that you are
hearing all of these questions and there
is some way toly them someh in your
life.  Remember that everything you
participate in to some degree on some
level even though there may be varying
degrees of significance still has
significance for all of you.  You are all
connected in various ways and you can apply this
information across the board
in any number of ways to your own lives.
Everything is valid everything is a
perspective everything is a gift and
everything is a sharing.  Extract from it
what serves you.  Good to you.  Hi.  Um,
before I ask my question, I'm just
curious.  How much do you actually tune in to
the person such as myself out here
asking a question?  It will depend upon
the interaction at any given moment as
to what portions or what aspects of your
energy we in that sense through our
consciousness.  It will from individual
to individual greatly.  Sometimes
sometimes we will be in touch with all the
threads of the connection to other
relationships that you are both in
present and in past and what you call
future ideas sometimes will be in
connection to what you call your higher self your
future self sometimes the
collective consensus
reality understand yes it will depend
okay my question actually is for a dear
friend that could be here today all
right she asked if I would please ask
she wanted to know about her her who is paralyed anyve
always both every
circstance canve any always individual can he
himself it depends completely on what
they choose  to believe the situation was
created in the first place for whether
they are willing to understand they have control over
it whether they are willing to
learn from it what they can learn and
whether they are willing to understand
they can learn the same lesson in other
ways less limiting ways it's up to them
it will be hinged completely on the
definitions of that person's belief
system but yes to all those
questions understand yes so if he to get
away from the idea of ​​the limit of
belief that he will never walk again if
that idea would totally around one of the
easiest ways to  do that as we have said
to get  in touch
was that creange
you do not
own the idea first of all is to what i
learning about myself by having created
the situation in this fion when an
individual gets in touch with what it is
they are learning about having created it
that to
them other way they can learn the
once a particular circumstance no longer
serves as the only way to deler the message
then they don't have toely on
that being the only experience they have
and they can transform it into other
experiences that deliver the same perhs
having the experience this way
age com way  and so many you create for
drtic measures to get you to face things
you need to face toulf the agreements you made
you don't have to do it that
way but because many of you operate on unconscious
level with these belief many
times it takes drastic measures you you
are
always you love to you love to
i would love toind
your friend that again v
friend that again v
limitation reflects great
strength understand yes and do not see that
individual as we do not see the
individual in
as them as strong enough to have chosen
this is a bold [music] up
up
anything because everything is transf transf
eternal if
anyone understand but  you don't even have to
see it that
way it is their lesson they can learn
from it can change it can be anything
they want it to be anything than you thank
you and you canstal deree
eneryent source an enery that you up
many ways very
enery that which accelerates vibration
in very specific ways in very humorous
way in ways that allow you to move
easily gliding effortlessly through
transitions it is as a lantern that
lights the path ahad of you that is
basic representation symbology in your
general consensus reality now  how it
specifically applies to you to determine
by answering the question how does that
particular cstal idea allow you to feel
remember that all cstals are triggers
and catalyst for the energy you are so
why are you attracted to it
specifically you're asking me
yes it was very beautiful see a lot of
light come out of it do feel the
happiness that it does it is a happy vibration
can you take that as a sign of
a reflection of the happiness you
Yes.  All right.  Then in that sense you
become the
cstal lerally it is only a catalyst is
only a reflection of the crystallization of
your consciousness in specific
modalities.  I understand.  Thank you.
Thank you very
much. Shning hello.  And you have a good day.
Shning hello.  And you have a good day.
I
want to know what you can tell us about
how our country is being run and I can
hardly wait for that you're running
[music] you you
you you
all you are your
government you open the lines of communication
as equal not attacking not
accusatory mode with
Let those you haveign toun what you them you
are all your
government understand you are running yourselves
understand you are running yourselves
that's up to you but the idea of ​​what
you have created your government to be to
some deree is as follows because much
of the present structure is based upon
the idea of  the fears that refuse to
face and takeibility for and integrate
as a society then what doing is creating
governmental forms based on those fears protect
me save
me in creating any entity out of
fear like any entity it will have to
survive on what it knows best the
generation of fear because that is what
it was created from take back
responsibility for that fear take back
responsibility for the fact that you are
all in this
allal won you canve you simply what you
would call
youind them the idea is that they are not losing their
power by you taking yours
and spously  with each other as
equal those lines of communication  in
whatever way yourination
lovinglys you don't have to attack you
don't have to
blame for they are only what you have
created them to be the
person be the government and
and
youle if want there
are infin number
of there is earth that is of the
vibration you desire to be that vibration
and then translate yourself to that earth
day by day individuals around you
will seem to be
changing it is you that will have changed
you will attract yourself to
whatever is the vibration you
those not that will earth that they you
will think is the same to some have
the
conviction act become
invved put out there the vibration in loving
terms of what you prefer your
world to be without invalidating anyone
else's point of view let them simply see
you let them hear the vote you cast so
that others can decide by seeing the
example in [music]
that would be good would be all right to
know who
I read some that some are influenced
by the
forces they are not
beingued if they have created in their are nectuera. [applause]
understand any vibration you are
not power not only to notu you it can't even find
you if you are not the samequ it doesn't
even know you Wonderful understand
yes you thank you
very much you
much you
good I another about
another about
earth makes me wonder about dreams that
seem so
real sometimes yes [music
] understand this
anything no matter what definition
anything you imagine is somewhere somewh
someh real because you cannot imagine
nonxistence your imagination is keyed
into other dimensions your imagination is the
gate to other dimension that's
what it is so anything you imagine diant asil to
manifality thatan not on ownm doesn't
mean in dream state as a nonphysical being that
you can't experience it it is
real yes everything you can imagine
somewhere somehow is real
Yes.  Does that answer your questions
efficiently?  I thank you very much and
pleasant
dreams.  Hello.  Are you good?  I'm hearing a
challenge between reality andion or it
being the same?  Yes, it is.  You are
dreaming right now.  Um, I find a day
today.  Yes.  I find myself more like um
looking myself in the mirror when I
was my face and looking in the mirror
and seeing a space person there looking
at me.  Yes.  Well, none of you are
original to your planet anyway.
I was in this weekend and I found myself
in one of
the was very real to me that that was a
spaceship and s yes and all children
there were just kind of like children had
come in the same spaceship I had.
Yes.  Now may I ask you a question?  Yeah.
Thank you.  What will you do with this
understanding?  What way will I go?
Well, um I have been on um I
became aware about years ago and
it's kind of like I invite people around
me yes to come and see for themselves
and see what they can get out of
participating different teachings.  All
right.  Anything else?  Any other way you
to express your service?  Well,
by being who I am.  Absolutely.  Another
thing that comes up for me is like day
today I find like I'm talking to people and
their face starts changing.  Yes.  I
see different
faing more dimensions of their being.
Yeah.  Sometimes I go to lectures and I
see speakers like I'm in the back
like I'm in the back I'm the
side I know yes what they got on
the back.  This is a very natural thing
now that many of you will begin to experience
because you are expanding
your awareness of what you are as a
multidimensional being.  Yeah.  Also like
dreaming dreaming thinks that I wake up
in the morning sometimes I don't remember what it is but I
know it was
very real.
Yes. And my son was in Sona with me and he
And my son was in Sona with me and he
had a dream very real and he expressed fear
of um on the dream it was like somebody
was asking him to lead to another
dimensional and somebody said no you
cannot take him yet.
And he says, "Mom, will they come after
me when you're not around I don't have toou
?"
No.  So, it's just kind of like kind of like a
challenge, you know, kind of like is this
real or is this anillusion?  It
is real.  What you call reality is an
illusion, but that's what reality is.
It's a dream.  You see the whole idea of
this transformation age is that you're
all to that dream reality is real and
that you calls reality is a dream the
one the more you blend the more dreams
can the more dream like yourrysical
can one way another from one
dire another you will create a blending
the two as into Teach
your child a posi meaning toly a posi
meaning and will be nothing to fear
only as one of you have already said fear
itself is the only thing that
generates any reason to fear
there is nothing inherent in any
circumstance that  is fear I w up this
up this
morning and
more kind like kind like not parade
and kind to why
myself in the mirror and I you're really
getting weird very soon what you call will be the
weird very soon what you call will be the
natural state of all of you.  Now remember
this what you are recognizing
in the mirror as connections to other
places and other times is not for the
purpose of running from where you are to
go and find them.  The purpose is toind
you of who you are, where you are and to
match that frequency there to create the world
you long for where you are.
That's the whole idea to match that
frequency to meet
us toate with us the conduve vibration
the conduve atmosphere in which we can
interact as equals not to run from the
earth but to create heaven on earth.
That's the whole idea.  What you are
seeing as these connections sometimes at
first can create within you a
longing and a desire to get back.
থিং you never very attracted to cstals
and I had a friend of mine call me from Houston
and tell me about a cstal
called which I got a strong power
feeding and that I wanted to experience what
that was like telling me anything
about that was from
Brazil it is as we perceive the energy
heavily connected to what you call directional in
otheral it will be a trigger a reflection a
catalyst it has its own power
but the power for the changes you go
through are not in the cstal they are in
you but that  particular cstal can be
very strongly al to a particular focus
if you have a particular idea that excites
you very much thatal canle the
idea of ​​thear [music]
[music]
Yes.  Why you such a may because I desire to
more level what else? my in
my in
more do you have that excit you [music]
more the most exciting one the
thing that excites me more than
anything more than anything teaching all
right in what
teaching others and morey morey
now
inf way [ way [
applause] allerucent all
allerucent all
dire andal
Yes.  So it allows a focus to bring
itself back in to a center
beam, a thin linear beam
to allow the energy to come through
you and proceed in that direction
effortlessly rather than remaining for a
while and as you say rumbling around
until you find a direction for
it.  It is something that represents a focus
not an idea of ​​concentration not effort
but simply a clarity of focus in
linearms.  I understand also the last
time we spoke you shared with us the
meaning of Halloween.  I thought it might
be interesting for people to that
again there can be many meanings but
the fundamental representation the
fundamental symbology of what you call your all
symbology of what you call your all
h your November 1 and your November 2
are the remnant traditional days of
recognition of the day before the day of
and the day after the destruction of
Atlantis that is hing unlocking another another
commicysical
nonysical and syed byent
in enery sense because of
November energy sense your actual new
year's day not January 1 November 1 is your
day not January 1 November 1 is your
true  spiritual New Year's
Day so happy new
year thank
you yes I just heard today
onion ofes and wher the writ of communion and
ofes and wher the writ of communion and
one of the witches who the resident witch
of new
salem said
that to the think wicken school
of they believe
that hallowen is their new year they have Yes
, this is
again through ancient traditions but has been
forgotten and lost in what you call ritual
and ceremony.  one of the
strongest traditions to remember the
idea and therefore logically
one of the ones that
manifested into what is now your
presentday understanding of the ritual
you call whichc is the ancient Celtic or Celtic
traditions of the druids
because that was a remnant aspect
of Atalan
culture responsible for the idea of ​​the
arranging of the stones in your eng area
as an attempt to what they believe they
and get back to the idea of ​​their
connection of nature and that is the
primary thrust of what you call now the
nature on your planet the memory of the
natural connection you all had inan
times thank you thank you how to
how to
you I would like to explore and
hopefully have transform what has been a
primary learning tool
I think this point I think it's now that
you relationships in bonding and marriage
relationships in bonding and marriage
bonding.  Yes.
Um I feel that I have outgrown my
relationship or have grown in a
different way.  Okay.  And in our
tradition or our culture we have what's
called divorce.
Right.  And I remember you told me that
in your society you come together for
whatever time serves you and then it can
change it can because everyone in our
society not exactly in the same way you
mean the term but everyone in our
society knows they are married to
everyone else in the society.  Therefore,
all the relationships that might occur with
our society are all relationships that occur with
the marriage.
Okay.  I put this one of the beliefs
around the process of divorce is that it
's painful that it's hurtful that
breaks up this and it breaks up that.
Does not have to carry that definition.
That's what I'm going to ask you.  How
can a person through this without and by
transforming that definition?  And what
about the others who don't carry that
understanding?  All right.  Now, let me
ask you a question.  Yes.  Do you know it does
n't be painful?  I know it doesn't
have to be painful, but it still feels all
right.  But do remember what a
feeling
is?  I forgot.
anying you have all you all you all you
all feelings are reactions to what you believe to be true
feelings are reactions to what you believe to be true
so any you feel a
certain way it's because you believe a
certain way because you have a
particular that causes those reings
are secondary reactions to definitions
you have bought useou
about you would have generating
if that that definition is
you don't redefine it rewrite it to the
definition you do prefer to have and as
soon as you do that and start acting
like the new definition is the one you
buy into most
strongly then you're  feeling Yes. [music] do
not expect that everyone must do so
in other to the second part of your
question if you are the idea as best you
can to give them the best you can to
change but they don't to do so that's as
far as your can go you to give
them through and honest communication of
understanding who you are and who they
are actually in a relationship with. Wableutange [music] Now this
Now this
is to make a decision about right now
seems to be a pattern in my life that I have trouble
making decisions now I
could say just because I feel that I have
therefore I can't do it.  Yes.  But
it's a pattern and I when how do you break a pattern like
that?
number once you recogn you have a habit
you don't have it anymore.  A habit is
something you do you don't know you're doing
.  Once you know if a habit, you
have to be beyond it in order to know
you had it.  You have to be quote unqu
looking back from the outside in order
to see the
pattern.  Once you know it was a pattern
you don't have it anymore.  And the only
reason it would continue or seem to
continue is because a you assume it must of
own accord.
B you don't believe you can change it you
believe you have to do something
special to change it you don't believe
just because recognition of
understand if
you it not doing anyore what makes it to
continue is you giving it the same old
definition just because it appears on
the surface to be sar don't assign the
same old meaning give [applause]
Second the idea is to also allow
yourself to be aware that when you are
living in the moment and doing what excites
you the most the things you need
in life will automatically come to you
in such obvious ways
won if anyon you find your cross and you
know which way to go if both opportun equal
it doesn't matter which way you go choose one
and by making that chice it
will then by having taken the first step
become exceedingly clear as to not that's
the step you want to take.
understand yes some seem so final as the
other nothing is
you are eternal and infin you have
all the time in cre what
yoururryx the more you relax with where you are
and the decs you do make the
sooner you will give yourself the
ability to byad
concussion that you cannar from
something you learn it doesn't mean it doesn't life
are no interruptions in
your life no matter what you choose they
all fit and if you have that definition
you will get out of them the ideas that
willve you more quickly assing i  don't
belong
takeer you make more and irrevocable
because you refuse toled place life the
sooner you acknowledge that it belongs
in your life because obviously there it
is and there are no extraneous and
pointless creations the sooner you will
understand why it is there what will be the
of your choice and the sooner you will be
able to transform it into what if
you understand if
you put you in touch with a belief that
used to be unconscious that is now conscious
and that means you don't ever have to
choose that again understand
this can go  for any decision on any
decision on any level  forever no
end understand yes So if if I'm feeling which I
am that that all I can do or all I
feel that I can do right now is stay
in the moment which makes me happy.  Yes.
And don't make a decision.  When I try to make a
decision it makes me unhay sad
let the decisions be
obvious.  Be in the moment you will
attract always the most obvious
path.  If it excites you act on
it.  Sometimes we are confused, excited and
fear.
exciter one with trust and one
with so be aware and be honest with
yourself as to whether or not you are
performing an action because of
anxiety fear and or because it really
does excite you is it an action or a reaction
Yes.  Does that mean you?  Yes, I would like
to ask you why I can understand what
you're saying and incorporate better
when sitting in the audience when
standing here in your energy as if I do
n't hear the word sometimes first
of all because you create there to be a
differ and that is one of your old
definitions but remember this no matter
where or when you are the energy and the
understanding you are feeling is your
energy and your understanding not mine.
if you anyange all inter because you
taking from the rquency.  I am as you say
dishing out and you are accepting it
into your reality and creating your
version of my frequency.  And that's what
you feel.
Right now what do is focusing understand
all that
level you need to
that
because if you not to some deree with my
frequency, you would not have been interaction
today.  Understand?  Yes.  Thank you.  Thank
you very much.
will in in
few
days and good day to
you entities body and
soul there is a proposed shift of the
earth ax in a sense most of it will be energetic of
an electromagnetic shift ismqucy ismqucy
them
either destructively destruction
destructively destruction
the idea is that any
transformation of this magnitude that
you are going through now can be
experienced either a positive or a netive
way there is a far greater for a
majority of your planet to experience in a
positive way because many of you have
already assimilated the idea of ​​the old
negative definitions and the idea of ​​the
transformation does not  have to be felt
across your world as widespread as it was
used to in a negative way.  But any
individual can still determine for
themselves that whatever frequency they
are will automatically determine whether
they plan to or not where they will be
when any of these shifts begin to occur.
If they simply know that the idea of
experiencing the shift as a trial by fire
is not something that they need in
their life, not something that they have to
experience in their life to wake up
then they will be somewhere else.  Even
if they are within the confines of a
particular event of that magnitude of a
negative nature, they will not be
touched.  Understand?  So it will kind of
take care of itself.  Whatever vibration you
are will be how you change
in with what you call the next
decade two of your time but the more you
are willing to wake up now the less you
have to shake yourself
away and the more you can use whatever
does happen as unlocking rather than the
idea of ​​a
catastrophe is it true there also will
also be a thousand years shi
approximately that is cycle with
what you call another years to 2000
years your will go through another
transformation where it will be similar
to our society and that is it will be on the
verge of  translating from physical
reality to nonysical reality no longer needing
the idea of ​​a reincarnational experience
at
all understand so that
question thank you
much all of us again to each and you our
deepest appreciation and unconditional love
your willingness to toate thisity with
us this day of your time remember you
are living a dream wake up and dream the
dream you prefer to dream it is up to
you you are aspects and reflections and
faces of the
multimensional of infinite
creation all you need to be trust
and
love you are living light
we than and
you exciting dream life and life
dream and loving
and  Good
day.  How did it go?  Great.  Great.
[applause] Thank you all for being here
Thank you all for being here
today.  Those you want to copy over here
and you can have your copies in a very
short of time.  got made