Hello sir, how are you all this evening
of your time as you create time to
exist? Allow us to begin this interaction this
Allow us to begin this interaction this
evening of your time with the
entitlement integrity and opportunity.
We have discussed many times with you
the idea of integrity. We have discussed
many times the idea of opportunity and
your willingness to act upon those
opportunities that appear in your life.
Now many individuals have realized that
when we say your word integrity, we are
not always necessarily talking about
that moralistic attitude although that
is included in the whole idea but
integrity as a mechanical aspect of the
combination of all that you are being
brought together and functioning as a
unified whole integration integrity
acting in an integrated manner. Now,
when we discuss from time to time that
some of you may choose to function in a
manner that represents lack of
integrity, we are not in your terms
bismerching your moralistic attitudes.
We are simply discussing once again that
even though you may have the best of
intentions, you may still from time to
time because of your habits, because of
your assumptions, because of your
beliefs be acting in a non-integrated
manner. that is still creating
separations, still creating segregations
and not pulling yourself together to
function as a unified whole integrated
being in a positive way.
Thus recognize that with regard to the
connection of integrity and opportunity.
Many of you will find that from time to
time again out of those habits perhaps
out of your choices perhaps out of your
fears perhaps many of you will still
choose to function in non-integrated
ways. And this functioning, this choice
can allow you to not necessarily
recognize certain opportunities when and
where they may appear all around you in
very blatant and obvious ways. Perhaps
not obvious to you because you are not
focused as an integrated being.
We have discussed the idea that if you
do in your life what excites you, you
will automatically attract all the
opportunities necessary for you to act
upon that will represent the path you
chose to be. and will allow you to
accelerate in the direction of those
things that originally excited you and
increase your excitation exponentially.
But many of you have made an assumption
that these opportunities must leap out
at you in very blatant ways being very
noisy. Not so. Recognize
Not so. Recognize
an opportunity
by definition may simply be something
you are aware of on a very typical level
of awareness. In other words, just
because you are aware of its existence,
that is an opportunity to know about
something is an opportunity to act on
that thing if it excites you to move in
that direction. They do not have to come
screaming out of the jungle, as you say,
in order to get your attention, in order
to be recognized by you as an
opportunity. Well, here I am. I say I am
functioning with an integrity, but
nothing is jumping out, jumping up and
down, making itself obvious.
But you may be walking down your street
every single day ignoring the obvious.
The fact that you simply are aware that
certain individuals and certain
institutions already exist in your
society that have everything to do with
the type of things you want to do. And
you simply are not allowing yourself to
be willing to know that they do to see
the obvious and to boldly go and
communicate with those individuals
simply because you think they have to
come running to you. No, they have
already come running to you. They have
come running to you by allowing you to
know they exist.
period. They have put themselves out
there. They have made themselves known.
The rest is up to you. Yes, sometimes
they may act in more blatant way, but it
does not mean that they must in order
for you to consider that as an
opportunity that as a representational
avenue of the things that excite you. If
you are simply aware that something
exists, that is reason enough to act
upon it. You do not need another
invitation. Your awareness of its
existence is enough. All that is then
left is the willingness that is up to
you to determine whether you are truly
in synchronous harmony and in full
willingness and belief and integrity
about the thing you say excites you the
most, or whether you are still willing
to play the shrinking violet and not
want to bother anyone with something
that excites you. But well, you're not
sure might excite them. If you don't
make yourself known to those that have
made themselves known to you, you will
never know because you are not truly
acting upon the opportunities that
actually do exist all the time, day by
day, very blatantly in your society.
Many of these things are simply based
upon the assumptions that you have been
brought up with. The belief systems that
have been drumed into you since you were
very young. The idea that certain
individuals and certain ideas and
certain areas are unapproachable.
Why? Nothing is unapproachable. Nothing
at all. It is up to you to form the
integrated spark of awareness, the
inspirational leap of cognition, to know
that as you walk down what appears to be
a very ordinary and mundane street in
your cities, in your world,
very often all the signs and all the
signals and all the opportunities and
all the tools that you really have been
asking for are all lined up one after
another right there every day, right in
front of you. All you need to do is
start going and interacting with those
things that have already made themselves
extremely obvious.
This is what integrity is all about.
Acting on every opportunity that makes
itself obvious that is in any way, shape
or form connected to the thing that
excites you the most in life. When we
say these things will come to you
automatically, that does not mean you
sit back in your easy chair waiting for
them to knock on your door. It means you
act upon the opportunities that have
already made themselves obvious to you
and then the rest will come in and make
themselves obvious as well. But you must
act upon what has already been laid upon
your table before the next course can be
served. You follow me?
So allow the obvious
to exist all around you. Allow the
opportunities that you seek to already
be standing staring you in the face
because many of them are and you are not
willing to recognize them as such
because you do not believe them to be
such because they are not acting in
expected ways.
Pay close attention
to the assumptions that you may still
make even when you think you understand
a metaphysical principle. You may still
be clothing it in many of the
assumptions of what your society has
taught you about how you think it does
or does not work. Always
always it will work in a positive direction for
it will work in a positive direction for
you if you are in fact acting upon the
opportunities that present themselves
with integrity always.
Many of you have discussed the idea that
things do not seem to be moving in a
direction you expect do not seem to be
moving in certain directions when you
say I know I'm functioning within my
integrity. I know I am acting upon the
opportunities but I do not see the
opportunities come. But that once again
is simply a matter of degree of
perception of different levels in your
society. For many levels still exist.
And it is up to you when you center
yourself and clear yourself to recognize
that you may yet still be peering
through one of those levels and not even
knowing that that level exists.
Allow yourself to recognize the obvious.
For many times, because of what you have
created your society to be, the truly
obvious is not obvious to you at all.
Allow yourselves to relax your
definitions about what you think a
principle is all about. What you think a
definition is all about. Incorporate and
integrate a broader spectrum of
definitions in all that you do. You are
surrounded by the abundance that you
seek. All you need to do is see it for what it
All you need to do is see it for what it
is.
At this timing,
once again, we extend to each and every
one of you our unbridled joy at being
allowed to interact
with the facets of reality that you have
created yourselves to be. For you are
all unique and everything you have ever
done inside and outside of integrity has
all been a part of your learning
experience and adds to the whole energy
that you are now creating yourselves to
be in the fashion you are creating. We
thank you for your willingness to create
the endeavors you have created to create
yourselves to be who you are. You are
cherished by many. We extend our
unconditional appreciation and love to
you for being willing to interact with
us and co-create this interaction in
this way to further the integration of
your society and the respective
societies within our association of
worlds and in return for this gift you
have given us we ask you how may I serve
you now
hello Bashar and to you about three
years ago on father's day an event took
place in my life and I've been trying to
put it in place ever since. Can you all
hear? I've been Can you hear better now? I've
I've been Can you hear better now? I've
been trying to understand the
ramifications, all the ramifications
when one person takes another person's
life. My brother murdered his wife. All
right. And I was wondering if that came
about as a result of uh free will uh or
uh pre-aggreement before they entered
this life. I was just it does not have
to play out that way. Pre-agreements
there were. But in no way, shape or form
does any pre-arranged
idea or pattern that you're going to
play out in any particular physical
life, in no way, shape, or form must it
play out through negativity, through
lack of integrity. Those agreements can
all be reconciled in a positive way.
Yes, it took place through free will.
But basically, those types of endeavors
that express negativity to that degree
take place because the individual has
not been taught that they actually do
have free will, has not been taught that
they actually do have self-empowerment.
So, individuals that perform those type
of acts act generally out of the belief
that they are powerless and they strike
out to take those with them so they do
not feel that they are going down alone.
You follow me? Yes. They must put upon
the idea of the external world all the
ideas they are not willing to be
responsible for in their internal world
because that responsibility is too much
for them to bear because they have not
been taught that they have the power in
that sense to transform it into a
positive understanding and a positive
action. So in a sense the pre-arranged
agreements have to do with the type of
interactions and the things that those
individuals work out between themselves.
But in no way, shape or form do those
pre-arrangements have to result in a
negative act in that sense. It could
have been arrived at in a positive way.
You follow me? Yes. However, in this
sense, since it did happen in that way,
you can still recognize it as an
opportunity for that individual
to choose if they desire reincarnation
or not and be on certain levels of
assistance to this individual that has
committed what you call the murder to
allow that individual to gain back their
power so they can recognize they never
have to do that again. to give their
power away to such a degree that they
must think that they have to control the
external reality of everyone else's life
in order to feel powerful within
themselves. There are many levels on
which the murdered person can be of
great assistance to that individual when
and if that murdered individual goes
through the confusion that they may be
feeling when they first enter the
non-physical realm. because in playing
their part in having been murdered many
times that is also a creation of
confusion and the lack of belief in
one's own self-empowerment. So in a
sense you have two individuals acting
out a belief in lack of
self-empowerment. They have played a
scenario out that has come to its
logical conclusion when you deal with
the idea of belief in lack of
self-empowerment. And now it gives both
of those individuals an opportunity to
examine the ideas of what they have done
to take responsibility for it and acting
through integrity no longer need to
create a reality within themselves or
reflect a reality to each other wherein
they must believe they are not
self-empowered and cannot create the
reality they desire without having to
hurt anyone else or themselves in order
to do it. You follow me? Yes, I do. So
anything no matter how negative can
always be transformed into a positive.
Do remember everyone is eternal.
Everyone is infinite. And in that sense
in what you call the long run, it does
not really matter. What matters is what
you make of what you do. What meaning
you give to it and how you choose to
learn from it and transform it in
positive directions. That being still
lives. Many individuals, almost all of you, at
Many individuals, almost all of you, at
one time or another, in the thousands of
lives you have had, in the tens of
thousands of years of reincarnation you
have created, have all murdered and been
murdered at one time or another. Here
you are again.
You follow me? Yes, I do. Um, one other
thought then you say that there are no
accidents. Then all things happen through choice,
Then all things happen through choice,
through belief.
Well, then I was thinking about the
Holocaust, what they call the Holocaust
in Germany. Why did so many people
almost as a unit opt for that? Well,
there are race and culture beliefs as
well and recognize that gatherings again
are no accident. Again, remember that
when we say you choose and create your
reality because of what your society has
been, that doesn't mean it's always been
a conscious act. Oh yes, I want to be
killed today. No, no, no, no, no. That
is not what we are saying. But
individuals of like frequency will find
themselves gathering together and
existing within that type of a reality
that is generated by their particular
frequency that they issue that they
generate. Now there are many reasons for
that particular manifestation.
One is simply that it was a
manifestation of the fear of the belief
in persecution that many of those
individuals have within their cultural
beliefs. It was a manifestation of that.
It was also to some degree a karmic
manifestation in the recognition. Again,
not that it had to happen this way
because karma has nothing to do with
retribution. Many of you may believe
that and many of you have created karma
and reincarnation to be of a retribution
nature. But karma in and of itself has
nothing to do with judgment and
retribution. But many individuals in
creating an unconscious recognition of
things they have done in the past in
past lives have gathered together and
taken upon themselves the idea of the
guilt and the idea of the persecution.
Sometimes to atone in ways they think
they need to atone. Again, that does not
have to happen that way. But recognize
that that particular culture that you
refer to as being persecuted in the
Holocaust have had many holocausts of
their own where they have been the
persecutors in times past. Do you follow
me? Yes, I do. Therefore, simply
recognize all we are saying is that when
you create your own reality, many times
in your past that has been done
unconsciously out of fear, out of doubt,
out of guilt,
now in no way, shape or form is what I
am about to say an implication or a
definition that needs to be thought of
as a distinct label for any one
particular person or group of people
upon your planet. But you yourselves in
your own cultural awareness are very
ready to admit that there is generally
one cultural group of people that deals
very strongly with the idea of guilt all
the time and it is that group you have
referred to. You know it so well you
even joke about it.
ID is to recognize that there is a grain
of truth in that understanding that the
willingness to operate within guilt will
usually attract someone to pronounce
sentence. I see. Do you follow me? Yes,
I do. Now, that individual that became
the persecutor in no way, shape, or form
is excused for having chosen that role.
It was their duty to be strong enough to
ignore the frequency of those that might
cry out for persecution with their
unconscious fears. But the idea still is
that that individual
took it upon themselves because of their
unconscious fears to become the symbolic
representation of all that was feared
within the other culture.
They are victims and perpetrators, two
sides of the same coin. One cannot exist
without the other. And when one side
does not exist, the other cannot exist
and will not exist. So if and when
individuals no longer decide they want
to play the idea or believe in the idea
of victimhood, there can be no
perpetrators. When individuals realize
they are self-empowered and can create
the reality they desire without having
to hurt anyone else to do it, there will
be no more perpetrators. And therefore,
when the perpetrators decide not to play
that game, there will be no more
victims. They will not be able to find
each other.
You follow me? Yes, I do. Does this
assist you? Uh, one more thought. All
right. when um if a mother came to you
and this has happened several times
recently. We had reports on television
and uh say a small child six or seven
years old was sexually molested,
tortured, murdered, what would you say
to that mother? First of all, recognize
in any endeavor that you are describing,
there can be as many reasons for why
that is happening as there are
individuals it is happening to. There
may be general fundamental reasons as to
why those things can occur. But the
specifics of why that particular
endeavor did occur will have very much
to do with who those individuals are.
Because many times one reason is that
those individuals will be playing
something out from another life and may
actually be literally reversing roles.
Now you see how it feels. The other one
may be saying now again this doesn't
excuse that action because no one has to
act in that manner and all karma can be
balanced in a positive way. It is simply
that your society has not completely
woken up to this fact yet. And so in
your nightmares you keep inflicting
these ideas upon each other in negative
ways. But also it has to do many times
with the parents of the individual
before a child quote unquote when it is
deciding to be born recognize that it is
not a child making that decision. But
when it projects itself into the idea of
the body of a physical child may also
come into reality to reflect fears that
the parents have within themselves. So
the child may say, "I know this is going
to be tough for you, but I will play out
a scenario to show you, within yourself,
the fears you have within you about your
own safety, about your own integrity,
about your place in the world. And I
will show you by allowing my body to die
through this particular act that you
live in a kind of world that you no
longer prefer and that you can do
something about it." Many times
individuals do not do something in your
world until they are witness to what you
call such a reprehensible act of
conduct. And therefore many individuals
will actually choose to be born to get
those individuals off their you know
whats to do something about why your society
to do something about why your society
does those things to begin with. You
follow me? Yes. There are many reasons
but again the soul is eternal. It is
infinite. And not that those things have
to happen and in no way, shape or form
that we condone them, but in the final
analysis, the soul is not ultimately
affected by any act one way or another.
You follow me? Yes. There is a strength
and a power to all of you. And many of
you can recognize that sometimes you
will actually choose those endeavors,
those particular types of interactions
because you know you are eternal.
because you know you have the strength
to go through it and because many times
you are doing it out of love for someone
else to get them to open their eyes to
something that is going on.
You follow me? Yes, I do. Thank you very
much. Thank you. One one small note when
I was in
you have the opportunity within yourself
to understand all of these ideas if you
will but approach all of your questions
from the point of view that you are the
creator of your reality and that you are
an eternal being. You can understand
almost everything if you take that
approach. Everything does have a reason.
The universe is not pointless, nor is it
extraneous. The infinite creation does
not create it to be so. Therefore, trust
that the things that do occur in your
reality and that the things you are
witness to do have a point, do have a
reason. If you approach it from that
attitude and from that trust, you will
be able to glean the reasons for why
something has occurred. Trust it and it
will come to light. Thank you. Yes.
Hello, Bashar. Unto you. Um I my mother
is ill with my mother Speak up. My
mother is ill with cancer and and I was
just told today that there's nothing
more to do for her. All right. There are
many more things to do. That's what I'd
like. One of them simply is is that if
that individual has chosen now to become
non-physical, then you can assist that
individual in the transference from
physicality to non-physicality. So that
there will be a small or no degree of
confusion about where they are and what
they can do once they are non-physical.
Because many individuals in your reality
will find that once you become
non-physical, you may at first carry
with you the strongest belief you had
about life when you were still
physically alive. And that will create a
reality around you that you will
perceive to be the real reality. Because
once you are non-physical, you are a
thought form in a world of thought form.
And what you think is instantly what
seems to be physically real around you.
And therefore, that is why many
individuals may not even know they have
died when they have died.
Therefore, you can be of great
assistance to that individual if they
have chosen to become non-physical to
allow them to become non-physical with
dignity, with joy, with effortlessness,
with love, with ecstasy, with ease, to
allow them to know, to allow them to
remember that it is only the idea of
stepping from one room to another room
in the same house. That is all death is.
They have made their choices. Allow them
to do so with dignity. There is no real
separation. There is no real loss. The
love is always there. It is always able
to be felt. You are never out of touch
unless you believe that you are.
So allow yourself to simply take stock
of what you are learning about yourself
from this situation because there is
obviously a reason why you are involved
with that individual and why they are
going through what they are going
through at this time. There is something
for you to learn about yourself as well
as what they are learning about
themselves. Use all the knowledge in a positive way
Use all the knowledge in a positive way
and you will enlighten yourself. raise
your vibratory level. And you may then
be quite astonished to find that if and
when they choose to make their
transference to non-physicality, your
willingness to treat the whole endeavor
in a positive way and raise your
vibrations will mean that when they
transfer into non-physical reality, they
are not actually so far above you as you
used to think. Just a little side step
to the corner. That is all the
difference between physical reality and
non-physical reality what you call
physical life and physical death is not
as large as you all think. It is a very
very short step
between your physical vibration that
which makes you physical and that which
allows you to be non-physical. A very
short step. Very short.
You are quite consciously holding
yourselves in physical reality if that
is where you find yourself to be.
A very small shift is all that is
required to go into non-physical
existence. Therefore, allow yourself to
project your love to that individual so
they can use your love to slide gently
into that next vibratory level.
Then you will remain in communication as
you need to and you will not feel that
you are out of touch. You follow me?
Yes, it does. Does this assist you? Yes,
it does. Thank you very much. Give that
individual out love if you will. Thank
you. Sharing.
Sharing.
Welcome to our garden, Bashar. And you
to ours. I'm a relatively new
acquaintance to you, but I think you're
an old friend of mine. All right, speak
up. Yes, I've been fascinated for quite
some time about the research uh the
archaeologists have been doing lately
with the Sumerian clay tablets which
seem to point and indicate that um of
extraterrestrial activity on the earth
in times past and my specific interest
was the 30th parallel in which um it
seems that the Giza pyramid has its
footing there. The Sphinx is facing
east. We're looking on the 30th
parallel. Then we have um on the Persian
Gulf what is now Basra
uh Iridu it was called by the Sumerianss
I understand and then also a wonderful
uh town in India of Harapa and then
Lassa and Tibet and I wondered if you
could enlighten me a bit on the the
connection. Thank you. You will find
that that line above and below your
equator will represent the trinary
vibratory electromagnetic frequency. a
particular standing wave resonance upon
your planet. Let us say a particular
type of interaction between all the
electromagnetic fields upon your planet
that is very conducive to the
transference of mentality and
information along those line. It is a
very strongly connected ring above below
the equator. In that way it represents
certain types of harmonic frequencies of
all the electromagnetic frequencies of
your planet. Now there are several such
lines upon your world but the 30th
parallel above and below are two of the
strongest in that way. Therefore, those
endeavors most intuitively felt, those
endeavors most strongly connected to the
idea of utilizing the electromagnetic
field within those particular projects
will generally gravitate. And that word
is not an accident. Gravitate to those
particular lines of resonance upon your
planet that represent a particular pulse
that allow certain endeavors to be more
easily accomplished than by going
against the flow of that electromagnetic
field. Yes. And then with uh any tilting
of the poles, does this change those
lines at all? To some degree or do they
float around the sphere? To some degree
those lines will change. It will set up
a new harmonic frequency. Some of those
harmonics are being established now, but
recognize that some of the same
endeavors will still have connections to
those frequencies because there will be
other avenues at right angles to the old
frequency that will allow them to still
remain connected in different ways, but
connected nonetheless. There will be new
endeavors that will take advantage of
the new lay lines of the new grid in
that sense. And those endeavors will be
representative of a mirroring effect in
what you call your near future. The
mirroring effect of the knowledge and
the understanding that was created in
what you call your past. So that you
will know you have come full cycle and
that you are now able to create your
version of those ideas that your
civilization created so long ago. Mhm.
And then the um the I what what I would
suspect would be landing lines or
approach paths uh for ancient um ports,
teleports or space ports at 45 degree
angles of the 30th parallel. Does that
ring a bell or does that seem some of
them are used in that way? But recognize
that your own past civilizations had a
much quote unquote freer technology than
you now possess. And many of those are
your own doing, your own civilization's
doing. And some of those markings and
some of those lines were also used in
the endeavor of learning astral
projection rather than the idea of
utilization of technology. Oh, I see.
All right. Well, this has been exciting
me even though other things excite me as
well. But I figured you were the fellow
to um to help me out with those
questions. I figure you are the fellow
because each and every individual has
all the answers to the things that truly
move them the strongest. flow with your
own electromagnetic lines and you will
find yourself containing all that you
need to know. It is all up to you. You
have the power. We are only functioning
as a reflection of what you already deep
within you truly know and are now
willing to bring to the surface and
allow to blossom on the surface of your
world once again as you did in times
past. We thank you very much for your
sharing. Thank you for your energy.
Sharing
Hello Kashar. Unto you. Could you tell
me uh two things about the pyramids? Is
there a link between the Egyptian
pyramids and those of South America,
particularly particularly the Mayans?
Yes. Could you expound on the link?
Briefly recognize that some of the
technology issued from the same
understanding or area you call Atlantis.
So they are connected in much that same
way. Also, can you explain what creates the
Also, can you explain what creates the
phenomena of material things such as
water or razor blades changing changing
those shapes, those forms are lenses for
electromagnetism much the same way that
glass can be a lens to focus light. You
follow me? They focus the
electromagnetic field of your world in
such a way as to create an isolation
field of a very specific frequency in
the electromagnetic spectrum. This
frequency has a tendency to cause
certain alignments of molecular
structures within different materials
because they are vibrating now at
different frequencies. They will realign
themselves in different ways and create
different observable phenomena as you
have called out. Some of this will have
to do with tapping the potential of a
particular type of energy in
specifically water. And that is why once
that energy is released, many of these
ideas that contain water will actually
mummify and dry out because they are
unleashed from that object.
from that object.
So it's not particularly a mathematical
configuration that creates that effect
of the pyramid. Yes, it is. But you see,
that is all there is to anything anyway.
It is all frequency. It is all
vibration. It is all quote unquote
mathematical configuration. That is all
matter is a mathematical configuration
of energy. This specific mathematical
configuration of matter of energy causes
that particular effect. It acts as a
lens in the middle of an electromagnetic
field and causes there to be a specific
type of focus within that generally
unfocused field. You follow me? Yes. It
is a diverter. It is a funnel. It is a
gate. It is a conduit. Many individuals
in times past both in the Egyptian and
the Central American and South American
sides utilized that focusing power to
cause resonant frequencies within their
bodies that aided and assisted them in
their alignment with all different
levels of consciousness. They were used
as temples of adaptation.
You follow me? Yes.
Does that assist you very much? Thank
you, Bishar. It is also the reason
symbolically because a cone is very similar to this
because a cone is very similar to this
idea and certain proportions will have
similar effects perhaps in a more
energetic way in a more vortex or
spirally oriented way. Cones will move
the energy in a different way whereas
pyramidal structures will generally take
it and focus it in a more static way.
That is why symbolically what you call
your witch or wizard hats are cones. You
follow me? It is also the reason for
what you call your dunce cap.
Because the idea was to utilize the
energy to allow you to uplift your
vibratory frequencies to allow you to be
smarter. So experiment with these ideas.
So experiment with these ideas.
You follow me very much. We are not
necessarily condoning the judgmental
symbols that have been given to these
shapes but that is the reason why they
have been adopted into those patterns in
your society as we perceive your energy.
Thank you very much. Thank you Bashar
shing.
Hello Bashar and to you. Well I'm real
excited to be here. Um okay. Um it's I
am real excited.
I know. Notice how I say that.
How excited are you? I'm stuck. Well,
thank you. Let everyone know how excited
you are so they can share it, too. Well,
this is the thing, though. The thing?
Yes. What is the thing? The thing is, it
really is at this moment. Um, I am, you
know, this moment. This very moment. I
am excited. You mean that one or this
one? This.
All right.
this now moment now. Yeah. Now
I'm experiencing extreme anxiety which
is something I want to discuss with you
because I have been going through um a
tremendous amount of excitement in my
life. Everything you know is just
happening the way I had pictured it you
know imagined it and it's do you
remember what we have already said about
what anxiety is? No I don't think I was
here for that. Oh all right excitement.
Excitement. Excitement and anxiety are the same
Excitement and anxiety are the same
energy. Yes. Well, one from a positive
point of view, one from a negative point
of view. In other words, it is literally
the same energy. It becomes excitement
when you retain a positive point of
view. It becomes anxiety when you are
filtering that energy through negative
beliefs. Okay. Then that's what I want
to discuss. All right. Because I feel
that I have been doing such a cleansing
thing. I mean, constantly I'm just
affirming, you know, things that are
going on and and it just then why did
you choose to stop affirming that?
That's what I want to ask you. Where did
this come from? One moment. One moment.
You are misunderstanding my question.
Okay. When you chose to stop affirming
that is when you felt the anxiety.
Not that you felt the anxiety as an
indication that you had chosen to stop
affirming. You understand the difference? Um I in
You understand the difference? Um I in
other words, you feel a certain twinge.
It is unfamiliar as the excitement you
are used to feeling it. It may represent
certain ideas within you that represent
negative filters. And so you translate
it as anxiety. But why should the
feeling of anxiety allow you to assume
you have stopped feeling excitement?
Because I have this uncomfortable
that's, you know, see you're just
hitting everything because I I I I want
to be neutral, you know, and that's the
thing. It's, you know, you want to be
neutral. Well, I I I You don't want to
be positive. Well, no. I'm What I mean
is when I get this twinge in my stomach.
Okay. That's the thing you're saying. I
know. And I know this negative thing
came from somewhere, right? It came from
somewhere. I'm sitting here affirming,
being positive, and boom, I feel this
thing in my stomach. I don't know where
it came from, but it did. And so, okay,
I want to neutralize it because it
doesn't feel comfortable. Now, can't I
make that, you know, acknowledgement
with myself. It doesn't feel
comfortable. So, I'd like to neutralize
this. I don't want to put a judgment on.
I want to say, oh, I'm feeling bad. This
is negative. I just want to neutralize
this uncomfortable feeling. You know
it's and how do you neutralize an
uncomfortable feeling? That's what I
that's by acting it out in a positive
way. By assuming that it is in fact
positive first of all. Good. All right.
If you feel it originally to be
negative, fine. Acknowledge it. Yes, it
came negatively first. But why continue
to acknowledge it as a negative? The
sooner you start assuming ah this
negative feeling must be happening for a
positive reason it will start turning
back into excitement. That's what I was
doing. I mean one moment one moment
there are many layers to your
assumptions. One of which is very strong
within you is this idea that many of you
have. Oh I was doing so well. What
happened?
That is calling it a negative idea. To
say what went wrong is to call it a
negative idea.
Allow yourself to begin to realize to
truly realize that even when it comes as
a negative at first.
What that means if you are willing to
choose to believe it means this is that
you have been acting positively. You
have been expanding. You have been
increasing your willingness to discover
more about yourself. So now this new
feeling even though it may come
negatively at first must be must be an
indication that you have now arrived at
a new level of integration. All right.
Now I have reached a level where before
I would have considered that level and
the thing it's going to bring to me to
look at to be absolutely impossible to
face. Now that I have arrived on that
level, I am reminded with a slight tinge
of anxiety that I have actually expanded
and am now ready to face a thing I was
not ready to face before.
Now I have identified that I am dealing
with something that I can now integrate
that I was not willing to integrate
before. So the anxiety can simply be an
identifier. Look, you're now integrating
something new on a new level. Why assume
you're going backwards? Why assume
you're not being excited? Why assume
you're not expanding? The anxiety is
just there to remind you this is
something that used to scare the jeers
out of you.
So the anxiety is there to simply say
you've arrived. Now you can deal with
it. Now you know you are powerful enough
to absorb it to integrate it. Now you
know you can transform it. But I remind
you anxiety says this is the thing you
were afraid of. But now look it is only
a little bit of anxiety and it still
blends with the idea of anticipation and
excitement. It is not the overwhelming
dread and fear it might have been three
of your years ago.
So why assume just because it comes as a
little anxiety feeling that it must be
something representative of a whole
negative streak in your life instead of
assuming that the anxiety must be a part
of your positive excitement and
therefore must have a reason for being
there. Because if you know you're a
positive being, if you say you believe
you're a positive being, then even when
you create anxiety, it must be for a
positive reason, right? You understand?
Yes, I do. So, you know, in the way I
look at it, this is just growing pains
then. Very good. Now, not that you have
to have them. And the more you allow
them to exist, when they exist, the
fewer you will have, but you all are
still going through some processing. It
is still some of the nature of your
reality. Don't begrudge it. Let it
occur. The more you allow it to be a
part of the process rather than
continuing to assume that just because
it exists it must be an interruption in
the process you thought you were doing.
The more you allow it to exist as a part
of the process the quicker you will not
need it next time. You follow me? Yes.
So um considering it just part of the
process will will that be a good thought
to have rather than trying to analyze
where it's coming from and you know my
my deal with it is like it's here and I
don't want to give it any power. I don't
want to even acknowledge it. You know
what I mean? One moment another myth
another assumption that to just think of
it gives it power. No, no, no. Don't be
so fearful of your thoughts. It is the
fear that gives them the power. It is
the fear to look at them that gives them
the power because you're ignoring them.
They don't like that.
Ignoring them, not facing them, that
gives them the power.
Looking at them doesn't give them the
power. Acknowledging them doesn't give
them the power. When you acknowledge
them, then you are in command. You are
in control. Then you decide consciously
whether or not to give them the power.
If you fear to face them, if you fear to
think about them, that's giving them
power because they are your children.
You are ignoring them. They will scream
and cry to get your attention.
You follow me? Yes, I do. So when they
say, "Mom,
[Music] yes, little anxious one, I see you. I
yes, little anxious one, I see you. I
acknowledge you. You are one of my
children and I love you." What is it you
wish? You love me? Yes, I do. You
acknowledge me? Yes, I do. What is it
you wanted to say?
Oh, nothing.
Just wanted to know. You still anxious one.
anxious one.
You follow me? Yes. Thank you. Thank you
very much.
Our love to you.
We thank you for applauding the
recognition of your own self-empowerment
sharing. Aar Bashar and to you. Thank
you. That's a greeting from one of my
lives as a pirate. All right.
See, how about those Lakers last Sunday?
But you don't you don't follow
basketball.
Is that some sort of religion?
Yes, it is.
For many.
Absolutely. So, I guess Essani doesn't
have a basketball team. No.
You should see them jump.
I guess that's because all you guys up
there are too short for basketball.
We could always lower the hoops. True.
Everything is relative, you know. Yes.
Well, perhaps we are too high.
Perhaps. Well, this discussion was just
to get everybody hooping it up here
anyway. Oh, thank you. Pun intended.
Always enjoy the humor.
And you play with us sometimes, so it's
fun. Absolutely.
Um
I have I have an uh a sharing that I
found interesting. By all means. Couple
of weeks ago you u were talking to
people about their experiences in
Shasta. I see. And um you made the
remark that sometimes people believe
that they can handle the intensity of
the energy that comes but when it
actually occurs when the energy actually
comes from an extraterrestrial they may
not actually handle it as well as they
thought they would. Yes. So, I've been
looking at this and I find it very
interesting. And during that week, I
And during that week, I
imagine what it would be like if um an
extraterrestrial would uh to pop into my
space or poke their head into my bedroom
as I lay uh sleeping as Whitley Striber
uh described in his book. And, you know,
I imagine various things, you know,
eight-legged uh extraterrestrials with
huge mandibular protrusions, you know,
and stuff like that, you know.
just to make it very interesting. All
right. And I do not mean to be so uninteresting
And I do not mean to be so uninteresting
to you. No, right.
It's okay, Bashar. Everyone has its
place in in existence. Yeah. And uh
I thought um you know, I mean, what
would I do? There'd be no place to run
if I felt that I had to run. So why why
exhibit fear? And uh besides, you know,
if an eight-legged creature with huge
mandibular protrusions
decided to take a bite out of me, I
mean, what could I do? So I figured
would say no thank you.
I could I could do that. You could not
attract that into your reality to begin
with. Well, that's true. Although um I
prefer to think that um or to believe
that uh I could I could attract
something that would not in fact
uh interact with me negatively. Oh,
right. Because I I enjoy the positive
manifestations. Yes. And I I could I
imagine myself just responding with a
gentle hello. Yes. Let him see that I
was not afraid and allow him also not to
be afraid of me. Yes. And uh so during
this week I was thinking of these things
and I was enjoying it. And I just
happened to turn on channel 28, a
station that I rarely listen to, and
there was this group happened quote
unquote. Yes. There was a group that was
talking about uh courteous behavior or
manners in greeting extraterrestrial
aliens. Nice.
And they were talking about eight-legged
creatures with mandibular protrusions
and various things which I knew that
really was a little bit of an
exaggeration of what I truly anticipate
would occur when there's face tof face
confrontation. Yes. Face to face what?
Well, I use the term confrontation
meaning face to face. Yes. You know, not
um Yes. Yes. Yes. Okay, you got it.
Anyway, um this is all very interesting
and I I concluded that I would react
with a great deal of um acceptance,
loving acceptance and no fear and I I
had the chance to experience this
particular phenomenon as a as an
eight-legged creature did in fact
manifest in my space. Nice. I was um I
was watching actually I was talking to
Kathy on the phone and watching
television. Actually, the TV sound was
off, but the picture was on. And I I was
sitting in my chair with my foot up on
the seat of the chair, my knee up to my
chest, looking over my knee at the
television, and suddenly this
eight-legged creature popped into my
existence from from above. Nice. A white
spider, guys. Dangling from the ceiling
on a on a thread of web. Nice. And it
was uh very interesting because I I was
surprised, but not in any way shocked or
or frightened. And I knew at the time,
oh, this is this is my experience. It's
either a first experience or it's a
symbolic experience of what I would
actually um how I would Yeah, it is very
real. It was it was quite fascinating
because um may I remind you of
something? Sure. Many different levels
of consciousness
to use a metaphor when they stick their
fingers into your dimension
may appear to be things that are quite
common to you but actually aren't. Ah.
Very interesting. Well, he he was he was
about 8 8 inches above my knee, directly
over my knee. And I looked up and
there was the space of the ceiling that
he came from was um just like any other
space. So, I knew that he was coming
down to check out my knee. There was no
question about that. And he continued
down to about two inches within my knee.
And testing your flexibility, I guess.
So there was definitely communication.
There was definitely communication
between us because Oh yeah. He knew that
I was there. He knew that I was not
afraid. I knew that he was not afraid.
Uh he may have been a little more
afraid. He may have been a little bit
afraid because he came down within two
inches and decided no, I don't need to
go any further. But it wasn't really a
fear. It was just kind of a
cautiousness, right? Because I
outweighed him by about a thousand times
or more.
But I had no I had no intentions nor
desire to to uh hurt him. Yes. And he
knew that too. Well, congratulations on
your encounter. Yeah. And I found it
interesting. It was my spider was a
white spider. Yes. And I know that the
spiders um what do they do? They
symbolize um things that can come out of
hidden places. dice. And uh in this
case, of course, there is some
difference in the symbology,
particularly because you've set up the
circumstances for a specific reason.
Some of those general ideas and meanings
and symbologies can still apply. But in
this case, of course, it is
representative of an integrated
approach, hence the whiteness. Right.
You took the words right out of my
mouth. Well, thank you. I would have
said that, but uh I I enjoy you talking
as well once in a while.
Anyway, I came away from the experience
um anyway, he took off off up to the
ceiling and you know, just made his way
off at the same time, you know, and I
came away from the experience knowing
that yeah, I was uh truly accurate in my
estimation of how of my response and I'm
ready for the next encounter. All right,
that's it. Thank you very much. Thank
you. shouting. shouting.
Hello. Hello.
Would you discuss the dynamics of
crystals? Uh what is it about the
geometrical arrangement that allows
you of energy and what what kind of
energy is it so on? Now we have already
discussed the idea that mathematics
in that sense crystallin patterns and
arrangements of energy
are representative of what you refer to
as matter in your society.
Vibratory frequencies that interact in
very specific mathematical ratios and
relationships basically turn into what
you perceive as solidified matter. This
is all very colloquial but as the
language permits this will do. Crystals
therefore represent
a state of energy
not very far removed
from its original state as energy.
It is a type of matter that is very
close to being energy. There are very
few elements, if you will, that go into
making up the majority of crystallin
forwards and they simply take upon
themselves the structure that represents
the particular standing harmonic waves
and reveal in those crystallin
structures the patterns of energy that
create generally speaking all physical
reality. So they are triggers and they are tools
So they are triggers and they are tools
and exhibit certain harmonic frequencies
that can create what you call empathetic
if you wish or sympathetic vibrations
within you to trigger within you similar
patterns of energy to allow you in a
sense as a consciousness to crystallize
and become more synchronistically
harmonious with the background vibration
of creation that the crystals represent
as the first solidified form of you
follow me? Yes. So they function as
triggers to allow you to bring through
yourself that energy to channel that
energy of your being in a very
crystallized way in a well-ordered but
spontaneous and transparent manner so
that you become more harmoniously
aligned with the pulse the patterns of
synchronicity itself of universal
creative reality.
So they are the tools now in your
society. The tools that symbolize more
integrity, more integration, more
simplicity most of all because they have
no moving parts are made generally of
one substance in that sense and
therefore represent a simplification
of your manipulation
of the energy you use to create your
physical reality.
Soon you will no longer even need them
per se and will begin to recognize them
simply as extensions
of your beingness, of your
consciousness, as symbols of the idea,
the patterns that your consciousness at
any particular moment may choose to
exhibit itself to be. They are all of
these things and many more ideas. Does
this serve you or is there some other
specific direction you desire? Uh yes.
Um
what kind of energy is it? And um it is
light. It is that which is everything
all physical matter is created from
which is in your terms light. Although
there are very many more forms of light
than you are familiar with and able to
perceive in your particular third
density dimension. By light, do you mean
electromagnetic? In a sense, yes. But
there are many more formats to what you
call electromagnetism than the narrow
spectrum to which your senses have
access. But yes, what you are familiar
with as light is one aspect of the same
material if you wish that everything is
made of.
Different crystals will have different
different resonant yes frequencies. That
is why they are different crystals
because they are different resonant
frequencies and each a different
resonant frequency will have a different
impact on the body. Yes.
But remember they are ideas and the ones
you attract are therefore simply mirrors
to reflect the resonance pattern you
have already decided you will be. Would
you give an example of how you would use
a crystal? Oh, let us say an individual
decides that they are now more
harmoniously aligned with the resonance
of opening up their heart and emotional
energy. So, lo and behold, all of a
sudden, out of the blue, coincidentally,
synchronistically, they will hear that
rose quartz is very good for opening up
the hard energy. But the reason they
heard that and the reason they attracted
themselves perhaps to a particular piece
of rose quartz is because they are
already on that wavelength. And
therefore the court is simply a symbol
to reinforce that belief to reinforce
that attitude to reinforce that action
by providing a type of a mirror in which
the individual can see and feel in
physical exterior terms the vibration
they are already beginning to radiate of
their own decision. You follow me? Yes.
Does that ser? Yes. Thank you. Oh, thank
you very much. Sharing.
Hi Bashar. Hi, my question is tonight is
actually from my daughter, my
10-year-old daughter Allison, whom you
know, guys. Uh, for about the past three
years, she's had an entity sort of
hanging about,
uh, who identifies himself as Ralph.
and she asked me to ask you tonight
since you couldn't be here where Ralph
is from and what he's for and the
purpose of his existence in her life at
this point. The basic fundamental
agreement between them at this time in
allowing that entity to function as a
guide, if you will, as a playmate, if
you will, is to simply continuously
reflect the childlike qualities so that it will
the childlike qualities so that it will
always be known by Alisan
that you can retain those childlike
reflections, those childlike energies
into what you book will really call
adulthood upon your planet. To know that
this communication from physical to
non-physical reality between different
levels of consciousness is not something
that must end because you go into
different phases of your physical life.
It is something that can change,
something that can transform, something
that can be given new meaning, new
depth, new dimension. But it is a
recognition as it is for many children
upon your planet especially now in this
transformational age that there are many
more levels of consciousness that have
openness and accessibility to all of
you. It is quite a natural thing to
speak with levels of consciousness that
are not physical. So Ralph provides a
reflection, a mirror, an understanding of another
a mirror, an understanding of another
portion of herself that she now knows
she need not sacrifice in order to grow
up. There will be many other things that
There will be many other things that
this particular guide and mirror will
reflect throughout the life.
Not that this individual needs to be
followed, but simply it is a friend and
willing to reflect for now as a friend.
It has many ideas it will share and it
will whisper and talks with her about in
dream reality about the agreements that
she has made for this particular
physical life. It is a gentle reminder
of some of those avenues and paths that
she has chosen. It is a soother in that
way. It is an equal in that sense,
someone she can really relate to in many
different ways. Since there are many
things about physical reality that she
finds she chooses not to relate to. You
follow me? Yes, I do. So, in that way,
this being can give her some standing
and some understanding to let it be all
right to let certain physical ideas come
in that seem to want to come in because
this being reminds her she can in fact
deal with them very easily, very
smoothly, if she's willing to. Now, not
in an impertinent way, but in a loving
way make a game out of the whole thing.
You follow me? Yes, I do. It is
therefore a playmate in that sense. She
has interacted with it many times
before. Some
Now, whether this may be or not
confusing in a negative sense, we do not
mean it to be.
Some of that energy that you are
referring to, some of that consciousness
also has connections into what you would
call animal consciousness.
And from time to time there have been
and may be yet again projections of that
consciousness in what you would call
animal form for Alien to interact with
and have as a physical symbol in her
life. Okay. She feels that this entity
is from Sirius. There is some of that
connection but for now it is not let us
say putting itself in a specific format
because the true energy of Sirius is a
very open and generalized one and has a
lot to do with being very playful. Okay,
that is why the dolphins upon your
planet have such a strong connection to
it. I see. Thank you very much. Or thank you
I see. Thank you very much. Or thank you
very much. Thank her.
sharing. Thank you for this opportunity. And you
Thank you for this opportunity. And you
um speak up. Yes, I will. Uh
I have been experiencing
by meeting an individual shortly um just
a short while ago
a little bit of fear. All right. Um how
exciting. Yes, it is. It's a positive
thing. But um as I'm trying to focus as
you are focusing as I you're right as I
am focusing these days more so um I feel
I'm here tonight to get the information
that I most need to know to help focus.
All right. Well, do remember you're
going to be giving that information to
yourself basically. Yes. And you're
helping me to mirror that. Thank you
very much. What do you think you are
fearing to discover about yourself in
this interaction?
What would be to use your imagination
just for a moment if you will? What
would be the most fearful thing you
could discover about yourself that might
come out of any interaction or
relationship with someone?
Do you have such an idea? Not really.
All right.
Do you feel that that individual
represents something that is a vibration
other than the vibration of your
integrity?
What I feel is that it may have
something to do from a past life
experience, but it's really my problem
to deal with. It's not a problem. Well,
it is your joy to deal with. I
understand. I've chosen it. Yes, of
course. In perfect timing. Of course.
Thank you for reminding me. So, the
relationship as it has now arrived
represents the timing of something you
in fact do want to deal with so that you
can integrate it within the total being
that you are.
As this relationship continues, if it
does, you can then be wideeyed and alert
to what those things are about yourself.
You will be examining by seeing these
reflections from the other individual
and you can deal with them in a positive
way and integrate them within yourself
very quickly, very rapidly if you wish.
Does not have to linger. Does not have
to take a long time.
Very good. Thank you. If this is just
beginning for you, let it unfold. There
is absolutely once again nothing you
could ever discover in any relationship
you attract to yourself that cannot be
used in a positive way. Trust it. Trust
it. Do not fear that you will attract
something that is a reflection of a decision to do
that is a reflection of a decision to do
harm to yourself. Why would you want to
do that?
If you can examine your belief systems
and come to the conclusion that there
really is no reason why you must inflict
the idea of negativity upon yourself in
order to learn what it is you want to
learn, then you will not need to do so.
And if you know you do not need to do
so, there is no reason to fear any
relationship you have attracted since
you have attracted it. You must know
what you're doing. Start trusting that
and all things will become clear as to
why that relationship exists.
Do you follow me? Yes. Are you willing
to trust it? It is up to you. You do not
have to just because I suggest it. Oh,
it's I know it's a matter of trusting
myself. Yes. Yes. Yes. And this matter
of trusting yourself does not have to be
such a shaky thing.
Yes. Many of you have said to us, "Yes,
I I know it's a matter of trusting
myself." Yes, it's a matter of that.
Yes, I agree. Yes. It's a matter of
learning how trusting myself. Yes. Oh,
that's a tall order. Yes. Trusting
myself. Oh, that's a big one. I don't
know. All right. Yes. I would like to,
but I don't know.
All right.
But it does not have to be that way.
Don't give it those definitions.
Remember reality, what you call reality is a
reality, what you call reality is a
product of the meaning you decide to
give to a set of neutral props.
You follow me? Yes. So if this
relationship has synchronistic meaning
for you, which obviously it must, you
determine what type of meaning that is,
and that will determine what type of
reality you get?
Simple, of course. Too simple, probably. Why?
of course. Too simple, probably. Why?
Why too simple? Why? Why? Why? Why is it
too simple? Why is it too good to be
true? because it's so obvious. Ah, what does
because it's so obvious. Ah, what does
obviousness have to do with things being
difficult? What I make of it as a reality. Yes. Now
What I make of it as a reality. Yes. Now
remember, now that many of you are
waking up to the fact that you harbor
these patterns and these habits within
you, they are no longer patterns and no
longer habits and you can't use them as
an excuse. Oh, I suppose it will be
difficult to assume that it is therefore
simple and therefore easy just because
it has always been the habit to assume
that things can't be that simple. I
suppose that will be the thing that will
stop me. This is what many of you might
be saying. But you are only redefining
the idea again in a way you don't prefer
to. Why assume once you realize it can
be that simple? Why assume it will be
difficult to realize it can be that
simple? You are only building further
You are only building further
definitions that take you farther and
farther away from the understanding.
You actually have a true understanding
that it is that simple and it will
always work and it never won't work. And
there are no exceptions to that. Not
even you.
The universe works for everybody in it.
Everybody. If there could be such a thing as an
If there could be such a thing as an
individual that the universe would not
work for, that individual wouldn't
exist. Again, the universe does not do
Again, the universe does not do
extraneous and pointless things. So the
endeavors and the relationships and the
circumstances and the situations that
occur in your life are there for you for
a reason as a part of your synchronistic
pattern of recognition of who and what
you are as the idea and the
consciousness you chose to be.
Thank you. Well, thank you very much and
pleasant dreams to you,
Shanning. Hi, Vishar. Hi. Um, I just recently had
Hi, Vishar. Hi. Um, I just recently had
a dream and it involved,
let's see if I can get this out the way
I felt it at the time. Around the crown
of my head as if toning um on a temple
bell. A temple bell.
Okay, that's pretty good. Anyway, it was
uh resonating and it was very very
strong. No, wait. That wasn't even a
dream. It was in a meditation. Oh, and I
was very aware of it and very very good.
Losing the definitions of the barriers
between physical and non-physical
reality, between dream and physical
awakeness. When did that really occur?
In a dream, in physical reality, in a
meditation? I don't know. I don't care.
It's the same thing. Yes, it's all the
same thing. I just kind of enjoyed that
a little bit more because No, another
kind of. All right, you kind of enjoyed
it. Now, you know I am playing with you.
I am not attempting to get you to watch
every little word, but we are in this
sense playing to lighten you up. Okay.
Proceed share. All right. As this was uh
as this toning occurred,
uh the crown of my head, the energy got
very intense. Very intense. And uh then
I saw mountain ranges and they seemed
like towering mountain ranges and I
turned and I saw more and more and more
mountains all the way around and the
same circular uh toning occurred in the
m within the mountain range also. And
then it was going on simultaneously.
And I was wondering if you could Did
this feel wonderful? Yes, it did. And I
I sensed the mountains to be maybe
something like Himalayan. All right. Is
that a question? Sort of. Because I'm
trying to put it together a little bit.
I Well, go right ahead. Put it together.
What do you feel it to be? A bridge. But
I want a bridge. A bridge. A bridge
between what and what?
That's what's not clear.
That's what I'd like maybe, you know, a
little help with. All right. Little tiny
help. Okay. All right.
If you were standing in the center of a
crown, would it not look like you were
surrounded by mountains? Yes. Well,
still don't get it. All right. I'm
trying here. Oh, no. No, no, no, no.
Don't try. I know. Relax. Relax. Relax.
Relax. You said you felt the feeling
around your crown. Yes. around the crown
chakra represented by many mountains.
Mount Shasta,
the Himalayas, the third eye chakra.
Yes. The idea of the fact that you are
now dealing with that higher energy.
That is why we were justesting with you
because we are reflecting the new energy
you actually have but which you are
pretending to be timid to use.
If you had approached this idea with
some degree of jocularity, it would have
all been extremely plain and evident to
you what was going on symbolically. But
you were creeping up on it, not willing
to truly own the power you know was
yours standing in the middle of that
caldera of that ring of mountains of that crown
of that ring of mountains of that crown
of mountains which represents the
heights to which you are now going. You
follow me? Yes. You are connecting with
the earth and the sky. You are the
bridge yourself between the ground and
the heavens,
which is what mountains have generally
symbolized in your society.
Okay, you follow me? Yes. Is any of this
making any sense? And is it workable for
you at all? Yes, it is. And and
and sigh sigh. Yes. And sigh. Well, I
feel all of the uh Oh, yes. Feel Yes.
You feel what? I feel the energy. Yes, I
feel the energy. Now, would you do me a
favor? Yes. Would you say it like you
mean it? I feel the energy. Do you
really? Yes. How does it feel? Strong.
Strong. Yes. In what way?
Full of life. Full. Full of life. Yes.
Full of life. Yes.
Now that is how you feel. Yes. Yes. Is
that how you feel when you recreate the
idea of the vision that you had?
Yes. Only I think what you were saying
before about it uh approaching it
timidly. Yes. Instead of approaching it
um and recognizing myself in the picture
as the picture. Yes. I couldn't feel it
fully then. And but you can I can
absolutely. Why not? No reason not.
Remember, remember remember memory is
created in the present.
Okay? You understand? Yes, I do. It is
always the first time, every time.
Understand? Yes.
So, feel it anytime you wish by being
the idea. And when you simply know the
feeling, you have the meaning. Act on
it. It is obvious the feeling can be the
It is obvious the feeling can be the
meaning
to propel you to link you to connect you
and follow me. Yes, I do. Are you having
a good time? Yes. Are you enjoying the
exploration of who and what you are? Oh,
definitely. Are you all?
Then yes.
yes.
Enjoy your exploring during your break.
We will resume contact momentarily. [Music]
How's it going?
All I say continue.
Hello Bashar. Unto you. I found
something more interesting in my
question. Uh Abraham has this article in
a magazine on something observed. The
Kit Peak National Observatory found
three brilliant arcs of blue light which
may be the largest objects in the
universe stretching between galaxies.
Each of the crysts is more than 300,000
light years long.
Could you elaborate on on what they made
of and how they were made?
We have discussed this idea to some
degree before. They are in a sense
shell of energy, shell representations
of energy, shell representations
if you will, edge on so to speak of the
intersection of one universal reality with your
of one universal reality with your
universal reality.
They represent high intense
energy systems
that are the physicalized representation
of the intersection of two energy
systems operating at slightly different
operating at slightly different
frequencies. This is what represents one
dimension of reality, yours, and another
dimension of reality.
You will discover
throughout your explorations of what you
call space from time to time. There will
be these arcs of energy that represent
the lines, the barriers if you will, the
framework if you will between the
doorways if you will, the warps if you
will, the fabric if you will, between
different dimensions of experience.
In a sense
they are
an unusual
type of linear black hole if you will.
Again this is a very colloquial term but
they represent high compression points
of energy in which you may find the
emergence from another dimension and the
merger towards another dimension. They
are passages,
highly compressed energetic forms
radiating at a particular intensity.
They are the cleavage lines, if you
will, between some of the different crystallin
between some of the different crystallin
structures or variances of one physical
reality and another.
Is this translating into your language
adequately? I think so.
I have to dwell on that some.
All right.
You may, if you wish, liken them to some
degree to asymmetric ripples friction. Interface boundaries
Interface boundaries
of highly compressed energy representing
the interface of more than one
interdimensional reality.
Does that make some sense?
Yes. Will that do? Yes, that'll do. Thank
Will that do? Yes, that'll do. Thank
you. Thank you very much. Sure.
Good evening. Unto you. Good. I've been
focusing in on more on what excites me.
And what seems excite me or does excite
me guys is uh actually having
an interplanetary spaceship. Yes, we
understand that excites many of you as
you form different connections. Now, we
are not saying this is by any means
impossible. Recognize you have the
technology upon your own planet to
create this and many of you are
beginning to do so. The idea also about
what excites you the most to remember
what we have discussed is that at any
given moment if you act upon what
excites you the most that you are
capable of acting on it will lead you to
anything else that excites you that you
may not immediately be able to act upon
because of the way you have set
circumstances up or the way timing
actually is. Many of you will find that
your having the idea of spacecraft will be
having the idea of spacecraft will be
representative of your willingness to
utilize the technology that exists upon
your planet and create the spacecraft
you can create.
Well, I wouldn't mind if I could have
one that already exists that was not
necessarily manufactured here. Yes, I
know you wouldn't mind.
But the idea is once again not that this
is not possible is to utilize the timing
for what it is. For you will simply find
that it is not primarily the timing for
that to be upon your planet right now.
But you can bring it closer by creating
your own and meeting us halfway.
There are many things for you to
understand the principles, the nature of
that level of technology. And if you are
willing to explore them in your own
terms upon your own understanding, then
by the time you are able to access a
spacecraft whose origin does not come
from your world, you will understand how
to use it. You follow me? I'm willing to
take lessons. No,
these are your lessons. Do you not
understand? Using what you have access
to on your own planet are your lessons.
Okay. Thank you. You understand? Yes. We
understand this does not sit well with
many of you that are anxious for the
endeavor and the experience that you are
relating to. But nonetheless, it is
representative of the timing. And again,
it is not outside the realm of
probability. at all. But the timing being what it is
at all. But the timing being what it is
allows you to know that actions upon
your world must be turned in the
direction of using what you already have
access to. That is what brings any other
probability closer.
Now in your dream realities, you are in
a sense being taught how and you already
know how. When you apply this in the
reality you have chosen to exist in, you
will be acting in the direction of
showing that you know how.
You have chosen to be where you are and
you have chosen to be in the type of
society at the technological level that
society exists at right now. That is for
a reason. You can assist in the
elevation of that technology if you are
willing to apply what you actually do
already know by acting upon the ability
to create that technology in your world.
Now you will find if you act upon that
endeavor that you actually already do
know far more than you may think
and that is one of the reasons why if
you act upon that you will assist your
world in understanding what it needs to
know to understand that technology.
You follow me?
Thank you,
Sharon. Hi, Rashar. Strawberry. How are
you? Perfect. And you? You're always
perfect. Yes. So are you all in whatever
way, shape, or form you choose to be at
any given moment. Right. I wanted I
wanted to let you know that the uh
Strawberry Patch has blossomed in my
imagination and creativity into a
project called the Strawberry
Connection. All right. And uh we've
designed a glass cathedral and uh and uh
crystal structure that uh sits over the
strawberry patch. You know, I can't do
anything small in the you know who says
simply planting a patch is small. Well,
me, you know. All right. If that is the
way you wish to do it, by all means, go
ahead. Yeah. Well, it's a lot of fun
stuffing into a very creative um
endeavor. Nice.
I wanted to ask you um a little bit more
about the transition from two
philosophical points of view that I've
been into. One has been um what is true
is what you observe to be true and the
other philosophy being what you believe
is what you then perceive.
And uh what is the difference between
these two ideas? Well, one is projecting
the concept that the observation
precedes the belief rather than the
belief. You mean seeing is believing as
opposed to believing is seeing? Yeah.
All right. Um there seems to be
a
co-fusion between those two principles
in terms of operation. Nice. There seems
to be evidence supporting both sides of
it. Of course, again, as we have said,
any belief system will always generate a
selfperpetuating system of logic to reinforce the truth
system of logic to reinforce the truth
of that system. Always.
It must be so because everything is
real. Therefore, what you truly believe
will always generate a system to support
that belief. And so, of course, that
system will work for you.
when you change it another system with
logic will come into play to support it
and you will get the feedback that makes
it seem as if that system works for you
which of course it will okay so when I'm
looking on a linear time track and I see
situations in which I apparently at
least consciously absolutely believe
that something was going to occur had no
concept that it was not going to occur
and then had the opposite materialize
this is uh indicative of the fact that
there was a uh
unconscious belief system that was in
operation. Is this what to some degree?
Yes. One of the reasons we have given
the talk, we have given this evening of
your time when we commence this
interaction was to point out that there
are many many things in your assumptive
minds that you may be setting up for
yourselves that blind you to the fact
that there are opportunities that make
themselves available to you in a very
blatant way that you do not consider to
be actually very blatant. And so in
setting up a certain idea of how you
believe something will turn out and then
it turns out differently that is an
opportunity to recognize the
circumstances that are actually around
you as they are at that moment many
times have far more to do with where you
said you wanted to go than you're
willing to admit that they have. I see.
So you you were actually refusing to
have it manifest in in c in the most
apparent ways. No, not refusing to have
it manifest. Refusing to acknowledge
that some of the ways that are
manifesting around you are actually
representative of what you want. I got
you. Simply because once again, you may
not immediately see how they connect
doesn't mean that you must invalidate
them as not representing the path that
will take you where you want to go.
Okay? But it must in other words once
again to put it on a simplified level.
Let us say you have a certain scenario
that a certain individual from such and
such an organization in that sense will
come running to you. You will bump into
them. They will say hello who are you?
You will say hello I am so and so. They
will say well what a coincidence. I've
been looking for an individual like you
want to work together. You say sure
everything goes as you say hunky dory.
But the idea is in other words that if
you are walking down your street and
that is the projection you have perhaps
simply the idea that you are aware
visually that a certain organization
exists but you choose to walk past it
waiting for something else to occur in
another way that might be representative
of ignoring the opportunity because you
are simply aware that the organization
exists. You could be the one to go in
there and run to them and say, "Hello,
this is who I am. Would you like to work
with me?" That is an example of the idea
we are talking about. Are you talking
about stubborn adherence to a particular
way that it has to happen to some
degree? Yeah, I've been real stubborn in
that. All right. Must be fun. Yeah.
Okay, that's helpful. Thank you,
Michelle. Thank you very much.
Shouting. Good evening, Bash and to you. Well, um,
Good evening, Bash and to you. Well, um,
last weekend we had the cacina dreams. I
went home and I had these just
fantastic, fantastic dreams. And in one
of them,
what's real strong, an image that stays
with me is this big fountain. It's a
circular shape, a round fountain. And in
the dream, I know it had a practical
function, like maybe it was some kind of
air conditioning system for some place.
And yet it was like a landmark or a
monument of some kind also. I see. And
in the center of it, in the round center
of it were a bunch of like crystals
sticking up all different types. And
then came a scenario of some kind of
betrayal of I was someone that um had
influence over like a princess or some
kind of head of some kind of leader or
something. And these this is a very
strong Atlantean memory. God, I thought
that. Well, then why did you have to
ask? Why not say it?
Why not trust these instincts and these
feelings? Um um yeah. Yeah.
Um um yeah. Yeah.
Why not? Why not? Why not? Because it
does not have to be a literal symbol in
order for you to derive the meaning you
need to derive out of it.
Okay? Just go with it as a symbol. All
physical reality, all physical lives are
only symbolic. Yes, they are real and
they are only symbolic. You are
consciousness. All symbols within you are real. Use
All symbols within you are real. Use
them as you imagine. They move you. It
does not have to be something that you
wonder. Was this really real? Was it
really physical? If you think it, if it
moves you, if it is the symbol that
works for you, use it.
Well, guys, like I had this symbol of of two
guys, like I had this symbol of of two
lands and just the feeling that they
were ancient lands and that in the dream
there was a gulf in between two lands.
And in the dream it came like a picture
of um like two round hoops and a gulf in
the middle. I could see like an
oldfashioned map or something like that.
And so um
I got that it was about some kind of
ancient lands, but I'm not sure what
what it is for me or what it felt strong
and it stayed with me for a long time.
So, I'm wondering what is it? Well, how
does it move you?
What do you want to do with the energy
you feel?
How does it want to make you dance?
In what way do you wish to express it?
Oh, just what comes to my mind right now
is ceremonies. Ceremonies. All right.
Perhaps you can reenact, recreate
recreation, recreation, recreate some of
the ceremonies of those times,
Adalanteian, Leorian times in those
ways, and bring bubbling to the surface
the fountains of knowledge contained
within you.
Hey, cuz act out your imagination. We
have said this many times.
Do you not think we are being literal?
Well, you know, I have a a kind of a I
don't know. It seems like a real desire
lately to
be in a different dimension because this
dimension right now is as soon as you
act these dreams out, you will be in a
different dimension.
You are your own dimension. Right? So
anytime you change the idea of who you
are, you are a different dimension.
Remember, you are beginning to learn
that a dimension is not something you
are in. A dimension is something you
are. Okay.
Okay.
Now you're in a different dimension,
aren't you?
All right. You are the dimension of
laughter and light.
[Laughter] All right, I got it.
All right, I got it.
All right. Act it out. Give it a voice.
Play it out.
Okay. Does that serve you? Yeah, it does. Um,
Does that serve you? Yeah, it does. Um,
and just what's coming real strong? I
know Corey James. Can you tell me
anything about that?
only at this time that it has a very
strong musical connotation.
Okay, that is all we can share for now.
That's fine. Thank you very much.
Sharing. Hello, Bashar. Hello. Um, I never felt
Hello, Bashar. Hello. Um, I never felt
very comfortable with the usual
described history of the origins of men
and women. Yes. Uh, they tell us that
which description we perceive you have
many. Well, apes are is one. Adam and
Eve, yes, is another.
Do you have any comment as to to some
degree you will find that lo and behold
in our perception it is actually a
combination of the two ideas
both what you call your evolutionists
and your creationists are correct
because you will find that you as a
consciousness now I am going to be very colloquial for
now I am going to be very colloquial for
a moment simply because that is the way
your language is so take the essence of
this idea some of it is relatively
literal. Some of it is somewhat
metaphorical, but you will get the idea.
As a consciousness, one consciousness,
all of you as one consciousness, when
you discovered the Earth,
you discovered it had what you call an
indigenous form of life.
Not exactly what you would call an ape.
Not exactly what you would call a human.
There are many offshoots, many variants
of that idea in existence at that timing
upon your planet as a natural extension
of the evolution of your world.
You in determining that you would
project yourself into physical
materiality desired an appropriately representative
desired an appropriately representative
vehicle, a body idea. So your
consciousness altered
altered
the indigenous form of life to make it
representationally capable of being the mirror of the
capable of being the mirror of the
spirit that you were.
And in that sense, you changed the
physiological evolution
through an act of creationism
and became what you now understand
yourselves to be as human form being.
You follow me? Yes. So you molded the
clay of earth figuratively speaking in
that sense genetically
through what you would call a mutation
within your consciousness. And so you
find that evolution in that sense up to
a point is correct. Creationism up to a
point is correct. But generally you will
find it is actually a blending of the
two since you find that all physical
materiality actually exists within your
consciousness. Consciousness does not
exist within physical materiality.
I see. Um, was this is this
consciousness uh extraterrestrial? You
are all extraterrestrial and you all
belong on Earth. None of you are
original to your planet. And yet your
planet is your home. You come from
everywhere. You come from nowhere.
Now we understand in terms of linear
time, yes, you all have basic origins
along a certain path through different
star civilizations and your Earth
incarnations do represent a particular
point along that path linearly speaking.
You follow me? Yes. And therefore, very
early on in the early days of your
projections into physical materiality,
there was still much coming and going
between your Earth communities and your
extraterrestrial civilizations because
you had not yet completely forgotten who
you were by locking yourself into a
particular cycle of focus within
physical materiality in your particular
dimensional plane. Now you are waking up
again and that is why we are back.
Thanks for coming. Thank you for coming.
I had a dream recently where I felt as
though I was on another planet and as I
came back to my body, a fleet of ships
flew into my solar plexus. Nice. You
pass through the ring of ships that do
exist around your world. They are in a
slightly different vibrational plane so
that you do not perceive them directly
but they exist. Can I see them
physically in time?
in time?
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Shedding. Hello Bashar. And do you
Hello Bashar. And do you
um
I um in in the last week I'm I have a
curios curious situation. A curious
situation. There he is. Yes. Uh I have
been uh keeping myself away from
relationship uh for insight in terms of
my own uh relationship to myself
and last week um one moment.
All right. For a moment that did not
translate for it is quite impossible.
Sorry. You always have a relationship no
matter how you define it. Yes. proceed
with the definition of the relationship
you are creating. Then in other words,
what I was not creating was a male
female relationship. All right. And then
last week in a specific way, we assume
you mean correct in uh let's say a more
romantic way.
Last week
[Laughter]
okay. Um last week evidently I created
uh three rather extraordinary men um
um each very successful, powerful,
wealthy, interesting who um all seem to
be
wanting me in their life for the rest of
their life. All right. So, so I was told
by a psychic that
I carry a certain energy that was that I
came in this time from another planet
that carries a certain energy that
triggers something in a man that makes
him think that I am the one. And
so it leaves me in a bit of a strange
All right. All right. Stop. What you are
basically carrying with this idea is
that you are attracting individuals who
you are then giving an opportunity to
begin to open up and recognize the
change that's going on on your world.
That you are beginning to realize you
are all married to each other.
Yes. And that the idea of relationships
do not have to be mutually exclusive to
each other but can be enhancing. All
right. That was the the next thing I
wanted to see what the purpose of this
situation coming into that is one of
them. Okay. The other is that uh two are
in the film industry. One is a star and
producer and my feeling is that I am
supposed to be joining with them or
serving them in some way to bring
something larger than just the personal
relationship there. I tend to not
feel that a personal relationship is
what I'm supposed to do. We understand
your definition. Okay. Proceed simply
with your feeling. Do what is integrated
for you. Be who you are and you will
allow them the best opportunity to learn
who they are.
Do you see a larger sense of purpose? In
other words, is there a film that I will
bring to one or two of them? or a film
is a larger sense of purpose than
learning who you are.
Well, when one does produce a film that
produces an impact on many people, we
know impact. Yes, in life. Yes, it is
highly probable. However, not unless you
are being yourself
honestly and allow full communication
within the entire relationship.
that you are to allow them to understand
who you are truly who you are honestly.
Communication will be critical
in these endeavors. If they do not
believe they can interact honestly
then you may create difficulty in any
form of impact.
So you must be honest about who and what
you are, what you are attracting. And if
you recognize that what you are
attracting is representative of who and
what you are, then make the assumption
it is mutually enhancing, not exclusive.
And that they themselves are connected
in many ways or they wouldn't be
connected through you.
Oh great. So you're saying maintain
these three relationships. I am not
telling you what to do. I am suggesting
that you follow your cleanest and
clearest most integrated instincts and
allow things to be natural.
Not normal natural.
You follow me?
I think so. All right.
do not necessarily impose nor
superimpose the particular frame of
sociological reference upon these ideas
that your society may want you to impose sociologically
sociologically
understand if you have attracted them
all there is a reason for it
do you think I should maintain a
nonsexual relationship with that is up
to you and your feelings I cannot guide
you in this. I cannot tell you what to
do. It is your life and you have the
capability of trusting your instincts.
You have the capability of knowing why
you are doing what you are choosing to
do. But first and foremost in all
endeavors, it is our suggestion that the
lines of communication about what you
are doing be absolutely clear between
all involved
so that all know where they stand. Yes.
All. I'm doing that except with one. All
right. I'm doing it except with one. All except
I'm doing it except with one. All except
with one. What a fascinating language
you have.
[Music] Uhhuh. Complete the triad. Okay. Make it
Uhhuh. Complete the triad. Okay. Make it
all.
All right. Relax. Enjoy. Take it easy.
Observe. Act
with trust.
Do what represents who you are. Don't do
what represents who you are not.
Period. That's all there is to it. It's that
That's all there is to it. It's that
easy.
You have been together many times
before. All of you. Ah, you are simply
playing out a dance. Let it be a smooth
one. It does not have to be a struggle.
The old patterns don't have to come into
it. You follow me?
You follow me?
Yes, you will tonight.
But this one I'm with tonight in
particular really wants
really wants
an exclusive marriage relationship. You
will understand tonight.
Okay. All right. Good night. Thank you. Shutting.
Shutting.
Hello, Bashar. Hello. We're about at the
end of the 40-year cycle, and I wonder
if you could share with us what the
event might be, the character of the
event that's going to bring that 40-year
cycle, which began on July 7. There are
many events. There is no the event.
Well, much of it has to do with the
release of information that is now
taking place and has been going on for a
little while. The release of information
primarily having to do with the
existence of our civilizations that your
world knows about. A lot of this is now
taking place. It is leaking out into
your society.
It is our perception that this
particular date in the 40-year cycle
represents a high degree of probability
that within what you call three of your
year's time 1,990
of your year of counting there will be
very strong and blatant
examples of our physiological existence.
So now that you are using this 40-year
cycle to release the information to
prepare your consciousness for the
realization that you are not isolated
within the universe. 3 years will be
then the time we perceive now to where
that realization can bring about more
physiological interactions in a very
blatant way. That is primarily what is
happening. It is not simply a single
event on a particular date.
Well, a little less than as we measure
time a year ago. Yes. You me brought up
this concept of the 40-year cycle which
had begun in July 7th, 1947. The date
itself simply represents the day that
represents the exact count of 40 years
from the date in 1947 of your counting
when your society knew beyond a shadow
of a doubt that extraterrestrial
civilizations existed. Some people on
our in our civilization but not broad.
We do not make the separation. Okay.
your civilization. But a year ago, or
approximately when you first brought it
up, your communication to us, at least
my interpretation of it, suggested, you
seem to say that there would be a
specific noticeable event sometime
during May, June, July of this year. It
is now going on. An event does not have
to happen on one day. The release of the
information is now accelerated to a
great degree. Do you not recognize the
amount of individuals that are now
discussing in areas that have never been
discussed before the idea of the
existence of extraterrestrial
civilizations? Do you not see it?
Do you not see the talks? Do you not see
your media? Do you not see your books?
I that have all come out within the last
few months of your accounting.
I understand. But I I my interpretation
of what you'd said
approximately a year ago was that there
would be what we think of as an event
that would occur in a shortened period
of time. And I was wondering if what
you're telling me is that there was
there won't be a single event. It's a
continuation. There will be many single
events. Any one of which may stand out
to any one particular individual. Yes.
Yes. That's it. And then next week I go,
"No, no, no. That's it. No, no, no.
That's it. No, that's it. know that, no
that, no that. You follow me? Everyone
will perceive a number of different
events, but the whole thing is one
event. I was hoping that there would be
a physiological manifestation. And there
is
where when you mean this the EUO
sightings and all of EUO sightings and
all of that extraterrestrial those are
constantly occurring
constantly. Constantly.
Constantly.
And again, within what you call 3 years
of your time, they will be far more
blatant to larger groups of individuals
over a wider range of your planetary
surface. Good. But there are single
events going on right now. And many of
these are adding to the accelerated
momentum of allowing your society to be
aware of the fact that the information
itself exists. There are many
physiological events but many of these
events that we are referring to are not
events of extraterrestrial origin. They
are events of terrestrial origin.
Terrestrial events. Terrestrial
organized events to deal with the
dispersion of the information. I got it.
Thank you. Thanks. Shutting.
Hello Bashar. I'm to you. Um it's nice
to um hear you share um so much truth.
Um it's it's very wonderful to to be in
a moment where somebody can be so real.
So real. It is all real. We understand
what you mean and we give you our thanks
in that way. But it is all real. Um for
me over the years I've had a lot of
experience. Um, I've seen flying saucers
up close. I've heard their engines. I've
met interdimensional beings. And um, I
don't have clarity on who they are,
where they're from, and what they're um,
what they're trying to accomplish. First
of all, they are from many different
places, not just one.
Um, yeah, sure. Sure. Could you be more
specific? There are many civilizations
interacting with your world. There are
beings from what you call our world,
Esasani. There are Sirius, there are
Arcturan, there are Plleadian, there are
Reticulum, there are realizations.
Our attempt attempt
quote unquote
is in assisting your planet through its
transformation in an unobtrusive way that allows you to
in an unobtrusive way that allows you to
know you are responsible for that
transformation, not us. Yes, I I I do
realize that. Um that is our basic
reason to assist you in returning your
power to you to help you wake up take
back responsibility for the creation of
your lives so that we can then interact
as equals rather than your world
continuing to hold us up in some sort of
awe or regard above yourselves.
Um well yeah I I see what you're saying.
I mean it sort of made me feel like a
like a man with a mission because these
things started to happen to me at a very
young age. Yes. Um I mean it is a I mean
I mean there there's so many things I
could say. Yes. You are assisting with
the transformation in your own chosen
way. Continue to do so in whatever way
excites you the most. That can be done
through your integrity. The things that
excite you the most are the indications
of the path you chose to be to be of
assistance in this transformation.
That's why excitement exists to let you
know what the things are that represent
your purpose in this life.
how you can be of best assistance.
So that is why we say acting upon what
excites you the most. That is having an
equal conversation with us. Not just
talking, acting, doing, creating your
planet to be one that has an equal
vibration to our world. So we can
interact face to face. I find that um
that I am acting and I find uh that
there are limitations now and then
actually not so much I mean they're in
myself but they're also around me and
you find that when you act you find that
uh the the people around you aren't
ready to act. In other words, they
aren't ready to go on with it. So you
kind of hang out and wait. No, no, no.
You do not wait. You act, you
continuously act in whatever way you can
act. That action is what will allow other
That action is what will allow other
individuals to know they can also begin
acting. If you stop and wait, they will
wait for you. Oh, yeah. Well, I see what
you're saying. I mean, it's we
understand different individuals will
proceed at different rates. Yes. But
that doesn't mean you stop acting on the
things you can act upon. Right. Right.
In other words, you realize that maybe
this particular individual isn't the one
that you're supposed to work with. Or in
other words, you've gone to a plateau
and you realize that you need to uh
maybe do a 180 and move in another
direction, so to speak. Yes. And that is
the continuation of working with that
individual because that's what they need to see
because that's what they need to see
from you, right? It's all relationship.
Absolutely. Does that assist you? It it does. But uh
Does that assist you? It it does. But uh
actually um when I asked you more like
specifically I I remember two events in
my life and and I'd like to know uh
actually three who they are and where
they're from. No no no
because we will not label and separate
them at this time when everything is
coming together under the association
understanding for now simply consider
all members as members of the
association of worlds. Yes, you have
your specific connections. Yes, you will
discover them when you need to. But use
the energy for how it allows you to
move. If you spend time labeling them to
excess, you will focus on details you do
not need to focus upon. Okay, I hear
you. All right. All right. Thank you.
Thank you very much. And pay attention
to your dreams. The information you need
is almost always most easily accessed
there. Well, that brings up another uh
point. Um I find that in the dream world
Yes. sometimes I do connect with the
core. Yes. However, I can't remain
there. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
Yes. I know I can. I know I can.
However, I flip through it. You do
remain there if once you reinsert
yourself in what you typically call
physical reality, you act upon the
version of that core energy you still
feel. You will then create a reflection
of that core energy in the physical
reality which is the whole idea. That's
true. Creating heaven on earth right
through our through our physical bodies.
I mean to bring it manifest it in. Yes.
Remember that again your soul does not
inhabit your physical body. Your
physical body is your spirit in physical
terms. So be the spirit that you know you are
So be the spirit that you know you are
and act like it and you will transform
the spirituality of your world. Um I
find that uh maybe you can give me some
help here. I find that I used to be more
uh what I call yin or more yogic and in
in those uh days I was more able to
watch my dreams, perceive my dreams,
influence my dreams, understand my
dreams. However, these days I'm in a
more what I call yang mode or business
mode. And therefore, I find that I sleep
more deeply and that I dream less. I You
do not dream less. It is simply now that
the idea is you now are recognizing that
physical reality is the dream you are
changing. That's true. So you are
applying it on the physical side. The
same things you learned how to do on the
dream side, you now can recognize you
can do on the physical side because
physical reality is but a dream.
Literally. Period. It's one that we
create. That's true. Absolutely. Yes.
Thank you very much. Thank you.
Sharing.
Hello, Bashar. Hello. I've need an
explanation. I've um an explanation.
Well, I'm not sure what I'm doing.
You're not. I get you are having a
conversation with me. Well, it's a weird
experience when I Well, thank you.
No, when I close my eyes. Yes. And can you
when I close my eyes. Yes. And can you
all hear? When I close my eyes and think
of a peaceful place. Yes. And about love
and happiness. Yes. And I put my hands
together. Not all the way together.
There's this energy there such that I
can't even put my hands together. Yes.
Then it pushes my hands outward. Yes.
And I when I feel this, I have such a
need to wish happiness for someone or to
share it with somebody. Yes. Is that
what it's meant for? I'm not quite sure
what to do at this point. It is very
similar to the idea we just discussed.
Put it out in your reality. Use it. Flow
it. Don't hoard it. Flow it.
And just how would you transmit that
through your mind? Just think of how do
you want to? How does it excite you to
transmit it? In what way would you like
to transmit it?
What way excites you the most? Through
my mind so they might not know so you
can help people that are hurting and
they won't let you in or
just you can create a conductive and
conducive atmosphere that they may not
be consciously aware of. That is all
well and good. How will you use that
energy physically?
How will you show that you are using
that energy?
You live in a world of physical action.
Yes, you can be subtle, but that doesn't
mean you have to be absolutely unknown.
How would you um how do you want to? How
do I want to? Yes. How do you see
yourself? If you could imagine any way,
shape, or form that you could actually
put this energy out through a physical
act, how would you feel happiest doing
it? By touching them or putting my hands
around them. Then what are you waiting
for? My little companions are talking to me.
My little companions are talking to me.
Anxiety. What are they chattering about?
Oh, making a fool out of myself. Oh,
making a fool out of yourself. Let me
suggest something to you. Making a fool
out of yourself can very often be a far
more worthwhile occupation than many of
you are willing to suffer through.
For a fool makes others laugh.
And that is truly healing.
And one other thing. Do you understand
what we are saying? Oh yes. Oh yes. All
right. I since a child I've had these dreams of
I since a child I've had these dreams of
um fleets of UFOs and when I was 10 when
I lived in Canada I saw one I was by
myself and I just looked up at it and it
stopped for a few minutes then it left.
Yes. And ever since then I've had these
dreams and I picture vehicles on the
earth using magnetic powers were above
or on these parallel energy lines. We're
not using any form of energy we're using
now. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
And I see all this and I'm not This is
very very very imminent in your future.
Many of your scientists, so to speak,
and many other individuals who are not
necessarily labeled as scientists are
beginning to explore and understand that
your world does provide you an unlimited
wealth of electromagnetic energy that
you can utilize in many different ways
and replace some of the systems you are
using now for your propulsion, for
anything you wish.
Do they have anything to do with um I
know I'm particularly drawn to the
pyramids and the Stonehenge and they
seem to have a form of energy around
them that they all interconnect as
highways. Energy highways. Yes.
Your world is covered by these energy
highways. Our spacecrafts very often use
them to facilitate entry into your
dimensional realm.
There are these flow lines not only all
over the surface of your world but
between your world and every other
world. Every world is a multi-dimensional
Every world is a multi-dimensional
multiaceted gate of many dollars.
There is constant
because through that relationship to
everything else you know who and what
you are.
One other I've been feeling lately that
I'm searching for home. I don't belong
here yet when I look out towards the
stars. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. I feel I'm
home's coming to me. I feel like you are
creating whatever you imagine home to be
where you are. You are bringing home
with you.
You are creating the earth to be more
comfortable as your true home. You are
recognizing your connection to
everything else and you are using that
definition to define what you prefer
your earth to be so that it will be the
home you desire it to be. That is the
whole point of the transformation
not to run away. Yes, we understand many
of you go through that shift of when you
finally know what your connection is in
that sense all of a sudden you feel I
don't belong here. But yes, you do. You
chose to be where you are. The idea is
to simply recognize that what you are
finally perceiving is that you now have
tapped into what your world can be. You
are tapping into what experiences you
have had in other worlds and you can use
that recognition to create your earth to
be what you prefer it to be.
You follow me? Yes. So use it that way.
You do not have to fear feeling foolish.
You will do a great deal of service
in allowing other individuals to know
it's all right
to feel however they are feeling because
they can use that in a positive way.
They can absorb it and incorporate it
into whatever they choose to define
themselves to be.
You are but the definitions
you give to yourselves.
That is it. Get in touch with those true
definitions and you can define yourself
in any way, shape or form you want to.
Then once you have created definitions
you prefer. Act like it and do not
assume those definitions will not
change. Change is the only constant in
creation. But know they will change in ways that
But know they will change in ways that
befit a grander definition and a grander
one and a grander one in a positive,
accelerative, expansive, ecstatic,
neverending, neverending neverending
exploration
of creation.
You understand? Yes. Thank you very
much. I have nothing to do with it. You
are welcome. Thank you.
shedding.
Hello Vashar. Hello. Hello. Um, I would
like some direction about my own that
way. That way is the D.
That way about my own channeling
abilities. I currently I currently do
channelneled writings and they're
effortless and they bring me a lot of
joy and others a lot of joy. And then
what would I possibly have to say? Uh
well I want I've experimented a little
bit with bringing the channelneled
information into voice and
do you prefer that mode? Yes. All right.
And I feel very shy about it. Oh yes.
Why? Why shy? I don't know. Yes, you do.
I do. Uh it sounds funny hearing my
voice. I can hear myself when I do it
and uh I just
What do you think you should or should
not be hearing?
I think I I I feel like I should be in a
deeper trans state and it's very light.
You are saying that to be in a trance is
to be unconscious. No, that's true. It
is not to be unconscious.
The idea, the whole idea that we are
here assisting you in is to be conscious
channels because channeling as we have said is
because channeling as we have said is
only doing what you really love to do.
Period. That's what channeling is being
fully who you are.
The physical channel before you is not
unconscious simply conscious in a
different way. That is all.
Okay. Thank Do not put the assumption
upon it. Let it come naturally. It will
change. At first it may seem light. It
will become much deeper. But that does
not mean you will lose consciousness. It
simply means your consciousness will
shift in a different modality.
Because the whole idea is to not lose
consciousness. Do you follow me? Yes. The idea is to
Do you follow me? Yes. The idea is to
blend the unconscious, the subconscious
and the conscious mind into one aware
awake state. So that when you are
walking down your street, you are
channeling. When you are standing still,
you are channeling it. When you are
running, you are channeling it. When you
are walking, you are channeling it. When
you are breathing, you are channeling
it. When you are speaking, you are
channeling it. which simply means you
are trusting in the moment
and not paying attention to the idea of
having to watch every single word.
Be sure you're not going to look like a
fool. Be sure you have all your facts
correct. Your natural integrity will
channel through you exactly the precise
thing that is needed to be said
precisely. always
always
you follow me? Yes, I do. I think the
reason why I like doing the chneled
writings uh writing so much is because I
get to reread them and I get to hold on
to the words and I what I want to do is
to release the words and not be so
attached to them. All right, but do not
be so harsh upon yourself. Whatever way
you choose to experiment and whatever
you choose to feel about it, it's all
right. It's a part of the whole
enjoyment. It's a part of the richness.
It's a part of the spice of what you are
learning. It's a part of the treasure of
knowledge you will be able to share with
others that then choose similar
endeavors. Yes, this happened to me
might happen to you. You can do this
with it. You can do that with it. This
is what I did. Do what you want. You
follow me? Yes. Thank you. You are
mapping for the first time
this path path
of yours.
You are a discoverer, a wanderer, an
explorer. What you find has merit and
can be shared with everyone else
by letting them know this is how it
happened for me. This is how I created
it. How did you create it? Isn't that
rich? We created a similar idea in so
very different a way. Doesn't that allow
us to see the true richness of creation
in its infinite diversity?
Do not fear. Thank you. Enjoy.
We thank you. And at this timing,
we would enjoy
reflecting to each and every one of you
our enjoyment constantly
in an accelerated way in experiencing
the spice
of all of you.
You make a most flavorful dish.
You are rich beyond measure.
Beyond measure.
Taste it. You are a feast.
Dive in. You are infinitely abundant.
Share the wealth that you are for you
have it all. All of it. The universe
denies you nothing.
But experience the integrity of the
choices you have made.
Do not run from them. You made them for
a reason. Learn from them.
Relish them.
Thank you for being
such fullbodied
beings. Our love to you all. Exciting dream life
Our love to you all. Exciting dream life
and life dream to you. It is all one.
We thank you. We bid you a fond and
unconditionally loving.
Good night. [Music]
How'd it go? [Applause]