you have created with your belief
systems between spirit and physical for
it is simply that your body is your
spirit in physiological
terminology your spirit does not
literally inhabit the body this is a
perception that you have all created
because of the way you have defined your
physical reality to exist because you
think of things existing within other
things because you have taught yourself
to believe that other things exist
outside of other things you have created
the perspective the illusion as it were
the reality same thing that your spirit
and your Consciousness exist within your
body but your body is simply an
extension of the idea that you are of
the Consciousness that you are now many
times you make the differentiation Body
Mind mind Spirit Emotional Self all
these things are truly aspects of the
total idea you are and you do in
creating there to be a definitional
difference create in your experience a
real difference but that real difference
is no more solid than the definition
itself definitions are what create
reality how you view it is how you
experi experience it what you put out is
what you get back what you radiate is
the frequency that identifies with you
and that manifests in your life
definitions themselves are physical
reality physical reality is the
definition you give
it Body Mind Spirit Body Soul these
ideas these seemingly different
ideas are
simply different
reflections of the same Consciousness
that exist I'll say coexist
simultaneously with all the other
manifestations all the other ways you
have of expressing the idea the
Consciousness that you are so
simultaneously you are Consciousness as
body Consciousness as Spirit
Consciousness as mind Consciousness as
Soul as emotional self you are at the
same time all these different ideas the
same Consciousness expressing itself in
all the different ways it simultaneously
can because you are made in the image of
the infinite Creator and therefore like
the infinite Creator you are a
multi-dimensional being as well you are
a reflection of the whole and so you
have many different ways that you can
express yourself what you think of perhaps as
yourself what you think of perhaps as
different quote
unquote ideas different experiences
completely such as having a physical
experience and then having a
non-physical experience these are
simultaneous manifestations of the soul
the overs Soul the Consciousness idea
that you are they all exist now they are
analogous to different frequencies as it
were different program s if you wish to
think of it that way all going on at the
same time your focus because of what you
have defined physical reality to be
seems to be limited mostly to the
physical reality but it isn't you are
very aware on all other levels as the
total being that you are but because one
of the variables and one of the
ingredients that you have built into
your definition of physical reality has
been forgetfulness the ability to forget that
forgetfulness the ability to forget that
you are on all levels at once you have
now then created a series of
circumstances that you call multiple
life experiences to play out that
scenario that momentum of forgetfulness
and now you have arrived at the end of
that cycle now that is why you are all
as we have said many times waking up and
that is why you are exploring all these
different ideas of Consciousness and
spiritual uality and mentality because
you are remembering that you do in fact
already exist on all those different
levels that you are remembering that you
are in fact a complete and total
representation of the Infinite
Creation and therefore you are
rediscovering aspects of yourself
presentations of yourself that are
simultaneously going on in what you
simply might refer to as a spiritual
band a mental
band and any other nomenclature that you
choose to give it but it is all one
thing you it is all
you it is all
simultaneously
you it is simply different eyes so to
speak that you have all within the same
body so to speak that you
are and you can express it in any number
of ways and you are expressing it in all
the ways that it can be expressed
as you wake up to this more and more and
more you will begin to
realize and connect with all the other
aspects that you are all the other
identities that you are all the other
realities all the other dimensions that
you are notice I did not say can
are notice I did not say can
be I said that you are for you are the
total sum of existence right now all
that is Infinite Creation infinite
Creator what you may choose to call God
is all of us together and all of us
together is the Infinite Creation
realizing itself manifesting itself in
all the simultaneous ways that it is
possible to
be for anything that is conceived of is
a reality for you cannot imagine
non-existence all the things that we
usually discuss with you are simply for
the purpose of allowing you at whatever
rate you are comfortable with to realize
the self-empowerment the decision making
self-empowerment the decision making
capability the conscious Commandment
that you have to be your expression of
the infinite to live and create as you
prefer to
we extend to you our appreciation in
allowing us to reflect back to you our
utter faith and utter belief in your
ability to be whatever you wish to be
because you are already anything and
everything there is to be it's simply a
matter of focusing on whatever window or
frequency or perspective of the self you
already are that you per prer to focus
as it is not a matter of a long and
difficult process to become something
you are not it is the simple flick of a
dial to another program that you already
are this is what we always find most joyful
this is what we always find most joyful
to reflect to you your own inner light a
light which illuminates every corner you
have created nothing is hidden from that
light when you decide that you are
willing to allow all to come to the
surface and when you are willing to do
that I guarantee you there is absolutely
nothing you will ever discover about
yourselves that cannot be applied in a
loving and positive way in your life
unless you choose to believe differently
but that is up to
you we remind you that when we talk
about the IDE of using trust we are not
telling you to do something you have
never done before we are not telling you
to do something you don't know how to do
all of you have always I know I know
some of you may not believe this all of
you have always used utter trust 100%
faith and trust throughout your entire
life simply matter of whether you trust
in negative or positive
reality but the mechanism m is the
same you have always trusted in
something whether it be a negative or a
positive so recognize that when we talk
about using trust you do not have to
pull out a large Dusty machine that has
never been used and take it all apart
and break it all apart and toil and
struggle and sweat to scrub it and clean
it as if it is absolutely fossilized no
if Works flawlessly and always has it
doesn't care this mechanism of trust
whether you feed negative beliefs or
positive beliefs into it it will simply
spit out at the other end whatever you
have put in
automatically and there is nothing
within that device that has a mind of
its own that will take what you put in
and turn it around into something that
you did not put in there is nothing
hidden within it the mechanism is simply
simply the idea that you are at any given
the idea that you are at any given
moment the idea you are willing to be at
any given moment the idea you have the
conviction to be with integrity at any
given moment that is all there is to it so all
moment that is all there is to it so all
we are doing in assisting you is
redefining the idea of reality that you
have been living to allow you to
recognize you can redefine it any way
you want to any way you prefer to
and that the mechanism has always worked
and always
will and there are no exceptions in
terms of your ability to use that
mechanism you all use it you always
will no one is excluded from having the
knowledge of using that mechanism if you
were you would not
exist existence itself implies that you
work the mechanism
flawlessly for everything that exists
fits there is no such thing as an
extraneous creation you can label yourself that way
creation you can label yourself that way
if you wish you can believe that you
lack deserv ability if you wish but by
definition if you exist you must fit
otherwise you would not
exist so to begin with at least Grant
yourself the ability the respect
the deserve ability and the
unconditional love out of which you were
created to Simply know beyond a shadow
of a doubt that no matter what process
you may choose to create you have what
it takes to create what you prefer
regardless of how you get there you have
what it takes or you wouldn't exist
period we thank you for this opportunity
in sharing with you we thank you for
choosing to function at this time as
ambassadors of your world for that is
what you are right now and we thank you
for allowing us to function as
ambassadors of our respective worlds for
I speak for
many and bit by bit and day by day your
willingness to co-create these
interactions and your willingness to
discover yourselves and be equal with
us is what creates an atmosphere that
makes it conducive for us to meet you
face to face in time where we can
function as equals share as equals
explore as equals in
ecstasy we thank you for this gift of
sharing in return I ask you now how may
I serve
you pouty Bashar good day to you body
and soul God that you know what they can
make a movie and a good song title out
of that one all right anyway I'm not
excited I don't know it's been like this
for quite a while I think the znob
you're talking about I lost it and I
can't tune the dial oh all right are we
in this case supposed to be laughing at
a joke uh normally I'm a comedian but I
don't feel very funny right now all
right so anyway it's been going on uh for
so anyway it's been going on uh for
quite a spell now and I uh now you do
remember that when we talk about the
idea of doing what excites you that
doesn't necessarily mean that every
single moment you're going to be jumping
up and down the idea of a peaceful
knowingness and absolute certainty can
also be representative of that
excitement of that vibration that
represents that you know that you are in
in synchronous alignment with the path
you chose to be doesn't mean you have to
be running around all the time it can be
a very steady conviction a balanced
knowingness a certainty understand oh
yeah that's kind of I guess the way it's
been just relaxed and I want a little
more excitement than that then what
would you like to do I don't know well
the closest thing to excitement is I
saved a girl last week from getting
raped all right I quit chasing her
all right you see you have the ability
to create a higher vibration with your
humor yeah do you find that exciting oh
yeah but it's shortlived why lived
because I don't always have an audience
to stand up in front of and tell jokes
too well any time you are willing to be
that person you will always have an
audience automatically I was hoping I'd get some
automatically I was hoping I'd get some
uh
deep uh subject of advice or uh
something to look at instead of gentle
flow which I oh gosh I don't know how to
ask you the right questions cuz even
last time I talked you I didn't ask any
question I just kind of talked a little
bit all right now the idea of wanting
something to be exciting what's wrong
with right now being exciting do you
remember the question we asked all of
you as to what was the most important
thing of all yep and the answer was
where I'm at right now the thing you are
doing right now therefore if you truly
allow yourself to understand that what
you are doing right now is and must be
by definition the most important thing
of all at any given moment then you will
start looking at it that way when your
attitude changes you will start
realizing that you are where you are for
a reason and will start allowing
yourself to get out of the moment what
you really need to rather than perhaps
assuming that this moment contains
nothing for you that would generate
excitement have the Curiosity and the fascination
have the Curiosity and the fascination
of a child and you'll be excited about
everything are you trying to tell me I
should go get that knob that I got
locked up in the drawer and turned to
Channel A little bit yes a child would
create the knob aha understand where is
your imagination oh boy I think I left it in
imagination oh boy I think I left it in
the second row all right the second row
is within you you can go and search it
and if you find it exciting to search
for it you will keep searching for a
long time once it becomes more exciting
to have the knob you will find the
knob obviously though at whatever rate
it takes that is obviously what you have
defined to be the most exciting thing
sometimes an individual can say that I
wish dullness to be what excites me for
now I wish to play around in the idea of
boredom this this is not dullness or
boredom it's more like a limbo and as I
if I look at it deeply it I get this
lorean aspect and I uh it's kind of just
hanging there and that's lorian aspects
do not just hang I got mine Tied by a
rope I guess on the
ceiling understand that a limbo State
mhm is for the purpose of recognizing
that everything in that limbo state is
an equal opportunity so act upon the one
you want to if they're all equal it
doesn't really matter which one you do
act upon and if you act upon one it may
become more obvious which one you really
would prefer to act upon but act upon
something and everything else will fall
into place the limbo state is not for
the purpose of remaining in it in an
inactive way the limbo state is to allow
you to understand that you are not
particularly locked into any specific
reality you don't have to be it is for
you to understand that you are now open
to any reality you want to be open to
and to act in a Direction the limbo
state is not for sitting in unless
that's what excites you to sit in that
limbo state but the only reason it would
continue to feel just like a limbo state
is because you simply are only acting
within the idea of maintaining the limbo
State rather than acting upon any one of
the opportunities the infinite number of
probable opportunities that are offered
to you in that limbo
state so the idea again is to act upon
your imagination if you have here is a
very simple mechanism all of you this
will work for anything and
everything very simple your imagination
as we have discussed is the template the
blueprint if
you conjure up in your imagination an
image a vision of how you prefer to
be then take whatever situation is going
on in your life hand it to the you that
you conjured up that is representative
of the excited person you would prefer
to be and watch how the U in your
imagination handles the situation you
have given them then copy
them and you'll get the same effect that
they get in their excited state of
handling all things in that excited way
that's what your imagination is for to
copy it it gives you the picture the
blueprint the path the methodology the
ritual whatever will work best for you
create an image and mimic mirror the
image then you will be that person and
you will have that lifestyle
automatically that's what a child does
it sees and it becomes it sees and it
becomes it sees and it becomes it does
not question whether what it sees is
valid a child knows it is within
Integrity so it doesn't have to stop and
question it it sees and it becomes it
expands and it
grows you can do that you can play it is
up to you thank you for that I basically
already knew what you said but I sure
love to hear you say it well thank you
but remember we are only reflecting what
you do already know and you do not
necessarily need me to reflect it thank
you again thank you very much have a
good day for playing with us okay see
you later all right
shoting Bashar good day to you good day
to you I'm in a rather unique position
I'm really
enjoying myself now I have a wonderful
attitude I feel good but I recently had
One Moment One Moment One
Moment if you please if you please would
you do me a favor sure all right thank
you replace the word butt with and and
yes I am in a wonderful place a
wonderful attitude I feel good and and
not but and I recently had a very bad
but and I recently had a very bad
physical situation I had a heart attack
oh all right it's hard to tell by
looking or listening but I did I've had
all kinds of advice yes about how to
proceed from this point on yes I don't
wish to do anything nothing at all I
prefer having a good time had a good
attitude looking good and feeling good
and that is not something it is great
but it is opposed to medical
advice in what
sense bypass surgery has been suggested
all right for one how does that allow
you to examine
yourself when you are given an
opportunity to examine that particular
belief system what does it get you to
face within yourself what does it allow
you to examine within
yourself I what comes
I what comes
up what comes up is a an expectation
that a change would take place which is
not within my control ah why
not uh my own position would be that I
would be sedated
yes uh going through a traumatic
invasion of my body but if you have
agreed to it why would it be that way or
have to be that way if it is
representative of your belief system and
you are choosing to follow your belief
system it doesn't necessarily have to be
represented that way not that we are
suggesting that it must be the only way
but if it is representative of your
belief system and you make the conscious
choice to do it believing that it will
be of reflective assistance to you it
doesn't have to be traumatic one
definition doesn't necessarily have to
bring along with it any other definition
they are not automatically attached
you can Define any idea in any number of
ways you can say quite easily heart
surgery is traumatic heart surgery is
easy both are true and
real or there can be many other ways
that are alternatives as well but they
are all just as
equal and have been certain others have
been presented all right to me does one
strike a stronger cord with
at the present time no none seems to be
better than the choice I'm making now
which which is just to
continue all right are you owning the
creation yes what is it you are discovering about
yes what is it you are discovering about
yourself in having created that
situation in your life in other words
why do you believe you needed to create
that situation it's just a wonderful state of
situation it's just a wonderful state of
being that I'm in I mean the heart
attack the heart attack yes why did you
choose that manifestation in your
life have you owned creating the heart
attack through through
a a a uh long period of doing something
bad for my body namely smoking all
right and again in of
itself no physiological idea is
intrinsically positive or negative
although you can recognize things that
might generally carry a negative flow
based on the mass conscious belief
system of any particular society and if
you carried with you the idea that it
was negative for your body then
examine why you would choose to have
done that why you would have chosen to
create the attack as you did did it
serve you in a positive way to have
created that attack
the way I feel now yes all right it must
have because I feel wonderful if you can
recognize the reason for any particular
physiological circumstance in your life
and allow yourself to receive the
information within you and recognize
that you are willing to receive that
information in other ways not
necessarily as abruptly attention
getting then you will allow yourself to
let that information in in smoother ways
and will not necessarily have to bring
yourself to the brink of an attack to
force yourself to look at something that
you refused to look at before and then
you can allow the original symptom to
clear up if it is really no longer
needed if there is something that it
brings to you information that it brings
to you that you are not willing to face
and integrate within you then it will
probably reoccur to continue to force
you to face things you are denying that
you should be looking at but if you are
willing to understand why you created it
the reason why you created it get out of
it the information you need to except
that you can get the information in
other ways more positive ways change the
attitude accordingly then the whole idea
can clear
up it is simply a matter of whether or
not you are bypassing the information
you need to be looking
at no pun intended for
sure are you understanding
yes have you gotten in touch with how it
has served you in that way do you feel
you understand
completely why you created that issue to
divert your attitude in another flow
don't know if I ever would understand
completely but I do do you understand it
enough to have created the Divergence of
the attitude yes then you understand it
as completely as you need to if you are
willing to trust that that is truly how
it served
you if you have examined it in that way
then trust that you are now allowing a
flow to generate through you and the
flow will clear out anything that you
would call a blockage but it is up to
you always examine what your strongest
belief system really is for
regardless of how you think you would
like to use it if you actually trust
more strongly in the belief system of
the surgery being able to do something
for you other than your own decisions
making a difference then it would be
strongly suggested that you follow your
strongest belief if you want
to understand yes thank you but sure has
this served you yes oh yes thank you
very much thank you
you
sharing hello Bashar and to you good day
um I'm sitting here trying to figure out
why I've created the reality of having
to go to the bathroom at this particular
moment in time all right
um are you dealing with
urgency oh that could be real
appropriate right um my question or my
brings you into the moment doesn't it
yes certainly
does um not scattered now are
you you know right where you are oh
yeah may I String this out a little
longer oh
sure all right go ahead thank you
um my husband and I um have been married
about two and a half three years and um
he we're we're kind of at an impass in
terms of kind of at an impass he is very
much drawn to the Pacific Northwest yes
he has a very strong urgency to move
there oh urgency again all right yeah it
seems I think it's an appropriate word
because it seems to have become much
more urgent lately and um why oh I I
think he's been examining where he
really wants to be all right um I think
he likes the the weather a lot of rain
and what about you I like those things
too but I'm having some difficulty with
it I love him very much I want to be
with him but I have um a couple of ties
here namely my family that I'm very
close with um that get a lot of love
support sustenance from and my business
is here were I to um upo and go to the
Pacific Northwest I would um be um
leaving those two things may I ask you a
question yeah now I am not attempting in
any case to
imply that you should or should not make
a move however in reexamining your
definition of this situation
the question I would enjoy asking you is
why are you looking at that type of a
move as an uproot as opposed to an
expansion good question why do you
assume that a physical move in space
represents a cutting off of
attachments I don't know but that's what
I've been doing all right do you have to
do you have to create that assumption
can you envision that if you truly do
desire to go to that area and you truly
do desire to maintain those connections
as you have said that if both of those
things really do represent the overall
idea of you functioning within your
strongest intention and strongest
integrity and strongest excitement that
somehow automatically those two things
would be seen as details of the same one
idea and that they would automatically
find a way to fit and that the timing
would work itself out one way or another
to allow you to not feel cut
off that your circumstances and
situations would simply surprise you by
giving you opportunities to always be
where you need to be when you really
need to be
there and that you are not isolating or
stranding yourself on some Far distant
asteroid I hadn't really thought of it
like that all
right just as a little suggestion please
perhaps simply to put certain things in
perspective and again this is not
necessarily to imply that you should or
should not
move take one of the maps that exist of
your planet on whatever scale you wish
to perhaps the smallest one you can find
and see just how short the distance is
between where you are now and where you
say you want to
move okay you can create it to be
experientially speaking the same
place understand it's all a matter of
perspective may seem like a great
distance from one point of view but it
doesn't have
to if you are many thousands of your
miles out in space and you are looking
at your planet doesn't seem like such a
great distance at all does it no so
you're saying it's it's more of a
perspective yes of course there is no
reason to assume that you are going to
be stranded if your life is flowing in a
natural direction and you really do
prefer to be in a certain area and you
really do recognize that you have a t
ments to other areas then assume they
are all inclusive and mutually enhancing
within the overall idea you are
expanding into and not mutually in that
sense excluding of each
other understand you are broadening your
horizons yes many individuals
paradoxically enough sometimes will find
to help reinforce that sense that they
haven't really necessarily put space or
distance between themselves and other
individuals or situations will find that
sometimes when they make a move many
times they actually wind up seeing the
individuals they moved away from more
often than when they live right next
door to
them understand yes so you do not
necessarily all we are saying have to
assume that the move automatically
implies a cut of your ability to be
where you need to be when you need to be
there understand yes let yourself
assimilate all these things as details
that all fall under your overriding
intention and that will allow them to
fall into line how they need to
automatically because all details pay
attention all
details are subordinate to your
overriding intention your intention is
not subordinate to the details in your
life you create the details with your
intention so when you expand your view
your definition your intention of
yourself all the details that you have
in your life that truly need to be there
will find a place to fit by definition
remember we said there are no such
things as extraneous and pointless
Creations if they belong in your life
they'll fit and they'll allow your life
to work as you want it
to understand yes thank you so let it
soak in and then allow the natural
decision the obvious decision to come up
and also do remember that even if
sometimes one individual and another
individual prefer different areas
physically speaking you are still
speaking you are still
connected you do also not have to assume
again that the idea of physical
distance in any way shape or form has to
be in your terms a hamper on the
relationship you
are understand yes does that serve you
yes thank you thank you very much
sh
Shing hello Bashar and good day to you
good day to you my question is I have
been married for 9 years all right and
my husband um a little over 6 months ago
decided he no longer wanted the
responsibility of being married and
being a father and my daughter and I are
now in a transitional State oh all right
and wondering where we're going all
right namely will I find my soulmate in
this lifetime well I've already been
with several
now once again we understand what you
mean when you use the term soulmate but
it has many times a broader definition
than you all think any individual you're
interacting with at any given moment
must by definition be your soulmate for
that moment because they're the on you
need to be with at that moment obviously
or you'd be with someone
else so in a sense that's one definition
of a soulmate for all relationships are
for the purpose of allowing you to learn
what you need to learn about
yourself and by being of service to
allow the other individual to learn what
they need to learn
now the
idea about what you typically referred
to as a soulmate can be very easily
understood when you recognize that
everyone is simply a
reflection in different ways to
different degrees of other individuals
that they interact with and if you are
looking for an individual that in your
terminology represents ecstasy
Joy spontaneity
spontaneity
creativity I assume this is what you
usually mean when you say I'm looking
for my soulmate correct be those
things by yourself be the complete
relationship with yourself that you are
and then you can attract an individual
into your life to reflect those things
you are
being sometimes the idea that you need
that soulmate in order to be happy
because you don't believe you're
complete without it means you're usually
going to attract an individual to
reflect your belief in your own
incompleteness if you know you are
complete within the relationship that
you are and simply would like to Express
a sharing of equals with another
individual you can attract an individual
who functions on an equal vibratory
plane to share with as an equal not
because you need them in the classical
sense but because they are you and you
are them because you are reflecting
identically to each other the joy and
the Ecstasy and the completeness you
know you are now when we say complete
that doesn't mean you're not going to
grow doesn't mean you're not going to
change doesn't mean you're not going to
learn saying complete doesn't mean
you're
finished being complete simply means you
know and trust at any given moment that
if you are in your terms doing the best
you know how to do with
Integrity then you are completely
whatever idea you are being in that
moment and whatever idea you are being
in that moment is absolutely equally
valid to any other idea you have ever
been or will ever be it stands on its
own as its own
idea it is not worse or judgmentally
better in an invalidating way than
anything else you have ever been it is
different it can be more expansive can
be grander in scope and
perspective but it is
equal equal and complete as what it
equal and complete as what it
is if it changes it is something
else it is not a better this it is
different it may be more conducive to
the way you prefer to be it may be more
representative of that but it isn't a
better this it's something
else because you every time you change
are a different person
literally because a person is your
artificial projection of an idea you're
being at any given moment so now you are
being given an opportunity
an opportunity in this sense to fully
feel the totality of your being if that
individual has definitions within their
reality that make them believe that
responsibility is a matter of Burden
rather than
Freedom then you have attracted into
your life an
individual that now that you have
reached a certain point of understanding
simply no longer complies with your
frequency and by definition must go
their way because they may still be
working on something or are working on
something different than you but this
gives you an opportunity to recognize
that you have changed as well and
therefore you can allow that
change to be representative of the ideas
you desire to become and in becoming
those new ideas those expanded ideas you
will then attract whatever individuals
are representative of whatever level you
are willing to have the conviction to
express in your life the stronger the
conviction the more willing you are to
represent the fullness of who you
believe yourself to
be then the more reflective the
individuals you attract into your
reality will be on that
level and if you are simply fully
willing at any given moment whether you
are finished learning or not which you
never will be but if you're willing to
express the fullness of who you are at
any given moment with absolute trust
then you usually wind up attracting an
individual who will reflect it right
back to you and that is usually what you
refer to as a
soulmate the one you made an agreement
with to reflect to you when you were
operating on
full when you have the willingness to
believe in yourself utterly even if you
were not yet the definition you prefer
to be you still trusted that you are
operating in the capability of becoming
that idea understand fully thank you for your
idea understand fully thank you for your
wisdom oh oh oh it is your
wisdom or it is ours together to share
it belongs to everyone it is not mine in
that sense I do not own it you help put
it into perspective all you need to do
is find out what it is that represents
the excitement in your life and do it
act on it with Integrity because
excitement is the vibration that
represents who you are that's why you do
get excited about things because what
excites you is who you are act on it
trust it it will support
you thank you I will do that thank you
pleasant dreams to
you Shing good evening and to you good
Shing good evening and to you good
day is there indeed a
planet we would call
Deus and are there Souls incarnated on
the Earth plane from that planet at this
time for the purpose of observation of
some sort we are on familiar with the
sort we are on familiar with the
terminology of that name will you define
it in terms of location and your
understanding okay I'm not really sure
because I don't understand it either I
have a friend who thinks she may be from
this planet all right and it's evidently
a planet that's been discovered since
I've been out to seea I work on ships I
haven't heard anything about it I've
asked people and uh she at first thought
people were approaching her and telling
her she was from Venus and then she read
or heard somewhere that there was a
planet discovered recently called
Deus do you have a spelling I think it's
d e m u s or d e m i u
s the only idea that we can make a
reference to through what we understand
of your society's
knowledge would perhaps be the
idea of one of the Martian moons
but that was already known by all of you
mhm there has been no planet in that
sense that has been
discovered in what you might call your
astronomical sense by any of you I see
for the
idea of any other planetary
body not within your own solar system at
this time is beyond your technological
capab ability to perceive yeah I believe
it supposed to have been in our solar
system then you are perhaps discussing
an idea that is in another dimensional
plane I see and in that sense what you
might be referring to are in your
terms psychic or telepathic recognition
uhhuh rather than the idea of
physiological Discovery now one moment one moment
Discovery now one moment one moment
[Applause]
as far as we can perceive at this time
and this may not be in your terms a
complete picture for this energy seems to be
picture for this energy seems to be
somewhat coming in from a
tangent what we can perceive of the
connection that is being referred to may
be as follows
in what you would call your past in
other civilizations upon your world
there were an influx of incarnations
from other
planets and it may simply be a general
representation reference here and there
to other civilizations but it is our
perception that this may represent In
general the overall influx of
incarnation from other systems at
certain times in your planetary history
I see to which this individual May
belong to one of those
influxes all right well thank you very
much well thank you now One Moment One
Moment One Moment if that
if that
individual in a centered
meditation will simply flow with feeling
not analysis but just
feeling and reason not forsaking reason
but not overly analyzing flow with a
vibration they think represents that
connection
mhm within what you call
approximately the time frame of three of
your weeks they can attract further
information that will help clarify that
connection into their
lives I'll pass that on thank you very
much thank you is that all that's it
thank you shooting hi
shooting hi
Hi how are you today of your time well I
much better to today much better today
yeah all
right um how will you be tomorrow
hopefully even better hopefully means
you doubt it well I've been having a
really hard time oh hard time oh right
do share so that all may learn how to
apply your sharing In Their Own Line
okay it's kind of I'm kind of nervous
why in front of all these people because
they are all extensions and aspects of
you all you're doing is standing in
front of your own mirror proceed okay
I'm just afraid of my emotions afraid of
your emotions
why because they get out of control no
they don't you can choose to allow them
to but they don't have a mind of their
own you
know also emotions are reactions to
something you believe to be
true now we will extend to you the
understanding that this interaction for
us is also the first
time everyone is new every moment mhm so
even if there are other
people they're doing this for the first
time too so by all means sh
too so by all means sh
okay
um last Saturday night I um yes took a
whole bunch of sleeping tablets and oh
all right I'm laughing now yes yeah and
right I'm laughing now yes yeah and
so um I was just it was just like I was
going to the refrigerator to to uh have
a glass of apple juice or something and
I just took them thinking I was going to
you know go to sleep and the reason that
I did that was because I would I've
under the past 3 or 4 months I've been
just under a real emotional decline to
where um I was just becoming totally
functionless yes and um it's kind of a
long story but the that's all right I've
got the whole picture okay the trigger
for me doing this yes was that I thought
that I had become so intensely
emotionally negative and insecure that
my boyfriend was going to abandon me
because I knew how intense and negative
I'd become and I know that's not my real
self because I've I've seen me as
another person oh yeah it's all right
now any self at any given moment that
you choose to be is your real self
because you can create your persona to
be anything and anything you created to
be is real and by the way any vibration
of emotionality you are feeling right
now now is helping you to release and
balance and Center yourself so don't
worry about the
tears you know what you are doing and
you are processing just
fine however the idea of the sleeping pills
however the idea of the sleeping pills
May simply have been symbolic and
representative of the fact that you are
finally becoming
tired of trying to be someone you're not
mm I know all right
now have you allowed this
experience to let you finally give
yourself permission to be who you prefer
to
be yes yes I've noticed some changes
already I've I've noticed incredible
changes it's almost like it
was I had to force myself to hit rock
bottom in order to get out of the block
we have noticed that many of you on your
planet are very clever in using that
technique many
many
times you will have bought into belief
systems so
strongly that the only way you will
allow all avenues to be equally up is to
hit dead botom or what you think is dead
botom however now that you have allowed
yourself to go through the
void you have now brought the power of
Creation with you for you were willing
to face
yourself and make a decision to continue
with the life and to know that you are
empowered you took yourself through the
D you are on the other side in a sense
the old you did
die and a new you is now in
existence with an utterly new present
and an utterly new past and an utterly
new future because whatever you are in
the present is what creates your past
understand yes yeah
so now are you willing as the new you to
Simply know that you can do the things that
know that you can do the things that
really excite you in life and that those
things really will support
you it's all right if there's still some
doubts I I have I have doubts because I
don't trust like I I said I don't have
enough trust in my emotions I've been
all right I went through now one moment
one moment
okay very
well and you were
worried now remember what we discussed at the
now remember what we discussed at the
beginning uhhuh all of you have always
used trust you trust perfectly in your
emotions it's simply that you trust more
in the negative ones than the positive
ones you trust implicit
licitly it is simply that you are
choosing to believe that your emotions
have a mind of their
own that's your choice to believe that's
your definition and it is your
definition that seems to give them
independent power they don't have
independent power you are utterly controlling them
power you are utterly controlling them
on your
strings utterly but you have created a
utterly but you have created a
definition that allows the strings to be
invisible to you so that you think they
have a life of your own and do not
notice the connection between the
movement of your hand and the movement
of the puppet that you are calling the
emotion start noticing that they only
move when your hand
does in other words the emotions only
will flare up in that sense when you
believe most strongly in making the
choice that they can act autonomously
then the strings become invisible as
soon as you understand wait a minute I
am empowering them they get their power
from me they don't have any other
me they don't have any other
source therefore I must be choosing to
activate them in that way now why would
I want to choose to activate them in
that way if I don't prefer it why would
I choose that scenario must be something
I believe in must be a definition I
bought into do I I prefer this
definition yes no no what definition do
I prefer this one then since I know my
definitions are what have created my
reality I can assume that my new
definition will create a new reality
because it's always worked that way you
have always used that mechanism you have
never not used it you function
flawlessly you always get what you most
strongly believe you will
and remember fear is a strong negative
remember fear is a strong negative
belief and it empowers itself in that
sense through
you anytime you put most of your
investment into one particular point of
view it's going to generate a
self-perpetuating cycle of expansion a negative spiral or
cycle of expansion a negative spiral or
a positive one it doesn't care it only
takes its orders from you
or you believe in negative emotionality
all right here it
comes oh you believe in positive
emotionality all right here it comes it
doesn't care you make the choice to
believe and when you make the choice
that's what you get so it isn't as you
say running a
muuk remember that even if it seems you
are out of control you are creating that
situation so you're in control of
creating the illusion that you're out of
control you always control it it can't be any
you always control it it can't be any
other way there is no other source of
energy other than the energy that comes
through you to empower anything that has
to do with you it doesn't come from
outside there is no outside it cannot
act on its
own understand yeah I understand I I
understand intellectually oh thank you
thank you One Moment One Moment very
good listen to the belief
system I will say I understand
intellectually because everyone knows
that is different from understanding
emotionally why because you define it to
be different if you know you understand
at all why not assume you understand as
you need to instead of continuing to
believe in the segregated definition of
understanding it intellectually and
understanding it emotionally belief in
the segregation is what creates the
feeling that there is a segregation in your
that there is a segregation in your
understanding believe that when you
understand you do understand on all the
levels you need to and that the idea of
levels in and of itself is your creation
you really are not composed of levels
you're one thing one Consciousness so
take it for granted not that I have in
this sense forced you to not that I say
you must because you don't have to but
we can suggest that it's all right to
take it for granted that when you
understand something at all you
understand it period on whatever scope
in whatever perspective you need to and
that if you simply relax into the notion
that you understand it that relaxation
will allow you to begin to
experience in concrete terms that you do
in fact understand it more completely
than you originally thought you did
understand I'm trying to all right relax
it's not that
complex you're making it more complex
than it has to be as simply as I'm
stating it it is that
easy may I ask you a question yes thank
you do you
believe that things have to be difficult
in order to be valid
up to this point my life has proven so
because my life has been very very I've
made my life very very difficult all
right next question do you wish to
continue to believe no well
fo now now now now here One Moment One
Moment One here's the fine line and
here's how your Society usually chooses
to Define these things all right you say
now I don't prefer to believe that
things need to be difficult in order to
be valid and usually the next question
is so how do I make them easier you
don't you allow them to be easier by
understanding that once you have the
ability to conceive of how you would
prefer it to be your ability to conceive
of it is the manifestation of that
reality that's it you don't need any
long involved process in order to make
what you have conceived come true the
conception is the reality all you have
to do is act like you know that trust
that if you have the ability to conceive
of it you are it the second you are
aware of any way in which you wish to be
you are even as you imagine that way
creating that vibration in your life
that vibration means you are at the
moment you're conceiving of it living
that way just start acting like that person
way just start acting like that person
from that moment forward say well what
would the person I prefer to be believe
in what types of belief would the person
I believe I wish to be have within them
they would believe this not this they
would believe this not this they would
believe life is easy
believe it it's just as valid I
understand that your Society is in the
habit quote
unquote of
invalidating one phrase over another
phrase because of what it thinks is
experiential evidence that one phrase
has more validity than another but that
experiential evidence so to speak that
the negative occurs more often than the
positive is only because you originally had that
is only because you originally had that
belief and all you're doing is
reinforcing the original belief with
experiential evidence remember that the situation in
evidence remember that the situation in
your life does not occur before the
belief the belief exists first then the
physical reality is experienced which
can reinforce the
belief but the physical experience
didn't create the belief the physical
experience comes into manifestation
to bring to the surface to a conscious
recognition what may have been an
unconscious belief but it was a belief first
belief but it was a belief first
nonetheless so once you have the
physical reality and you recognize I
don't prefer this reality it's there to
show you that you had a belief that that
was the most likely reality you could
manifest therefore it gives you the
opportunity not to believe you're stuck
with it not to believe your failure but
to show you look this is what you
believe if you don't prefer it what
would you prefer to believe as soon as
you redefine it your physical reality
says to you I'll match
it I promise I guarantee you I can't do
anything else that's what physical
reality is about I've been able to do
that with some things all right then use
those as examples and apply them over
the entire scope of your reality no sit
situation is inherently now pay close
attention to this no situation is
inherently more difficult than any other
situation only your definition of that
situation makes it seem to be more
difficult than another situation so get
involved in clarifying your definitions
of why one circumstance would seem to
have to be more difficult to accomplish
than another one understand what you
believe that makes it seem more
difficult once you have clarified why
you believe this is more difficult than
that then it won't be you will allow
them to be equal you will understand the
definition you have bought into and you
can rewrite it and as soon as you
rewrite it it will replace the old
definition automatically just live as if
it has done so and you will get the
effect in your life that it has it is a
simple mechanism let it be that simple
it is that that simple I guarantee
it it is that easy nothing is too easy
too simple or too good to be
[Music] true as we have said a few times one of
true as we have said a few times one of
the greatest I'll say shocks not meaning
it in a negative way one of the greatest
shocks to your overall Society
collectively and individually will be to
allow yourself to finally discover that
what you have always thought of has a
fairy tale attitude is actually the way
life works
of believing is
seeing not seeing is believing that's
how that's how I that's how I know the
reality to be then act like you know it
you know you because of the pressures of
society everyone tells you you can't be
like this W it's
wo whoo I just freak out whoo
whoo there are no pressures in society
that you can feel if you don't buy into
them just because other individuals may
choose to send pressure doesn't mean you
have to sign for
it send it
back and I do not mean send pressure
back simply don't accept the
charges you don't have to you are your
own reality they are their reality
whatever they choose to send you you can
look at it examine it say all right well
I like this I don't prefer that accept
what you prefer send the rest
back there is no pressure other than the
pressure you buy into your
reality you have to accept it you have
to believe it belongs in your reality in
order to feel the pressure If you don't
believe it belongs in your reality you
won't feel it it will be what you call a
non seiter it won't relate to
you what do you mean you don't like my
orange skin I don't have orange skin
that doesn't relate to me you must be
talking about someone
else anything that doesn't belong in the
reality you have defined you prefer will
be that much of a non seor you simply
won't understand that they're referring
to
you understand yeah yeah I understand I
have um a question concerning some other
um a question concerning some other
people that I know was one of the causes
they are not the cause I know I'm My Own
Creator I understand all right but I'm
still confused and I haven't been able
to let go right um it was some people
who took I lived with for a number of years
took I lived with for a number of years
and um they helped me out of a very very
negative life-threatening
situation and um kind of nurtured me and
then I was in a very serious accident
and I got a bunch of money and it's
still going on that's one of the
pressures it is not a pressure I know
okay okay it is a situation as neutral
as any situation okay the meaning you
give to it determines the effect you get
out of it positive meaning in positive
effect out negative meaning in negative
effect out the circumstance itself has
no meaning it is blank devoid of meaning
empty neutral zero
zip so continue well um I was on
disability for a long time work this
conversation and
and
the people here we go again pressured me
to give them a whole of money and theyed
more and then they got to my lawyers and
they some negotiation yes they were able
to get a whole bunch more against the pi
case and it left me in a situation that
I was penniless all right and I but
remember that you are infinitely
abundant I know but I don't understand I
put so much trust One Moment One Moment
One Moment because of what you are
discussing with me now it is very
obvious that you believe in the ability
for other people to pressure you well I
did and that's what you
got you got an absolute reflection
through your trust in negativity of
pressurizing but I thought it was
positive it can be positive if you allow
it to be you can always transform
anything in a positive way all we are
saying is not surprising that it
happened because then you obviously
believed in the idea that individuals
could pressure you so obviously you
attracted individuals that would reflect
to you your strongest fear that's the
service they did you now if you
understand you no longer need that then
you will allow a flow of infinite
abundance to once again come into your
life and if you simply understand that
you have to buy into the pressure then
next time someone offers you the idea of
the pressure you won't give them your
money to buy
it you will not pay for it you will not
bu it the understand yeah I understand
the confusion in my brain is that
whether it still comes up as to
whether I'm the wrong one or they are
because no one
is you are both co-creators of the
situation if it has presented to you a
circumstance you no longer prefer get in
touch with your act your part in
co-creating it redefine yourself and
move on
then you will simply put yourself in a
position and create an atmosphere around
you where you can allow there to be the
conduciveness of the flow of your
abundance and you will be a totally
different person having absolutely no
more relationship to the idea of a
history that belongs to someone you no
longer are
are
literally no one is right or wrong and
if you stick around to try to determine
that you are continuing the invalidation
and the pressure mhm it is not a matter
of being right or wrong it is a matter
of learning
to be what you prefer to be and you are
being given an opportunity in the
circumstance to no longer believe or buy
into certain beliefs you no longer
prefer so don't continue to buy into
them redefine them move on you'll have
another reality plain and simple mhm all
right you are doing just fine relax you
are learning in the way you have agreed
to learn you can change it it's but
you're doing just fine yeah remember
that your confusion and disorientation
are simply forms of meditation that you
are also judging to be negative cusion
confusion fusion with more of yourself
depression is simply meditation
[Applause] judged it is when you withdraw to the
judged it is when you withdraw to the
center of your being to get the answers
you know you need because you know
they're not outside you do not
automatically assume that what you
typically call confusion and depression
and disorientation in your Society have
to be intrinsically inherently negative
things give them a positive meaning and
you'll get a positive effect out of them
MH they are all different forms of
centering of meditation and so how would
I
find self-security because it boils down
to you are secure insecure with myself
you are secure the idea of believing in
insecurity is again doubting the power
that you are you don't have to find it
be
it act like you
know that you are infinitely abundant
and connected act like you know you have
the ability to make decisions and that
your reality will stick to your decision
act like you know no one can force
anything on you if you know no one can
force anything on you what's there to be
secure about why do you need protection if you
about why do you need protection if you
know you can never really be attacked or
abandoned or abandoned
remember as one of the individuals in
your Society once said you can say the
word alone as alone or you can say it as
all one so if you prefer to believe you're
one so if you prefer to believe you're
abandoned you will say alone if you
understand you are always connected to
the infinite you will say all one how
can you be
abandoned understand mhm well thank you
yes you are doing just fine relax and
expand unconditional love to you mhm
thank you at this timing you may all
enjoy a short break we will resume
contact in approximately 10 to 15 of
your minutes [Applause]
how's it going great
great here's the uh the next 10 names
after the last there's two more up here
Don Stewart is 11 12 is GTO or ghetto
GTO ghetto uh 13 Bob Beck bobc 14 Trina
15 Lola Soul 16 Daryl laan 17 Pat Dodge
18 June Bernett 19 John Blake 20 Bill
Dashi and please come up afterward and
line up please have uh about a 10 or 15
minute break at the most there's
Refreshments in the other room and you
can uh order your copy of tonight take
tonight say continue
bash Andre you good
day um I understand that before we come
here we make
agreements and my question is if you've
made an agreement with two other
people and two of them are willing to
keep it but the third one isn't what
happens remember first of all that there
is a lot of leeway within the general
idea of what may be called an agreement
it does not always translate into an
absolute specific type of interaction
the agreements that you make prior to
what you call physical life can be to
some degree specific but they will
usually be representative of General
themes that you will play out and an
individual even within the light has the
leeway and the free will to play out the
overall agreement in any number of
different ways either within Integrity
or outside of it you can still find an
individual involved in the particular
theme that you have agreed to play out
you follow
me so far yeah all right now
therefore the idea is not to necessarily
assume that they are not fulfilling the
general agreement even though they may
not necessarily fulfill the specifics
that you perceive to be representative
of the agreement or one way the
agreement could be
fulfilled do you wish to delineate the
particular specific situation you are
describing mhm proceed okay um are you
familiar with an entity called
nemus by a general energy stream but not
necessarily by a specific as it may
manifest through different individuals
on your
planet for it can be changed according
to the
Persona to some degree that funnels
connection with that
energy understand I'm not sure he he has
said that his he would be known by
another name yes the idea once again is
simply to understand that all beings all
levels of
consciousness that make associations
with any other level of
Consciousness the being they make an
association with will always be able to
translate in their own terminology what
they believe the original Consciousness
to be it can appear very different from
being to being as they may relate their
connection to the same Consciousness it
still can be representative of the same
overall Consciousness but it may appear
very different and so the vibration will
be to some degree different from
Individual to individual as they have a
personal relationship with that
particular energy MH but if the three of
us have made an agreement and one backs
out what happens to the what is your
definition of backing out not doing it
in what way not doing it not completing
it in what way
your definition of what may represent
completing it may not be a definition
necessarily or the only definition of
completing it what is your specific
definition what is the scenario oh well
like that the the person would allow the
that is doing the channeling would allow
the energy of this nemus to to come in
yes as she had agreed all right and if
they do not feel for some reason that
they are ready right is that not allowed
yes but then what happens to like say me
in my part of the agreement what happens
to it yeah what is your part in it the
facilitator and
um you know setting it all up and yes
are you willing to assist that
individual because you are excited about
the idea
overall I it's what I really want to do
you are willing to be of service to the
individual right then allow yourself to
be of service by assisting them to get
in touch with the trust and the
unconditional love they may need to
understand to allow them to feel
comfortable in letting the energy come
through the idea is that if an
individual seems to be in your terms
backing off then obviously there is
something within them they need to come
to terms with right be of service in
that way and allow the individual to
come to terms at their own good timing
you cannot force them and at the same
time you can recognize that that doesn't
necessarily have to be the only
individual the energy comes through
oh okay now may I ask you a question yes
please do well thank
you can it come through
you um not well see what I do I hear it
yes I hear it in a different way so
telepathic so which I've always done yes
so well no one's going to listen to me
what no they won't why not because what
people are into now is channeling and
what they want one moment it's true one
moment I know what you're saying however
the whole
idea is for individuals to become
self-empowered and recognize that you
are all always channeling and that
channeling is simply allowing a flow to
occur without worry now I know that I've
known that for a long time all right and
I have been able to do that cuz I hear
and see entities all right and always
have then why is that not sufficient
because what I have observed yes is that
what people want when we're doing this
is like when she does yes
so if I would say the very same thing
which I could do yes they give no
validity because I'm not in a trans and
because I'm One Moment One Moment true
yes it is true but it's true because you
attract individ idual that fit your
belief that no one will give you
validity because you're not in
Trend that's the only reason it's
true but so how can I by having the
boldness to understand that your way is
just as
valid seems to me not meaning to be
derogatory here at all that there's more
hesitation on your as well as the other
individual's Parts equally really
yes so all you're getting is a chance to
work with someone who's exhibiting the
same degree of hesitation that you are
oh what a wonderful reflection for
you what a wonderful opportunity to
validate the way you are and to
understand that if you are that way then
obviously there must be some individuals
the way you do it will serve
hm for every individual that is willing
to express who they are there will
always be an
audience but if you don't believe it
then you won't Attract it and then it
won't be so
obvious but it's only not obvious
because of your
belief that the way you do it isn't
valid and can't be of service that
individuals won't accept it I know what
you mean however let me remind you and
everyone present right
now that the way you are experiencing
this channeling even though it may have begun
channeling even though it may have begun
for the purpose that you stated the main
purpose of this channeling in the way it
is being done is to put itself out of a
job right to render itself obsolete
right so that each and every individual
know they have the accessibility you
already know you have right therefore if
you are bold enough to be one of the
first examples of that why hold [Music]
back well I I probably do have a fear
yes obviously obviously but don't worry
about it if that is the way you really
are if that is truly representative of
the way you flow you will find
individuals who will be able to allow
you to be of service to them while they
will be of service to you by allowing
you to recognize that you must by
definition fit into the overall reality
and therefore for every sender there
must be a
receiver understand yeah but my greatest
fear is that they won't realize I'm
receiving all right or is that is that
but you can tell them you are I know but
but what what I really do see that they give
what what I really do see that they give
twice the validity to if if someone's in
a trans I could say EX we understand
that that for now is seemingly the
majority attitude upon your planet so
but when will it change right when you
change it that's when it will change when you
it that's when it will change when you
take the first step to present it in a
format that they can get used to as
being just as valid if you don't give
them the opportunity to see any other
way it will take longer for them to
realize there are other
way H
H um yes so could you give me some help
in what to do how to do it cuz obviously
I don't know what to do oh obviously you
do it is simply that you are not willing
to act upon it you know how to present
the idea that you have access to
information can be of service to
individuals it doesn't necessarily have
to be something that comes with banners
and horns and
lights the idea simply is is that you
offer your services to assist as a
reflection to all who may require it in
that way you don't even have to
necessarily Define per se how the
information is
coming just be involved in a dialogue
with whoever is attracted to your
willingness to quote unquote as you say
advertise that you are willing to engage
them in a self-reflective dialogue that
will allow them perhaps to see things
they need to learn about themselves I do
that to one degree right now well then
well I want it to be more than that well
it can be as soon as you validate your
methodology as soon as you do not see it
as limited it won't be okay you will
then be able to be one of the examples
that creates the
change okay somebody has to
right might as well be you okay well
thank you
could you tell me about the two crystals
that have just that I have the no no you
have the ability to know everything you
need to know do I about those two large
crystals that have come into my
awareness remember simply that they are
triggers catalysts to awaken Reflections
within you to
yourself okay thank you thank
you
shoting Aloha and to you aloh
quick um I've been uh having a really
great time all kinds of things and one
of my sparkliest excitement is crystals
and I asked you before about some ones
that were Smoky clear and cloudy and now
there's another the next batch came out
a little different and I'm really I
enjoy that I know that there's a
synchronicity with the symbolism oh do
you now oh yes well would you care to
share what it is as a matter of fact
well all right uh these the ones that
I've been uh coming across lately have
clear on the bottom and then uh like a a
diagonal strip of some cloudy but it's
not really cloudy just like spots and
then it's clear on the top again and I
have two two exciting versions oh all
right one of them is the there's a
little Galaxy in there it's just
swirling around like the Milky Way all
right and the other one is uh it could
be an opportunity for somebody who would
like to play to clear a crystal oh right
very good both of those very exciting
yes thank you for discovering tools that
can reflect those
ideas I was wondering if you'd like to
share anything about those crystals no I
thank you remember this is weaning time
yes you already know trust it act on it
okay I would like to uh invite anybody
who is interested
um I would like to start something and
anybody else who would like to be
involved in something we could do after
the class here somewhere else where
people would like to be in physical
contact like a circle of massage or
energy you know sharing and anybody
that's uh interested in doing that we'll
talk thank you thank you
sharing hello Bashar Andrew you good day
thank you for all your hilarious
comments and for yours um thank
you those about to come thank
you uh what I'm interested in tonight is
what is the the scenario of what happens
between lives you know can be many
different things simply remember that
you are a thought form in a world of
thought form there are because you have created
form there are because you have created
there to be so many different levels so
to speak in what you call the
non-physical reality quote unquote
between lines linearly
speaking any number of scenarios can
occur the general foundational scenario
is whatever you believe in most strongly
will be what you experience immediately
because there is no time lag in
non-physical reality understand right so there are
reality understand right so there are
layers of frequencies of vibrations that
represent different degrees of
perception and Clarity of definition of
the reality you know yourself to be and
it can range all the way from
individuals not even knowing they are in
your terms non-physical all the way to
individuals who simply absolutely know
beyond the shadow of a doubt that they
have the opportunity to project
themselves into any type of experience
whatsoever on any plane in any
definitional sense anywhere in between anything at
sense anywhere in between anything at
all whatever you would imagine can be
experienced in that non-physical realm
instantly now because of the way you
have created your world to be because of
the momentum that has been in the past
generated you have even allowed that
radiation so to speak to quote unquote
leak into what you would call the lower
levels actually creating the idea of
lower levels of non-physical reality in
which you can be non-physical and still
not yet know that you have the ability
to go anywhere you wish and be anything
you want to be you can create an
automatic assumption in those levels
that you perhaps have to
reincarnate creating what you call the
karmic cycle which is nothing more than
an assumption basically that you have to
keep reincarnating it is simply recognition
reincarnating it is simply recognition
of a momentum a momentum which can be
played out in many different dimensions
of experience but what you all have
assumed in the past has to be repeated
here it doesn't is up to
you does this explain some of the ideas
yeah it helps a lot cuz the the second
part was the the key how do you graduate
so that you know that by knowing right
now that you have that choice that you
have always complete and utter choice if
you become non-physical with that
knowledge you will know that when you're
non-physical and you will say
h what do I want to do
now and you will be very clear about it
great so there's nothing that says you
have to come back no oh great
however the one thing
you will do to
ensure that you might come back is to
deny the validity of the physical
existence because if you do not validate
it as equal to anywhere else you could
go that how you attach yourself to it
through your denial of it that's what
allows you to come back well the way do
you do that just learn to love
this unconditionally right for it is
just as valid as any experience you
could have and you can create physical
reality to be an ecstasy and a joy if
you're using the idea of non-physical
reality to run away from physical
reality to escape that as if it were a
prison then that's simply not a
recognition that if it seems to be a
prison you're the Jailer and you will
keep putting yourself back into physical
reality Until you realize you hold the
key and anytime you want to turn the key
in the lock you can and that's when
you're really free when you free
yourself understand right I always have
the fear that I'll love everything 99%
and there'll be one little thing I'll
forget about you
know and I'll have to come
back one person I forgot to
forgive all right but that's a
definition too that's a belief that's
right yeah okay thank you thank you
thank you
shoting hello Bashar good day to you I'd
like to ask about um the relationship my
husband has with his ex-wife it's a very
angry situation and it's very painful
for him still still in what way um in
that any communication the two of them
have seems to end up in arguments um
and it stays with him for a long time um
so he believes in Conflict yes why how
does it serve him to believe in
Conflict um I believe that he thinks it
keeps him from being
vulnerable is vulnerability a sign of
weakness to him yes can he redefine it
as
strength vulnerability being complete
openness complete openness being
complete connection to the infinite
being Infinite Strength that's
vulnerability I understand that and I am
trying to work in that in myself also
all right my question is that I don't
seem to know how to help him with this
situation well first of all by being
yourself fully yourself fully an example
of the things you do believe work and
allow him the opportunity to see in you
by example the attitude the Assurance
the trust
that he can then see and say you know I
like what I see in you I would like to
be that
way think I'll match you think I'll copy
you so that I will not necessarily have
to have the old assumptions of how I
must react to people and instead can
choose to act the way I choose to
regardless of how anyone else choos es
to for all he is doing is reacting right
and not acting so really all I should do
is just be an example of what I believe
well that's all you can do you can't
force anyone to change you know that I
know that and every time I try to
discuss it with him we seem to end up in
a battle all right but remember
Sometimes some individuals will not
allow themselves to get the picture
until they finally
understand that when you are willing to
serve him in unconditional love but that
doesn't mean that that is a sacrifice to
what you prefer as a reality and if the
way he chooses to be means that you
prefer to move
on then he will perhaps eventually
see that's what happens if he chooses to
remain the way he is and perhaps if he
desires to maintain a connection with
you he will then begin to understand
that he might want to
change so the idea is to be of service
be loving be supportive but do not
sacrifice what you prefer if the
individual is not reflecting the
Integrity you prefer in your idea of
relationship move
on you have served them all you can and
perhaps sometimes you actually serve
them best by allowing them to see what
happens if they stay the way they are by
moving on are you actually saying moving
out of the relationship or simp moving
on with what I'm doing both if
necessary now remember that once a
relationship is begun it always goes on
it never really
ends but as you understand it if an
individual is simply not willing to use
the service you are providing by being
an example being a reflection if they do
not appreciate the idea of who you are
for that reason if they simply refuse to
learn that if simply insist on creating
conflict and you don't prefer that then
by all means yes physiologically
speaking why should you be in that
relationship okay understand yes is is
my part in being in this
experience for me to learn well both of
you yes but as we perceive the idea if
that individual in your terminology is
more focused on the idea of conflict it
can mostly be a lesson concentrated for
him that you can
reflect okay I understand thank you oh
thank you allow more
you allow more
information in the assistance you will
receive also in your dream reality do
not worry relax and allow the
information to come through for there
are those that can be of assistance to
you in the form you would call guides in
your dream
reality all right all right thank you
Pleasant dream
hello Bashar and to you good
day good day I've been reading some
books of Nicholas Tesla okay and while
reading the books I found out that I was
very angry with u Thomas Edison all
right and also uh Steins and I said oh
no here we go again could
you tell me who or I was in
that general relationship of the
development of electrical power in the
United States no that's what I thought
but I can tell you who you are now oh
good who am I now someone who can
translate the idea of Tesla's work into
something that will work in your Society
now okay so do
okay so do
it
okay does that serve you yes thank you
very much well thank
you remember simply in many cases we
will be very hesitant to assign a
specific label that we feel would limit
your focus the idea is to Simply recognize
focus the idea is to Simply recognize
that if you know the energies and the
vibrations and the ideas you are
connected to now then be that person now
and anything else you need to know you
will discover but you do not need to know
discover but you do not need to know
that idea nor need to form a specific
Connection in what you would simply call
a reincarnation ational sense to be able
to give forth the idea that excites you
now if you identify with a particular
frequency that is represented by those
individuals then simply assume whether
it is direct or not that you belong to
the same Club act accordingly and give
forth of your gifts along that
line all right all right thank you very
much and remember the S and 1/2 cycle
per second
pulse than Shing oh One Moment One
Moment remember also that that is the
product as you say in equational terms
of
dividing the circumference of any
world into what you
call the speed of
light and you will get a number that
represents the pulses per second in the
electromagnetic spectrum that is the
frequency of that planet
understand yes thank you thank you
shoting hello Basher Andre you good
night I have two opportunities in
relation to my physical well-being that
I would like coaching in
coaching do you have one of your
footballs S I want to get on the team
all right the first one is in regard to
my desire to have a baby yes I've been
actively engaged in pursuing that desire
for a number of months all right and uh
so far unsuccessfully
unsuccessfully so far I have not
realized that desire oh all right that
doesn't mean it's
unsuccessful why do you recognize that
the desire
exists why do I recognize that the
desire is this is that the question
you're asking me yes
if you wish why does the desire
exist I will shorten it to that
okay um why do you want a child I want to
um why do you want a child I want to
have a child I have the feelings of
uh motherhood yes I've I've um always
wanted to be a mother and this is the
time in life that either I'm going to be
one or I'm not oh why because I'm
reaching an age where women no longer
have children in our Society oh really
what age is that over 40 yes so and I
have been told one moment one
moment so so you are that age so
what I'm concerned about the about
having a child now I see and I it seems
to me that there are many
individuals in your society that we are
aware of that have had children past
that age
yeah and there's a certain cut off date
for women in our society where they can
no longer have children I see who
invented that
date we
did can you change the
date that's one of the things that
I'm working on yeah working on well
don't work so hard at
it maybe you're constricting the flow
out of
desperation I've always had the attitude
that I would have children when I was
ready to it would be no problem well
then and been doing visualizations yes
so what has changed um being told by
medical professionals that I'm not in
that my body is not going to have
children well no not until you're ready
to and I feel that I'm ready all right
and I'm concerned do you have a childing
that shifting that do you have a child
then you're not
[Music] ready now are you willing to trust
ready now are you willing to trust
that instead of being desperate that you
are coming down to some sort of a wire yes or
yes or
no are you willing to trust that if you
really do recognize that the timing is
perfect is Flawless then why not trust
it
still why not simply recognize that you
have put out the desire and that your
desire is your recognition of the fact
that you have made such an agreement and
therefore when you relax and stop fining
the agreement with all of these Notions
of what your Society tells you is and
isn't possible then you will relax
sufficiently to allow the agreement to
fulfill itself whenever the timing
really is appropriate and therefore
since you know it can fulfill itself
whenever the timing is really
appropriate if that timing happens to be
beyond what your Society thinks is an
acceptable margin so
what that's fine and I'm concerned about
my ability having been told that I may
not physically be able individuals are
told that by medical personnel because
at that time it is true because it isn't
representative of the timing and if you
have made a specific agreement with a
particular being who is not a child at
this point so to speak then if it is
Paramount that the timing for that
particular birth be the only
timing sometimes many of you simply
ensure that you will not have a child
before the time timing by rendering
yourself incapable of having one and you
will be told you are incapable of having
one but as has happened many times in
your Society no matter what the medical
practitioner says all of a sudden
there's the child mhm well I could have
sworn that's right I was sure you
weren't cap well well there's the shot
well I guess
well I don't know what to make of it
it has happened many times you know why
not simply trust that the desire you
originally felt is indicative of your
awareness of such an agreement and let
the agreement fulfill itself in the
timing that really does represent the
perfect timing for the Fulfillment of
the agreement okay the more you worry
about the
deadlines the more constriction you put
on your enjoyment of the now and the
longer you make it take to allow the
agreement to occur because you don't
allow yourself to become very quickly
the person the being made the agreement
to be born
to yes you simply aren't that person
yet relax about the definitions okay and
remember on our world I am aware of
individuals that have
children around 200 yes I so I've heard
I'm very anxious to
visit Where can I find out the easiest
way to visit our reality is create it
for yourself first
mhm when you then know it is possible
for you you will then know you are equal
to the idea we are and that's what will
make it more conducive for us to meet
you mhm but only when you know it's
possible for you
first understand yeah terrific that's
great relax
okay and within the next 3 days of your
time see what kind of information you
get in your dream reality from the child
okay relax relax
relax may now I ask you about the other
uh Health opportunity that I have at the
same time which may or may not be
related briefly okay I have a um
difficulty breathing no had uh
chronically since a child yes that has
gotten worse over time and seems is
quite acuteness that I have trouble
sleeping and um also I've done a lot of
visualizations and and uh work on it and
I wonder if you have any suggestions and
what I'm missing in the lesson in this
um this
breathing to some degree it is tied in
to the idea of the child that's what I
thought in the
sense ah all
right now you have been together many
times before you and the supposed child
we are
discussing what you are doing now is
being given an opportunity by the
child to come to terms with being
comfortable in physical reality and not
assuming that it is suffocating you this
is something that happened in another
life of
yours when you know it is clear for you
to exist in the physical reality with
comfort you will then believe you can
bear a child into a world that will
support it and not suffocate
it because you believe you were
suffocated by physical reality in your
other life
mhm and in a sense to some degree you
have created a focus on lives where you
have literally died of
Suffocation mostly it will translate
into the idea of what you call
external pressure that you buy into the idea once
pressure that you buy into the idea once
again of not having enough
time to some degree that idea is wrapped
up in the
Suffocation understand that you belong
you belong you belong you fit your
timing is
Flawless lengthen the span of your
breath because you have all the time in
the world you're not in a
hurry relax you're infinite infinite
infinite take infinite
breaths what's your
rush it is the rushing that finds you
short of breath I see and it is also
connected to the idea that the child you
fear that the child because of what
you're experiencing will suffocate in
the same
reality the delay
on the child's part is to give you the
time to discover that you don't have to
suffocate if in that sense you don't
believe you have enough air for you how
as a mother can you support the child
mhm understand yes so in your
imagination relax feel the eons that you
are feel the
eons breathe
Infinity think in longer Cycles
not in terms of length meaning waiting
waiting waiting just feel the depth of
infinity that is all present in each and
every single now for each and every now
is
eternal each and every now is
infinite feel yourself expanding across
the ages do not think so much of the
barrier you call time do not not think
so much of time as a
barrier then you will find you will
expand deepen the
vibration all right terrific thank you
very much bisher all my love to you and
you feel love expanding
sharing hello Bashar and to you good my
name is Bob all right and uh I have a
Fascination and interest with the occult
science of numerology all right
numerology I would appreciate your
comment and sharing some ideas on that
uh all right now like almost any idea it
will be a tool valid like any other idea
but remember it is a reflection it is a
way of thinking of yourself it is a way
of psychically perceiving the ideas of
all mentality your connection to the
infinite it is a tool a
conduit a catalyst a
trigger that has to do with your
vibration it is simply a tool that has
an affinity for your
vibration a tool your vibration has an
affinity for so it works for you as a
trigger to allow you to expand in your
senses in your sensing in your awareness
of yourself and all around you which is
simply an extension of you to some
degree it simply repres presents a
recognition of the mathematical ratios
as to some degree does astrology the
mathematical ratios of the vibratory
patterns that represent the collective
agreements you have all made with each
other uhhuh so it is your way of
symbolizing codifying some of those
agreements in a way that Mak sense in
your dimension of experience and will
allow you to extract knowledge through
that translation device it is a way to
speak to other areas of yourself in a
way you find
acceptable uhhuh does that aister you
yes it does so it's a valuable tool that
we can use all tools are if it attracts
you use it okay if it doesn't don't it's
that simple okay but they are all
extensions of you the power is within
you you are simply using the tool as an
exteriorized trigger a catalyst to get
you going okay in
time you will simply do the sensing
without the tool you will be numerology
you will be astrology you will be the
idea itself that it represents so you
will not need to go through an
exteriorized tool okay does that a hist
yeah it does the word that I caught it's
a catalyst to move me on so I suppose
that's the reason for my Fascination yes
okay so I think it's working oh yeah
well thank you very much okay thank you
by the
Numbers
shining hi bashard hi I would like to
see if you could give me some more Focus
Direction on my connection with animals
connection with animals I'm happy in my
lifetime with what I'm doing but I like
and and and I'd like to become more
focused in what way in
working with animals all right now we
have discussed the idea of using that
sparkling imagination have we
not yes how do you see yourself working
with animals then give me a
picture I've done a lot of different
things and I am doing a lot of different
things but obviously if you believe
there is another way for you to expand
on some level you must have an image of
what that means I would like it to be on
a more spiritual level tell me what that
means paint me a picture if you were
doing it on what you call a more
spiritual level describe what you would
be doing describe a typical interaction
with an animal doing it the way you
desire to do it well since I
automatically communicate with them yes
how much more spiritual can you
guess well except for I just communicate
with them and and what do you mean just
well I was thinking that maybe there is
a way of doing something that within
work or for what purpose in what way to what
or for what purpose in what way to what
end how would you like to apply your
connection well I can heal them because
I can understand what they're saying
well all right anything else but that
well what else is there do you want to
do that well I do that well all right
well what else do you want to do I guess
my question is the work that I'm doing
now yes is fine for now oh fine for now
yeah well I mean it gives me money it
gives me does it give you Joy sometimes
why only sometimes because I don't think
that the government is where I always
want to be for the rest of my life but
you are the government I don't know if I
want to be working for our
government then change yourself and you
have changed the
government well I realized that now you
can work within that structure as you
recognize it or you don't have to that
is correct but again it comes back to my
original question how do you see
yourself doing what you want to do give
me a scenario where are you what are you
doing well right now I have a new puppy
that I'm going to train in tracking all
right but that's not specifically what
I'm asking you but that's specifically
what I'm doing right now yes but you are
expressing to us a desire to do
something something we assume in a way
you feel would be a more expansive
representation right for me and for them
then give me a picture what does that
mean if you are not going to be where
you are now in your governmental
structure where will you be will you be
in some sort of a building will you be
outdoors where will you be how will you
be interacting what will you be doing
with the knowledge how will you apply it
I would have to be outside well thank
you that's the first disc deson you've
given me since I've asked
continue outside what does it look like
where's that imagination tell me what
the picture looks like well I could live
in a jungle quite happily well thank
you then go to
one if that's what excites you the most
that's where you
belong why aren't you
there well being realistic I beg your
part
are you now really going to tell me and
expect me to believe that living in a
jungle isn't
realistic are there not many people on
your planet that live in
jungles this is true are they not real
they're real then it's realistic to live
in a jungle well I think my question is
is could you help me direction I am
well I mean I don't just leave tomorrow
on a plane and go to the Jungle why
not you think I'm being factious I'm not
why not give me a reason well I would have
not give me a reason well I would have
to have some kind of a plan or a
destination oh
really all right which jungle excites
you the most [Applause]
well Africa the African jungle excites
you the most all
right then put the vibration out there
and trust that it's representative of a
realistic reality then you will attract
into your life the circumstances that
will easily effortlessly joyfully
ecstatically get you there is that what
you think I should be doing in this
lifetime are no shoulds you're missing
the point what excites you the most is
who you are what excites you the most is
what you can most effortlessly and
abundantly do that's why it excites you
to tell you that it is the most
effortless and abundant thing you can be
doing and the thing that can be of best
service it's not a matter of should it's
a matter of saying whether or not you
really want to be who you are or
fighting it
then do what excites you the most that's
who you are it's not a matter of should
or
shouldn't you don't have to do it you
don't have to be your natural self you
don't have to follow what excites you
the most you don't have to trust that it
will support you in life but if you do
your life will be effortless abundant
and ecstatic but you don't have to have
an effortless abundant and ecstatic
life so I'm not going to tell you that
you should do it I'm only telling you that
should do it I'm only telling you that
you can do it and I'm guaranteeing that
if you do follow your excitement you
will have an ecstatic abundant and
effortless life so you decide whether
you want to or not I can't tell you if
you should maybe you want to suffer I
don't know and if you want to suffer then I'm
know and if you want to suffer then I'm
not going to tell you you shouldn't
because obviously if that's what you
want to do you're a big
girl you can make your own decisions I
don't have to make them for you oh I
like doing a lot of things then do them
and recognize that the one you can do
that excites you the most will be
representative most of who you are if
you cannot act immediately on the one
that excites you the most radiate the
desire for it and act upon whatever
circumstance you can act upon that
excites you the most at any given moment
whether it's seems connected or not
excitement is what tells you it is
connected and is what tells you it will
lure you into a circumstance to give you
the capability to do the other thing
that excited you more that you weren't
capable of doing
before it works that easily life is an
exatic explosion of synchronicity of
coincidence finding yourself in the
right place at the right time to get you
what you want but only if you act on the
thing at any given moment excites you
the most by trus that the excitement in
it is what connected to all the other
excitement even if it doesn't appear on
the surface to be connected
example yeah have now expressed the idea
of a desire to be in an African jungle
working with animals oh joy oh joy says
you you do not necessarily after an
honest
examination find that there is any true
capability you have immediately of
acting on it directly so you look around
what is the next thing that excites me
the most that I am capable of acting
on well now this doesn't seem to fit at
all I feel like I want to go the thing
that would excite me the most would all
of a sudden to be a take a trip to my
local bookstore now that doesn't seem to
have any fit at all but it is the thing
that excites me the most with
Integrity so I'll do it all all right
I'll Trust it I'll do it so there you go
you are at your
bookstore and as you enter the
bookstore you'll notice there is a sale
on books of the African
jungle and your fascination draws you to
it and you open it up and lo and behold
in that book you discover something you
did not know the information that Sparks
an inspiration within you well what do
you know it's easier to get there than I
thought I could do it this way perhaps
the way the book has
suggested or maybe when you walk in the
bookstore you'll win a contest to go to
Africa or maybe someone will walk along
notice your interest in the African book
and say well I have an interest in the
African jungles too I happen to be going
there next week and I was looking for
someone to do such such with me do you
know of such a person what says he I
want to do that oh what a coincidence
well come along I will pay all your
expenses now too good to be true
why life does work that way when you let
it that's the way life works when you
let it it's not too good to be true it's
not too simple it's not too easy oh
that's a fairy tale that never happens
in in realistic life oh yes it does all
the time happens all the time to
me all the
time never is there a time when it
doesn't now your world is learning that
you can allow it to happen notice I
didn't say make it happen all the time
too if you are willing to Simply trust
it and Trust the idea that excites you
as being capable of supporting you
both abundantly and in allowing you to
expand in the thing that gives you Joy
and allows you to be of service by doing
the thing that gives you the most Joy it
is only the thing that gives you the
most Joy that's going to allow you to be
of best service for if you're not
enjoying yourself how can you help
anyone else understand I understand has this
else understand I understand has this
explained the mechanism to some
degree uh I need to go to where the
excitement is you are the excitement the
idea is to act upon it by whatever
Avenue presents itself to you trusting
it yes go to where is representative of
the thing that excites you be in that
space okay and you will be supported
okay thank you very much thank you BVO
Shing good evening Bashar and to you
good day
my question has to do with an individual
that uh left uh ven's airport on August
28th and didn't bother to come back his
name is Norman
Jackson and
uh I feel that he may have uh fallen
into some trouble and I've been looking
for him give it
him give it
approximately one and a half to two of
your months within that time frame there will
months within that time frame there will
be information on the whereabouts of the
individual is he still alive I cannot
tell you that he does not wish to have
any of that released I cannot tell you
that it is not a matter of his wish it
is a matter of the timing it is a matter
of the things that we are allowed to say
that will violate the process going
on I understand all we can sense is that
within from our perspective generally
speaking five weeks of average will be
sufficient time to understand all that
has transpired thank you we thank
transpired thank you we thank
you other sources of information will
serve you
sheding good evening Bashar and to you
good day thank you it's good to see you
again been away for a little while all
right yeah if you say
so out there in the ozone okay um I've
been I've been doing pretty good and um
I'm finally getting together a by
cultural band I'm a singer and
everything's One Moment One
Moment did you all believe this person
when they said they were a
singer are you a singer yes really
really all right would you do me a favor
sure say I am a singer I am a singer
thank you I believe you now more
conviction okay yay well I do so many
other things yeah so to uh to bring
about this thing that really excites me
that uh well I'm finally getting this
band together and it's going really well
and all of a sudden something happened
what happened I started losing interest
in singing
oh no what the conviction was
there right all right what are you
interested in then
singing I know it's a paradoxical type
of wonderful Paradox and irony are the
beginnings of the recognition of the
total Soul use it now okay there are
times you say when you are a singer
times you say you are not yes all right
what are you when you're
not I'm a private contractor in uh word
processing programming one more time
I do not think some of the individuals
even in the second row caught that I'm
sorry I'm a private contractor and we're
processing programming does this excite
you yeah there's times I really dig it I
really like it all right so sometimes
that is what you really are yes anything
else no nothing else no all right just
those two things those two things so you
are either a singer or the program
yes all
right so when you are not excited about being
so when you are not excited about being
a programmer do you then allow yourself
to be the
singer I'm always being the singer kind
of underneath the other thing kind of
underneath well it's like I use the all
right you are a singing programmer
yeah or are you a programming
singer well I use both I guess I use the
programming to support all what I need
for singing oh really
why uh because uh it's taking a lot of
money to put it together
so so I go out and do the other work to
support myself in life and to it doesn't
sound like you really want to want to
what do the other
work no I don't really want to I really
want to just sing well thank you for
being honest then why don't
you just sing and trust that it can
support you well it has in the past it
has yes well then why not allow it to
continue to do so well I'm just going
through getting the new band together so
so I managed to get the work but I don't
have the show ready so what has that got
to do with anything well I need to be
working for the financial aspects of why
in order to pay for my living expenses
oh really are you
sure well it kind of looks that way well
it may kind of look that way but that's
also the way you created it to look
really well of course you create your
reality with your beliefs if you believe
you need to do something that you don't
really want to do in order to allow you
to do something else you really do want
to do you will create the reality where
you have to keep doing the thing you
don't want to do to be able to do the
thing you do want to
do but you don't have to do it that
way you can allow your abundance to come
in many ways many ways remember once
again that abundance is simply the
ability to do what you need to do when
you need to do it doesn't mean it has to
be in a certain format it can be and if
you are excited about doing something
else then by all means go with that
excitement but that doesn't mean you
have to force yourself to do something
you really are not excited about doing
you can trust that other opportunities
will come to you that will be exciting
even though they may not seem to be
typical even though it may not appear
obvious as how they will bring you the
abundance if they come and they excite
you they will bring you the type of
abundance you need
understand yes are you willing to allow
it to work yeah are you sure are you
willing to understand that you can
simply allow your situation to transform
into one that may on the surface be
judged by many of you to seem to be
upsetting and disorienting and oh no
I've lost this but then realize in a
positive way that you have opened
yourself up to another situation where
you may not need those things that you
have been needing to support yourself I
would like it very much but when the Inc
comes do you know the paycheck doesn't
come from the singing as yet you're
missing the point I am if you really
believe in yourself as a singer yes why
not let a reality come to you where
either you will be in a circumstance
that you will attract opportunities to
allow you to pay the rent easily or you
will attract an opportunity where you
don't need to pay
rent sounds
good tell me more mhm
more mhm
can you are you capable of
imagining a scenario in which you do not
necessarily have to pay
rent yes I can do that can it be real to
you yes does it excite you yeah I like
it then allow yourself to recognize
whether it comes to pass in exactly that
format or not is not the
point radiate the
strongest frequency of the idea and the
intention you most excitedly are and act
upon the opportunities that come to you
that also come with excitement they will
bring to you the circumstances that will
give you what you need even if it
doesn't come in the way you have been
taught to expect it has to because it
doesn't have to it can come in many
other ways and if for some reason being
who you are means you
must pay rent in what you call the
classical fashion if being Who You Are
are means that paying rent is the path
of least resistance you will have no
difficulty in paying it but if you
simply find that it doesn't always have
to manifest that way then let your
abundance come in all the different ways
that it
can open up your definitions expand your
definitions of how abundance can come to
you let it fluctuate maybe one month you
will pay rent maybe the next one you
won't well I don't mind paying it if I
got it I understand but the point is you
don't have to struggle to get it right
understand yes open up to different
opportunities that could allow your
abundance to flow in different ways
maybe your landlord will come up and say
you know we gave everyone the
opportunity a long time ago to pay too
much and now we're going to give it back
to you in the form of not having to pay
any rent this
month that's one way yes there can be
many other ways
say singer I your esteemed
singer I your esteemed
landlord am leaving how would you like
to be the new landlord and not pay rent
that's really weird that you should say
that oh why is it so
oh why is it so
weird I kind of got sort of an offer
like that oh kind of well what do you
know surprise
surpr yeah it
is why don't you trust those type of
offers as representative of other
formats you could be receiving
abundance true but it's just not firmed
up yet but it it that's happened firm it
with your trust okay understand yes I do
well thank you very much thank you very
much B thank you for singing your song
to all of us
thank you
for at this
timing allow us to extend once again to
each and every one of
you the perfectness of all timing and
the flow of yourself as life itself you
are the reality in which you exist it is
you be the idea you know yourself to be
body and soul it is who you are live
it we thank you we bid you fond and
unconditionally loving and exciting
dream life and life dream you are
dreaming right now wake up and live the
dream you prefer to
dream good day than you [Applause]
how it go great
thank you all for being here
tonight as I mentioned before