Allow us to begin this interaction this
evening of your time with the
entitlement patterns and
patterns and
meaning. Patterns and meaning. We have
discussed many times the idea with you
that all situations and circumstances
within your physical experience, your
day-to-day reality are
reality are
basically neutral props in relation to
each other with no inherent meaning
within them other than the meaning that
you give them.
Everything being blank, empty, neutral
allows you by giving the appropriate
meaning to extract from that
circumstance the effect that you desire.
As we have indicated, positive meaning
in, positive effect out, negative
meaning in, negative effect out. Simple
physics, simple mechanics. Now, let us
take this understanding a little bit
further. We have discussed the idea that what you
We have discussed the idea that what you
experience to be your physical
reality in a sense is a
combination of vibratory frequencies.
This combination of vibratory
frequencies represents all the probable
or potential realities there can
possibly be. They all exist right now,
right here, all at once.
they for what can be called the
background reality so to speak. Not that
there is any one real reality any more
real than any other. Not that there's
one truth against which to measure other
realities for their validity or truth.
But the background reality is the
composite of all realities, all truths
in what you may call a holographic
fashion, overlaid, intertwined,
interwoven. In a sense, laying in weight
for a specific stimulus to bring to the
surface of that general background any
particular reality that you may choose
to call a dimension of experience or a
universal realm.
Now, how you call those particular
vibratory frequencies to the surface and
allow yourself to experience that
particular reality is through your
beliefs, through your attitudes, through
the vibration you create yourself to be.
through for all practical intents and
purposes the meaning you choose to give
to the idea of a fundamentally
homogeneous background through the
meaning you create do you then actually
create the physical reality you
experience. So in a sense it is not so
much the experience that gives rise to
meaning it is meaning that gives rise to
the experience. When you project yourself
experience. When you project yourself
into physiological reality and determine
as a non-physical consciousness that you
will create certain types of experiences
that is the meaning you are giving to
that particular life you are creating
that particular aspect you are creating
for yourself as a non-physical entity to
experience as a limited physically
focused entity. It is that meaning, that
overall desire that then vibrates at a
certain frequency and then calls out of
the background vibration through a
sympathetic synchronization all the circumstances
synchronization all the circumstances
necessary that represent the meaning you
have injected into the general life
theme or structure that you are about to
live as a physical being. Is all of this
making some sense so
far? All
right. Simply put, the idea is that all
circumstances are
neutral. The meaning you choose to
believe, the meaning you choose to
create in life about your life is what
generates the particular types of
circumstances you experience to
reinforce and reflect and represent the
meanings you are creating. Giving
meaning. It is meaning that gives rise
to the experience.
When you project yourself into
physiological reality and determine as a
non-physical consciousness that you will
create certain types of experiences that
is the meaning you are giving to that
particular life you are creating that
particular aspect you are creating for
yourself as a non-physical entity to
experience as a limited physically
focused entity. It is that meaning, that
overall desire that then vibrates at a
certain frequency and then calls out of
the background vibration through a
sympathetic synchronization all the
circumstances necessary that represent
the meaning you have injected into the
general life theme or structure that you
are about to live as a physical being.
Is all of this making some sense so
far? All
right. Simply put, the idea is that all
circumstances are
neutral. The meaning you choose to
believe, the meaning you choose to
create in life about your life is what
generates the particular types of
circumstances you experience to
reinforce and reflect and represent the
meanings you are creating. Giving
meaning is the actual act of creation
itself. To give meaning to something is
to create it into existence in your
particular experiential realm. Nothing
has builtin meaning. There are no
inherent meanings in anything. All
vibratory realities are simply a neutral
set of circumstances in relation to one
another to some degree representational
of a type of crystal lattice work that
represents the overall holographic
experience of all reality of all
creation. But the meaning that you generate within
But the meaning that you generate within
your attitude, the idea that you create
within the being that you are is what
generates the type of frequency that
then pulls out of the homogeneous
background all the experiences that then
represent the meaning of your life. Many
of you as you have discussed with us go
through life searching for the meaning
of your life. But you see your life is
created simply by the meaning you give
to it. So when you are searching for the
meaning in that sense you are chasing
your own tail in many
ways. The idea is to recognize as we
have discussed that you have the power
of conscious commandment. The ability to
make decisions consciously that you know
are decisions that represent the life
you prefer to live. And then when you
give your life that meaning that is the
style of life you experience for the
vibration that you are will pull out of
that background all the circumstances
literally all the situations literally
all the relationships literally all the
objects literally that represent the
meaning the vibrational resonance the
harmonic you have given to your life.
You have given to the circumstances that
you have generated through the initial
meaning that you had which created the
spontaneous creation of your life to
begin with as a physical being as a
physical entity. So simply allow
yourselves to know you are the definers
ultimately of the life you experience.
And as you define it, as you give it
meaning, your life takes on only and can
only take on the colorations and the
characteristics and the flavors and the
atmospheres of the meaning you decide
your life will have. And that is what
you will see reflected in the
holographic background, the matrix of
all universal probable
reality. The idea we have also discussed
is that everything is synchronous.
synchronicity. Everything is
interconnected with everything else.
This is a part of the holographic weave.
Every single portion of the whole
contains the total information of the
whole. Every single area is
representative of all creation.
Everything is all here, all now. So
whatever vibratory frequency you are on
determines what aspects, what faces,
what facets of the total reality that is
right here that you will see and
experience as your life. So the way to
generate most easily the particular
vibratory frequency of the life you
prefer is to give your life the meaning
you prefer to give it and to cease to
assume that the situations that occur in
your life intrinsically come with a
meaning that you may not like. There is
no reason to play victim in this. There
is no reason to assume that you are
assigned a meaning in life and that you
have to stick with that idea that you
have to live that out. Even if it is a
struggle, even if it is a suffering,
when you decide what meaning your life
has in that sense, what your life is to
be represented by, what attitude, what
actions, what preferences, what
knowledge, what applications you decide
are pertinent to who you are. You give
your life the meaning that it can then
take its clue from and pattern itself
after looking for the meaning in the
events as they occur. In a sense is
after the fact. Give your life the
meaning you prefer to give it and it
will conform in all aspects to the
meaning you have decided it shall have.
You all
understand? Well, thank you very much.
At this timing, allow us once again to
extend to each and every one of you our
utmost appreciation and joy in your
willingness to interact with us in your
willingness to function as ambassadors
to your civilization and allowing me to
function as an ambassador from our
respective civilizations and the
association of worlds. And in return for
the gift of your sharing, I ask you
simply now, how may I serve you? Good
evening, Bashar. Unto you. I've had two
dreams that I would like to share with
you. All right. Uh one very recently and
one several months ago. And the reason
that they are foremost in my mind is
that the the same symbol was given to me
in each of the vers. I created the
symbol in each of them. Yes. Yes. Yes.
That symbol being that symbol being uh
two a dragon on either side of a piece
of metal. The first dream my husband and
I are looking for a place to live. I He
drops me off in this neighborhood to
check it out and says he'll be right
back. I start looking around for signs.
Omen signs, not signs. I look up signs,
right? I look around for um um I look up on top
I look around for um um I look up on top
of a skyscraper is a billboard with an
old crow in large letters. Next to it is
a huge neon eagle. All right. I walk
around to the back of this apartment
building and I see at the end of a large
banister a clear quartz crystal about 3
feet in diameter and 5t tall. And about
four feet away is a large rectangular
lapis stone about 1 foot square with
gold marbling and a strange drawing in
black that I somehow know is face being
coded information. Not drawn on but
somehow just made to appear there. All
right. It is ancient civilization
encoded information upon your own world
as well. But continue. Okay. and a small
rock beside it with similar markings.
Then I went around to the front of the
building and saw it wasn't the kind of
neighborhood we wanted to live in. I
in. I
Okay, I woke up and went back to sleep
and in the dream a crystal ball with a
dragon carved in bar relief wrapping
around it. I'm cautioned not to buy it
because it's machine and not handmade.
Then I'm in an apartment and the person
there has a crystal ball with dragon
that he says is handcarved. When he
shows it to me and then leaves the room,
it becomes a silver sheet of metal with
the dragon's carved dragon carved on one
side and the other side it's half etched
and half drawn. When I wet my finger and
smear it across the top, the drawing is
erased and then some integrity with
regards to the artist comes into play
there. That's the first dream. All
right. Okay. Um, the second dream
happened recently when I was on the
mountaintop. I programmed myself to have
a lucid dream and it it actually did
happen. Oh my my. What a problem.
In the dream, I found a ring. It was
silver that was a dragon that wrapped
would wrap around a finger that it was
on. It was uh kind of materialized and
dropped onto a carpet. And I recognized
it uh to belong to my stepdaughter even
though it hadn't before. and I gave it
to her. In the hallway, I was running
away from some danger. I don't know
remember what that was. And I felt as
though I were were running through
molasses. I couldn't get any momentum.
And then I said to myself, I'm dreaming
this and I can create this any way I
want to. And at that, I moved
effortlessly and created a door. I
stepped through out of the danger. On
the other side of the door, I was given
a work of art sculpted in a blue black
metal, which is two magnificent dragons
on either side of a flat rectangular
piece of this metal. Nice. And I felt a
sense of wonder and joy at this. And so
that it appeared twice. I'm wondering
what it means.
Oh, thank
you. Always give me the fun part.
Allow us to determine the idea of a very
ancient energy, a very ancient knowledge
which is usually symbolized by the
dragon. And specifically because of the
metal, you are also speaking and
referring about an ancient technology
that you are very familiar with or let
us say were and are becoming familiar
with. Again, very ancient old Orion
energy within you. And what you are
seeing is to some degree a pantheon of a
time frame from your very beginnings
upon your incarnations of Earth up
through certain ages unto the
revelations unto yourself of the balance
of the polarities of the positive and
negative energies, allowing you to know
you control your own destiny, that you
create your own destiny, and that it is
becoming less and less complex, and you
are regaining your own power. In that
way, you in that sense are the artist,
the designer of your path. And now you
are looking back upon your work, the
path you have designed to bring you
where you now find yourself in the
present. You have now stepped through a
new gate, a new doorway into a new
reality, a new world. So you are
reviewing the painting, the path, the
sculpture of your life, and allowing
yourself to recognize that always,
always, always you knew what you were
doing in danger, out of danger. You were
always relying upon the ancient wisdom
that you began this journey with so very
long ago to carry you through to the end
of the hallway, which is not exactly
where you are now, but you are almost
there. You follow me? Yes, I do. Does
this assist you? It sure does. Thank you
very much. Thank you very much for
reclaiming your own ancient wisdom and
recognizing your own inner life.
Sharing. Hello, sir. B to you. It's wonderful to
Hello, sir. B to you. It's wonderful to
talk to you again. Fine to you. Um I
have a couple questions. The first one
is about something that's um started
happening to my body. Um it started
first uh when I was here only see
talking with you and it's been happening
to me more and more in meditation and
now just sitting around. like
um when I'm sitting quietly, my body
will start to move back and forth. Um
sometimes quickly and sometimes slowly
and um then from time to time I'll get
surges of energy. Yes. Yes. These are
all typical symptoms of many different
things going on with many of you. Now
you have your own understanding of this,
do you not? Your own intuition.
Just that it's some kind of a vibration.
Some kind of a vibration. All right.
The some kind of a vibration is simply
an expansion, an increase in your own
awareness, your own energy. You are
gathering more and more of yourself
together. You are now aware that you are
more than you used to think you were.
And you are sensing more of your own
energy, more of your connection to
universal energy and now are feeling and
interpreting these energies through your
body in cycles, in rhythm. You are
beginning to recognize that everything
is energy, everything is frequency,
everything is energy. vibrating at a
particular frequency. And when you
change and expand the idea of yourself,
you will change your frequency. You will
uplift it. You will accelerate it in
different directions. For a while,
because it is not used to it, your body
may react with physiological responses
to this energy. But as soon as you
acclimate to the new level on which you
are existing, it will smooth out until
you assimilate the next level. You
following? Yes. Yes. So your centerings
and your meditations are opening you up
to more of your own energy that you can
now apply in your life in any way you
care to. That was my next question. How
I could use the energy. That's how.
Okay. What excites you the most in life?
What excites you the most? That
excitement is your indication of how to
best apply it. That's what excitement is
for. It lets you know where to apply the
energy that you now are aware of.
Excitement is the vibration in and of
itself that represents the path you
chose to be. So whatever excites you the
most with integrity apply your energy in
that direction and you will be serving
fulfilling your purpose being served by
the universe automatically abundantly
and effortlessly. It all goes hand in
hand. It is all one event. Use it as you
see fit. All right. What do you wish to
do? That changes from moment to moment. Yes.
That changes from moment to moment. Yes.
Well, so I I usually do what excites me
in the moment. Thank you very much.
Thank you. Um, one one problem that I am
having problem well
I've heard a couple of other people ask
you about this since since March 15th um
during the workshop I've been
experiencing some incredible mood
swings. I'm either very unhappy or very
happy. Many of you once you begin to
integrate that energy because you are
not used to exploring such wide ranging
aspects of your polarities will begin to
do so. You know it is safe and that's
why you are swinging like a pendulum
getting all that you can out of the
exploration of who and what you are. You
are going to the very ends into the very
depths of all the different aspects of
your persona and personality so that you
will make sure you gather all of
yourself together and will not leave
yourself hanging at some remote
destination on either side of your
emotional being. As soon as you begin to apply and
being. As soon as you begin to apply and
center and acclimate and accelerate a
little bit further, the giant swings
will instead of going this way begin to
accelerate. And as they accelerate, it
will propel you forward in a more linear
direction. You follow me? Yes. I thought
it would have started to do that by now,
though. It is. It is. Again, simply
recognize that if you are sitting around
watching for it, waiting for it to
happen, then you may have a much longer
period of observation. The more you do
with it, the faster it will acclimate
and balance and center within you. Thank
you. Oh, thank you very much. One more
quick question. Um, time's up.
Can I have a little more time? Yeah.
Thank you. Um, I'm wondering if there's
anything you can tell me that will help
me with the disharmony I'm experiencing
with my brother. Disharmony? Yes. What
are you learning about yourself in this
interaction? That I don't want to be the way he is.
That I don't want to be the way he is.
All right.
Are you? No. All right. Is there some
way that you can be of service to this
individual? Well, um I'm not sure. I
try. Well, no. I am myself.
I express my integrity with him. And
your unconditional love. Absolutely.
Unconditional. Well, it's getting there.
It's getting there. All right.
You must worry about the
disharmony in expressing unconditional
love. You can allow yourself to
recognize that the individual may be
working through certain ideas and
lovingly trusting that you can be used
as a reflection, as a mirror to allow
that individual to see what they need to
see, to integrate within themselves the
things they need to integrate. Can you
allow yourself to be this for him?
Well, um I haven't yet. when that his energy
um I haven't yet. when that his energy
is disruptive to you. Well, that's he um
I allow him to knock me off center when
we interact and it's very disturbing.
Why do you allow that?
I guess I'm just now learning that I
don't have to. Oh, very good. Now, you
see the balancing act coming full
circle. You have someone who is allowing
you to learn what it is like to be
centered and balanced so that you cannot
in a very short time find yourself
anymore falling off from one side to
another. If you carry with you the image
that you are walking a tight rope, it is
very easy to fall off on either side and
explore the wide range of polarities you
say you have been exploring. When you
allow yourself to know that the rope is
very wide, you cannot fall off. You will
always be on center. You follow me? Yes.
This individual to some degree
represents some of your ingrained
beliefs that the balance point between
the polarities you are experiencing is a
very narrow and knife edgeike phenomena
when in fact it can be a very wide
plane. You follow me? Mhm. Does that assist
You follow me? Mhm. Does that assist
you? Yes, it does. Once you know you are
stable as who you are, then no one, no
matter how you allow them to influence
you or move you or interact with them,
will ever find it possible to push you
anywhere near the edge of the center.
For for you, there is no edge. There is
only the center. Wow, that's wonderful.
And that will also allow the polarities
you are exploring to balance and blend
within you. Is there anything else I can
do to help him? Only be yourself.
Thank you very much. Trust your
instincts and remember you can force
nothing on anyone. Yes, I know. Thank
you very much. Have a dream conversation
with the individual as you may have
already attempted to do. You have had a
few. Allow yourself to know that there
can be much soothing and understanding
and awakening and awareness in the dream
conversations that will allow you to in
your terms awaken into your physical
reality with a new insight a refreshed
understanding of how to approach
instinctively that individual rather
than approach them analytically. You
follow me? Yes. An instinctive natural
approach, one such as what you call your
tree that bends in the wind may be of
best benefit for that individual. Thank
you very much. Thank you very much.
Pleasantry. Good evening.
Sharing. Hello Bashar. And to you. God
bless you. And to you. Thank you very
much. Um, I've had many different exper Okay.
Um, I've had many different exper Okay.
I've had many different experiences with
space people and I was wondering what
vibrations you may be picking up that
may aid me in better understanding of
some of the different things that I've
gone through in my life that could uh
aid me more in the present. All right.
You can assist us in tuning into that
vibration by sharing with us the ideas
about how you wish to use what
connections you are aware of in terms of
your daily life. How do you wish to use
the vibrations, use the energy? How are
you of service?
Um I'm not quite sure what you mean by
that last statement. What are you doing
with the information? What are you doing
with your knowledge? How do you apply it
in your physical reality that you have
the connections you know you have?
Well, uh I'm basically on a fruit diet.
I'm very much into that in prayers and
also uh taking animus and passing myself
out. All right. Those in your terms of
centering within yourself. All well and
good. How are you applying it outwardly?
Uh I share it with people but uh on a
limited basis the people that will
accept it. All right. Of course. Always
you will only attract the individuals
who will be able to utilize some of that
information. Is there some other thing
you wish to do with this energy or
information that you feel at this time
you are not doing?
Okay. Well, what what I would like to do
is get in touch with more contactees
because I feel it's very important. A
very good I also felt uh what is
stopping you? Um
getting in touch. I don't know. All
right. Are you going to get in touch?
I'm trying. I'm trying I'm working well
in sense that I give some support in
helping other people in uh different
organizations. I help pass out flyers
and UFOs. I come here I help uh ways to
get connected with other people. That's
why I'm here to get connected with
people. All right. Are you enjoying
this? Uh yes I am. It's a little
different.
Uh I've also had some uh I feel very
heavy connections for salt and
technologies that I have that flow
through my mind. All right. But I don't
have the schooling background. But you
can attract the individuals that do. I
Okay. Yes, you're right. And I felt that
way too. Yeah. Uh but those people have
not come into my space yet. I get
perhaps you simply have not announced it
enough yet. I see. What would you
suggest? Well, you have already done
some of that right now. Okay. And there
perhaps are individuals this evening of
your time who can if not make direct
connections with you refer you to
individuals who may be more
interested. That is one way. The idea is
to simply make yourself obvious in that
sense as to who and what you're all
about so that you veritably radiate the
idea that excites you the most and that
will automatically attract the
individuals necessary. Do you think that
that is something difficult to do to
attract the individuals that have the
things you lack so that you can supply
to them the things they lack?
No. But it hasn't happened. All right.
How have you seen it happening? or have
you seen it as
difficult? In other words, when you
consider the idea that you wish to
attract other individuals, do you create
scenarios in your mind that make it seem
like an obstacle to do so or do you see
yourself interacting very easily?
I reached out and uh other people that
were contacts reached me. Yeah. And we I
reached another terminal but the
terminal uh in the end just absorbed
information and then
uh didn't uh it said I was useless.
Useless. Yes.
Useless. No use at all. Yes. But in in a
sense that they uh just wanted
information that was it. Okay. What's so
useless about that? I don't find
anything useless at all about that.
Okay, I can see what they're doing. All
right, but you are implying that you
wish to attract individuals of a
specific nature to aid and assist you in
the manifestation of certain ideas yet.
Right. All right. Can you picture this
happening? Yes. Easily.
Uh, yes. Does it excite you to see that
happening? Oh, yes it does. All right.
Yes. I can get real stirred up about
things, but then after I'm all stirred
up, I don't continue on or Why not?
Uh, something else comes up. I think
something else, I guess. I don't really
know. It's just All right. All right.
All right. But I could get excited about
something and I can start out with it.
Yeah. And then uh I just it just doesn't
uh manifest continue. It just doesn't
continue on. Doesn't come into a reality
or something. All right. Allow yourself
to recognize one of the things we have
discussed with many of you is that you
have upon your world an assumption. This
basic assumption that you have been
taught is that if it doesn't manifest in
the way you think it should, you think
the process has stopped. Rather than
assuming that the next thing that
excites you is a part of the ongoing
process, you assume that if it changes,
that means it has stopped. It
hasn't. It is simply that everything
will always transform into what is most
representative of the path of least
resistance. And you may not always have
conscious analytical awareness of what
that might be. So if you know you have
initiated a certain vibratory energy, a
certain excitement and you see it
progressing in a certain way and then
all of a sudden it changes, why give it
the meaning that it has stopped. Why not
give it the meaning that it is still
going but in another mode? in the mode
perhaps necessary to attract you to the
individuals you originally wanted to
attract in the first place but who were
not likely to be attracted by the
original way you were doing it.
You follow me? Yes, I do. Allow yourself
to begin to look at life as a continuing
series of the energy you have initiated
but changing its form chameleonike over
and over and over again to make all the
connections to the different vibrations
you say you want to connect into. It has
to transform into a different frequency
in order to be attractive to different
individuals who think differently than
you. You follow me? Yes, I do. Is this
You follow me? Yes, I do. Is this
assisting you so far? Yes, it is. All
right. It is a completely different
viewpoint, a completely different
outlook, and one that can have a
profound difference upon the way you
allow yourself to know that your life is
manifesting what you want. But it is
only the assumption that it stops. Only
the assumption that it is interrupted
that creates the interruption you
experience. Allow yourself to know that
if you truly trust that what you are
doing is representative of who you are
and who you chose to be in this life,
then no matter how it changes, no matter
in what way the excitement continues,
the fact that the excitement continues
is the sign that the whole idea is still
continuing. Not necessarily in a way
that you have been taught to think it
must, but in the way that it needs to to
represent the path of least resistance
to get you where you are going. Because
you cannot have a conscious analytical
awareness of all the probable paths it
could take to get you where you want to
go. So don't even
try. Let yourself trust that how it does
take its course. Even if it appears to
have nothing at all to do with the
course it started out on, if the
excitement is still there, it is the
excitement that lets you know water is
still in the river no matter how many
tributaries it may take to get to the
ocean. You follow me? Yes, I do.
Excitement still is representation of
the flow. So you still know the river is
flowing. Follow it. go down the channel
it leads you on. That represents the
quickest path to the
sea. If you think, "Oh, no, no, I can't
go this way." That is not how I was
going before, but you still sense that
the excitement is there, that the water
is flowing. You are the one imposing the
dam in the
river. Allow yourself to go with it. No
matter how it meanders, the way it
meanders is representative of the path
you chose to be. And the meandering is
necessary in order to arrive at your
destination in the quickest possible
way. You following? Uh, a little bit.
Yes, I am. All right. We are simply
saying the same thing in many different
ways. Uh, I'd just like to ask you, uh,
I'm very much into this fruit diet. Do
you sense that maybe I'll be coming to a
peak or or a plateau on it that will
give me more free time?
Allow yourself to trust your body
consciousness. Allow yourself to ingest
things that your body may say it needs
for stabilization from time to time. You
do not have to force yourself into a
spiritual vibration. Allow yourself to
know that you will balance out and equal
out and you will simply know and have
the appropriate instinct as to what
feels correct to ingest within your
body. Allow yourself also to understand
that when you allow yourself to know you
are following the path at any given
moment that you've created for yourself,
you will then be more strongly in touch
with all the different levels of your
consciousness. And that will allow you
to know you do not need as much
unconscious time in which to connect to
those levels because you are doing it
consciously. That means you will
probably sleep less. That means you will
probably experience the idea of having
more time, but recognize also at the
same time that you have all the time you
need. Everything is in perfect timing.
You do not have to rush things along.
You are an eternal being. You are right
in step with the transformation. What's
your hurry?
Can you tell me uh the people that I had
met aboard the spaceship, where they
come from, what planet? Some of the
energy is plleadium
and some of the other energy
is some of it is connected to the
various association worlds. Some of
which your world knows and some of which
it
doesn't. For now allow us rather than
labeling to simply allow you to feel the
energy rather than differentiate between
civilizations that consider themselves
at one with all the other civilizations
that they interact with.
For now, consider it an association
energy. The energy of the association of
all worlds that are interacting with
yours. You have met many representatives
in that way in your dream
state. But let it all be
one for now. Thank you very much,
Bashar. Well, thank you very much. God
bless you. Live life.
Hello, Bashar. And to you. Um, a lot of
exciting changes.
Let the other individuals hear your
excitement. Um
well, one of the main changes uh after
the workshop, I shared some very long
dreams with you. Okay. And um this
experience of my dreams has changed
completely. U they're all like little
flashes. All right. And um little
flashes of dreams. Yeah. And I I it's
hard to uh put them all together. Why
must you? I guess that's not necessary.
What do these flashes represent to you
the moment that they happen? Insights.
Yes. Connections. Flash matrix. You are
bridging. You are allowing yourself to
come to a collective revelation. You are
aligning your entire
synaptic structure within your brain.
True insight. Yeah. Holographic vision.
These things propel you, allow you to
use the energy in whatever way you wish.
You do not have to necessarily allow
there to be a linear bridge or a link
between them. They are multi-ensory,
multi-dimensional. There does not
necessarily have to be a linear
connection apparent in your physical
world. True. Um there's a lot of
daydreaming and uh
sometimes I remember some of these, but
then I only remember them for a few
minutes and then they're gone again.
Yes. Again the idea is that as you blend
your dream reality and your physical
reality as you live the dream then there
is not so much separation between the
physical awake state and the dream state
the non-physical state and so there is
less to remember typical memory quote
unquote as your planet is used to
thinking of it being a relationship from
one state to another state that you are
no longer in. So if you allow yourself
to recognize that memory is creation in
the moment and that you are living that
dream then it's you know nothing to
remember because you are still in it.
You are living it. It is not a
flashback. It is a flash now.
Is there a purpose in the fact that
these are no longer stories? These are
so that I they are highly compressed
representations of the information or
the definition that you are at the
moment you have the spark. It allows you
to know that at that moment you are
simply aligned and you are quote unquote
kicking yourself or igniting yourself if
you will to transcend or step up to
another level of operation.
You follow me? Um, I probably have to
listen to the tape. Uh,
perhaps a recognition that you do not
need to analyze it. But again, the idea
is to live it, live it, live it. In the
living of all you experience, all the
idea, all the understanding and all of
the meaning will come out in the actions
that you perform instantly. You will
understand it by doing it by moving with
the spontaneous feeling. This is let me
give this analogy as we shared with some
individuals in your society earlier this
day of your time. You recognize there
are circumstances in your reality from
time to time where you see individuals
because of the circumstances around them
simply leap into spontaneous action and
do something and after it's done they
say I didn't know I could do that. I
just all of a sudden knew there was
nothing else to do. So I did it and
there it is. Every moment of your life
can be lived that
way. Really every single moment. So those
Really every single moment. So those
flashes are for you a representation of
the beginning of living your life that
way. Every single moment. One continuous
flash. Those flashes are for you a
Those flashes are for you a
representation of the beginning of
living your life that way every single
moment. One continuous flash of
revelation and
action. Poetry in motion.
So it is not so much that it will allow
itself to resolve into a linear
story. It is in and of itself the energy
of your living, the energy of your
action. And anything you need to know to
understand will come out in the doing of
what the energy allows you to feel, you
are all
about. Yeah. I think one particular
insight today had that message in a way. Um I
today had that message in a way. Um I
saw quickly a face of Aristotle looking
very young. All right. And cheerful.
Okay. But he had his right eye removed.
All right. I was wondering somehow I
knew I felt I knew what it meant and
then I start to analyze it and I lost it
and I guess I was doing exactly what I'm
not. The removal of the right eye of the
symbol you call
Aristotle represents now that as you
look through the left eye you are using
the right brain more creativity less
analysis. Right. That's what I that's
what I felt it meant to then trust it.
Yeah. you know what you are doing and
you understand the meaning that you give
to these symbols and you understand why
they generate in your life. Go with it.
Yeah, that I'm glad you confirmed that.
Um and I have one more question. Um I
was sort of excited. Uh oh, sort of
excited. All right.
Excited. I was excited about um the idea
of taking a class in channeling. All
right. You go right ahead. Have a good
night. No, but that's not uh the I I mean I
No, but that's not uh the I I mean I
feel like going right ahead, but could
you share a little bit about the kind of
entity I would be channeling or Nope.
Except to say recognize the whole point
is to channel you not someone else
higher self. Uh if you wish to call it
that. Yes. But the idea is to act like
the higher self in physical terms. And
that means you will be channeling the
higher self. Was there an agreement
about a particular comments? No
comments. We are not going to lay down a
plan for you.
Yeah, I understand there's no right or
wrong in it. Uh move with the flow. Move
with the flow. Move with the flow.
Got the message. Thank you very much.
Thank you, Bashar. Have a wonderful
time. I believe you will.
Sherry, how you doing? Bashar. Perfect. And you?
how you doing? Bashar. Perfect. And you?
Very well, thank you. Well, thank you.
Thank you. Well, I was going to ask you
tonight about a painful back I've been
having. All right. But the last week
I've been thinking a lot about conscious
choice while you went over tonight. So,
I think that kind of answers things.
I've been working so I've been working
with a lot and it feels a lot better.
All right. But anyway, what I do want to
ask you about is that uh I've been
having a lot of night uh sweats, guys.
And uh I I really haven't been able to
come up with anything. Are you
releasing? Probably a lot of things such as
Probably a lot of things such as
um boy, where do you want to start?
Anywhere you wish. Every place is the
beginning.
Um been releasing
um toxins.
Yeah. All right. Toxins. But why they
build been building up so much? If
that's one of the things
there are many ideas within your
physiological system that have been
inherently quote unquote locked into
your body for many years when you arrive
at certain levels many things that have
been in your body for years will come
out. Mhm. It is not necessarily that
they are there because of things you
have been doing recently. Mhm. I mean
it's been like the last three years this
has been happening. Yes. And some of the
things you are releasing in those sweats
have been in your body for 10 years.
Some of them have been there since
birth. So, it's a very positive thing. I think
So, it's a very positive thing. I think
so. Good. Well, I think so, too. Oh,
thank you. Then we agree.
But just go with it. Or I mean, is there
anything I can do to help resolve it?
Well, what does your understanding of it
allow you to create in your mind about
the purposes for it?
Just that there's some things I need to
clear out. All right. Does it excite you
that you are clearing out? It does now.
Yeah. Now. All right. Then the added
variable of your excitement will change
the experience. That's good. Thank you.
Thank you. Okay. Thanks much. Allow
yourself if you wish to visualize and
image the energy pouring through all
your pores. Imagine that you are
breathing with your entire body with all
the energy that you are. See the cycle
of blue electromagnetic fluid going
through your body and removing all the
ideas of impurities and allowing them to
dissolve outside you. Taking in
refreshing electric energy and then
removing the impurities and allow it to
accelerate but allow yourself to do it
comfortably. All right. Mhm. So in
essence everything really starts with
conscious choice. Right. Sometimes in
your world it can start with unconscious
choice. Well, yes. Resolving from the
unconscious. Yes. But then once it
becomes conscious, you no longer have an
excuse. But that's how the
Oh, well, yes. I realize I am doing that
out of an unconscious
habit. Now that you know you're doing it
out of an unconscious habit, it's no
longer unconscious, is it? It's true.
So the idea is to know that when you
have recognized that you are in control.
Mhm. Direct it as you prefer to. I will
give it the meaning as we have discussed
that you prefer to and then you will see
a change to fit the new meaning. Mhm.
Sounds good. Thank you. I'll use it.
Thank you very much. Well, thank you
very much.
wanted to uh tell you how much we all
appreciate your sharing with us. I've
gained a great deal from listening to
you. Well, allow me to convey how much
we all appreciate your sharing with us.
Thank you. Um recently I had listened to
some communications from friend in
reference to the transitions between
third and fourth density. And I had a
question. Um the past two years uh
beginning about two years ago I have
seen the entire focus of my personality
even my physical body everything has
changed to such a point where there is
no longer the person that I was two
years ago seems to be no longer present
correct I'm very curious uh as to what
has happened to that personality has it
moved into a parallel in a sense reality
and an aspect of myself has moved on
into forth and I have became I'm not I'm
just curious looking at it in any number
of ways each of which is a mathematical
arbitrary point of view neither of them
are any less correct than any other way
to look at it is all real you can look
at it that way you can say that the old
persona has dissolved back into the
homogeneous background matrix and in a
sense lies in
potentia rather than in realization
there are many ways to look at it again
each of which is correct
Because the whole idea of how you can do
that to begin with means that you
already exist in every single point of
view there is to exist within that you
are all points of view and where you
decide and when you decide to look from
and how you decide to look will
determine the idea of the persona that
you are. What happens to the persona you
no longer are is a matter of how you
choose to define it to feel comfortable
with the idea. All of them are true. All
the definitions are
correct since you have created the
persona out of your imagination to begin
with. Okay.
Okay.
Does that help? Yes, it does. Thank you
very much. Oh, thank you very much. And
yes, the idea of parallel
existence is also correct.
Sharon, hi Bashar. Hi.
This is my first time up here, so I'm
really excited to talk with you. This is
my first time, too.
Being that I am never the same persona,
the next moment of time either, just
like you. Thanks. Um, I wanted to talk
about myself. Oh, all right. Go right
ahead. I have rheumatoid arthritis. All right.
I have rheumatoid arthritis. All right.
And I've had it since 1982, 1983. All
right. And proud of that. Yeah. I'm
proud of that. No, not really. But um
when I first had it, I found the idea
that I create my own reality. I mean, I
found the realization that I had had
created an illness for myself to be a
real burden. All right. Now, I'm coming
to understand that this is a real
opportunity for transformation for me.
And I have no desire to spend the rest
of my life in pain and ills. So I wanted
to discuss this with you from two
perspectives. One, from a real mundane
physical perspective. I wanted to talk
to you about that. And then two, from
the transformational aspect of it. All
right. Both are exciting. Okay. From the
physical point of view, what I'm doing,
I'm seeing a regular AMA doctor. I'm on
some heavy duty medications and they do
have some potential serious side
effects. This concerns me. All right.
Um, I'm wondering if there's anything
that you can tell me that I could be
doing in addition to this medical
treatment that I'm under a day-to-day
basis to help me with the pain and
energy problems and so forth. All right,
let's ask what we have asked other
individuals. First and foremost, are you
doing in your life? What excites you the
most? Um, I I don't know if I can answer that.
Um, I I don't know if I can answer that.
Um, why not?
Well, I'm doing lots of different
things. What's exciting me right now is
this. Yeah. This is really exciting me.
Why? Um, cuz in my heart it just means
so much to me. Why? Why? Um
h geez, I haven't thought about that and
I'm really not sure. Go right ahead.
I'll wait. Think about
it. Okay.
Um the possibilities
the realization that I create my own
reality that we all create this together
that we're all one. Um very freeing
idea. Yes. It's it's fantastic to me.
Very flexible. Yes. Yes. Not rigid. Yes.
Right. However, I've I've created a lot
of rigidity. Rigidity as you know that
was up to this point anyway. All right.
Which point is that? Oh, this one. Up to
this moment. Which one? Oh, this one.
This one, too.
And that one. And the next. And the
next. And this one. This one. This one.
All right. All right.
Now, may I ask you a question? Okay.
At which point do you imagine? Just play
along. Okay.
At which point do you imagine you will
no longer be creating the idea of the
art project? When do you picture you in
your terms will no longer be the being
who contains that idea? 10 years from
now. Well, unfortunately, I do think of
that as a future thing. But although
when I see myself when I see myself, I'm
still mean. I'm this age and all that.
Okay. So, I'm not an old Let's play
along for a moment. Okay. 10 years. Is
it in your terms gone? God, I hope not.
Is it gone in 10 years? Oh, can you see
yourself in 10 years? You know beyond a
shadow of a doubt that in 10 years you
will not have this. Is that true? Yes, I
believe that. Five years.
Yes. Four. Yes.
One. All right. Here comes the
hesitation. Now, this is a very
appropriate tool. what we call examining
your threshold of believability.
This lets you know what kind of patterns
you are setting up at this particular
moment and in all reality can give you a
very good idea of how long you will
create it to take to alleviate that
particular situation.
In the very next moment that can change.
We are not saying that just because in
one moment you say well I'm not sure
about a year that in the very next
moment you can say well yes 6 months no
problem. Mhm. The idea however puts you
squarely in touch with what your
threshold of believability is. For when
the hesitation starts to go 10 years no
problem 5 years absolutely a year.
Then you begin to come right up against
what you truly believe is possible for
you. And that lets you know right at
that moment how long it will likely take
if you change nothing from that moment.
However, fortunately for you,
fortunately for you,
the realization in and of
itself makes a change in the energy and
follow it. Wonderful. Yeah.
So in 10 years absolutely no problem
correct right five years right one year
right all right six months
give me tomorrow
that's up to you okay that's up to you
again this demands absolute honesty with
yourself absolute honesty all right well
and good I can say well tomorrow or will
it be gone? You can say absolutely. But
if you don't really believe it, it will
not absolutely be gone. What I'm
wondering about is, you know,
consciously of course I desire to be
well. And what I'm wondering is if there
isn't some unconscious stuff that I'm
not aware of. All right. Yes. In a
sense, however, once again, if you have
an idea within you that there is some
unconscious stuff that you are not aware
about that may be allowing you to have
the experience you are having, then you
are beginning to be consciously aware of
its existence and that means it is no
longer unconscious. You do not
necessarily have to absolutely always
know all the specific details about what
may be unconsciously creating your
reality to allow yourself to begin to
replace it with a vision of a reality
you prefer. Okay, follow. Yes, you can
simply allow it to automatically be
replaced by creating the reality you
prefer. And this is what we are
assisting you to get in touch with for
now. By examining your threshold of
believability, you now are beginning to
gain some concrete and conscious
awareness of what you really believe is
truly possible for you and within what
kind of time frame it is possible. So
that you in creating the vision of
yourself as a healthy whole individual
will know that that vision is an honest
one absolutely representative of the
beliefs you really have and that you are
not just playing a game with yourself by
saying yes I see myself tomorrow being
healthy but I don't believe it. Right.
Yeah, but yes, I see myself in 5 years
absolutely being healthy and yes, I
believe that. So if you are going to
create a vision of yourself in perfect
health, create it to be the vision of
the five years, hence you that you
absolutely believe beyond a shadow of a
doubt is a healthy you. And once you get
in touch with that, just having done
that will accelerate that you towards
you from the future. So that bit by bit
at a more accelerated pace you now can
become that you and you will not have to
wait 5 years. Okay. You follow me? Yes.
Also one other trick we have talked
about before in terms of manipulating
the idea of time. Manipulating the idea
of the past and to create the past and
the future from the present not the
other way around is to create within you
an energy that represents the following
idea. Each and any of you can use this
if it appeals to you. If you have in
your threshold of believability now an
idea well yes I believe this has to take
oh say 6 months for it to alleviate
itself then send the energy 6 months
ago so that you will have had the
intervening 6 months and it can change
overnight since you will have taken the
necessary 6 months you believe is
necessary so that you will have had the
intervening 6 months months and it can
change overnight since you will have
taken the necessary 6 months you believe
is necessary by initiating it 6 months
ago. Aha. You follow me? Yeah. So you
would do that through a visualization of
absolutely past. Absolutely. Time is
completely flexible and many times the
simple realization that that is so may
actually bring about the change unlock
you completely. Are you feeling a little
warmth within you now? Yes. Yes.
Allow yourself to recognize that you are
now centering. You are beginning to feel
your signature vibration. And the more
you center into the idealized blueprint
state of who you know yourself to be,
the less likely that state will be able
to contain a definition of any type of
disease. You follow? Yes. So feel that vibration.
You follow? Yes. So feel that vibration.
All right. Get excited about it. know
that you are in control and can be from
many different directions all at once.
Okay. Time is your play phase. All
right. So, you've really answered my
question and it's in the
transformational aspect of it. Okay.
What I'm wondering about just in the
meantime while I am working with all
these ideas if there's any day-to-day
thing I heard you recommend a tea for
somebody last week or I'm wondering if
there's anything that might just help me
in the meantime physically.
Do you know of what you may call the
form either load stone or hematite?
I'm not familiar with it, but I can.
Individuals that are present this night
in your time can acquaint you with some
of this idea. It can in certain
doses have a balancing grounding strong
magnetic effect within you to help align
some of the magnetic currents in your
bodies which can then alleviate some of
what you may call the arritic buildup.
Uhhuh. Are you talking about actually
ingesting? No, no, no, no. Holding
exterior and doing a centering
meditation not taking very much time.
Also to some degree copper is very
conductive and conducive to alleviating
some of the electrical pads that create
a vibration you know as arthritis as
well. Okay, just little bits just
experiment a little bit with this idea.
Do not have to get as you say heavy
duty. You are the switch anyway. These
are only triggers and for you they can
be very strong triggers. Have no
expectations. explore in an open
childlike way. Okay. With a childlike
flexibility rather than the rigor of
what you normally associate with old
age. You follow it? Yes.
You follow it? Yes.
Have fun. Thank you, Michelle. Well,
thank you very much. And trust your
imagination for in those meditative
states, you may come up with something
else that you feel so inclined to
associate with. Be it something you
ingest or be it something you simply
surround yourself with or something that
you do. Listen to your imagination. All
right. Okay. Thank you so much. Oh,
thank you so very much. Happy dancing.
Hi Bashar. And you. I'm really happy to
talk with you again. values. Um,
something that I really like is a lot of
times when I I have a question that I
want to ask you, sometimes I'll just ask
you in my mind when I'm not here and the
answer comes that comes from you.
Oh, okay. Recognize that many of you as
we have allowed and offered use our
vibration to get in touch with that
aspect of yourself that operates on a
similar frequency. So, the answer comes
from you and you are using us. Thank you
very much. As a lure to find yourself,
we are simply a reflection, a lure, a
mirror for you. In that way, it is not
that it directly comes from us. You tap
into the frequency that allows you to
operate as if you are us what you think
us to be. You assign us the capability
of knowing those things. And so, in
forming a connection with that
vibration, you grant yourself the
ability that you have always had. We
thank you. That to us is a gift.
It's pretty exciting. Yeah. It's fun,
too. Um, when I came here, I didn't even
know what question, one of the questions
that I was going to ask you. All right.
And I got the question and then I got
the answer right away. Very good. You
see, it is not that you need questions
to speak with us. The idea is simply
equality of understanding.
Um what it what one of them was was when
a person finds themsself afraid. Yes.
What is a really quick way to get out of
that and and what works for you? Well,
the thing that came to me was
unconditional love. Yes. Absolutely.
Just in to feel love in some form and
the circle. Yeah. So that is the way
that works best for you. Your
imagination gave you that. You gave that
to yourself and you also extracted it
from the universal knowledge of all that
is. That is how it works for you. Other
individuals may get other answers and
each and every other answer is correct
for that individual and each answer is
representative of the vibrational
frequency that individual is operating
upon. So congratulations for finding the
answer that is you. Thank you. Thank you
very much. I don't usually remember my
dreams very often, but there's been a
couple times in my life where I had
very, very vivid, bright, colorful
dreams. All right. And that happened to
me about a week ago. And the dream that
I had was that
um what it seemed like was the day
that a lot of different spaceships came
to the earth and everyone was aware of
it. It was like time stood still and all
these people were in a big circle.
people on the earth were in a big circle
and everyone knew that it was real and
and it just seemed incredibly real to
me. I felt like I was there. Yeah.
So, I'm just wondering if you can tell
me anything more about sensing the
unification that can occur between our
respective worlds when you do allow time
to stand still. That means when you live
in the present.
Understand it is no accident in your
classical terminology that one of what
you call
your media plays your film refer to as
Day the Earth Stood
Still that involves your interaction of
your planet with our worlds has that
entitlement. For as you have just
perceived, it refers to the idea that
when you allow everything to be in the
moment, and when you are at perfect
peace, standing still is when the whole
universe opens up before you and you
don't have to go anywhere to find it.
It's all right
here. And that day is now. That is quote
unquote coming.
Well, that goes along with what I was
just thinking of. I feel like things
that I've been wanting to create for a
long time are just manifesting so fast.
Yes, you are living the dream. And
that's why many times you don't have to
have a conscious recollection of a dream
from the sleep state because you are
still dreaming right now.
You follow me? Yeah. As you blend the
two realities, there is no longer any
separation. Therefore, there is nothing
to wake up and
remember. You are still living it. You
are still sleeping in that sense. Not in
a negative sense. You are still dreaming
and you are awake in the dream. When it
becomes one thing, there's no longer a
separation that necessitates the
remembrance of a specific separate
experience. So many of you will find that you will
So many of you will find that you will
seem to dream less in the classical way
and dream more in the active
way by understanding that what you are
experiencing right now is a dream.
Literally literally you are all waking
literally you are all waking
up instead of sleepwalking and bumping
into things. Now you are opening your eyes
things. Now you are opening your eyes
into the dream you
prefer. You follow me? Mhm.
Anything else? Yeah. All right. Uh the
thing that I'm sort of having trouble
with. Sort of having trouble. Oh, you're
having trouble having trouble with
is that so many great things are
happening that I'm having a hard time
choosing which ones to do. And there's
things that have seemed really
important. What? Should I choose this
one or choose that one? Let it be
obvious by all means. And if you
recognize that many things are equal
choices, then it doesn't really matter
much which one you choose, does it? No,
but it doesn't seem that way. It seems
hard to That is only because you are
placing the idea that you have to make a
decision about it upon the idea. Let it
be obvious. Act upon whatever excites
you the most that you have the ability
to act upon. The things that you don't
have the ability to act upon. By acting
upon the things you do, the ability to
act upon everything else will come and
everything will fit into place. It is
only your assumption that there isn't
enough time for everything that makes it
all lumped together in a way that makes
it seem impossible to choose. Everything
fits perfectly. Let it make itself
obvious and then you will not have to
make a decision. The decision will have
been made by the way it comes to you.
You follow me? Yes.
Yes. Thank you. Thank you very much. The
last thing is that I also this week have
had Oh, this has been incredibly
synchronistically I mean I thought it
was incredibly before but
and one of the things that kept uh
appearing a lot through different people
was about myself channeling and being
also in the channeling class. Oh wow.
And someone said to me that that they
had some reference to a spirit guide
that wanted to speak through me. And so
I was wondering wondering about that.
Well, then you said to the other person
that about I guess what I'm trying to
ask is what is the difference between
channeling your higher self or a spirit
guide and also what where do angels come
into all this? whole
blanket. On one level there is no
difference at all. On another level
there is a differentiation and it can be
seen as its own consciousness. It can be
seen as consciousness that has been
embodied that you have interacted with
perhaps in many different lives. This is
what the majority of spirit guides can
be. Spirit guides can also be
consciousness from other plains, other
levels of consciousness in many
different ways. This is not to say they
are not their own consciousness but on
one level we are all the same
consciousness. We simply remove the idea
of the labeling because in all practical
purposes it is rather arbitrary.
Anything you need to know, any name you
need to know, any label you need to
know, you will know when you need to
know it if that assists in the
connection. Angels in a sense are a
level of consciousness that in your
terminology have never experienced
physical reality in any dimension
whatsoever with all of them. Mhm. And as
such still you are all angels because
there is an aspect of you on every
single level including that
one. So remember that even though you
are interacting many times with what you
call a separate spirit
guide much of what you actually
experience as the communication itself
is your energy because it is the job if
you will of the spirit guide to lure you
into using you.
So the channeling that you see right now
before you is not directly my
consciousness. It is the consciousness
of the physical channel allowing itself
to alter to match my vibrational pattern
so that a model of my consciousness is
created for you. And then there is again
yet another removal in that you have to
create your version your model of what
you perceive coming through the channel
in order to perceive it at all. So by
the time it gets to you, it's made of
your energy. And it is you molding your
energy to create a faximile of what you
think is happening through the channel,
which is a faximile of what is happening
from me. Follow me. Well, are you saying then
me. Follow me. Well, are you saying then
that you don't really need a spirit
guide if you can know that you're just
um that that's your own higher self? In
a sense, yes, that is correct. The idea
is that you will probably intermingle
with all other consciousness anyway and
that other individuals simply wishing to
be of assistance will be of assistance
to you. So you'll probably come across
them no matter what. But the idea is to
understand that on one level all
consciousness is the same thing. And if
you simply recognize that then
paradoxically you will be channeling
yourself and at the same time it will be
easier for you to be in touch with all
other levels of consciousness as well.
Well, when the person said this to me
and another person said something about
it, I was afraid of channeling and
then oh I thought
all the religious ideas. All right, let
me remind you simply right now nothing
can control you against your
preference. If you believe that you are
the creator of your reality and you know
what vibration you are, then simply
realize that the vibration you are is
the vibration that you will attract. It
cannot be any other way. Fear that you
may attract something negative is the
calling card.
You follow me? Yeah, that's I was afraid
I'd do that, too. So, all right. I got
it. If you choose to do it at any length
of time, allow yourself to realize, wait
a minute, this is not what I prefer. And
then do what you do prefer. And it will
change the whole scenario immediately.
Just like switching the dial. I no
longer prefer this program. Click. You
are no longer receiving the old program.
Unless, of course, you have a belief
that your dial can get stuck in the
middle and you receive portions of
those. But that has to be your belief.
You follow me? Yes. As you feel yourself
to be, so you align and that is the
energy you will
experience. And if there are fears
within you, then explore them with great
vitality. And in doing so, they will no
longer be fearful and you will transform
them into positive vibrations which will
attract what you bring. I feel that
that's already happening. And I I found
a book about channeling that as I'm
reading it, it just is wonderful. And
there you are. You attract all the tools
that you require when you require them
automatically, effortlessly and that is
communication from your guides and your
higher self and you and you had said
about the labels that at times you can
know about your spirit guides. That was
what I was going to ask you if I could
know that. Yes, you can. Relax,
meditate, allow yourself to balance out,
be very relaxed, no expectations, and
then talk. You'll get an answer. Whether
you validate it or invalidate it or not
is up to you. You will get an answer.
And if it feels correct, use it as a
symbol. It will work. All right. Okay.
If it doesn't work for you, don't use
it. It is as simple as that. You will
sense how to align yourself. You have
your own truth sense. And your truth
sense simply means you know what is
representative of the vibration you are.
All right. That's great. Thank you very
much. Happy channel. Thank you. At this
timing, you may all channel a short
break and we will resume contact
momentarily. FA continue.
FA continue.
Hello Bashar. I'm to you. Uh Bashar, I
would uh uh appreciate your perspective
on a the uh the basic agreements that
are between my daughters and their
father. Um I would like to be of service to to
Um I would like to be of service to to
my daughters at this time. They're going
through a lot of pain because of the uh
the scenario that has been happening.
define um their father uh left when they were
um their father uh left when they were
one and three and disappeared from their
lives except for three times in which
but all three times he has come into
their life uh gained their trust and
love and then disappeared and this is
the appears to be the disappearing phase
of the third time they're now 14 and 16
and going through a very painful
reaction to this I feel that I
understand what I have gained from this
from from this situation. But I would
like to be able to aid them and be of
service and help them to understand
their agreements and how best they can
deal with this. There are some that
connect into many other different
lifetimes. One of which is when they
were in your terms husband and wife and
had as the energy of the father a child
in a similar reciprocal relationship.
And in this way there was the idea
within that
relationship of a lack of support, a
lack of fundamentals as you understand
within the relationships. But
also recognize that what is being done
now is a playing out to some degree of a
lack of understanding on their part in
another life as the husband, as the wife
of the fact that no matter where anyone
is, they are connected and that you can
sense that connection regardless of
physical proximity. We are not in any
way, shape or form condoning a lack of
integrity upon any other individual. But
the idea in this way is to understand
that they are connected in many ways and
that physical proximity does not have to
be symbolically representative of that
connection. Also there are many
connections they need to make between
themselves and their own understanding
of who they are, their own relationship
to creation. And they are being given,
not that it has to be done in the way it
is being done, but they are still
nonetheless by agreement being given an
opportunity by the individual you call
the father, an opportunity to come to
terms with their own self reliance,
their own stability, their own
independence in that way. and an
understanding that once again they are
connected in many different ways to all
individuals and that the quote unquote
wanderings of the father can function as
remote eyes, remote senses for the
children in that way so that they can
through their inner sight, through their
imagination play through, see through
the eyes of the father wherever that
physical local may be. And this as a
lure will stretch. Pull them out. Pull
them out. Pull them out in many
different ways. They have agreed to this
particular type, this particular format
because in other lives they were in many
ways too sheltered, too dependent in
that sense. And so in this way they are
being pulled out in a very polarity
demonstration. So they will be forced to
stretch and broaden their perspective.
Now this does not mean it has to turn
into a cynicism which is possible if
they are looking at this through the
typical way that your society looks at
this idea. They can also understand that
in very many ways they are very
connected to the father that they are
never really apart and they can allow
this experience to stretch and broaden
their perceptions in many different ways
and it does not have to arrive at a
particular idea you would call a cynical
approach to familial relations. Is any
of this making sense so far? It's making
sense. Uh it's making sense but I don't
know how to help them to understand it.
All right. Define name, define age of each.
right. Define name, define age of each.
Uh Francesca 14, Justine 16.
Remind if you
will, though it may seem on the surface
to make no sense. In story fashion,
Francesca of the wild and exuberant
lifestyles that she may allow herself to
remember she has lived. The idea of
being a center of attention in many ways
through many
lifetimes and now finding that the
attention that is craved being that
which abandons. Allow there to be understood
abandons. Allow there to be understood
that the vitality of the lives that were
lived can be reclaimed but it is within.
The fire burns within and again it can
be a creative
by
justine. In this way the coolness of
analysis the scope of comprehension that
is capable within this individual can be
brought to the surface with the memory
of many nights gazing at the stars. many
nights putting all the pieces together
and contemplating the idea of the
relationship of the heavens and the
earth. These individuals are in many
ways like the fire and the water and
they balance each other out and in
combining can form if you will the
metaphor of the steam that will allow
them to expand and know that they can
float ethereally that they can cover the
whole ground together by combining the
understanding of their relationship and
in a sense not in the same way of course
as before marrying each other allowing
the bond and the binding that exists
between them to blend them together to
expand in ethereal ways so that each can
support the other so that they can form
the type of relationship between
themselves and with themselves to
creation that they need to in bringing
up the idea of the fiery lives and the
coolness of perception that they have
both had many times by hearkening
stories to them if you will perhaps as
one way by bringing them into scenarios
and circumstances that may rekindle some
of those attitudes in another way.
Adventures in life, experiences of
meeting new individuals, particularly
for Francesca, and the idea of cool and
serene panoramas for Justine, can spark
and bring within them once again a
recollection and a remembrance of who
they really are at their core and can
allow them the absolute confidence and
assuredness of the stability of the
foundation of each of the individuals
that they represent. You follow along
somewhat. Uh, I understand what you're
saying and I I understand your
identification of each of them. I I do
not yet have a handle on how to really
communicate with them. They're not open
in this way.
Uh, such as my perception sometimes.
Sometimes. All right. Why not simply
trust your own sensing as to when that
is conducive? All right. And at the same
time you can create as a perfume if you
will as a flower creates an atmosphere
around itself an atmosphere within your
relationship with them that would allow
them to slide to desire to slide into a
relationship with you wherein they will
be willing to allow you to make
suggestions that they can then follow.
Even though it does not have to be made
in a demanding form, it will seem as if
they are sliding in directions they
prefer to in subtle and unobtrusive
ways. Radiate the atmosphere that they
simply like magnets allow themselves to
be attracted to those particular ideas,
those particular type of scenarios that
will allow them to discover who they
really are. Each of them is at a high
time of psychic activity. And this can
be stretched in many different ways and
exercised if you will like a mental
muscle. This is what they are about to
learn to do. And they may give
themselves Justine perhaps more of an
opportunity through analysis or reason.
Francesca perhaps more of an opportunity
through actual experience in the living
of the life to expand those psychic
intuitions. But there will come a time
when they will have to exchange roles in
many ways and share the attributes of
one another so that they will allow
themselves to be complete within the
relationship and the mirror that they
are to each other. You follow me? Yes, I
do. But radiate the petals of the
flowers, spread the petals around and
create there to be a conducive
atmosphere, an idealic atmosphere in
which each of them will discover the
magical area, the magical kingdom within
themselves. Now, one area that this may be extremely
Now, one area that this may be extremely
conducive is the hard energy of the
planet that you call
Hawaii. Each of them can find the type
of scenarios and the type of areas that
they may find most conducive to bringing
them out. Thank you. Thank you. It is up
to you. Um, one other question about
Francesca. she is experiencing
um sporadic rashes and itches and uh
this kind of thing. I thought it might
be related to this situation. uh but
it's nothing that I I definitely know my
yes to some degree in a sense it is some
change in the environment will also aid
in assistance to some degree but it is
once again a reaction to some degree to
the apparency of abandonment and the
strong fire that burns within and the
desire and need for a particular type of
recognition. Thank you. Is there anything that I can
Thank you. Is there anything that I can
do for her? She she gets very angry at
me because I won't take her off to the
doctor. She wants to go to the doctor.
They'll give her something and it'll
make it go away. Uh is there anything
that I can do to help her because she
has no openness to any other um reason
that this is going on?
What is your reluctance to follow her
belief system?
It's that I feel that I they will give
her something perhaps that will help the
itching, but it won't help. I
don't because I believe that it's caused
by her mind in the situation. No, I
don't. So, then why not trust and follow
her belief system for now to allow her
to play through what she needs to play
through? Okay. To the recognition and
decisions that she needs to. Okay. I I
understand. Thank you.
Um um I've been asked to ask you what uh
is the earthly um equivalent in terms of
herbs of cortisone. There are
some one aspect is contained in an idea
you call Berdo.
one in an
aspect you call wormwood.
wormwood.
Some in what you would call some
Peruvian plants name unknown within the memory of
plants name unknown within the memory of
the
channel. There are also many herbs that
many individuals more familiar with that
particular methodology will be able to
assist you with within the gathering
this evening of your
time. But some of them in your terms are
very strong
reactants also. You will find that anis
and fennel
seed can also create some of the
enzyatic reactions that are
desirable. This is a fluctuating thing
with the energy of the individual that
is referring this idea to themselves.
For now the doors are closed to us. The
information therefore by our
understanding will come through other
lines. Thank you. Um, one last question
that I feel relates to um, my daughters
and I. About 13 years ago, I had a
dream, a quote dream in which uh, I was
I on a spaceship and there was a large
pool with dolphins swimming in it. And I
was I was asked if I wanted to go off
with them and go to another planet and
live. And I said, "No, I can't. I must
take care of my children."
Um, at that time I had no understanding
of the dolphin significance or anything
else really about it. I'm very
interested in what energy that was and
why I never was given in the dream the
vision of the beings who spoke to me.
Was that because I was not ready to see
that? Were not given the vision of the
beings that spoke to you? Well, I don't
believe that it was the dolphins that
spoke to me. I did not see the entities
that offered to take me with them. And I
would like that there are other
connections, but what makes you think it
wasn't the dolphins as well?
Well, it may have been the dolphins.
I've had a very strong connection with
with underwater energy all my life. Some
of that is generally representative of
Sirius, although there are arc tourist
connections as well.
Why not simply dive back into that pool
in your dream state and see what further
communications you can initiate. Thank
you. That's very beautiful. I'll do
that. All right. Is up to you. Thank
you. And again, simply remember that you
know what you are doing and you
recognize the timing. You will
understand the labeling and you will
understand the origins of some of this
as time progresses. Some of it is
serious energy. Thank you. That is
usually the one most often associated
with the dolphins and symbols of water.
Thank you very much. Thank you.
There is a diamondlike doorway through
which you can also pass. Use that in
your meditation. See a clear blue white
diamondlike shape. Go through it. Thank
you. Thank you. Sherry. Hello Bashar.
And to you. Um I'd like to ask you to
have a look at my future track please.
Which one? Um, my professional one.
Which one? Um, this one from now in the
immediate future. You mean is that not
from now till now? Yes.
Uh-huh.
Uh from now till now. Yeah. All right.
Okay. Um for
um for many years um my profession has
been in the metaphysical field in
healing and counseling and workshops and
so on. And uh a couple of months ago I
found myself um in the middle of um
international in the international money
market. Um big deals and big deals. Yes.
Um big money deals. Yes. And my question
is uh do you see in my future track that
uh my work will increase in this and
actually be a success or is it not is it
not there? I mean is it not going to be
a success? Is it not going to happen? Do
you see it?
Um I did but I did uh but having um
invested quite a lot of money in it and
still it hasn't come to fruition the way
I want it to. Um I this is why I'm
asking you the question because I want
to stop worrying about whether it's
going to happen or not. Well, go ahead
and stop
and then maybe something can happen.
Okay. I knew you would you'd come out
with these funny remarks. Um,
recognize that many of the funny remarks
you are hearing are simple indications
of the fact that you are completely in
control of this idea. All it takes is
examining the belief systems you have
about it that will determine the outcome
for you. Okay. Now, why are you excited
about that idea? Because it's very
exciting to think that I can become a
millionaire overnight. All right.
Um that is money the only way you will
allow yourself to be abundant?
No. No. No. All right. No. I'm abundant
in many ways, but money but the money
abundance is certainly one aspect of
abundance that I wish. All right. All
right. And um are you willing to allow it to
And um are you willing to allow it to
come to you in ways other than what you
might immediately expect that it should
come? Yes. All right. I I'm willing for it to
Yes. All right. I I'm willing for it to
come in any way. Um are you desperate
that it must come?
Is this an act of desperation?
[Music] Well um there there there are moments of
Well um there there there are moments of
desperation. Why? Why? Because of
frustration. I would say that um I spend
many hours and um many dollars um in
this and then it it something falls
through and then then I then there's
frustration. All right.
All right.
Are you always abundant?
I am. Then why are you frustrated?
Because the abundance I'm talking about
about my being abundant isn't
necessarily dollar abundance in my bank
account. What's the difference?
Uh well, I do see a difference. Why?
Because if I go into a baker and and
say, "I'm I wish to give you my
abundance in return for this um
strawberry shortcake." Yes. He's not
going to give it me. Why not?
How will you know that? I know. You know
that. I know that. Why do you know that?
Why do I know that? Why would you rather
not know something else? You're right.
You're right. Why would I not? May I ask
you a question? Yes. Are you saying it
is absolutely outside of your ability to
imagine that you could just simply walk
into a bakery and for some reason that
you don't have to know the baker might
consider just giving you something? Are
you saying that's beyond your
comprehension? No, because many
wonderful things and like that have
happened. Well
then I insist that it must not continue
that way.
Now I am just exploring many ideas with
you. What we are saying in no way, shape
or form is an indication of what will or
will not happen. That we cannot
determine anyway. That is up to you.
However, in examining many times the way
you look at abundance, it can allow you
to determine what it is you are doing
and why you are doing it. If it is in
your estimation and imagination highly
probable that you can simply allow
yourself to effortlessly attract what
you need when you need it, no matter how
it comes, why would you insist on having
an intermediary symbol before you will
allow yourself to have what you may be
able to have far more easily in another
way? because I have okay visualized um this
because I have okay visualized um this
abundance this dollar abundance for for
many many years
and it hasn't come any other way and now
wait a minute wait a minute you are
contradicting yourself you have just
said you have had abundant experiences
where it did not take the idea of money
yes but this particular dollar that's
not what we are asking you oh I'm sorry
could you Repeat you. In other words, a
particular scenario using your example
allowing something to be acquired from a
bakery. In your terms, it can either be
given to you or you can in your terms
with money purchase it. Yes. Mhm. Yes.
Now, if it can be given to you more
easily, would you still insist on having
to get the money in order to purchase it
anyway? No. No. No. Well, then why are
you being so insistent that you have to
have the money to represent abundance in
your life?
Because all the things that I wish to
have, I know that I will need. Watch
yourself. You what? You know you will
need the money to get them. That's what
I was about to say. Why do you know you
need money to get them? Many people used
to say, "I know I need money to get that
bakery good." But if somebody gives it
to you, is that not an indication that
you don't always know that you need the
money to get it?
Yeah. If there is one exception, that
can become a lifestyle.
[Laughter] Now, we are not meaning to imply that
Now, we are not meaning to imply that
you go through life panhandling.
Thank you.
But simply recognize that many times the
reason for the quote unquote blockage of
the monetary symbol in many individuals
life is their insistence upon it. They
are constricting the flow themselves
because they say they cannot imagine
that any other way might be the path of
least resistance more than having the
money. If you already know that with the
analogy of the bakery, it can happen
that you can be given the baked goods,
why not simply assume that that is the
rule and not the exception rather than
assume that the money is the rule and
not the exception? Just because you see
it that way very often in your society
doesn't mean one way or another that one
way or another is the rule and not the
exception. When you decide what is the
rule and what is the exception, that's
how your life becomes structured. So if
you decide that you
prefer allowing your abundance to come
to you in whatever way, shape or form
you need it to without the money always
having to be the rule rather than the
exception. Then you will find things
coming to you and you will probably not
need as much money as you think you
need. When you allow your abundance to
be equal across the board in all the
ways it could come to you, then you may
find that in proportion to the way
things come to you, you will need far
less money. But you will always have
just enough, exactly enough to bring you
the things that need to come through the
utilization of the symbol of money.
So let us say in your life if you can
create your life to be
75% other forms of abundance and 25%
money then you'll only have 25% of the
money. If you insist on more than 25%
you're actually fighting your own
flow your own ease of creation. Because
if your life says but why don't you want
75% of your abundance in this other way
which is the more effortless
way. You follow me? Mhm.
Now these things that for now you think
you know you need money to have. Why do
you think you know you need money to
have them? Can you imagine that they
could even just for a moment come to you
in another way? Is there any other
possibility at all other than insisting
that you have to have money in order to
get these things you desire? Is there
any other way that they could come?
Well, in my imagination, of course, yes.
Here's the clue. Oh, yes. In my
imagination. As everyone knows,
imagination is not real.
Oh yes it is. Your physical reality is
absolutely and utterly nothing more than
what you imagine it to be based upon
what you have been told to imagine it
is. Now you don't have to buy into that
anymore. Your imagination is absolutely
real. And you may take me literally. I
am not speaking philosophically.
Imagination is representative of real
reality. All that it takes is for you to
decide that's the reality I
prefer, then you start acting as if it
is really real. And as soon as you start
acting that that's really real, what you
picture as opposed to what you have been
experiencing, then what you picture is
what you will begin to experience. Okay,
that's exactly why I'm here tonight
because that's exactly what I did with
these fields. One moment. Okay,
what is also important is to get in
touch with why you desire the reality
you desire. Yes, to picture it and to
act as if that is real is to bring it
into manifestation, but not if it goes
against the grain of your path of least
resistance and not if it goes against
the grain of what you really believe you
are capable of or what you really
need because then you'd only be fighting
yourself. Mhm. I understand that. All
right. So, the idea we are asking you is
yes, you created the pictures of the
money deals and you created them to come
to fruition. Uhhuh. But if
that representation in and of itself is
representation in and of itself is
actually a constriction of your
abundance rather than representative of
an expansion of your abundance, you're
going to create a salemate as you have
done. You follow me? I follow you. I was
not, however, aware that that there was
any um constriction in it in in my
desiring it. Correct. But the result
that occurs i.e. the stalemate
makes you aware that there is a
constriction. Uhhuh. That is why you can
always understand that what happens in
your physical reality is always an
absolute 100% reflection of what is
going on within you in terms of the
beliefs you are examining. Okay. So
there was a constriction. So then of
course that that's what manifests. Yes.
Uhhuh. And the constriction can be for
negative or positive reasons.
So it's up to you to determine the idea
of why you want the scenario you have
created to come to fruition. And if it
is primarily because you don't believe
there's any other way to get what you
want, that may be the reason for the
constriction to show you yet there are
other ways. They are quicker. They are
more effortless. They are easier. Why
insist on what you have pictured when
your reality is showing you that that
may not be the easiest
path? Why fight and beat your head
against the wall when all you need to do
is say, "hm, it's not happening as I
pictured. There must be a reason, a
positive reason for that. Therefore, I
will look around and see what other ways
what I want could come to me rather than
insisting that this is the only way it
will come."
It is that willingness to examine all
other probabilities in the face of what
is happening that gives you the
opportunity to use that circumstance in
a positive way.
You follow me? I do follow you. So let
us again examine the idea of why you
have to have the manifestation as you
have visualized it. Why must it be that
way or you will not allow yourself to
believe you'll be able to get what you
want? No, I haven't. I have not um
denied myself the belief that I will get
what I want. It's just that I was so
wholeheartedly set on getting it this
way now. Yes. And so, and so that's why
um I don't see why it isn't coming to
me. What is it you
want? I want one of these deals to
close. And in other words, let me put it
this way. Is the deal in and of itself
the goal or is the deal a step towards
something? It's a step. What is the
thing? It is a step towards
money, dollars for what? to enable me to
do what I want to do further in life
which is um expanding my activities in
any way I wish with in in a relaxed way
where I don't have to think of of
earning money to pay my rent earning it
to eat where it's just there and all the
survival functions of this earth are
just taken care etc you know okay what
activity
I haven't decided on them Oh, in detail.
Is that the thing? But why should I why
do I have to constrict myself into such
a Oh, that is not necessarily a
constriction. Let me put it on a very
simplistic level. If you do not know
what the money is going to let you do,
why should the money come? Okay. Well, I
know some of it. I don't know all of it.
Then name something. Okay. Uh I want to
travel all over the world. I want the
world. Yes. Why?
because I would like to
um investigate more deeply different
cultures and meet people that I know
that I already know but I haven't met
yet this lifetime etc. Now you have
provided us with a clue.
Let me ask you a question. May I?
Yes. Are you going to wait until you
have the money to start acting upon
whatever opportunities you could be
acting upon that represent being that
type of person or are you going to act
as that type of person act now? Well,
I'm waiting for the money because then
because I think that that will enable me
to do it in the way I want to do it.
That's your stumbling block right there.
You are waiting for the money before you
will be who you are. What it takes to
allow the money to pour through is to
start being who you are and acting upon
the opportunities that present
themselves in your life now. That is
what will create the momentum that will
bring you the money. Until you act upon
what you have available to act upon now
and until you be the person you say you
want to be when you have the money, then
you do not create the vacuum into which
the money can be pulled. You are not
creating any space for the money to come
in because you're not doing anything
with what you have available to you.
Yes. Okay. Well, I know I could travel
already. Yes, anyone can travel. But
with the money, I could do it in the
style that I want to do it. The point
I'm missing it, right? Could you do it
again, please?
You are
assuming assuming that you cannot travel
in the style you want to travel in,
right? Without the money. That is not
necessarily true. The point of the
matter is start acting like the person
you want to be. Start being that person
now and you will attract whatever it is
necessary to attract. You will start
traveling and you will find that you
will be able to start traveling in style
in certain ways. But always the style
will be conducive of what it is you
actually are learning within the
traveling. Also recognize that you will
simply attract yourself into
circumstances that will probably make it
more conducive for you to have the
money. If you start moving now, until
you start moving, you will not create
the type of momentum that will bring you
the money. Let me put it another
way. There is no such thing truly as an
individual that is more rich than any
other individual. Everyone, everyone has
actually just enough to be the expanded
idea. They are just enough. No one has
more than they need. Now, when you start
acting like a person that travels in
style, you will attract a lifestyle that
reflects that. Right now, you are
waiting to act like that type of a
person. And so the money and the
lifestyle is waiting for you to take the
first step. So the idea is look around decide
step. So the idea is look around decide
what is available for you to act upon
already. If you were the person you want
to be, how would you act differently
than you are acting now? Act that way on
whatever opportunities present
themselves in the style of a person who
is used to acting that way. And when you
take the first step in that style, you
will then be making a commitment to that
life style and it will come to you. But
first you must act in that style. You
must have the life of that type of a
person. You must be the person who has
that type of a life and act that way on
everything you do. Everything you do.
Because if you were that type of a
person, the slightest thing in your life
would be done differently than you are
doing it now. You would be doing it as
that type of a person does that thing.
So create the picture of how you would
be and then do everything in your life
no matter what it is like that type of a
person would do it and you will generate
the radiation the vibratory frequency of
that type of a person and you will have
the lifestyle of that person. You
understand? I understand what you're
saying. Um that is not a real mechanism
for you.
It's real.
But um okay.
So so you go and you buy a ticket um
first class to go to India and you stay
in a castle and you live that lifestyle
of that type of a person. You act upon
the opportunities that present
themselves to you at whatever level they
present themselves with all the style
you can muster on that level.
You fill that level up with all the
style you have and that makes room for
another level of
style. Until you do everything in the
fullest style, you will not make room
for more style to happen to you. Okay.
Okay. I get it. I get the technique. You
see, if you are saying, well, this
incident is beneath my style, then you
do not act upon it with full style. So,
the universe says, well, you're not
acting like a person who lived that way.
You are treating and reacting the
situations in your life in a meager way.
So, here's what you get, a meager
lifestyle. Mhm. When you act to the
fullest on everything as it presents
itself, then you are creating the
lifestyle of a rich person. Because a
rich person does the smallest things
with that kind of style. You follow me?
Mhm. That is the attitude. If you
develop it, you will develop a life that
is appropriate too. Mhm. Does that make
sense now? Yes. Yes, that does make
sense. Uh that does make
sense. So
keep it simple. Keep it simple. Yeah. So
I'm still I'm still thinking. So what
what did I miss in in You didn't miss
anything except the idea that you are
elevating certain things above other
things and the things that are in your
life are worth being there and you are
creating to be
unworthy. When you give them the work
that is their due, all the work in the
universe will be
yours. Follow me. Mhm. Mhm. So that's
what I have to look for. What are the
things that I have uh made unworthy in
my life? Live everything in your life in
the style of a person who is rich.
Uhhuh. Uhhuh. That does not always mean
if you will actually observe rich people
that you have to spend the most on
everything you do. No, no, no. I
understand. All right. It is the
approach. It is the attitude. It is the
finesse. It is the
confidence that is what creates a person
to be
rich. They know they already own it. And
therefore they know that what comes to
them is a part of their Welch, not a
part of their poverty.
Thank you Basha very much.
Shing. Hi Bashar. Hi. My very first time. I'm
Hi Bashar. Hi. My very first time. I'm
kind of excited. Me, too. Once again,
I'm not kind of excited. I'm very
excited. Okay. Hi, Alra. I'm thinking of
going into a new business. All right. Go
right ahead. Have a good night.
I love children. Yay. I was a nursery
school teacher for eight years. All
right. And I studied cartoon voices. All
right. and thought I thought what I
would do is I'd dress up like little
animals. All right. You know, like a
little bear or a little bunny or
something. All right. Bear bunny. All
right. And uh and then uh plan children's
And uh and then uh plan children's
parties. All right. And do it with a
little bunny voice or a little bear
voice. Well, you go right ahead.
And uh it it's kind of an idea because
um kind of an idea. It's not kind of an
idea. It is an idea. All right. It's an
idea. Yes. And I'm very I'm excited
about it. Yes. But I'm But I'm wondering
if it will come about.
That's like saying, "Here I am behind
the wheel of my very own car. I have
turned it on and my foot is poised above
the gas pedal and I'm wondering if it
will go.
What do you mean? You are wondering if
it will come about. You say you are
excited about it. You say you know
clearly what you want to do. Do it and
then it will come about won't it?
Okay. I All you are missing is the trust
that it will support you which of course
it will if it represents what excites
you the most. That's right. You got it.
You got it. No. All right. I got it.
It's that simple. Trust it. It never
doesn't work. Never. Never. Because I'm
excited. Because you are excited and
because you are willing to trust that
when it's something excites you, it
represents what you are capable of doing
in life most effortlessly and most
abundantly. Advertise that fact. Tell
everyone who you are and they will want
you to come and do your bunny voice.
Okay, I'll do it. Thank you very much.
Can I ask you another question, please?
You'll have to ask if you can ask. All
right. Um, I'm starting a new business,
too. And another new business that I
kind of like a contact. Okay. To sell uh
precious jewels. All right. And I just
wonder if I have the background in
business knowledge to make uh a business
out of it. Let me put it this way. Act
upon the things that excite you the most
that you know you are most capable of
acting upon and it will lure you into
whatever scenario you need to gain the
experience to act upon anything else
that excites
you. Maybe you will give a party for the
child of a person who will teach you the
business you need to know. Oh yeah. Oh
yeah. All excitement is connected to all
other excitement. Act upon the things
that excite you that you are capable of
acting upon and that will lead you into
the scenarios that give you the skills
you need to act upon anything else that
has ever excited you. Just like you
said, all the little tributaries, they
all meet in the ocean.
I I believe that. I really do. Thank
you. Act accordingly and you will see
the results. We guarantee it 100%.
Can I ask you one other question? Okay.
Uh I was I've come several times. This
is the first time I've ever spoken, but
I've come several times and you said one
time that
microwaves were good to have in the home
for cooking. Now, I said that. Well, no,
the way you said it. Wait a minute. I I
want to make it perfectly clear. Thank
you. But I do not remember ever saying
But I do not remember ever saying
microwaves are good to have in the home
for cooking.
But what you did say, what you did say
was to heat water in a microwave would
change the vibration of the water and
then it was good for us to drink that
water. What I said was certain microwave
What I said was certain microwave
frequencies can alter it in beneficial
ways. Many microwave frequencies will
impart a certain structural change to
the water that will be temporary and
then there will be no additional side
effect once the microwaves are turned
off. I see because I was thinking about
getting a microwave oven. Your own
electromagnetic energy will structure
the crystallin energy within water
appropriately, far more swiftly than any
of your microwave devices will. Simply
imagine blue white electromagnetic light
going from any portion of your body,
your hands, your head if you wish, your
heart, your solar plexus into the water
and allow yourself to know that within a
very calm meditative state, you will be
imparting to that water a certain
crystallin structure and therefore
extracting from that water the power
inherent within the crystallin structure
of that substance. And in drinking it,
it can align and assist in your
alignment and assimilation of your
acceleration to higher energy. I see.
Okay. Thank you,
Bashar. And be of assistance and allow
it in your terminology to create all the
understanding that is necessary for
smoothness of transition.
Yes, he's been in and out of the
hospital several times over the last few
years for various
operations. And it occurred to me that
he might now be preparing particularly
my mom for his
absence. Um what else can you tell me
about that? Do you sense this is we can
gaze upon them allow the state
vibrational frequency that they put you
in to take you where you need to go and
so that you can understand the
relationship between the three of you.
Thank you. This is what we can assist
you with at this time. More information
can come from other individuals but
right now it is not our place to do so.
Okay, I understand. Um, I'm planning to
go on a trip
um shortly after the 1st of June and be
gone for a couple of weeks. If I felt
that he was going to be leaving while I
was gone, I would not go. I would stay
to be with my mother.
We cannot tell you what to do, but it is
our suggestion that you stay around.
Okay? because there may be many
processes that will allow you to know
when the timing feels correct for you to
go on your way. Thank you very much,
Bashar. Thank you very much. Love to
you. Swim freely. Thank you. At this
timing, once again, allow us to extend
to each and every one of
you the ocean of our dreams. The ocean
of your dreams. so that you may know you
can swim freely in that ocean and drink
deeply of the knowledge that is
inherently your
own. Allow
yourselves to connect in the vast ocean
of electromagnetic energy around your
entire world with all
occurrences, all
fluctuation, all energy gates, all
vortices. And know that you are a part
of the matrix, a part of the web, a part
of the net. And that the pulse of the
entire world will be felt by each of you
when and where you choose to be
sensitive. And you will play your part
in the symphony and the orchestration of
that energy upon your world.
We thank you for your willingness to
create this
crystallization which allows our
consciousnesses to interface with your
own more
smoothly. Our unconditional love to you
all, excitement to you in your
transitional time. It is a very exciting
place and time to be and you have all
chosen well. We thank you for your
boldness. We thank you for your
brilliance. We thank you for your love
and we bid you a fond of good night.
Good night.
[Applause]