All right, I'll say how are you all this
evening of your time as you create time
to exist.
Allow us to begin this evening of your
time with a
reminder that last week of your time we
said we would discuss a tool, a device,
a perspective that is referred to as the
harmonic wave. in alignment with the idea now
wave. in alignment with the idea now
that many of you have been discussing
that you have labeled harmonic
convergence in your language. Allow us
to begin to recognize what the meaning
of this idea is about in our perspective
from our point of view in our
interactions with you from the
perspective of extraterrestrial
societies as they are beginning to
interact with your terrestrial society.
The explanation in mechanical terms of what
explanation in mechanical terms of what
you call the harmonic convergence is as
follows. Many of you have begun to
instinctively recognize that many
changes are taking place upon your
planet. That these changes are
indicative of levels of awareness. you
have created within yourself that have
heretofore not been experienced upon
your planet for quite some time as you
count time for tens of thousands
hundreds of thousands perhaps of your
years. The idea of this recognition of
harmonic convergence is basically an
observation of the over overlapping of
many different frequencies of energy,
frequencies if you will of
consciousness. Many
harmonic convergence is simply
representative of a nodal point if you
will an overlap of many different cycles
coming into reinforcement play one unto
another reinforcing each other opening
up a gateway a doorway in one sense
reinforcing each other in one sense
cancelelling each other out forming a
vacuum assume, so to speak, a limbo
state, a state of
disorientation, a state of floating in
which you find yourselves able to
perceive all the different variations,
all the different probable realities
that can exist. So that in that floating
state, you can choose which reality you
prefer to create upon your planet. Now
different societies at different times
have different cycles not only upon your
own world but on many other worlds have
their own timing for their own
convergences their own bringing together
of harmonics of resonances of
frequencies as we have discussed many
times one large scale
cycle small perhaps in one perspective
but one that generally repeats itself
over and over and over again in your
particular earth society that we have
discussed with you many times is the
cycle you call the 40-year cycle. In
plain terms, it seems to be that in your
particular brand of
consciousness, you will generate a cycle
of 40 orbits, 40 years in which to
create changes that allow there to be the
changes that allow there to be the
ability to see things that are
180° polarized from the way you used to
see them 40 of your years ago. 40 years
has been used in much of your religious
literature to indicate the change time
necessary for whole societies, for whole
cultures in your planet, 40 days for the
change of a single individual.
This 4-year cycle in your terms of
counting has allowed us now to apply to
a particular tool called the harmonic
wave the ability to show you in clear
and graphic terms how your cycles play
out in your society and show you the
determiners that show you where you are
within the overall series of events that
is indicative and representative of your
entire transformational age which is
generally 80 of your years in length.
You are now approximately literally
halfway through
through
assistant Erica. Yes. Yes.
[Music]
Yes. For this to be easily translated.
Once again, a visual aid to assist
you in holding this diagram
aloft. Many of you will begin to
recognize first of all familiar patterns
within this. You have seen similar
symbols throughout your society for
quite some time. The idea of what you
call the lotus flower. Many different
forms of vibratory energy
representations that you have called
mandalas. And in that sense harmonic
mantras you have seen expressed in this
format. Generally speaking many of the
ideas are as you say your
interpretations offshoots of this
particular tool. This is a literal
mechanical tool that we utilize to gauge
the momentum in particular societies
that we interact with to determine the
ideas that they are playing out and in
your counting of time when they shall be
most likely to be played out. Now what
you now call the harmonic convergence is
actually the second part of a fourpart
harmonic. The first part which was
initiated in your terms 40 of your years
ago in your year
1,947 can be called the harmonic
initiation. Second, what is now going on
in your society is the harmonic
convergence. Third, and we will point
this out in a moment, what will occur in
your society will be harmonic
identification. And number four will be
the idea you call harmonic
synchronization. These are the four
general steps that fit this particular
template. And when you overlay this
template on any society, once you have
determined the cycle of orbits that
society is using, you can utilize this
template, this tool to determine the
timing within the rest of the
transformational age that will bring
about certain changes to what you call
generally the year. Now the very center
of this
diagram what can be referred to as point
A is the harmonic initiation begun in
1,947 and is very strongly connected to
the fact that that is the year wherein
you began as a society even though it
may have at first been covertly to
recognize that other civilizations what
you call extraterrestrial civilizations
exist and that you are in that sense not
unique or alone. Unique in the way you
present yourself, yes, but you are not
alone. That initiation, the beginning of
that ripple, like a stone dropped into a
pond of water, begins to create
vibrations that move outward in ever
expanding spirals and
circles. As each of you may be familiar
with, when you have a chord, what you
call a string upon one of your
instruments, if you pluck it, you see
that the chord vibrates back and forth.
And you see what you call ghost images
of two chords as the two end points are
fixed and the middle begins to vibrate
in harmonic resonance with itself in
polarity resonance. You understand? Yes,
those cords, those pluckings, those
vibrations are represented by the yellow
petals I shall call them. The idea of
the stone first dropped and then the
resonances going out and coming back
together at the end at the tip of the
yellow petal. Now the tip of the yellow
petals define a small circle within the
large circle. That is where you are now.
That is the harmonic convergence area.
The coming together of all the vibratory
intercases, all the vibratory
axons if you will that determine the
particular type of opening and momentum
you are going through.
out. Notice in the center of each yellow
petal is a straight line with arrows at
either side defining the widest point of
polarity resonance. Simply stated, the farthest
resonance. Simply stated, the farthest
point, the farthest polarity experience
that any chord will strike.
We will get back to that at a moment.
But simply pay attention to the fact
that at that widest
point, we will be discussing
that at the very tip of the yellow
pedal. You can recognize as we have said
that that is the harmonic convergence.
Now your year
1,987. So from the center of the circle
to the tip of the yellow pedal
represents 40 of your years, 40 orbits.
from the tip of the yellow petal all the
way to the outer large circle is another
40 orbits. So you have an
80year diameter in that sense if you
wish or as you call it
radius 80ear radius.
Now at the tips of the yellow petals,
you can see
that for every two of those yellow
petals, they define a larger orange
petal. Do you all see that?
And at the tips of the yellow petals,
there is again a representation in the
large orange petal of another polarity
resonance, another larger chord. And the
widest point in that pedal is defined by
the tips of the yellow pedals. So that
is polarity resonance manifestation
number two. Do you all see that?
There are no more petals in that sense,
but now only the spheres that fit within
the larger sphere. Those moving into
green in that
sense. From the point of the tips of the
orange petals where the lines cross
again from that point outward, the next
point is where each circle meets
tangentially as you say, the edge of the
larger circle. So you have at the center
point A, at the tips of the yellow
petals point B, at the tips of the
orange petals point C, and where the
small circle meet the outside of the
large circle, you have point D, A, B, C,
D in your counting.
Now recognize that at the tips of the yellow
recognize that at the tips of the yellow
pedals now 1987 in your counting is the
harmonic convergence and the outward
movement as you are passing through that
apex now brings you on an outer curve
going to the tips of the orange
petals that is
approximately 30 of your years. Hence
approximately what you would call your
year 2017 at the tips of the orange petal you
2017 at the tips of the orange petal you
begin to see that there are no more
pedals that the realities that you are
now converging that were initiated 40 of
your years ago at point C will be
represented by the harmonic
identification. This is the point we
have discussed with you many times that
represents now when the vibrational
frequency of the particular reality you
prefer will literally begin to separate
from all other realities literally
placing you in whatever parallel earth
you are now most strongly aligned to.
And as you then begin to separate from
all other realities all other parallel
probable earths you begin to continue
the outer curve towards harmonic
synchronization. when that will be the
only experience you will have on your
earth will be representative of what you
have identified yourself with and
accelerated from point C within you in
forming synchronization at the outer
edge that is 40 of your years hence then
that will be utterly and only a world
that contains the things that you
identified most strongly with at point C
when you sep separated from all other
probable realities. Are you following
along so far?
Now look at it simply as a crisscrossing
of energy as a building of acceleration
and momentum that leads you from point
through that point to another point
through that point to another point at
each point of which there are including
the center 13. No accident that this is
your 13th day. The idea as we have
discussed of 13 is that 13 is the
transformational gate number. It is that
which allows you to face all the
different portions you have perhaps
hidden from yourself segregated yourself
into. It is the passing through of a
doorway. It is why it is a
transformational in your terms magic
number and why there is so much
superstition associated with it in your
society because it gets you to face
yourself because you are in the limbo
door of facing all that you
are. These 13 points represent gateways,
vortices of energy within this harmonic
wave template. This is what basically has
template. This is what basically has
determined and what has been picked up
by many individuals in your society as
the reason for the harmonic convergence
going on now for the gathering together
of all probable
realities. Two more interesting
points. We have generally observed that
within any particular
society, there will be two
manifestations in your culture that will
indicate when you have and in what way
you have begun to accept the idea, if
you have begun to accept it, that you
are going to begin to blend with other
societies other than your own.
These two points occur at the two
polarity resonance manifestation points.
The widest parts of the yellow and the
widest part of the orange pedals
indicated by the straight line across
the yellow pedal and the curved line
across the orange pedals. Number one,
number two. As you can see, number one
occurs approximately by definition
halfway along the line from beginning to
now in your yellow pedal. You
understand? Number two occurs right in
line with the harmonic convergence
because that is where all probable
realities coincide. Now, we'll play a little game
coincide. Now, we'll play a little game
for a moment.
These two points, the polarity resonance
manifestations usually manifest in a
culture through some art form, some way
that that culture expresses itself most
strongly and usually is the strongest
and most graphic representation of how
that culture thinks of itself in terms
of relating to other extraterrestrial
cultures. So you can see that the second one which
So you can see that the second one which
is usually an amplification of the first
occurs now in your year
1987. The first one being halfway
between your year 1947 and now 1987
occurred in what you call
1967. The game, the guessing
game is to decide what cultural
phenomena artistically
speaking in your year 1967 represented
in the most graphic way your ongoing
relationship with extraterrestrial
cultures. Yes. Say it louder.
Yes. Now, we know some of you may find
this quite amusing.
The idea of what you call your Star Trek
program was initiated exactly halfway in
your year
1,967 and now in your year 1,987 is
being reinitiated a
reinitiated a
new. It is the same expression upgraded
updated to encompass your new
understandings and all the things you
have learned to incorporate within
yourselves within the last 20 of your
years. for the second half of the yellow
petal. This will usually occur in every
society in a unique way to that society.
You have fit the pattern perfectly. You
have fit the template
perfectly. Some of you may think the
idea of that program to be a frivolous
representation, but it is your most
overriding understanding. Why it has
endured for so long is because it
represents the blending of your society
with other societies in the most graphic
way you allowed yourself to represent it
at that time. And that is why it is in
your terms a worldwide phenomenon. There
are no accidents in this sense. There
are no accidents in that energy. And
there is no accident in the sense that
your interest in that particular
phenomena in expressing it that way has
only grown and not diminished.
So in this way you can understand that
point C your year
2017 represents the time generally
though it may fluctuate a little bit
earlier approximately perhaps five of
your years
earlier will initiate and represent the
idea of when there will be within your
society the capability of
physiologically joining us with your own
spacecrafts. That is when your
technology will allow you to develop the
idea similar to our spacecraft. You will
have them by your year
2017 if you maintain your adherence to
the template, which it seems in all
likelihood you will. And then by your
year 2027, you will be absolutely interwoven
2027, you will be absolutely interwoven
into what you call the Galactic
Association of
Worlds. 40 of your years hence not so
very long. You are accelerating rapidly.
Took you 40 years to get to this point.
Will take you only 30 years to get to
the next point and then only 10 after
that. Will you be a part of the
association as absolute
equals? You are accelerating very
rapidly and you fit the pattern very
strongly. As an aside, some of you may
recognize within this also the natural
mathematical relationships that you have
called the Fibonacci series. And if you
look very closely, you may also
recognize, if you remove a few lines,
the old
yinyang symbol. For the yin-yang
symbol. For the yin-yang
symbol comes directly from the harmonic
wave template. And that is what was the
ancient understanding that has been
rendered into your polarity
manifestation. Allow yourself to
recognize that this wave, this energy
that this wave, this energy
wave is one that represents the
frequency, the momentum, the
acceleration. And this harmonic
convergence is simply your ability to
understand that in coming together in
focusing your consciousness for any such
endeavor of harmony, love and light that
you will create an impact on your planet
that you will allow change to occur very
rapidly and allow us to remind you that
even though your earth crystal is also a
part of the harmonic wave, the harmonic
convergence, these vibratory
frequencies, It is not such without
It is not such without
you. Rather than being in the harmonic
convergence, you are the harmonic
convergence, it is you. It is the people
on your planet.
Whether in your terms they understand
the terminology, whether in your terms
they believe in the terminology, you are
all a part of the momentum that brings
you into this nexus point that will
accelerate you according to the curve in
the diagram towards that time when you
more and more will be taking your place
consciously among all the other
societies that recognize their
connection to creation in that way. Has
this translated adequately for you?
There will be opportunity for such will
be
provided later as you say to study the
diagram and understand it in your own
timing at your
leisure and to use it as a template but
not something that rules you. Simply
something that reflects some of the
ideas you are choosing to be.
Thank you, assistant.
Did you all have a good time?
No. All right.
We could have copies made of that. Yes.
Are those colors correct as you perceive
them? It is not such that the colors need to
It is not such that the colors need to
be correct in that sense. They are
simply defined for the purpose of your
visual aid to allow there to be the
strongest clarity within the different
sections. Thank you. At this timing, allow us to
Thank you. At this timing, allow us to
extend to each and every one of you once
again our deepest appreciation for
creating the harmony now and the
convergence now of your society and our
society. In return for this gift and as a
In return for this gift and as a
reflection of the perfect timing of
everything in your lives, we ask you
now, how may I serve you?
Hi, Vishar. Hi. Um, it's no doubt I mean
I'm kind of excited because I'm in limbo
and I'm confused about something. So, I
know I'm at the perfect perfect place.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Okay. So, I'm
going to read this cuz I'm a little
nervous. All right. Um, I hear people
say, you know, there's this belief that
it's our birthright to have the life
that we want. Nice. And that we can
create anything of for our life. It's
our choice and the gift of free will.
Um, what's troubling me is that I feel
that there's this other force that holds
me back from really feeling free to have
the life of my dreams. And I'd like to
give an example. All right. Okay. Um,
like when I was very sick, I would say
to myself, I want to be well and I will
be totally healed. And then this other
side of me would say, "Well, maybe I'm
not meant to be totally well and maybe
it's not really going to happen." And
now I'm faced with the same thing. Like
I it's just like a thought. I'll say, "I
want to be totally abundant and have an
outrageous ecstatic life." And then this
other force in me says, "Well, but maybe
you're not meant to be ecstatic and
have, you know, so I feel like not in
control and not all right. Okay. And I
really want to All right. Be the
creator, but All right. Well, well, yes,
you are. First of all, you are never are
not. Secondly, listen to your
definitions for that is not another
force within
you. It is simply another idea, another
reflection. Because this is the time of
polarity, observation, you will all begin to
observation, you will all begin to
develop the ability to see both sides.
That doesn't mean you have to manifest
the one you don't prefer. But you will
have the ability to more clearly than
you ever have before see completely both
opportunities so that you then have the
clearest ability to choose which one you
do prefer to manifest. Just because you
see it, just because you are aware of it
doesn't mean it will manifest if you do
not prefer it. But you will develop a
stronger ability to see both sides. Do
you understand?
Uh yeah, but there's another point of
that. All right. What is your next
point? Well, I understand what you're
saying that I'm getting the opportunity
to look at both of myself. Okay. Um it's
like I almost feel like not deserving of
that power just to claim something like
you always say, you know, uh prefer. All
right. And I don't like I would like to
feel, hey, that's what I want, so go for
it. And then I feel well, you know, like
I'm like I'm not in I don't feel that.
Uh all right. But you can look at it
this way again. If you wish to approach
everything from a positive point of
view, if you're going to play around
with the idea that you don't deserve
what you prefer, then treat that
experience of non-deservability as one
more option, just an equal option. You
can now choose to play the game of
believing you don't deserve what you
prefer. put it on the same level as
everything else as one more option
rather than relegating it to somehow
being the motive mechanism behind the
options that you are witnessing. Simply
allow it to be one more option equal
with all others and not representative
of some underlying force that is
connected to the options you are
viewing. You understand? Yes. Does that
assist you? Yes. So there's no outside
force beside our own No. No. I know
you're going to say that. There isn't.
Okay. It is simply an opportunity to
look at one more idea, one more
perspective, one more point of view that
you could manifest if you wish
to. The idea of non-deservability is
just as valid a point of view as any
other point of view. And so it will crop
up as an opportunity along with every
other possible point of view you could
have about any given situation.
Understand? Yes.
This is of the same question. Okay. So,
when people say surrender to the flow,
Yeah. like I used to think if I
surrendered to the flow, I'd be a
secretary, you know? It's like I mean, I
know that sounds weird, but I really I
mean, it's like I think it's like from
going to a church or something, you
know? It's like, well, there's this
other will out there, so if I if I don't
No, no, no. There is no other will out
there. The will is within you. It would
be an absolute contradiction for the
creation to have created free will and
then override it.
Understand? Oh, definitely. Yes, I do.
Does that assist you? Yes. So, I'm just
going to look at both points as equal
and play the same game as if one is the
same and then I probably would prefer
doing the one that's most fun which
would be that one. Yes. By the way, yes,
you are doing just fine. and individuals
that we recognize as doing that fine, we
usually decide to have a little fun
with as we decided to last week of your
time. Yeah, Bashar, thanks a lot. I'm
I'm so glad you didn't call me last
week. I love you and it was perfect. I
did call you. I know you did. I'm sorry.
Exactly as it manifested. I called you
to be an equal and you were. I know you
did and I felt it. Thank you. Thank you.
I love you. We love you as well deeply.
Shutting. Hi Rashar. Hi.
Hi Rashar. Hi.
Um first of all I would like to briefly
share the fact that I have read the book
our book in numeric physics at least
eight times. All right. And some parts
of it even more. And each time I read
it, there were new revelations. That's
the whole idea. I know. And well, that's
I know that, but I thought be good to
share it. Well, thank you. It felt like
layers of separation were being lifted
for I was reading it. Yes. You are all
little onions.
Peeling away the outer layers, the
layers of separations. And now and then
because of your habits in peeling those
onions, you may shed a tear.
And it happened particularly when I
consciously uh made a connection to the association
uh made a connection to the association
as I was reading. Yes. I said I'm now
connected to the association and it was
a wonderful experience. Thank you. I
just wanted to share that and talking
about um actually exciting experience
talking about excitement. Yes. Um, I've
been doing a lot of thinking about Oh,
all right. Uh, your normal your regular
question to people, what excites you the
most? Nice. And a lot of us just don't
know what excites us the most. You like
to play that game. Yes. That That's
right.
Well, you do know, but you all like to
play the game that you don't know.
um prolongs the responsibility.
Okay. Well, I
had I wondered about that a lot and I
thought I found what excited me the most
as a result of which I was going to make
a career change. All right. And it
turned out that I didn't. All right. And
when but you did at that moment. Uhhuh.
Again, remember that when we say what
excites you the most, we mean at that
moment. Right. So at the moment I
decided not to make that change. Not
making a change was the thing that
excited me the most. Yes. But at the
same time I thought well I've never well
I had wanted to go into a different
field and why didn't I do it and I
started again thinking does it really
excite me that much to continue doing
similar things and then I realized that
what really excited me was not anything
I was doing but but what excited me was
the fact that I was part of the
transformation. Yes. and that I was an
observer because I'm I'm really watching
and feeling it. Yes. And that is really
what excites me. It will still involve
some doing. Okay. That's since you live
in a physical world of action, right?
Because for a while then I thought it
doesn't really matter what I do because
it is all right for you to do observing.
Eventually you will come around to
understanding that you will prefer to do
doing. Well, okay. Yeah. Then I felt
good about that. Then I listened to the
tapes of April a year ago which was
activity month guys and where you talked
about this doing and I thought well I'm
not doing very much. It is all right for
a while to do observing as long as you
understand in that way that observing is
not all you will do.
Yeah. Well that's that's where I have
the conflict. Why is it a conflict?
because I don't see myself doing the
things. Well, I see because I don't know
what the doing things are that excite
me. But you don't have to right now. If
you know that the observing excites you,
observe with all the excitement you can
and you will eventually observe
something you want to do. Okay?
Okay?
Simply give yourself fully to whatever
it is that does excite you with
integrity. And the next thing that you
need to do will come along and you will
see it. Okay. It is as simple as that.
Let it be that
simple. All right. Okay. Thank you very
much. Well, thank you very much. It will
work. Okay.
Guaranteed. Sharing.
Hi, I I've had something I've been
dwelling on for about since 1970.
Dwelling. All right. Uh, I first got
into Scientology and I was running a
process. Think one moment. One moment.
Can you all hear?
Okay. When I first got into Scientology,
I was running a process called think
about matter, think about energy, think
about space, think about time. Yes. Yes.
Yes. Doing the same thing four times
over. All right. Yeah. Again, again,
just round and round.
Anyway, at that time I had uh I think it
was the only time I'd ever red tagged,
but I ran into something that I' I'd had
a communication line or an agreement or
something with a group and I broke that
communication line and I always wondered
what this was. I I uh thought I'd find
out someday, but I never did.
The idea of the agreements you run
across when you connect into the
centering of yourself do not always
necessarily re-emerge in the same way in
which you originally ran across them.
The idea is to put into action the
essences, the feelings, the motivations
that crop up within you and in the
actions the agreements you have made
will play themselves through you. you
will channel them into action rather
than sitting around waiting to recapture
the way you originally ran across the
energy. Understand? I see that they seem
to be quite a bit of upset on the other
end of the line for
not really. No. No. Okay. Not
upset. Simply
that the vibration is in
idle, not agitation but
idling to allow you whenever you are
good and ready to let it flow through as
action as
doing rather than the idea once again of
observation of analysis.
Understand? I understand. Thank you. No,
does that serve you? Yes, it does. Well,
thank you very much. Remember that time,
space, matter, and mind are the same
thing. Okay. Thank
Okay. Thank
you. Shooting.
Hello, Bajar. Hello. How are you?
Perfect. And you? Perfect. Oh, thank
you. What? I wanted to explain to you.
All right. All right. One moment. One
moment.
for those in your terms that are
new. Perfect means that at any given
moment whatever you are is a perfect
definition of the thing you are at that
moment. Saying that one is perfect does
not mean you will not grow. Does not
mean you will not expand. Does not mean
you will not change. In that sense it is
not meant in what you call an
egotistical manner. But simply to us,
you are all perfect at being whatever
you are being at this given moment. When
you change, you will simply be perfect
in a different
way. Continue. Anyway, I um definitely
feel a very strong connection with
convergence. My whole life everything is
converging. I feel a lot of the time a
great portion of my life I spend I don't
even feel I'm really me. It's like I'm
something is looking through me and I'm
in this energy.
Yes, as we have said, it is you. You are
looking through you in that sense
because the persona is an artificial
construct of your consciousness. Well,
thank you. Yeah, my higher self or
whatever. That's what I feel like. All
right. And it is what you are in
essence. Yes. Uh thanks. I uh basically
with my music and stuff like it's all
converging and when you start talking
about vibration and stuff, I started
realizing ah that's that's why I feel so
connected with all that. Yes. Everything
is vibration. Yes. And so I've
definitely gotten more connected with
that and everything is just rapidly
speeding. Oh, thank you very much. Thank
you very much. My question is
is am I at this time you had expressed
something last week. Am I at this time
uh say in the future my future self
existing on a higher level of say a
fourth density level or a physical
density level from say your system or
the plleadian system or you have as all
of you do connections into every other
dimension that exists whichever ones
begin to stand out are the ones that are
representative of whatever vibrational
direction you are creating at any given
moment. M you do not need to label it so
specifically. That is why we now suggest
that any connection you feel that you
would colloally refer to as coming from
somewhere other than your earth simply
be relegated into the overall
association rather than saying oh is it
from here or is it from there for that
is limiting. Right? Understand? And it
will always fluctuate
since you have connections to
everywhere. Whatever you are looking at,
whatever you are working on at any given
moment will determine which of those
connections you perceive most strongly
at that time. Great. Well, thank you
very much. Well, thank you very much for
playing your part. Okay,
sharing. Hello, Bashar
Strawberry. I've been having a lot of
fun channeling the last vestigages of my
lower self. All right.
Anyway, I was wondering if you were
planning to converge with anything this
weekend yourself.
Again, as we have stated, there will be,
if you wish to put it in colloquial
terms, a beam of energy from the
association through a dimensional gate
that can be simply defined by the three
points that you call your shasta, your
Fuji, your Hawaii. I will be a part of
that frequency, a part of that
vibration, sending unconditional love to
you all so that you can use that light,
that energy
to synchronize your own with it so that
you can create whatever you wish to
create. I will be involved in that way.
Lovely. Thank you. Uh good. Thank you.
One last little thing. Could you give us
um a bit of a concise
um concept of your point of view on
spirit of play? Spirit of play. Yeah. It
is the natural way of life. You are a
spirit at
play. That is what you are doing where
you are
playing. You are a spirit. Remember that
your physical world, your physical body
is your spirit in physical terms. That's
all. So spirit of play in that sense is
synchronization harmonization with the
harmonization with the
fundamental beam or frequency of
creation itself. For if you wish to put it that
itself. For if you wish to put it that
way, the infinite creator or God as you
call it is literally the spirit at
play. Does that assist you? Yes. But
there is when you recogn I think it's
when you recognize the attitude when you
recognize this connection that you feel.
Yes. To play. Yes. You let that flow
through you, you are in synchronous
harmony with the prime frequency of
creation. It is called unconditional
love and ecstasy. That is the spirit of
play. Ecstasy.
Lovely. Thank you. I'll see you at the
conversion. We're already there.
I'll see you there anyway. Oh, all
right. Shutting.
Shutting.
Hi, Bishar. Hi. Um, I've had uh
headaches from tension for about the
last four months. All right. Are you
tired of it?
Yeah, I'm tired of it. All right. Are
you sure? I'm very sure. All right.
Don't want to hang on to them any
longer? No. Oh, all right. When will you
let them go?
Simple as that.
I can allow it to be more complex if you
want it to be. No, no, no.
Why are you tense?
Uh, financial matters.
Is that supposed to be a reason?
That's what it started with. Oh, all
right. What is it now?
I really don't know. No. All right. Are
you exploring ideas of abundance? Yes.
Do you remember the idea, not that ours
is any better than yours, of our
definition of abundance? No, I don't.
All right. Our definition is as follows.
Abundance.
Stop. The ability to do what you need to
do when you need to do it. Period.
That's it. That's all abundance is.
There are an infinite number of ways to
allow abundance into your life. They do
not all have to manifest in just the one
way or the few ways your society tells
you are the only ways that are
representative of abundance. Things can
simply be given to you. Things can be
exchanged with you. You don't always
have to have the idea of what you call
money, though that is just as valid as
any other way. Allow your abundance to
come along the path of least resistance
by doing what excites you the most and
allowing yourself to be in the flow of
universal support because you are
infinitely abundant. Infinitely
abundant. The only time you do not allow
yourself to experience your infinite
abundance is when you narrow down your
infinite abundance to one or two ways in
which you will allow your abundance to
come to you. One or two ways in which
you will recognize abundance and refuse
to recognize it any other way. If I
don't have the money, I'm not
abundant. Infinite abundance can be
manifested in any number of ways. Do
what excites you the most and it will
manifest along the path of least
resistance just like
electricity. It follows similar
rules. Are you following along so far?
Totally. Are you doing what excites you
the most? Yes. Are you sure? Pretty
sure. Pretty sure.
Is there anything else you could be
doing that you are not doing about the
idea that excites you the most? Yeah,
there are other things. Are you going to
do them? Yeah. Why? Why? Yes. Why? No,
it's funny. Just when you were speaking,
it became clear to me that the times
that the headaches actually led up. Yes.
There were there was a flow of things
into my life. Yes. That was that were
not coming as money. Yes. That's still
abundant. Yeah. No, I see that clearly
now. All right.
It doesn't have to be as often as many
of you are taught to think it has to
be. So let it come in whatever form it
will and then you will be able to simply
continue to do what you need to do when
you need to do it and you will be
infinitely abundant. Understand? Yeah, I do. And
abundant. Understand? Yeah, I do. And
then when you let go of that
tension, there will no be headache
within you.
Understand? For all pain is simply
resistance to your natural self.
Remember remember once again this whole
idea is about learning to be
natural not
normal. It is only the idea of
assumptions of normality that create the
tension. I have to be normal. Have to do
it this way. Everyone says so. If I'm
not doing it this way, I'm not abundant.
Everyone says so. I have to be
normal. That is
tiring. That will give you a head
ache and maybe some aches in some
polarized portions of your anatomy as
well. So, let it
go. Let yourself
flow. And you will not bottle the energy
up. It will not have to hammer to get out of
It will not have to hammer to get out of
you. Let it radiate from you like a
golden glow.
Understand? I really do. Like a halo.
Thank you. Thank you very much. You are
welcome. Pleasant
dream shedding.
Good evening. And to you. Good day. Good
day. Oh, we're always talking about
doing what excites us the most at the
moment. Are we now? Yes. Yes. And we
talked about u with integrity. With
integrity. So we get a definition for
integrity. All right. Definition for
integrity. That which unifies, which
moves as a whole rather than that which
segregates, separates, that which
understands the control is from within.
That which does not see the idea as
control as an external idea and
therefore leads to domination.
Understand? In other words, to put it
very simply, everyone is as powerful as
he or she needs to be to create whatever
they desire in life without having to
hurt anyone else or themselves in order
to create it. That's one by integrity.
It is called trust. Infinite trust that
whatever you can conceive of, you have
the ability to attract into your life in
an effortless and abundant way without
having to force your ideas on anyone
else in order to get it to work. You are
self-sufficient. That's what it means by integrity,
That's what it means by integrity,
integral,
integrated. Understand?
Could you give us an example maybe of
uh what would be out integrity? And you
know anyone who forces the idea of
themselves, their point of view, their
reality on someone else as you say
against their preference is acting out
of
integrity. Understand? Okay. So it
should flow. But what happens if it
doesn't seem to flow naturally? It
doesn't seem to move easily. Then that
is your assumption that it is not moving
as it needs to. The idea can be an
invalidation and a lack of integrity.
The perspective that it is not flowing
as it should in a sense is a judgment.
If you allow yourself to truly trust
that what is in your life is what needs
to be there and are not afraid to face
whatever that moment brings you, then
you will not assume that what is in your
life has no business being there.
Everything is a part of your life. There
are no interruptions in it. Functioning
outside of integrity creates the
illusion that your life can be
interrupted by things that have no
business being there when in fact it
can't. Understand? Yes. So if you see
something that is in your terms not
flowing as you think it
should, then allow yourself to retract
your expectations. Find out why you have
the beginning expectations you did.
Allow yourself to discover what beliefs
exist within you and allow yourself to
explore those beliefs. redefine them
because whatever situation came to you
is giving you an opportunity to
discover how much different you might be
than the reality you say you prefer to
create. For if you are not a being that
is in synchronous harmony with the
reality you say you prefer, you will not
get that reality.
So when circumstances occur that in your
estimation do not seem to match the
picture of the integrity you had, it is
showing you on some level that there may
be another facet of yourself you still
have not yet looked at and defined to
allow it to blend and harmonize within
the overall idea. And that's an
opportunity to allow the thing you
prefer to occur that much more quickly.
But when something occurs and you don't
believe it's a part of the process and
you deny it and run from it, then in
that sense you allow it to take that
much longer because you're not willing
to face the thing you need to face to
integrate that within you to move on to
the next step. The things that come as
they come are a part of the path. So if
you embrace them as your creation,
acknowledge them as what you need to
look at at that moment to be a part of
the path you prefer to be and not run
from them as if they are not a part of
that path, you will be acting within
integrity. Understand? Yes. Does that
assist you? Yes, it does. Are you sure?
I'm pretty sure anyway. All
right. Thank you very much.
It is in that sense willingness to
discover all that you can about what you
have created yourself to be in absolute
trust that it can all be applied to you
in a positive way if you choose to
believe that and your willingness to
discover these things and interact in
that way is a sign of
integrity. Thank you. Thank you.
Bye-bye. Shing.
Evening, Bashar. And to you, good day.
Yes. I have a burden on my shoulders. I
need release. All right. It's gone.
Thank you. Um, go like this. Brush it
off. All right. Um, three years ago. Oh,
one moment. One moment. Can you all
hear? Speak up. Speak up. Will you do me
a favor before you begin? Yes. Are you
standing up very straight? Now I am. All
right. Take three deep breaths.
Give yourself three pats on the top of
your chest and say, "Ah, life." A life.
Now do it and mean it. Ah, life. All
right. Okay.
[Laughter] Um, are you still standing up straight?
Um, are you still standing up straight?
Yes. All right. Do you feel a little
less of a burden on your shoulders when
you stand up straight? Yes. All right.
Continue. Yes. Three years ago, I left a
very difficult marriage and difficult
situation. Oh, all right. If you say so.
Okay. Well, it was and it took me a
while to leave. A long time to leave
that and all right. Re not realizing I
was under the control of my husband and
mother. All right. And when I left two
week two weeks later, I met my soulmate
and life became wonderful and exciting
everything I wanted except except what?
My family. Except for your family. Yes,
my immediate family. Um they all have a
hatred for my husband, my filmmate.
Okay. And uh my um mother has u just
hated him since the day I met him. Why?
I don't know. Have you asked? Well, yes,
I do know. All right, then.
She thinks he's too old, doesn't have
enough money, blah blah blah blah blah
blah blah blah blah blah. All right.
Um
planet has more interesting reasons than
I've ever encountered. Yeah.
My son
re My son refuses to meet him. Why?
Decided he hates him. Why? He won't say.
Except that um if everybody else doesn't
like him, why should he? Oh, all right.
Which would be my ex-husband and mother.
Oh, all right. My daughter was with us
and caused trouble. She had to leave.
And um I've had to withdraw from the
family about about a week and a half
ago. All right. And I'd like help with
this. In what sense? Um,
okay. Well, I don't know whether I
should just completely withdraw or try
I've tried for three years to make peace
and it hasn't worked. All right. Are you
happy? Yes, I'm happy. All right. Uh,
how do I release my guilt then? Guilt?
Mhm. Why do you have guilt? I don't
know. I feel Are you responsible for
them? No. Well, then so it's all right
then. You're saying to release them?
Well, in a sense, yes, they are
releasing themselves in a way. Yes.
No matter what you are going through, no
matter what reason you have attracted
whoever you have attracted, if that is
what you feel represents the ideas you
need to experience in your life at this
time, then there may be created polarity
expressions, vibrational polarities with
other individuals and you will simply go
on your separate ways. If you do not
care in that sense to maintain the
understanding that whatever anyone goes
through I'm speaking from their point of
view is what they need to go through at
that moment. Now the idea in that sense
is you can let them go and that
paradoxically is the quickest way to get
them back.
I understand because then if you simply
make a statement that you know, you
believe, you trust that you are doing
what you need to be doing, you will
radiate as an example for them to
understand that you are
happy. Whether or not that changes in
terms of the situation you have now
doesn't make a difference because if it
does change, it will only change into
another form, another way, another
method of the happiness you are now
willing to create. Understand? Yes. So
there are no I told you so. There are no
regrets. There are no guilts. The only
reason you are feeling guilt or creating
guilt in your reality is because you are
attempting to be responsible for what
they are choosing to feel about you.
Do you wish to live your life according
to what other people think you should
do? No. Do you believe you are acting
with an integrity? Yes.
End of conversation. Okay, I understand.
Thank you. Love them. Love them
unconditionally unconditionally for that is the only way
unconditionally for that is the only way
to give them the opportunity to love you
just as unconditionally in return. Okay.
If you are not willing to love
them, then you do not provide for them a
gateway through which their love can
manifest if they decide to share that
with you. Remember that once again,
guilt is the true opposite of love, not
hate. Guilt. Understand? Yes. So, love
them unconditionally and remember also
that by the strictest
definition, anyone you relate to at any given moment
anyone you relate to at any given moment
is your
soulmate. Anyone understand?
Anyone understand?
We know what you mean by the definition
you have given to this new individual.
Mhm. When you choose to be blended and
harmonized within yourself and balanced,
you will generally attract the
individual you have made an agreement
with in life to reflect that
harmonization and balance back to you.
But by the strictest definition, anyone
you're in a relationship with at that
moment is your soulmate. Because by
being in that relationship, you are
getting out of that relationship the
things you need to at that moment. Yes.
Understand? Yes. But we know what you
mean. Thank you. Okay. You will always be
Thank you. Okay. You will always be
connected to that family in that sense.
No matter what physiological
transformations take place.
Yes. Being who you know you are will
create the best opportunity for all the
others involved in the relationship to
allow themselves to transform in
positive ways as well. But you cannot
take responsibility for them. You can
only be responsible to them by being as
fully as you can who you know you are
with love and integrity. Plain and
simple. Thank you. Thank you. I'm
unburdened. Oh, thank
you. Simply carry your head high, stand
straight, and it will do wonders for
your guilt.
Thank you. Sharing. Hello, Bashar.
Hello. Um, I had a question about my
challenge. Speak up. speak up. Okay. Um
uh I've had a number of dreams uh where
I'm learning about channeling and I am
actually channeling in them. And
um um I was wondering are those
agreements that were made earlier or in
a sense but does it really matter? No.
Now is now. Remember that all memory and
all past is created in the present
anyway. Understand? Yes, I do. There is a very
Understand? Yes, I do. There is a very
strong clue in that for your channeling.
Say that again. There is a very strong
clue in that for your channeling.
Thank you.
All memory and all past is created in
the present. When you remember, you are
present. When you remember, you are
creating that memory
now. Right now. There's nowhere else to
create it. It isn't in the
it. It isn't in the
past. It is of the idea you call the
past, but it is created now.
Yes. Okay. Well, that brings up one
other point. Yes. In one of the dreams,
um, I had I was channeling, but the
voice was sounded so far away. Yes. that
um and I was getting distracted by the
people and I um decided to go ask either
you or Daryl a question. So I went up to
this mountain and I asked Daryl um how
come the voice sounded so far away? And
um I've asked this before. I said it was
just a matter of changing my viewpoint.
But what Daryl said in my dream was that
uh um it was because it was my in my
future. And then he asked me what the
date was. Yes.
And um I don't know how to bring that
from into now.
I have already given you your clue.
Okay. Now is the only time in which you
exist. Where else could it be?
True. Where else could it be? Well, when
what's the idea of a future self?
It is a convenient linguistic symbol in
your old way of
talking. When you create the notion of a
past and a future, it is a convenient
way of describing a concept to you to
allow you to understand the basic
principle. And then we can change the
symbols that are used, the language that
is used to allow you to truly understand
the real mechanics of what is going on.
Okay? So, as soon as you, as you say,
get a handle on the fact that there
really isn't any future and there really
isn't any
past, you will have your answer.
Okay? Experiment and explore with that
in your meditations. Bring the future
into the present where it belongs.
All right. All right. Thank you. Thank
you. Enjoy. I will.
Remember the view from your own mountain
is just as beautiful.
Sharing. Hello Bashar. Hello. Last time I asked
Hello Bashar. Hello. Last time I asked
you a question, I described a crash that
I had on my motorcycle. Yeah. and that
it was a symbol for what was going on in
my life. Yeah. Uh since then, what's
gone on in my life
is perhaps leading towards a crash and
I've realized that that crash was a
belief system based on a belief system
that I no longer wish to um I no longer
prefer to have. All right. Are you
afraid a crash might be coming up?
Yeah. And I see that that can I can
attract myself to that. All right. But
why are you giving the old meaning just
because the symbols may appear the same?
Why not give them a new meaning and
understand that they do not have to
represent the idea of a crash except
perhaps in a positive manner crashing
through a
barrier? Can you give the symbols you
are apparently seeing another meaning
other than the old meaning that seems to
indicate a crash in a negative sense?
Can you use your imagination and
reassign a new value to the external
symbols? Yeah. Yeah. I can I I can begin to see
Yeah. Yeah. I can I I can begin to see
them differently. All right. I can I
can begin to see the changes in myself
of becoming the person I've imagined and
prefer myself to be. All right. May I
ask you a question? Sure. Oh, thank you
very much. You're welcome.
In your estimation, as we have discussed
with many of you before, in your
threshold of
believability, how long will it take you
to become the person you prefer to be?
I know it can be instantaneous. All
right, I know you know that.
But do not fear. We are talking about a
practical tool for you which when you
acknowledge what it is, can allow it to
shorten. But only when you acknowledge
what it is right now. Well, I just
turned 40. Yes. It's not going to take
another 40 years.
Not very likely.
Maybe. So, you know beyond a shadow of a
doubt. Yes. That you will be who you
prefer to be. Not that you will not
change. Not that you will not grow, but
that you will be who you prefer to be
definitely within 40 years. Yes. 40
days. 40 days. Do you absolutely believe
it? Yes. Now, I'll tell you something. I
perceive you do have the energy to do
that. So, it is up to you. If you really
So, it is up to you. If you really
believe it, you can do it. I believe it.
All right. 30 days.
Or do you want to stick to 40? I'll
stick to 40.
All right.
10 days will not matter that much. No,
no, that's what I figure. All right,
right,
then. Create for
yourself the broad expanse of one of
your deserts and wander 40 days and 40
deserts and wander 40 days and 40
nights. and allow yourself to recognize
that in the broad expanse of what you
call the desert, there isn't anything to
crash into. It is limitless. A limitless
into. It is limitless. A limitless
horizon for you. Understand? Mhm. Yes, I
do. And when you travel as far in your
meditation, as fast in your meditation
as you can within that desert, when you
finally stop when 40 days are up, you
will be exactly where you began.
But you will not be the same you. All
right. Understand? Yes, I do. Well,
thank you very very
very much. Thank you very much. Has this
been of assistance to you? Yes, it has.
I was uh number 13 on this list and I
think all right now number 10 already.
You are standing in the gate of
yourself. Yes. On the threshold of your
own present.
Find you. Thank you,
Tokashimi. Hi, Basher. I That is 13 in our ancient
Hi, Basher. I That is 13 in our ancient
language. Oh, I wasn't on the list, but
I happen to be in a neighborhood, so I
thought I'd come over and say hello.
Hello. Hi. Um, things have been kind of
quiet lately. Uh, seems my antenna got
bent or moved around and I don't have
any channels anymore. It's been like
that for the last few weeks. But uh
remember that the idea of when things
seem to be getting
quiet can represent simply that you are
acclimating to a new energy and not
measuring things by a difference but by
a similarity. Now remember that most of
you are used to thinking that things are
happening when you see differences
around you. Now that you are acclimating
to the energy, it may seem as if things
are going away, fading out, when in fact
all that's happening is that you are
getting used to the level that you have
for so long thought to be so far away
from you. Understand? I hear what you're
saying. Yes, it sounds good. It is an
opportunity to understand that from that
apparent standing still position, you
can now go as far and fast in any
direction that you choose to. As soon as
you think of it, conceive of it, if it
contains a spark of excitement, you will
start rapidly accelerating in that
direction. You are now fluid, able to
slide in any direction at any moment.
That quiescence is deceiving. Remember
that standing still, the feeling of
standing still is exactly the same as
being everywhere at once, going
infinitely fast.
Remember? Yes. And I'm glad you said
what you said because I want to see what
you're going to say to this. All right.
Now, it's a case of probably other
people have mentioned it. It's like I
feel like I'm stuck on his island and
I'm sure anxious to get off of it. All
right. And what would you say to that?
You are not
stuck. That's all you're going to say.
Why do you picture the idea once again
from a negative point of view? We have
just given you the positive analogy of
what it feels like to be isolated in one
spot. You are feeling that way because
what you are perceiving is that you're
actually connected to everything
everywhere. So the feeling you have of
being on an island and being stuck is
simply the negative point of view of the
same idea that you are holographic. That
is every point within the holographic
matrix contains the whole. So you might
as well be where you are.
I'm disappointed. Now pay
attention. Any island you could be on
will be the same in the sense that you
can do anything from that point you wish
to do. You are only perceiving it as an
island through your choice of approach
through your choice of perspective. You
are feeling it in an isolated way
because you are focusing on the
sensation of standing still rather than
the sensation of the infinite speed that
allows you to understand you are
actually everywhere at once. When you're
everywhere at once, you can create the
illusion that you're only confined to
one small local. Are you understanding
any? I understand, but you blew my whole
damn game because you were supposed to
tell me if I could see the island, I'm
not on it. And you supposed to tell you
that because you already know that. Aha.
But see, that's what I was going to come
back and say. I happen to be on a tall
mountain, a high mountain. Well,
actually, it's a big volcano and I could
see the whole island, but I'm still on
it. But remember, these interactions
follow the rules of following the path
of least resistance. And if you already
know the information, I do not need to
provide it for you, nor will I have
access to it. That's true. I just felt
like coming up and saying hello and
playing a little bit. Thank you very
much. Now, thank you also for functioning as a
Now, thank you also for functioning as a
reflection for many individuals who have
been going through similar things.
Allowing them to understand the
principle that if you can see the habit,
you are no longer subject to the habit.
and allowing you to remind them that if
you can see the habit and are no longer
subject to the habit, then to use the
habit is no longer a habit. It is an
excuse. I thank the both of us. I thank the both
I thank the both of us. I thank the both
of us. That is the one and the same
event. Thank you for your polarity play
and thank you for being here and letting
me play it. Thank you. Okay. Always
willing to play. Good.
Charing. Hello Bashar. Hello. How are you?
Hello Bashar. Hello. How are you?
Perfect. And great. Uh uh my question
pertains to us being on onion and being
peeled and also teary. All right. I have
this problem to
where I guess it's not a problem just a
whatever situation that happens that
comes up. I talk to people uh higher
authorities that I work with and my eyes
tear. Yeah. I don't understand this
phenomena. Could you help me with that
and let me understand what it is that
makes my eyes tear like this?
May I ask you a question? Sure. Thank
you. If you were in their
If you were in their
position, how would you
feel? What would that be like?
to do what they do. Those people of
higher authority authority um I'd
probably be a little less uh vulnerable
or whatever. Maybe that's what I feel. A
little less vulnerable. Well, I feel I
it's hard to express the uh feel that I
get when I talk to an individual on a on
a onetoone basis and he gets tearyeyed.
Do you understand that? That is
releasing, that is centering, and it can
be equalizing. Do you understand that?
Yes. Uhhuh. To cry in that sense is to
center from the negative. To laugh is to
center from the positive. Okay. But
sometimes it gets a little embarrassing
when you're sitting there talking to
people. Oh, that's just a judgment. Oh,
on my part. Yes. Oh, I see. I see. I
didn't realize it was that easy. Well,
perhaps you can simply say, "I'm just so
happy to see you.
That's a good way to put it. Yes. No,
but it's hard to put it that way. Why? I
don't know. I don't understand why it
comes out that way. Repeat after me.
Uh-oh. Here we go. Yes. I'm so happy to
see you. I'm so happy to see you. Now,
do you understand that you're saying
that to yourself?
Yes. Yes. And do you recognize that you
are not in a negative way vulnerable?
And in a sense, they are tears of joy at
recognizing that your life will always
contain what you call the guidelines to
allow you to know you are always firmly
in control. You are simply using those
individuals as reflective mirrors for
your own self-empowerment to allow you
to know you will always have the
guidelines you need. Understand? Oh,
yeah. Great. And bit by bit you release
and get closer and closer to the center
of who you are using those authority
figures to represent your own higher
understanding of self. I see.
Understand? Oh yeah. Yeah. Now I do. So
you are in that sense peeling away the
layers and shedding a tear. Boohoo as
you say. Really? Really? But that is
only the old understanding that you are
losing something.
something.
innocence. You sometimes believe that
what you are
losing quote unquote is your innocence,
but in fact what you are doing is
gaining it.
Understand? Oh yeah. Yeah. I do. Now let
yourself feel as much as you wish to
feel and see the irony in the
circumstances as well. For when you see
irony and paradox, you are coming from
the center. use it as a tool and you may
all of a sudden find which I don't know
you may choose to think is just as
embarrassing that you might all of a
sudden laugh. I see. I'm sure the
authority figure wouldn't appreciate
that. But why are you so sure?
Well, I guess I shouldn't be sure,
should I? I guess not. You don't have to
be. That's true.
If you are willing to see them as a
reflection of you and you as a
reflection of them, then why not simply
attract a so-called authority figure who
will appreciate it? That's true. Who
will appreciate you, right? In that
sense, that's all you are attempting to
do is learn to appreciate
yourself. And you are worth it. You
deserve to be appreciated for the
creation that you are. Great. That's
what I thought, too. All right, I'll
agree with you 100%. Thank you. Thank
you. Thank you very much. Thank you,
Bashar. Ching.
Hello, Bashar. Hello. I have a question.
Oh, during a meditation some months ago,
I felt the presence of my spirit guide.
All right. And did you feel touched?
Yes. All right. And she had two others
with her.
uh guests. Yes. All right. She gave me
two names. Two vibrations. All right.
And I'd like to know if you could tell
me something about them. Maybe, maybe
not. Uh the names sounded like Esoddora and
Uh the names sounded like Esoddora and
Moranta.
Do you have a vibration for what you
recognize as your particular guide? Yes.
Share. Share. Um, her name is Eloise.
In our vibration, our
translation would be closer to what you
would call literally in your name
culture, Isadore
and Miranda. The concepts as we are
Miranda. The concepts as we are
perceiving of Isador and
Miranda represent the free spirit and
the ruling queen.
aspects of your own consciousness,
aspects of your own experience in other
lives, and connections to other levels
of consciousness that you have had in
the past that you are now almost ready
to recognize in full consciousness.
Again, associations with other levels of
dimensional consciousness and also
associations with other levels of your
own consciousness expressed by the
polarities of Isidor and
Miranda. the idea of the free spirit and
the ruling
queen. They are about to share
identities within
you within the
chalice of your feminine
self within your life's blood for they
are representative of the idea of the
color crimson of blood in that way as
you call it.
One
moment. Some of these aspects go back to
what you would call your ancient
China. Some of them involve what you
would call expression and expressionism
on many a stage of what you would call a
theater. Much of it involves the idea of
acting and
action. One moment.
Are you to some degree familiar with a
tool upon your planet which you refer to
as the tarot deck?
Yes. You
can as a tool, as a focusing device, as
an
assistance, scan through what you would
call the 22 major cards of the deck and
perceive which to you represents Isidor
and Miranda. Utilize them as symbols of
Miranda. Utilize them as symbols of
focus to blend, harmonize, and balance
those energies within you. for they will
create a third
identity. And when you begin to relate
to
that, you will begin to rekindle and
find some of the natural power
connections you have with the earth
itself and allow a third
representational harmonic to be born
within you. At this point, since you are
in mid-process, this is all we are
allowed to
say. Will that serve you? Absolutely.
Thank you very much. Thank you very
much. Shutting
love and greetings for sure. Hello.
Uh first I'd like to share with the
people here and you this latest book
from Star Trek uh Strangers from the
Sky. And the thing that's fascinating
about it written in 1987. It is talking
about changing the past and the future
in the now through uh past lives and in
other words changing them in their
dreams now. Which I thought was kind of
nice. All right. Anyway, uh kind of
nice. Well, delightful and coincidental,
right? If you want to use the word. No,
thank you.
What I'd like to ask you about, I have a
friend here with me, a crystal, nice um
that has been a delight, delightful
friend to me. But um I had it in my hand
and had my hand in a psychic psychic's
hand and the psychic told me it was sent
to me and had a lot of information in it
for me. But it was sent by a friend in a
sense. Yes, it is designed as an
information crystal. More often than
not, crystals, again, this is a symbolic
tool. But crystals that contain either a
recess or a small upraised portion on
one of the facets will be those designed
to contain and carry encoded information
of a certain nature. Uhhuh. Well, this
has one on two different faces, right?
Anyway, she said that it was sent to me
by a life form that uh on earth we
wouldn't recognize as a life form, but
that I'm connected with for lack of a
better way to describe it in the now in
a different point of view or elsewhere
or else when was dying and wanted it was
uh came to this planet was shot down by
the American government not literally.
Okay. In any case, it wanted me to put
blue fluorite in water inside my pyramid
and send it to it. And I'm wondering if
it helped because I've been doing it.
And do I transformed? Not death as you
understand it at all. These are
colloquial translations.
Okay. Do I need to continue with the
blue fluorite in the pyramid?
If you do, it will be for other reasons,
not for the original reason. Do you have
to continue? Uh, one moment. One moment.
If you were to remove that blue
fluorite, what would you do with it now?
Well, I I don't keep it in there
constantly because I use the pyramid for
other things, but I use it on my body
with my energy body and this crystal and
other uh fluoride of different colors.
If you were to take it somewhere and
plant it in the ground, where would you
take it?
I guess since I'm going to Jolie's
mountaintop for the convergence, maybe
there. Thank you. Okay, end of
conversation. Thank you. Sharing.
you. Sharing.
Hello, Bashar. Hello. Um, speak up.
I'm a little nervous. This is the first
time I've been here. All
right, speak up nervously. All right, I
will. What I have to ask you about is um I
What I have to ask you about is um I
recently went to Peru. All right. And I
took some photos there and there's a
little bit background for this. I'm
going to be doing uh a short workshop. I
usually teach crystal healing and
rebirththing and touch for health and
things like that. But I've been asked to
do something on UFOs. And I asked the
people, "Why would you ask me to do
anything on UFOs?" Why not? And well,
that's kind of what they said. They went
into meditation were told to ask me. So,
I've been talking with friends and
looking around and I've had a few
experiences that I didn't think enough
to fill the workshop. However, I do have
some ways of working with crystals that
I think might be helpful to people to
tune in. But anyway, so when they had
asked me then the thought was this was
before I went to Peru that maybe somehow
in the summer and the things that I did
that I might have some kind of greater
understanding which I'm getting or
contact. Well anyway I didn't see
anything in Peru but I did have a
marvelous time and wonderful other
experiences. But when I developed the
photos, there's a photo that was taken
at Machu Picchu that has an orange disc
on it and uh I don't know what the
origin of that is or if it in fact has
anything to do with extraterrestrials or
if to some degree there is a
consciousness connection and here is how
it can play itself out. In your
utilization of your knowledge of
crystals, recognize that they represent
to some degree some of the technology
that you will be using in what you call
your future. Allow yourself to develop
your innate intuitive understanding of
how crystallin forms in certain
relationship physically to each other
will create different energy flows,
different gates, different openings
within what you call the space-time
matrix. That is your first key. Yeah,
that it has to do with the idea of
creating the vibrational harmonics, the
resonances necessary to quote unquote
tunnel through from one dimension to
another. Use your emotionality, use your
heart. That's what the orange
represents. It is a projection of
consciousness, a reminder for you of
things that are familiar to you in what
you call the past. Arrange the crystals
as you used to in those mountain top
layers and allow yourself to remember
that you are actually turning
keys. Sense the relationship physically
that those crystals need to be to each
other. You will open doors and allow
others to feel the harmonic resonances
within them. That is your first key to
restructuring and remembering the
placement and relationships of those
devices. The next step will come
later. Understand? Uh yes, I'm not quite
clear. The the orange disc that showed
up on the slide that I took projection
of consciousness in the vibration that
represents emotionality. Understand? Not totally.
emotionality. Understand? Not totally.
All right. You have what you call a
mental field. Yes. Yes. The intersection
of another consciousness within that
mental field creates the idea, the
cross-section that you are referring to
as that disc. Its vibrational color
represents the level of energy that you
are using the frequency the emotional
band orange. Yes. So using your emotion,
no banan, your instinct, your
intuition, allow that energy to flow
through you as you arrange the crystals
and begin to see the relationships of
how the energy amplifies and reflects
and reinforces each other to create
different ideas that eventually in your
society will turn into actual devices
that will have no moving parts.
constructed simply out of very precisely
machined different types of crystallin
material. Understand? Yes. I think you
are beginning in a sense to build the
engines in a certain way that will
translate the idea of local of time and
space into an idea back within you and
allow you to transport yourself where
and when you wish to go.
Great. All right. So then then the disc
on there is not a rep not a
representation of any extraterrestrial
in a sense. Yes. But not as you
typically think of it. But not as
typically. It's it's a connection of of
one energy with mine. Yes. All right. Of
a beam in a sense with yours. And you
are seeing the cross-section of a beam
which you call a disc. All right.
Understand? Yes. Thank you very much.
Think holographically when you look at
the crystals and see the planes within
them. See the dimensions within them.
All right. All right. You have to some
degree a mathematical penantrant on an
instinctive geometric level. Use it.
Thank you. I will. All right. Thank you
very much. And thank you. This timing
you may all take a short break. We will
resume contact in approximately 10 to 15
of your minutes.
How's it going?
Please have a break. Remember
it.
Our way will fly continue. Dreamer. Dreamer. Ice.
Oh, okay. Um, I was here one time
before. This is my second time. It's
been a couple months since I've been
here. And before uh you mentioned that u I
And before uh you mentioned that u I
have the energy of a pilot.
You recall that
we
[Music] communicate by
communicate by
sh moment you wait nigator.
wait nigator.
Y he
say you are you be
navigator pilot you call it y continue y continue
you
wish speak b direct
I don't see that makes that much
difference see I was curious if Um you could give
see I was curious if Um you could give
me a little more information on that. Uh
something that might assist me in the
things that I'm doing now.
Crystal plane you na guy think see image crystal
plane you na guy think see image crystal
latis work crystal
matrices matrix see n all harmonics all
vibration pilot navigator aware
within harmonic variation ation of
location. Time and space all is
vibration. Pilot sense this. Pilot know
this. Pilot feel space. Pilot feel time.
Navigate by knowing. Feeling open.
Moving. Understand
very much so. I really do. Move in fear.
All travel in spice. All travel in time
is travel within feeling of center of
being self. Understand?
Yes, I do. I do very much. Ease help to
you very much. So ease allow you to
play beginning to
Yes. Yes. Absolutely.
Thank you for
play. We come to this time through now
for to
express reminder. You being different on other
reminder. You being different on other
side of harmonic days. You be not same
people. You come, you play, you be
within. We play, we be together, you
share. In mind, in dream. Harmonic days,
harmonic nights. You sleep, we dream.
You awake, we play. We be where you be.
All points. Jump free in water. Play us.
You I I think I got that.
I I think I got that.
All for all you come play. We be around
you in water. Dreamers dreamers. We be
together. You us together. Dreamers be
now. You think we all are? Yes. Sharing.
to let you know this is an dreamer who
is a dolphin who is off the coast of New
Zealand. I say I say dreamer B thank you
thank you Dreamer B you call
dolphin water brother water sister you
come play New
Zealand be home many in Japan many in
your Malibu many in your
Malibu many in your
Hawaii dreamers be dreamers Play you
play sharing. Hi dreamer. Hi dreamer.
Hi.
In in our
newspapers recently there have been two
articles about bottom nose dolphins dying. I
about bottom nose dolphins dying. I
think uh several of them have died off
the coast of Chesapeake Bay or
something. Confusion be
Confusion be
electromagnetic wave
fluctuation. Alter course of sensitivity
within navigation navigation
follow
electromagnetic see land not sea to
close be the idea we share intimacy with
you on land as well as within sea. We
not need this idea. But changes in
electromagnetic mentality you share. We
share bring us close together in
whatever way work fastest sometime at
cost of
life. You understand?
Um I didn't quite get that.
Magnetic lines of energy change and move
on planet
now. Confusion in following lines. Take
to land, not take to sea. We believe
take to sea. But understand reason to
bring us together. Hearts and souls and
mind on land. If you will not come to
see, we come to you.
Thank you very much. We thank you.
Share, you come, you play. Allow
magnetic mentality blend and
homogenize. Then be no confusion for us,
no confusion for
you. We find each other on common sea,
common ground. We remain where
comfortable but play.
What happened to the um the spirits of
those that left the body, the dolphin
body? Many leap back into life. Many
stay in dream to play in your dream
waters with you to share and send love
and heart energy to guide to sing and
whisper in your ear to lure you back to
see to play.
Okay, thank you.
Thank sharing.
Hello. I'd like to ask you a little bit
more about vibrations. Vibration.
Yeah. Uh I feel I'm very curious about
it. that uh vibration all that be all
vibration your
curiosity about everything
you curious about vibration you be
curious about all creation okay
open key
doorways vibration signature
turning of key open tunnel to a
different dimension.
Thank you. Um I think I got confused
about what you said the other day when
uh you talking
about was talking that lady about like I
understood like each and each moment
each object has a specific vibration.
Yes. At that moment each object be time,
space it occupy. Now each object be all
vibration frequency go into making each
object in each space in each time each
object slightly different. Okay. But
then when you don't feel the difference
between time and space and matter and
all these that means it wouldn't be
different in the vibration either. Be at
one everywhere same time when no
difference discerned all be within you.
You be everywhere. Okay. You be all time
space. You be all object
within. Be at one. Same as no difference
felt no difference is okay but it's okay
I understand now fine
now the last thing is is there
any you got like some challen before it
was about spectrum of
vibration is such a thing or is still
like maybe sound spectrum and all
different some different spectrums of
vibration All vibration is all exist all
now forever was is forever now is okay
and that's all it is all transform into
itself in different way forever now.
Okay fine thank you very much sure hello
hello
dreamer I would like to thank all the
dolphin iousness for the dolphin
balls. I uh of all my earthly
possessions, my most prized possessions
are these balls. And uh I took them to
SeaWorld and I put them around in the
petting pool and the the dolphins come
over and sometimes they think they want
to take it. And uh you make music, they
make music desire with you. I was uh
tapping them to the tune of a song
called Higher Love. As a matter of fact,
it's uh beyond exciting. Every time I go
to SeaWorld, I realize that I will not
be happy until I spend a lot of time
with you all. Why you not be happy all
time? Then you spend forever with us.
I just feel really like I'd like to
spend lots more. I am happy. Very happy.
Yes. You be happy wherever. Whenever.
Then you be with us. We be with you.
Wherever. Whenever you be. You're
unhappy. We not find you.
I was just kidding. I just could be
happier. I
happier. You're not happy. Be if you can
be happier.
Oh, all right. Scratch it off.
Scratch
the dolphins at SeaWorld. It seemed like
there was like one or two that would
come over that that were regularly. Um I
was just wondering if there's like some
communication, you know, do they know
the balls in particular or some be
aware, some be limited by experience of
that nature.
Some be different aware of different
specific thing in different way. They
very much you understand like you human
from time to time different
personality different thought different
view not all be at one with same all
dreamers selves
okay I beyond love you if there's such a
thing in all we love you too
[Music] hi dreamer
hi dreamer
Oh. Um, I've been spending a lot of time
in Malibu and uh I've been calling the
dolphins and going out and playing in
the water and nobody's come to greet me.
Can you tell me why you
expect or you play for play? Ah, at
first I did expect and then I found out
that I needed to play for myself. You
play for play. We feel play. We come
play but different timings also exist.
You play for play. You be dolphin in
Malibu. Yes.
I I have to other human come play with
you. Okay. You be
Okay. You be
standing as you say. We be along
shortly. Okay,
Okay,
you fill in. It's okay.
Oh, I will. Thank you very much.
Fine. Share.
Hello, dreamer. Hi.
Last month, I had a very strange uh
experience. Strange?
Yes. In my dream reality. Dream, I
believe it was. And um I was sleeping on
my side on a couch and as I turned over
there was a creature, very tall and
spindly and it bent down towards me and
its face was not frightening but it
surprised me and I got very scared and I
swiped at it and um uh screamed very
loudly and I felt very sorry that I had
done that. No, sorry B.
Do you have some sort of
mirror of mind of ascension of self?
Elongation of time track eye
perspective. You have distortion in
mirror of idea of self presented to you
afraid of selfportions of future
connection. connection extra
connection extra
terrestrial as well but present to you
distortion of future connection idea
bring into home bring into now bring
down to size yourself.
So I just must bring it into perspective
into the now. Yes,
I see. Be that self of towering
configuration is power reflection of you
to yourself from France.
Okay. And I also wanted to thank very
much four dolphins that played with me
in Africa as a child. Thank you very
much. Love unconditionally. You love
play moment.
Understand? Remind. Harmonics is gate.
Swim through. Jump through. Play. Love.
Laugh. Life. We play. We share. Same
dream. We be. You be. Together. One.
Seas and star. Seas and star. Light for
all. Enough around. Light for all.
Enough found. We thank. We share our
love. Good day. Shing.
Shing.
Hello, dear friend. Until you Goodbye,
butterfly here. Yes. Yes. Flitter.
Flitter. Uh, that's what I need. I think
a little flittering. More flinging. All
right. Flap your wings. Stand up
straight. Stretch yourself.
I have always asked you questions.
pertaining more to the mirror mountain
dice. Remember that one yes Ilia Ilia
car and it is accelerating beautifully
and rapidly and I'm delighted on a small
Oh, thank you for your help. Without
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Without
you. Yes.
Yeah. This is on a more personal basis.
Uh I I am not I'm so I'm dear where we
go. Um
I've had a little dispersement lately
and I'm not even quite sure what's
happening. I wanted to mention to you I
remember when I was about five or six
years old I remember having around my
bed at night time they took me in about
five people standing and talking to me
and I remember these long beautiful
conversations which my mother used to
come in and turn the lights on and make
me get out and look under the bed and
look in the closet and there's nobody
here and this is night after night and
finally I couldn't that was the end of
my communication. All right. I have a
feeling lately I I what I'd need maybe a
little help on is there is some
gathering to do of what might be called
interactions that have occurred. Follow
the eyes, sink into your eyes, look
through those eyes and go where you need
to to gather the different portions of
the idea that need to be gathered. It
seemed they helped me with a goal at
that age. Literally literally sort of
set my future out with a great deal of
help and love and aid in a sense. Yes.
But you have defined it yourself simply
reflected it back to you.
Now these I assume are like spirit
guides. Yes and no. That's what I'm
wondering because lately Syazi has been
very strong and I just I mean to me it
was strong and yet I find that people
say she will only communicate through
one person on this planet. No, thank
you. But recognize it simply as a
general idea of the energy for there are
many layers and many different types of
energy inherent within that blending. It
is not just that which you have
personified as that being. There are
many other levels and expansions of that
consciousness that have to do with the
whole society and whole other societies
overlapping intertwining. It is time to pick up your
intertwining. It is time to pick up your
basket and
gather certain things and bring them
back to your home.
Is are there any I I get I don't know.
It's like I tried to make a contact and
it just I don't know what's happening.
How is your health? It's gone through
some problems. All
right. Can you now
picture going to a few different places
other than where you have been to gather
certain ideas into your basket to take
them home?
You mean mentally going to other places
and perhaps even
physically? Five places. How many? Five.
Five places. Physically and mentally.
Yes. No, I hadn't thought of that. a
little more on that
together in we can only give you the
first okay somewhere in the desert
it can be Arizona if you wish
solo trip yes it can be mental but we
perceive you may find a desire to allow
it to actually be physiological and it
can take you through the changes to
align you as might be necessary to bring
back in that basket of gathering the
experiences and perhaps even a symbolic
physiological representation from each
area to take back in that sense home to
the mountain with you to be complete in
that sense in your own mind when you
return. Five
Five
fingers on the hand that
now opens to
reveal more information of who and what
you are. I do not mean to be
mysterious but in this way there are
five connections for you awaiting only
you to gather them into your
basket. Now is the timing to begin and
as you said they can be physiological as
well as number one is the desert. I mean
what five things that I carry back such
as ideas or combination of I assume
physiological items as well as can be
yes and the experiences that you go through
and the experiences that you go through
in gathering them in finding them are be
what will be incorporated into your
entire identity
you will piece yourself back together
meditate relax our suggestion the only one we can
relax our suggestion the only one we can
give you is to start with the desert
You've never led me wrong yet. I will be
in the desert. I am not leading you.
That's right. Oh, that's right.
Sorry. Thank you for suggestion then.
Thank you. And it is simply a reflection
of how we perceive you to be at this
moment. It is the assistance we can be.
Thank you. Thank you. Remember that your
wings will carry you lightly.
That is the best message I think I've
ever received is lighten up. Yes. I
think we could all use that one. Begin.
Begin in the desert. In the desert.
Thank you. Thank you. Shutting.
Hello. I want to share. I just want to
say my first time here. Mine too. Yes, I
know. Thank you. Uh this is a special
occasion for me. It's my 50th birthday.
All right. after talking about the 13th
tonight. That was very interesting the
gate and so forth. I uh one small
question. U All right. Itty bitty itty
bitty. Yes. Is because it's about my son. He
Yes. Is because it's about my son. He
was born about four years ago. All
right. And uh my wife and I feel we've
grown very close and love and
understanding since then on all levels
except physical. All right. Okay. And
we've been talking about the triad a
week or so ago and that the third point
is the fulcrum. Yes. And we have a
feeling that our son is the fulcrum and
we we've developed polarities. All
right. Since then they can be amiable
polarities. Oh yes, definitely amable.
Yes. Um, but we'd like a little more
maybe a little more understanding as to
the actual mechanics of it and what we
can do to speed up the process of
integration on this back together. You
can allow the reflections of other
relationships to serve you in the way
that they need to. Allow yourself to
interact with other individuals as well
and explore all the different aspects
that being in the one relationship you
are in allows you to discover within
yourself and integrate those. But you
can sometimes do it most easily by
allowing other individuals to reflect
back to you. In different relationships,
the things that will enhance any other
relationship you are in. I see. Okay.
For not necessarily any one individual
will be able to provide you
physiologically with all the different
facets of yourself that you need to see.
True. Relax perhaps simply the definitions of
Relax perhaps simply the definitions of
what you think a relationship ought to
be. Yes. and allow the whole relationship
Yes. and allow the whole relationship
you have with everyone on your planet to
blossom. Very good. And then as you seem to
Very good. And then as you seem to
proceed in opposite directions, you will
find that when you incorporate your
entire world, your entire sphere, you
will automatically meet on the other
side. I had that feeling.
Yes. Does that serve you? It does very
much. Thank you. One moment.
One small clue that we perceive may have
something to do with your vibration in
your meditation. Perhaps when you are
drifting off to what you call sleep,
imagine a set of iron or dark steel keys
opening a
doorway. Walk in, play around, see what
you find. Bring it out into the light. Blow
find. Bring it out into the light. Blow
off the
dust. Bring it out into the sunlight and
see it sparkle. whatever is
there and absorb it into your
heart. Taste it with your heart. Pull it
out again and see what a difference it might
again and see what a difference it might
have made within you as to who you now
consider yourself to
be and what idea you wish to be and what
direction you wish to
move. Then place it
somewhere, not dark, not locked, but
easy to see, to remind you, to refer to,
just to look at, to glance at at any
given moment.
on top perhaps of what you call a mantle
on a hearth, brightly lit, in a cheery
room full of candles and
light. And above and beyond
all, full of rich and richly interwoven
tapestries. Thank you for allowing us to play the
Thank you for allowing us to play the
keys of a familiar melody to you and to
push some buttons beneath the surface.
Thank you. Thank you.
One moment. One
moment. Not that you necessarily have to
have any
direct in your colloquial way reference
to this, but this vibration may help
you. We are not necessarily speaking
reincarnationally, but you may find some
assistance with the vibrational name you
call Cromwell. Shedding
Cromwell. Shedding
sharing Bashar. Yes. Can you see my fan
I brought with you tonight? I brought
her with me tonight. Fan fan. Hello.
Say something.
Uh, the reason I brought my dog, my
drone dog, her name is Emmy. Every time
I play your
She runs over. She sits in front of the
speaker and she just sits there and
listens with with beautiful eyes looking
at the speaker.
Nope. Runs over and has a conversation.
Doesn't just listen. She really has a
conversation with you. Yes. Oh, for
heaven's sake.
[Laughter] [Music]
[Music]
Understand again that time and timing is
not what it is for you for what you call
animal consciousness.
The consciousness is different in the
animals real time. It is not the same
necessarily real time that you
understand. For them it is real and it
is in that sense for us. I see. Great.
I've learned a lot from her. Yes.
Um my friend Vita who is my teacher uh
said a Latian word which is lime which
represents the life principle of luck
slhappiness. All of a sudden luckiness.
Yeah. Luck. All right. All right.
[Music]
That's the way I wrote it. All right.
All of a sudden the word vibrated in my
heart chakra and felt good all over. I
felt excited full of love. That is
identification to the word to the idea to the frequency
to the word to the idea to the frequency
to the vibration. Harmonic
identification. Okay. Now this is
something that happened to me
afterwards. Yes. I had goosebumps all
over my body. All right. Then her voice
seemed too loud and strident to my ears.
Yes. Every time she talked, it sounded
like knocking in my ears. Even though
the tone she used was no different from
what she mostly used. In a sense, it is
because you had gone beyond words. And
in that sense, they were now to you seen
to be simply the representative symbols
that they were. You were receiving the
essence directly, and therefore anything
extra would only seem to be superfluous
to some degree.
I
see. She She talked softer. All right.
Yes. And her voice still knocked in my
ears. Yes. And she had to talk so low I
could hardly listen to her because it
was so low. Nice. And if she rose the
pitch of her voice, the knocking was
again. Nice.
So, how am I ever going to get over this
knocking? By allowing herself to receive
the communication directly,
telempathically in your heart.
Understand? Is it because that I'm
partly Latian? You have those
connections? Yes, I have the connection.
So, it was it was the
word lime. Okay. Yes. That unlocked it
in my uh in my heart chakra.
Yes. It was a timing word. A road sign
if you wish that you set up for yourself
to unlock you at the appropriate timing.
I see. Cuz it's changed. I mean um you
always will. I got to tell you
something. Oh, all right. If you got
after it happens, all I wanted to do was
sleep. Yes. Many of you will have that
reaction at first so that you can
connect into your higher self in the way
that you are used to unconsciously.
Bit by bit it will become more conscious
and you will sleep less
as you begin to wake up into the
recognition of yourself.
Thank you very much and thank you as
well. I wanted to ask you one thing. Oh,
all right. I know two questions but
we'll consider it one and a half.
I'm standing here. Do you see me like a
person? No. What do you see? I sense you
as a series of relationships to
different ideas and different
vibrations. All of them. I see. I see
the you you are
the real as a reference to all the other
you's you are.
I mean
quite a handful.
That's what my husband says. And
understand that when I also make a
reference to all the you's that you are,
I am not just referring to the you you
think yourself to be. I am referring to
all the other individuals that you are
with in your room. Oh, I see. I
understand each and every one of you as
the relationship to all the other ones
that are present as well. Oh, wow. In
other words, it is similar to
understanding and being able to define
one facet on a crystal simply because
all the other facets
exist. Understand? Yeah. That is how we
sense you. Thanks for calling my name.
My name is Thank you. Thank you. 99 sharing.
Hello Bashar. Hello.
Oh, one moment. One moment if you
please. May I? Yes. Thank you. Cheer up. All right.
You may be talking directly to me. All
right. Uh speaking to the audience is my
question. Well, I just got through
saying that you are all the same you
manifesting in different ways. That's
right. That's right. Well, um I wanted
to thank you first of all for uh talking
about the harmonic convergence because
that was real interesting for me. All
right. What are you about to say? The
harmonic indifference.
No, not
me. Not me. Oh. All right. Uh are you
familiar with the person uh uh a Leam
Morian person by the name of Bonnie? A
Lamorian person? Yeah. as a female
person under what is it the inner earth person
under what is it the inner earth person
came to body not by that particular
vibration we are aware of an entire
stream of consciousness that can
represent itself in many different ways
that may be connected to the time track
you call lamuran
well but to us it is more of a
homogeneous identity rather than a
specific persona it may be interpreted
in an archetypal way by different
individuals as a different persona.
as a different persona.
Well, there was a person named Bonnie
who made a tape of uh in talking about
the harmonic
convergence and um there was all kinds
of negative stuff that she was talking
about. Yes. U some of the people in this
room I think have heard this tape uh or
know something about it. She's I'm
paraphrasing the tape, but she talks
about stuff like the uh the Earth has
the possibility of tilting on its axis,
creating a All right. All right. Stop.
Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. That's great. I
I I'm I'm happy to stop.
Once again,
remember there will be changes and there
will be shifts and particularly in your
electromagnetic field. But the
opportunity is to understand that you
can create a positive or a negative
manifestation of the transformation of
the convergence. It is up to you.
Whatever vibratory plane you are on will
determine whatever effect you get out of
it mechanically. Individuals who present
the negative point of view give you an
opportunity to decide whether you prefer
that reality or
not. It is not verbatim. Excellent. So
in this same line then I'm spec I'm
interested to know since not everybody
can go to Hawaii I can't go to Hawaii
wherever you are is a gate you are a
gate is is there anything specific that
we can do some A what excites you the
most b know you are doing it in
harmonious alignment with everyone else
who is doing what excites them the most
A and B and is there any specific timing
that we should do this that would help
the most for this since most of you are
set on the idea of your 16th and 17th
dates Then you may feel like you are in
alignment with individuals if you
participate most in between those dates.
But any time will do
since you are in the harmonic
transformation and have been for
approximately 40 of your years will be
for approximately another 40 years. It
is all within the same time frame within
the same event. And time being a
relative thing will simply be perfect
timing for you will match the vibration
of whatever turns out to be perfect
timing for anyone else
by definition. So if I understand you
correctly, you're just saying just have
a good time. Yes. And it'll be that'll
be just the right thing to do to help
this harmonic convergence come off.
Right. In a sense, yes. The idea is for
each and every one of you to begin to
understand that ecstasy is your
birthright. Mhm. So to allow yourself to
fall into that flow, to do what excites
you the most with integrity and to know
you are doing it in harmonious alignment
with a number of other people will
create a momentum, a direction to the
flow of your mass mentality. You will
have a strong impact.
You will in that sense have an inertia.
Understand? Okay, that's great. Just one
real quicky. Why why do you call
yourself we? Why do you represent
yourself as we? Thank you. Sometimes I
can say I. Uhhuh. But that is a specific
reference to my own personality
structure. Usually when I say we or the
word we translates in your language, it
is a reference to the fact that I am
connected into many different levels of
consciousness and always channeling
through myself the necessary perspective
and information that we perceive will
serve you best. But we plug into many
different levels of consciousness
functioning as you would call it like a
switchboard. So when I say we, many
times I am referring to many different
we. Uhhuh. And sometimes those we are you.
Uhhuh. And sometimes those we are you.
Okay. Thanks a lot. Thank you very much.
Shutting. Hi Bashar. This is Hi. I had a
Hi Bashar. This is Hi. I had a
remarkable thing happen Friday. By all
means remark on it.
Um as you know I've been obsessed with
these Zetas. Yes. And uh obviously
they're obsessed with me. No, in a
sense. Yes. And um f um I connected with
their energy and channeling. And then
Friday morning as I was driving my car
to work
uh my mind was just sort of free
associating to a story I had written
many years ago. All right. And there was
some connection with these little
creatures that I had created, these
fantasy creatures that were a
combination between a kitten and a bee.
And I called them the cat beast. And
some I don't I didn't know really what
the thing was except that they lived in
a red house that a man built that the
boy built for them, the boy in the
story. And something about all those
little cat bees living in that house
connected somehow or other with this
whole energy and they suddenly just
started to channel through me while I
was driving the car to the point where I
was kind of going, "Okay, Shirley Mlan,
let's get the pleading to steer the
truck here." That kind of thing. And uh
it was just it was remarkable. I mean,
I've never an energy just wamp on me
like that to a point where I was just
really being taken by it. And I finally
got the car parked and then I said,
"Okay, is this" And I just said, "Is
this the hive?" Because I remember you
said they had a a hive mentality in a
sense. Yes. And they said, "The house.
We are the house." The house. Yes. The
home. The hive if you wish. Yeah. And I
just going, "Wow." And the eyes. I mean
I just those eyes like you said
something about the eyes they they is
just incredible. The name they have or
the vibration they have for themselves
would loosely translate into your
language as the household. The
household. Yes. That is what they call
themselves. The household.
Wow. Well, I blended with them then in
my channeling class and I didn't get any
verbal, just more of the pictures of the
eyes. Oh, thank you for being one of
them.
Oh, that's great. Thank you for giving
birth to
many Zeta babies in that sense. Oh, yes.
You're welcome. Little industrious
ideas. Oh, yes. Many, many, many. Yes.
Yes. Yes.
Part of the hive, part of the home, part
of the hearthf, part of the household.
Yes. Delivered with the inner sight of
the cat.
Oh, the curiosity in that way that
transforms you, not kills you,
right? And allows you to recognize your
place in the household.
House of red simply means earth since it
is recognized as one of the most
physiological dimensions. Understand? Wow.
dimensions. Understand? Wow.
Yes. Yes. Thank you. Oh, thank you.
That's it's just remarkable. You have
remarked on it. Yes.
Thank you. I'll see you in Hawaii. All
right. Byebye. At this timing, allow us
to remark once
again on our
joy in
experiencing your
household. Thank you for inviting us in.
Thank you for sharing
conversation and love and
ideas. Our love to you. And
remember you are the convergence itself.
It is you. You are it. You are the
definition of the momentum, the
inertia. You create the spin. You make
the world go
around. You are your
world. It is your
household. Our unconditional love to you and your
Our unconditional love to you and your
household. Pleasant
dreams. Awake. Awake. Live your
dream. We share and shall in that sense
see you on the other side of the
door. A fond and
loving good day. [Applause]
Thank you all very much for being here
tonight. [Music]
Those of you who want a copy of
tonight's we see Lyn right over here.