say how are you all this evening of your
time as you create time to exist.
Allow us to begin with interact evening
of your time with the laying of a little
foundation that we made entitled
conviction. The idea of conviction
The idea of conviction
now will be playing as you say a very
important a paramount role in your
belief system as you go further and
further into what you have called the
transformational age on your planet.
Now in very many ways
more than just our location are we alien
to you. In many many ways are you alien
to us. And in no way, shape or form in
any of these interactions do we ever
intend to allow you to assume that we know
to allow you to assume that we know
better than you about the way you wish
to create your planet. It is your
planet. You can do with it what you
wish. We have chosen to understand from
our point of view that we will not and
therefore cannot interfere
in the decisions that you make for the
overall direction in which you will take
your planetary society. Now, we have
perceived in many of you the idea that
certain changes are taking place within
your examination of consciousness and
that these changes and the directions of
your examinations have become similar to
directions and examinations and
explorations we as a society have been
familiar with for quite some time in
your terms of so in a sense we are
matching that frequency accepting what
to an invitation to dialogue with you in
this way unobtrusively to share with you
perspective of how many of the things
you are examining now have worked for us
have served us to give you an
opportunity to at least understand that
if you decide to go in the route that
you are examining with the exploration
of the expansion of your spirituality
and consciousness it will benefit you in
certain way it will lead to certain
conclusions and certain effects upon
yourself we are not here to tell you that you
we are not here to tell you that you
should do this or must do this is up to
If you should decide
that you will have the conviction of
your beliefs in this direction, we can
guarantee that you will aid and assist
in the ability of our respective
civilization to merge, to blend, to grow
together, and to explore infinite
creation in more expansive ways in joy
and ecstasy. I can guarantee just as
well that if you as a society rather
choose to have the conviction of many of
the negative ideas in your life that you
will create a post society founded in
negativity and in what you call perhaps perfect
and in what you call perhaps perfect
misery. The choice is up to you. Now
there is a wide range obviously of
endeavors and expressions in between
these two extremes but the idea and
nonetheless fall into the same category
of conviction. At any given moment
whatever definition whatever belief you
have been taught to buy into most
strongly about what your reality can be.
Whatever conviction you give to that
belief will utterly determine and always
utterly determine the way you actually
experience your physical reality, your
physical life. Because physical reality,
what you have for so long called solid
material reality, is only the product of
the definitions you have been taught to
give it, of the definitions behind which
you have been taught to put your
conviction, your belief. That is the
only thing your conviction itself behind
a particular definition that creates the
apparency of what you call solid
material physicality.
This is an immovable object. This is a
solid piece of matter.
It is only apparent in that way because
you have been taught to have so much
conviction behind that idea. In and of
itself, it is not empirically a fact.
It is only made into a fact. It's the
level of conviction you apply to the
idea that it is solid and impeccable.
So now the whole idea of conviction
begins to be the key to transforming
your reality in ways that you prefer it
transformed rather than continuing to
live your physical life in ways that you
do not prefer to live it. under the
assumption that life happens to you
rather than beginning to understand that
life actually happens through you.
All you are doing is changing the
definition. We are not asking and we are
not saying that you must have any
greater degree of conviction than you
have ever had before. The conviction,
the level of conviction, the level of
trust will be the same. It has always
been 100%
absolute infinite conviction, infinite
trust has been expressed by each and
every one of you. Every moment of your
life. Every single moment. Infinite
trust, infinite conviction. It just
depends upon what definition you're
putting your conviction behind.
Negative or positive. That is what
determines what you get out of life. how
you experience your physical daytoday
reality. Infinite trust, infinite
conviction in negative definitions and
cycles of negative repetition occurs.
Infinite trust in positive definition,
conviction in positive definition in
infinite cycles of positive
manifestations occur. This is simple
physics, simple mechanics. There is
nothing mysterious about this. And we
are not discussing some arcane
philosophy or figure of speech. We are
talking about in your terms a mechanical
tool. Your conviction
Your conviction
as you apply it in the direction you
apply it that
without exception
determines the effect, the feedback, the
echoes, the reflection, the experiences
you have in your physical life. The
style of them, the flavor of them, the
content, the degree, the epito,
all of that stems from your conviction
and what definitions you have chosen to
buy into behind which you place that
conviction. So now we turn to the key in these
So now we turn to the key in these
conversations
and the key is not again a change in the
momentum of the conviction but a change
in the direction of the definition.
Conviction will always be your strongest
power to create your physical reality
because your society as we perceive it
has created
one particular definition
and that says it is difficult to change
what already is. And because it has
taught you to put your conviction behind
that, that is what makes it seem as if
you need so much more conviction than
you have ever used to create something
you want in your life rather than
getting something you don't want. That
is the only definition that makes it
seem as if you have to use more energy
to try harder as you say. But you don't.
Only the definition itself that change
is difficult makes it seem so because
you have so much conviction behind it.
If you put your conviction, the same
conviction, the same amount of
conviction behind the new definition,
change is easy. In fact, change is the
only stable constant in creation.
Things must always change. If you put
your conviction behind the new
definition, your life will loosen up.
Literally, it will allow you a far wider range of
it will allow you a far wider range of
degrees of experience and
expressibility. Just because you have changed a few of
Just because you have changed a few of
your ideas, a few of your perspectives,
because you have moved a dial, pushed a
lever, that much, just that much makes
all the difference literally in your
world and in your life.
Again remember I am not speaking
philosophically. I am speaking
materially as you say pragmatically
practically. These things are applicable
to your physical life.
Within many of the interactions we will
have this day of your time. This idea
this concept will come up perhaps a few
times and we can see in these
interactions how perhaps it can be
applied to specific ideas specific
scenarios that you have created.
For it will and intent cover them all.
For it is in your terms the bottom line.
Conviction and definition.
and definition.
That's all there really is to your
physical reality. Conviction and
definition. That's all it has ever been.
But that is what reality is.
You all pull along so far as this
translating into your language
adequately. Can we take this opportunity now to
Can we take this opportunity now to
extend to each and every one of you our
unconditional love and our joy of
empathy and deepest appreciation in
allowing us to experience the gift of
your consciousness this day of your
time. We thank you for co-creating these
interactions with us and for choosing
this day of your time to function as
literally representatives and
ambassadors of your society. Make no
mistake about it. That is what you are
right now because there are many more
than just myself tuning in. As you said,
I in that sense thank you for allowing
me to be a representative of our
respective collection of societies
within what we have the association of
worlds. So that through these
interactions bit by bit and day by day
your world our world can co-create an
atmosphere a third alternative
a third alternative
that will allow more conductivity and
conduciveness of us to interact as
equals. For that is what we desire with
you to interact as equal. for you to
know that you are equal to any being in
creation so that we may share as equals
and once again explore as equal
expanding the infinite for both of us in
our own way.
We thank you for this opportunity. We
thank you for this gift of sharing and
in return for this gift I will ask you
now how may I serve you?
You and then you first of all I haven't
communicated with you in a long time.
How are you?
I'm perfect. Thank you. Um, I have a
couple questions.
First one is this man named Wor wrote a
book called
Have you been asked a lot?
Oh, really? Well, I haven't been there.
Oh, what?
Okay. I'd like to ask you where the
beings were from.
The star system you have labeled
reticular. It is similar, if you will, continue
It is similar, if you will, continue
your research to what you would call the
extraterrestrial beings that are
associated with what you call your fatty
and barney kill. Um,
Um,
why didn't he experience this being?
Because most interactions of that nature
now as they take place between members
of your society and members of the
association of liberals will for now
usually bring up the deepseated and deep
rooted fears that all of you have had
ingrained within you since birth.
Right? And that is why he did not experience it
And that is why he did not experience it
at first as loving but understand that
later he did. Uhhuh. And were these
beings um actually experimenting
in one sense on one level? But do
understand this. This is of primary
importance. None of these interactions happen
None of these interactions happen
without complete agreement.
Right? I understand that. Even if your
society members don't remember that
agreement and much of that quote unquote
experimentation is for the purpose of
assisting the members of your society to
make certain physiological adjustments
within themselves that will allow them
to acclimate to the increase in the
changes of the electromagnetic energy
upon your world. now in your
transformational age so that they can
also dispense the information of their
interaction in ways that will benefit
other people so that other people do not
have to have the experience in as
fearful a way as they originally did.
Right? Because prior to reading this
book, I always wanted to meet you so I
love it.
Yes, we know.
Oh, but after reading the book,
Yes. I feel like maybe I wouldn't want that
I feel like maybe I wouldn't want that
in my life. I win because
we understand.
You see many times individuals do not
feel bad. Individuals have expressed to
us, oh yeah, I will meet you right now.
5 minutes down at the door.
But the idea simply is is that many
individuals that have expressed that
have been given an opportunity when they
are in a remote local to have such an
interaction. And even up to the moment
that they arrive at the local and in
your terms are waiting and waiting and
waiting for us to arrive. They say, "Oh
yes, I'm ready. I'm here. I'm right
here. It's all absolutely fine with me."
And then as soon as they really think
something might be coming, they usually,
right? Because Because
because
so many things have been ingrained
within you and placed on what you call
an unconscious level that when you
finally interact with a level of energy
and we are not saying we are better than
you but with a level of energy that is
more highly accelerated. That highly
accelerated energy has a tendency to
pull from you those things and bring
them to the surface to force you to face
the things you may not be ready to face.
The fear that you have, the fear that
any of you would have in that
interaction is in no way, shape or form
a fear of us. It is a fear of yourself.
Okay, I got that. So, um are these um
beings from the cicum of the same
density and evol?
They are slightly different. In what
way? That may not be something in your terms
That may not be something in your terms
easy to explain in your terminology.
Okay. They have a physicality. They are quasi
They have a physicality. They are quasi
third forms in certain way.
But the idea is that they also exist in
many other levels that do not exactly
have counterpart terminology in your
language. For now, suffice it to say, you
For now, suffice it to say, you
obviously have the capability and they
obviously have the capability of
interacting with you in your dimensional
level. Although
sometimes some of the interactions that
have been reported in your society as
taking place in your physical reality
have actually only taken place
telepathically. Okay?
Okay?
But the telepathy is so real that it
seems physical to you. And also some of
what you are calling the operations
happen on that level as well. Not
actually physically. Even sometimes if
there are in your terms marks on the
body, your mind in believing it is
physical will create the marks even
though nothing physical was ever
actually done in your level of
dimensional experience. In other levels,
yes, sure.
sure.
But not in your level.
Right. Okay. Do they have as much
understanding of our society as your
your civilization does?
A few of them do. They are learning in a
different way to some degree. They are
somewhat relatively new to the
association in terms of as those things
go but we cannot exactly place what you
would call a time factor on it because
like us they have the ability to
transcend the idea to some degree of
space and time.
Do you ever communicate with that
director? Yes. Now and then
Yes. Now and then
um okay I have two other quick
questions. Um, one remember I don't know
when it was, you know, the eyes of Mar
15 and Alask.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
Okay. Well, the worst I've ever had that
kind of experience that I didn't know
resulted of something I ate was about
maybe two weeks ago and I just had it
extremely badly 4 hours.
Right. And I wanted to know if you could
um
what did you process in that?
I couldn't quite get to that. That's why
I'm bringing it up.
All right. Is it that literal? No.
No.
All right. The idea to some degree
is some of what you have now been
discussing. the releasing of some old
fears that is deeply entrenched
that serve to lighten you up in the
release. It is simply that sometimes
when individuals do think they are
ready, they will process in a very rapid
way that may for a while cause some pain
because they are willing in your terms
to stand it. Not that it has to be
painful and not that it necessarily will
be as painful the next time you may
choose to do it. But simply many of you
recognize that rather than having it
take months or years, you will get it
all, as you say, out of the way and over
with quite rapidly. Even though you
realize that there will be some degree
of physiological pain in processing it
that fast, you may still be willing to
do it because you know you're strong
enough and bold enough to do it in that
way. And in that sense, assimilate the
energy very rapidly.
I have an incident. It happened the
night before um my company. I was the
director of the film.
There are no answers.
A very rapid and quick adjustment was
made to acclimate you to the overall
combined consensus energy of all the
group that is involved in spreading that
information. Right. Okay. And one more quick thing.
Right. Okay. And one more quick thing.
Last night I learned that um I was very
afraid to be in the ocean that I would
be um I don't know bitten by a shark or
something. the dream. I said to myself
never to ask an entity about it because
I don't know why I'm afraid to be in the
ocean. So, I just wanted to bring that
up here because I don't know what it is.
To some degree, it is a last vestage of
something we have discussed, you about
the idea of diving deeply into life and
not worrying about what others in that
sense may think of you.
So the idea simply is your understanding
that you have passed through another
level and now you are willing to immerse
yourself completely in that ocean. The
idea is not something you still have to
do. The idea of the shark in the ocean
is something you already let go. You
simply gave yourself the opportunity to
realize it in a dream fashion.
It is not an indication of something you
have yet to do.
Right. So does that serve you?
So does that serve you?
Yes. Thank you very much.
Well, thank you very much. Enjoy your
swim.
Oh, you are so far out.
Only approximately 500 of your light
years. I recorded and you asked for ambassadors
I recorded and you asked for ambassadors
and my wife and I got a dream channel.
All right.
Oh, all right.
Uh, this year has been amazing for me.
Amazing story. Uh I used to lie a lot to
judge your situation because I lied
about the age of five so deep undercover
that I never told myself but only
recently in the last month must have
been uncovering the fact that I was in
fact phased out and phased back into the
age of eight
and uh had quite a meeting program and I
went to had your help in my dream. Um
this story has to do with carrying on
and closing kind of the third time for
the next 22 years and showing the
training of the people that were taken
in as returning to the years and a
scenario that ends up with the very
complete and high level uh in evolution
uh beautiful happy high and possible
pictures of the future of the earth.
Yes, my wife and I are giving this famous I
my wife and I are giving this famous I
want to turn into a dream. I like your
guy right now.
now.
The idea simply is that you obviously
like anyone who is involved in these
ideas are to do quote unquote your part
in assisting your planet in creating an
easier ability to choose the things in
life that represent that degree of
service, that degree of creativity. The
idea simply can be summed up in the
typical question we ask all of you. Are
you doing in your life the thing that it
excites you the most to do? Perfect.
All right. As long as you are doing the
thing that excites you most to do at any
given moment with full integrity, then
you are fulfilling your mission.
Because excitement is the signal that
all of you ask for. When you ask for a
side of what your purpose in life is,
the thing that comes with the most
excitement is who you are. Do it. Be of
service. Act on it physically. Put it
out there. Share. Be of service in
whatever way you are creatively excited
to be of service. And doing that and
radiating at that pitch, at that
frequency is what creates more ability
for more people in your world to be able
to see reflected in you an opportunity
to know that they also can do the thing
in life that ignites them the most
without worry, without doubt, without
struggle, without strife, in ecstasy and
joy and never ending happiness. Yes.
Yes. Happily ever after is possible.
May I leave my name, my phone number for
the people that may want to contact me
to maybe share anything?
Well, that's up to you. If not, it's
your plan.
Robert Cameron 88303.
You may discuss these ideas with any and
all that are attracted to do so in your
own timing. And we thank you for
whatever you have recognized is the
reason you have chosen to be of
assistance in the transformation of your
planet this day and age of your time.
Thank you for playing your part. Okay, hands.
Thank you. Could you appear to have a
more precise description of the
electromagnetic energy that you take
with you will be prescribed or more?
A more precise description of the
electromagnetic energy that your society
will utilize in the next 3 to 5 decades.
The idea of simple is the utilization of
the electromagnetic field that exists
around your planet right now for all of
what you may call your needs of power
and also a recognition that the
electromagnetic field is what is
responsible for the creation of what you
call your math mind or mentality because
consciousness the consciousness that you
are when it intersects or I shall say
interacts through the electromagnetic field of
through the electromagnetic field of
physical reality of the physical
universe. Then that intersection
spontaneously creates a physical version
of consciousness and that physical
version of consciousness is what you
call mentality and is what is
responsible for your teleathic link with
everybody. So within what you call the
next 3 to 5 decade, you will consciously
use the electromagnetic field as your
wave forms to communicate with each
other more telepathically. And you will
also draw from the electromagnetic field
all the energy you require for any
technological expression of those
elements. Many individuals in your
society throughout your history have
already recognized it. Adam among them
is an individual y'all called Nicola
Tesla. The research of his work and a few
The research of his work and a few
others will give you some insight and
understanding as to how to tap into as
you say plug into the electromagnetic
field of your planet and draw off the
energy in whatever way you require to
draw it off. Approximately 7 and 12
cycles per second is the vibration of
the electromagnetic pulse of your planet
earth. Any world that you wish to determine the
Any world that you wish to determine the
electromagnetic pulse rate of in cycles
per second can be done through the
following formula or equation.
If you will say what you call
the circumference of a planet in your terms
circumference of a planet in your terms
of miles and divide that into
what you call the speed of light in
terms of your miles per second. You will
then arrive at a figure that represents
in cycles per second the electromagnetic
vibrational wave of any planet. Yours is
approximately 7 1/2.
In forming sympathetic vibration, in
aligning it either sonically or
electromagnetically with that pulse, you
can create a sympathetic harmonic state
through which depending upon the type of
device you invent can draw off energy in
a number of specific ways and apply that
energy in also any way you wish.
Experiment and explore with these ideas.
do the research of the work that has
already been done on your planet for
there's much information that has yet to
be utilized.
Will this suffice?
Why not?
I would like to know is the use of this
energy is contingent to our morality. In
other words,
the negative use of this energy create
destruction comparable to or worse than the atomic
comparable to or worse than the atomic
warfare.
In this case, it is not dangerous to let
human beating
from that. Anything can be used in
either a positive or a negative way.
Anything, everything. Yet it could be
used in that way. It is simply that our
perception of the energy of your world
now of your morality of your
consciousness is such that within what
you call 3 to five decades your energy
your morality will be sufficient to use
it in a positive way. We have already
perceived in your combined collective
unconsciousness that approximately 10 of
your years ago you have already decided
as a society that you will not destroy
yourselves. And that is why we can't
share what little we are sharing at this
time. But do you understand what we are
sharing at this time is very little. We
are not being very precise because you
are not ready for the precision.
But whatever information already exists
upon your planet because you have made
the decision to use it basically overall
in a positive way.
So they are not ready to discover if
they have more of a to use it in a
negative way. That is our perception of
your combined energy and we perceive
once again that in approximately 50 of
your years your society will be able to
use it and understand it fully in a
positive way. It could change but as we
receive your energy now that seems to us
the most highly likely scenario. You
understand? Yes. One last question.
Yes. One last question.
Yes.
Is your
space? Oh yes. We power ourselves literally on
Oh yes. We power ourselves literally on
light itself. That is all you need.
Light is what everything is made out of.
Light is all there is. It is the basic
fabric of creation in physical terms.
All we do is transform certain ideas
into other ideas through the utilization
and amplification and direction of
light. Now the idea also is to some
degree that because it does take a certain
that because it does take a certain
integrated point of view to use some of
these ideas in certain ways, some of the
ideas will not even manifest and effect
at all positive or negative until you
approach them integrated and positive
point of view.
simply because of the nature of the
association of your consciousness itself
to the electromagnetic energy.
There can be ways it can be used
destructively and it has been done
before not only on your planet but on
others. But the idea first is that for
right now because it has been used that
way before then much of that information
is so deeply varied that it will not
come to the surface again until you are
good and ready to use it in a positive
way. So it is our estimation that you don't
So it is our estimation that you don't
really have to worry about it because
you have your own safety valve firmly in
place. Understand?
Understand?
Does that serve to answer your question?
We thank you with unconditional love and
sharing. Edard
star. Barnard star simply in our perception
Barnard star simply in our perception
contains a civilization
that approximates your Renaissance era
in its own way and forms
again in our perception at this time.
the most likely or one of the most
likely civilizations that you, your
society, will begin to interact with in
much the same way we are interacting
with you. Now when you create your one
world of peace and begin to go to the
stars, the civilization within the
Barnard starred system in a set will be
your or one of your first interactions
as a full-fledged member of the
association of worlds to aid and assist
them in their transformation. Again, in
much the same way we are assisting you
now. Now their society is different in
many ways even though there are
similarities. One of the ways it is
immediately different is that they are
already to some degree being prepared by
many of you in dream states. They
already recognize the idea you call
channeling. But they do not recognize
the idea that there are different
entities that are represented by the
idea of energy coming through. They have
one word for the entire phenomena. No
matter whom it comes through or who it
says it is that word in their language
is way.
In this way they have already begun to
establish an understanding that there is
or can be communication from other
societies. But they do not necessarily
at this point understand the full impact
of what it means in terms of your
interaction or the interaction you will
have with them in what you would call
your near future.
Understand? Can you describe the bees?
They are in your terms humanish
humanoid enough.
There will be
some slight physiological differences
but that exists the reason of their
humanlike appearance exists because as
representative of the first or one of
the first beings that you will interact
with on your own in that sense
facilitating on your own in that sense
because you will still be of a close
vibration to the dimension you are in
now. Then more often than not, you will
interact only with other societies that
are very close to your vibration. So you
will have enough degree of similarity to
be able to assist them, to be able to
understand them, to be able to relate to
them. And so you will attract yourself
to them or to someone similar. Their
main difference will simply be no more
than something you would recognize on
your planet as a difference of racial
type or ethnic background. It will be
unusual in many ways, but it will not be
in your terms so out of place that they
could not have existed on your planet as
another race. Understand? I will not
give you any more details at this time.
Allow yourself to understand that many
of you are already in contact in your
dream state. Allow yourself to bring
back the information you require in this
way. These are many times when we're having
These are many times when we're having
dreams when we're sharing with you say
people or certain people we don't this
could be an ongoing sharing
okay sometimes
are there aliens living
does that answer your question
your mathematics
it used to be based on 12
but the idea now is that we do not use
mathematics in any way, shape or form
similar to your own utilization of this
idea. It is now something that is far
more instinctive and intuitively felt.
It is interwoven completely into our
perception of the universe as a
holographic structure. We do not use it
in your terms as a science anymore.
Does this make sense? Does that answer
your question?
Thank you very much.
One moment. One moment. You are next.
All right. Thank you. Are there aliens
living on Earth right now?
Yeah. Are you living on Earth?
Are you living on Earth?
Well, no. I mean like
I said
I know what to do. I am playing with
you. Remember simply for the benefit of all
Remember simply for the benefit of all
that are collected at Savior that much
of this information will also be
underlined to explain many different
principles when each of you brings up a
particular idea. And the first principle
is none of you are original to your
planet. So in that sense, you're all
aliens living on Earth. However, you are
also obviously native if you were born
upon your planet. But I know what you
mean. From time to time, there are.
Right now, there are not as many as
there have been. And it is not in any
way, shape, or form a permanent idea
because now we are pulling back to allow
you to make the changes that you need to
make. Anyone that in your terms is still
closely connected to your physical plane
is doing so from another dimensional
frequency so that you do not perceive
them as physical at all.
There have been times when that hasn't
happened in a very physical way as you
would understand this term physical. But
right now it is not common place. There
are a few of what you might call
temporary bases but not really living
constantly on your planet as you would
understand that there's much coming and
going and right now because of your
society's tempo more going than
some I'll miss some say when they speak to
I'll miss some say when they speak to
certain people you're not from this
place and to me I feel like everyone's
from here but no one's from here
everyone's When someone you call
psychically sensitive picks up on that
vibration, all they are doing is picking
up on a line of connection that may
stand out above many other lines simply
because that connection may have a lot
to do with some of the ideas that that
particular person is playing through in
this particular line. But like Leo often
could site where you're from like Carrie
or mystery and I'm getting
once again the idea of telling someone
they are from there is not inaccurate
but it is an indication of the strongest
connections you have in this life in
another life. You may have been from
somewhere else
because of the different connections you
need to make in that life because of the
differences of that life.
Okay. Thank you very much. And you
Thank you very much. And you
I
like you. Speak up so that all may
share.
Oh, what is that? A question.
All right.
Well, I just wanted to know a lot of you
going through a very strong connection.
Another question.
I also
All right.
I feel like I have a very strong
feel. I wonder
I wonder
who he is or what I can do to change.
May I ask you a question?
Well, thank you. Do you believe you made
an agreement to be together?
Do you believe you are doing the best
you can with all the knowledge you
contain to fulfill that agreement on
your end, then relax
then relax
and don't worry that you're missing
anything. If you really are doing the
best you can and if you are as sensitive
as you can be and if you are being as
fully the person you need to be as you
can be, you're doing what you need to
do. And that person in choosing to be
your son knew what he was doing. Relax.
You're doing fine.
Okay. All right.
All right.
Does that Yes. Yes.
Red joy and
joy and
some of it. Some of it is a connection
of past life association. Some of it is
also a symbol of what we have just been
talking about. some connections to other
dimensional realms to reinforce to you
an idea to mirror to you to reflect to
you an energy and an essence
that represents that symbolizes the
direction of your path in this life.
the opening and the revealing of beauty
and sensitivity and love and remember
that includes self love not self-doubt
understand some of it has to do with a
few other lives you have I'll say live
in past terms understand that it is our
perception that all lives are
simultaneously occurring right now but I
will use your typical terminology and
say lived at them I want to ask you why
not? I do.
Well, that's because that's what you're
used to.
They are both true. They are both true
because you are the creators of linear
time. That's the definition of your
reality. So it's true and real for you.
I understand what you are saying and we
do but we proceed at whatever we
perceive to be the pace that serves the
collective and therefore since certain
individuals are completely in your terms
new to the concept that all your lives
exist. Now we will then bit by bit begin
with your terminology so that they are
familiar and then we will change it to
our terminology so they become familiar
with that. But we will simply proceed
whoever pays we believe serves the
benefit of the group. We do not rush
into these things because we have no
need of desperation to change your mind
to our way of thinking. Understand? And
remember that for many individuals on
your planet still the idea that you even
have more than one wife is confusing.
Understand? So we would simply take it a step at a
So we would simply take it a step at a
time.
We do not want to spout nonsequittors,
things that do not in your terms make
immediate sense. We will simply take our
time. Does that serve?
Does that serve?
Yes. Whatever Whatever
the last
it is acclamation to new levels of
energy and the remnants of resistance to
that change.
All right. I the other thing
it's that yes you
yes you
um I've heard that the universe can be
explained totally in terms of geometry
sense I like your comment on that
I like your comment on that
all right here it is
one point
that's it
everything is here and now everything in
a sense it would be what you call
holographic geometry the idea simply are
you familiar with what you call in your
society a hologram
yes all right then do you understand the
reference to the structure of the
universe that we are making everything
and everywhere yes that's the equation
now in your terms perhaps it might be
more precise from your dimensional point
of view to say the potential for
Everything is everywhere. But it is just
as real to say everything is everywhere.
And in a sense that is a geometry. But
it is a geometry which doesn't
necessarily have to be expressed in
physical terms. It is quote unquote a
single point. Even the idea of a single
point is a physical concept. It is
something even let's say less than that.
But that's really all it takes. the idea
that at every point is the information
of the whole. Let's use perhaps what you
might call a visual geometric analogy.
All right? Let's say you think of the
universe as an infinite grid laid out
flat to the horizon as far as you can
see. You have lines running this way,
this way, and this way, this way. What
you would call X and Y. Let's leave the
third dimension out of it for now just
for the sake of clarity. All right.
All right. So now you have this flat
grid that is the infinite universe. And
let's say that each intersection point
represents literally a point in space, a
coordinate, a piece of information about
the structure of the universe. All
right. All right. Now let's suppose that
All right. Now let's suppose that
someone with this analogy with this
model decides that they want to know as
much as they can. They begin a journey
of walking along that grid, picking up
information from each of the points and
they must keep moving and moving and
moving and moving and traveling far and
wide, looking and looking and looking to
a horizon that will never end, realizing
that it will take forever
to reach the end. If there is an end,
there probably isn't.
So this is one type of way of
understanding the structure. However,
perhaps more precisely in terms of
experience or effect, the structure can
be like as follows.
If you take what you would call a
reflective ball, similar to what you
would call a metal ball bearing in your
society, and you place it anywhere on
the grid, well now you can recognize the
reflection of the entire grid is in the
surface of that ball. And you can access
all the information of every point just
by looking at the ball right here, right
now without having to travel far and
wide to access that information. So in
your dimension, the third dimension, the
physical universe, the universe seems to
be laid out flat and you have to travel
far and wide to pick up on your
understanding of its structure. But in
what you might call the creative state,
the fourth density state, the higher
state of the universe, the original
state, quote unquote, all of these are
very arbitrary labels. But within that
state of its true I will say very loose
term geometric configuration that entire
grid that seems to be laid out flat to
all of you is wrapped up in that one
spot in that one point of space and or
second and you're always at the center
of it. So in experiential terms, in
practical terms, the geometry of the
entire universe as far as you are
concerned in terms of your ability to
access any information at all is always
exactly where you are, one single point
because in that point you can access all
of it. Is this making any sense?
Is this answering your question
sufficiently?
So you can call it that. But that's your
terminology for infinity in all
directions.
Well, that's it. Thank you very much.
Well, thank you very much.
Yes.
Most of the changes in your terminology
will be of a society nature,
social nature, social change. There are
energy changes. There are physical
changes in your electromagnetic field
taking place that not only are let's say
pushing the momentum of your society
changes but are also the result of the
changes in your society. Hand in hand in
hand they are interwoven.
One does not come first. They are
simultaneous and support each other
completely. The idea of the changes, the ones that
The idea of the changes, the ones that
will be felt in your terms
electromagnetically, is that you may
recognize changes in what you call your
changes in what you call your
atmosphere, your weather. There may even
be here and there some physiological
changes in the very structure of your
earth itself. However,
we understand it has long been, I shall
say, predicted that there will be
widespread catastrophe.
It does not have to be felt that way.
And we already perceive that because of
what you are exploring, you have already
as a society done much to alleviate the
need to experience many of the changes
in a catastrophic way because you have
already been willing to transform it
into positive understanding. In other
words, if you are willing to wake up
now, then you don't have to shake
yourselves away.
So the idea is that while there may be
isolated occurrences upon your planet of
the changes that you are going through,
it will not be in our perception as
widespread over the whole planet in a physical
over the whole planet in a physical
sense. It will be widespread in an
energy sense, in a social sense.
The idea simply is that you are learning
to create unity by truly validating and
truly equalizing the infinite diversity
of expression on your world. And so many
of these changes
will reveal themselves in massive
transformations of political, economic,
religious, and other social
institutions. You will transform them more into ones
You will transform them more into ones
of service. More in the format you would
call a networking of consciousness to
serve, to connect, to flow, not to rule,
to cast apart, to control. No,
these are the monumental changes that
are taking place.
The idea of anything that has been
called on your planet an Armageddon is
more of a personal idea than something
that truly represents a war that
surrounds your planet. You understand?
These are the changes. Again, some of
them will be felt and experienced
physiologically, but in no way, shape or
form as much as they would have been had
you gone through these changes all say
50 of your years ago.
Now I am going to use a very rough
analogy. It is not meant to be an
absolutely literal translation. But
let's say that 50 of your years ago in
order to allow your transformation to
occur in a positive way, you would have
had to experience the idea of 10 large
scale negative occurrences to reach what
you would call a state of balance and
accord. Now you have rendered it down to
Now you have rendered it down to
approximately 2 and 1/2 from 10. And the
idea is that even those two and one half
do not have to be experienced in very
shattering ways. You are already
loosening up your definitions of what
some people have in the past called
monumental sweeping changes in your
societ. Well, let's take an example that
we perceive happened recently. Your
society what you have called your stock
crash. Now, how many of you really care?
How many of you really believe you're
going to be negatively affected by that?
Not as many as used to be. So, you are
beginning to understand that your entire
economic structure is not really based
upon what your society has taught you
for a long time. It is. You are
beginning to recognize how arbitrary the
labels are and that you can still create
what you want regardless of the
fluctuations of what you simply call a
graph on a piece of paper. because
that's all it really is becoming to you.
You are beginning to understand that
economy is something completely
different and is actually based on your
own personal power and interactive
service rather than the idea of an arbitrary
rather than the idea of an arbitrary
medium of exchange.
You understand?
So the idea simply is is that you do not
have to go through trials by fire
in order to understand that you want
love and light. If you understand you
want love and light now, act that way,
live that way and do what you can do
with an action and conviction to create
your world to be that way now and you
will transform the energy in a positive
way. So you will not have to force
yourself through negative changes just
so you will shake apart the old
structure. Remember that
destructurization, which is what you're going through,
which is what you're going through,
doesn't have to be destruction.
Understand the difference.
You are pulling your society apart. But
if you do it in an intelligent and
conscious and loving way, you will not
have to shake it down to its very
foundations in a negative way. Some
people may still feel, and even some
groups of people on your planet may
still feel that the only way to wipe the
slate clean is to literally physically
eradicate large groups of your
population. and allow them to reincarnate and begin
and allow them to reincarnate and begin
again.
But that is something that now no longer
needs to happen. The more the
individuals in any given area understand
they can change the energy while they're
still alive, then the more they will
benefit of that change in physical
terms. It's up to you. The more each and every
It's up to you. The more each and every
one of you shared the idea and lived the
idea of the world you prefer to be, the
more you reflect as a living example to
other individuals what they can also
choose to live like and create the world
to be. So the more examples there are,
the less likelihood there is that
individuals are going to have to take
your world through a change of
negativity in order to simply understand
that you want love, light, peace,
harmony, and creativity. They're yours.
Create them. Choose them. Listen.
Does that satisfactory answer your
question? Yes.
down some foundation. Well, let me once
again explain it perhaps more clearly
from our point of view. We, let's say,
are looking at your planet. We scan your
world with certain ideas to pick out
what you would call the sensient or
self-aware or thinking life form on that
planet. The difference between what you
think of yourself and what you call
animal life. You follow me?
We are scanning your planet now for the
idea of all of the beings on your planet
that are self-aware beings. What you
would call the intelligent beings of
your planet. In other words, who
inhabits this planet? You see, to us,
the idea of the animals are equal
inhabitants. But we understand the
difference that their consciousness is
focused in a different way other than
what you and I refer to ourselves as as
self-aware thinking beings. You follow.
When we scan your planet, what do we
come up with? But surprise surprise,
there are two alien races on Earth. Land
humans and water sedations.
You are equal alien races in completely
different environments, but you are both
selfaware reincarnational thinking
intelligent beings.
You have on your very doorstep another
completely alien race.
You don't have to go to the stars to
find one.
Lucky, lucky you. Even though we do not
believe in luck,
but the idea simply is is that they give
you an opportunity to begin to merge and
blend with them as one society. So that
as one society, you will make it that
much easier to blend and merge with
other whole societies such as our own.
They want to interact. They want to play
with you. They have in many instances
entered your dream realities where you
are more freely able to let them in
because of your expanded state of
consciousness in what you call the dream
level. They have done this many times
and have assisted you in many ways. All
of you. They want you to learn to play
and interact with them. They can teach
you much about spontaneous ecstasy.
Much. And because of the environment
they have lived in and because of what
they have chosen to create themselves to
be, they simply have for a long time in
a conscious way been in telepathic
connection with many other alien
civilizations on other worlds. In
particular, an affinity has grown
between the idea of intelligence in the
serious star system and your dolphins
because they share many ideas in common.
Will this do?
Well, thank you and happy dream.
Yes. All right. Are we balancing?
To some degree, there is validity to
this idea in the same sense that if you
have before you what you may call a
battery device that contains a number of
cells and you remove a good number of
those cells, the battery will probably
become in your term inefficient in
distributing its electrical power. You
follow me? So a similar analogy to
something does follow in removing too
many of the crystals from their natural
centers in the earth. However,
it has not been in this point
irreparable damage. And if you remember
that each and every one of you are
master crystals, you can with your own
consciousness create what you perceive
to be a rebalance of the energy. But
more often than not, it is our
perception that in what you call your
future, a few crystals around your
planet will be created to represent all
the symbology and all the connectedness
any of you need to the idea of being in
the presence of a particular crystal.
But remember, they are only triggers.
They do flow energy. They do flow power.
But in terms of them working for you,
they are only catalyst and triggers for
your own power because they are simply
expressions of your consciousness.
Understand? So there may be as there
used to be a few master crystals placed
around your planet that are used and
focused on by all so that you do not
necessarily each and every one of you
have to have thousands upon thousands
upon thousands of crystallin shards with
you at every moment. You are now
integrating everything on every level
and so the ID will also include what you
call your externalized tool even the
crystals in that way. That is why now in
certain areas around your planet some
crystals are being discovered that have
already been created and carved in
certain fashions to represent the
triggering of that level of your
consciousness. Some of this is inherent
in what you call the crystal skulls that
come from your central American area.
They are very powerful gates, very
powerful keys to tapping into other
dimensions and other levels of
consciousness. Understand?
These are sufficient if you will but
drop your borders and share them
and place them around your world in a
certain equilateral matrix on what you
would call the natural lines of
electromagnetic flow. They will serve as
networking devices and they are
sufficient in and of themselves.
out of this.
At this timing, there may still be here
and there individual crystals that can
serve to trigger specific ideas for
specific individuals, but that is
lessening as you take them all to heart
literally. We thank you at this time. You may all
We thank you at this time. You may all
enjoy a very brief break. We will resume
contact in approximately 10 of your
minutes of counting. Sorry. Continue.
I need your help. I have
You do?
I do. Yes. And I tried everything.
You tried everything? Yes. Um,
Um,
did you expect anything else?
No.
I for the last couple weeks
and I have done a number of things to
help. I've looked at what could be
emotionally, psychologically. I'm a
chiropractor active stress and I've been using the
active stress and I've been using the
thing that's helped a lot is crystalite
malight. One moment.
One moment.
You say you tried everything. What about What about
regression?
Was the word clear? Try that. Okay. Um,
Okay. Um,
find someone you feel comfortable with
who in a loving way can take you through
what you might call a little bit of
regression. Not only back to earlier
times in your present life, but perhaps
to a few of what you would call your, in
your terms, past or if you wish,
alternate contemporary lives.
Okay? and see what that does with regard
for your throat.
I will do that continually and see what
what's going on with that.
Let's just say that what you might
discover would help you release
a little bit of a
constriction. A little bit of a
You are just a little bit and yes I am
purposely being allegorical.
Just a little bit choked up about a few
things which someone can help you bring to the
which someone can help you bring to the
surface and
let out.
That is simply our suggestion
and once again
allow us to remind you it will not take
very much
you are as usual right on the threshold
but if you wish take the suggestions for the
if you wish take the suggestions for the
regression and see what happens
have a wonderful time going Down memory
lane. Down memory lane. I Okay, I hold on. I
Down memory lane. I Okay, I hold on. I
have to I know.
Thank you very
um I have a question regarding something
psychic told me which also brings up
other questions about psychic. I was
told that I had a misconnection in my
brain, an energy connection that was
resulting in in something happening in
my reality. Um, can you tell me anything
about that?
The idea simply is analogous to what
many of you will experience now that you
are opening up your sensitivity to
different levels of energy. The idea to
put it on a groundwork level is that
there is a very similar neurological
phenomenon between what you call
channeling and epilepsy.
and epilepsy.
The idea simply is is that what you
would typically call an epileptic
individual is shortcircuiting in a
certain way and transferring the energy
back upon itself.
What at the idea you call a channel lets
it out in a certain way. Many of you are
now creating these synaptic
realignments to help facilitate new understandings of
to help facilitate new understandings of
new levels of energy so that it can be
translated through your neurological
makeup into something that as you say
makes sense or can be applied in your
reality's understanding.
You see, in what you call the past, many
individuals have utilized a particular type of
have utilized a particular type of
approach to get them to begin to cause
what may at first seem to be a
misalignment, but is in reality simply a rearrangement
but is in reality simply a rearrangement
of their neurological pathways. And this
particular approach more often than not
took the form of either a strong
electrical shock or a very sharp blow to
the head at some point in the life. Have
you had either of these?
My mother told me when I was very very
young when she carried me down a flight
of subway stair she dropped it.
I see.
I wound up with a black head.
Yes. This is a typical path in your society
This is a typical path in your society
for creating an unlocking from the
belief systems of your society you don't
want to buy into
so that you can ensure that you will
focus with your new neurological makeup
only on those things that will represent
what will serve you in the idea of what
you are now exploring and what you
really wish to absorb as information.
To some degree that is the result of
what was psychically sensed within you.
It is the fact that you are rearranging
your neurological makeup and to some
degree have rearranged it to ensure that
you would receive information on certain
levels. This is not the whole idea but
it is one of the aspects that was being
sensed. Understand? Understand?
Yes.
Um
I did it like it was almost like I
needed to feel to reconnect that um
parallel. All of the healing takes place when you
All of the healing takes place when you
allow the energy you get in touch with
to come through. And that does not
necessarily mean that you have to make
an agreement to channel something else.
Simply allowing the flow to come through
you will create the alignment
that you need.
Have I done it?
You are doing it.
Do you have any pain in your head? Once
in a while I get headaches but nothing
really severe.
All right. Then you are adjusting
nicely. Are you doing what it excites you the
Are you doing what it excites you the
most to do?
More and more every day.
All right.
I have another question about
scientific. uh my experience with them is when I
uh my experience with them is when I
would ask a particular sentence about
something and they would say well um
this is going to happen say on the job
situation and
sometimes it doesn't always happen
correct and I realized that my reality has a lot
and I realized that my reality has a lot
to do with it
well has everything to do with it
everything let's lay another foundation
for everyone shall
prediction prediction prediction.
There is no such thing as a prediction
of the future.
There is a sensing. This is what psychic
ability is a sensing of the energy
that exists. That is the most likely
energy to manifest at the time the
prediction is made.
That can change.
When predictions come true,
then that individual may have simply
sensed a momentum that was very likely
to not change because it perhaps had a
great deal of energy, a great deal of
momentum, a great deal of drive and
desire behind it.
But many times recognize that all that a
psychic prediction or sensing is doing
is telling you look you have several
categories behind these few categories
is where you have a great deal of your
energy. Therefore it is very likely the
psychic says that these may be the first
ones to manifest in your physical
reality because that's where you're
aiming. That's where you have your
sights locked on. Now, if all of a
sudden you are made aware that you have
your energy piled up behind something
you don't want it to pile up behind, you
will say, "Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
That's not what I prefer." Therefore,
being made aware by the prediction of
where the energy is, if it gets you to
change it, you have now rendered the
prediction obsolete just by being aware
of the prediction to begin with. So many
times a prediction's purpose and a
prediction's service is to render itself
obsolete by putting you in touch with
where the energy is because if you don't
prefer that it's there you change it.
Understand? But all psychic sensings are made in the
But all psychic sensings are made in the
present of the present. No matter how
far in the future the psychic is talking
about, what they are connecting into is
the momentum in the present. that may
lead to that manifestation if nothing
changes. Understand?
Therefore, there will always be a wild
degree of fluctuation in the
manifestation of any psychic sensing and
that should always be taken into
consideration because the very next moment of time
because the very next moment of time
means you are a different person and in
a sense actually require another
reading. In order to become accurate,
you must require a reading every single
moment. Understand?
Understand?
In order for someone to absolutely
understand the flow of your energy and
as you would say, validly predict
everything that could occur, they have
to hang on your coattails every moment
and take another snapshot every moment
to see where your energy is every
moment. Now if something within you has
a great deal of momentum and is unlikely
to change then they can perhaps let that
one ride being in all likelihood you
will manifest it. But they are simply
picking up on what you call the odds of
where you have placed your energy but
certain things can happen to allow you
to change that very abruptly.
Does that answer the question
sufficiently? Yes.
Yes.
I'm I'm in a relationship sort of that
You know, if I may interrupt you for a
moment. Thank you.
There is in your terminology
some time on our part spent in I shall
say practicing interacting with your
society simply because some of the concepts in
simply because some of the concepts in
your language do not translate at all in
our language
and some of the things many of you have
said when they get translated, I shall say
when they get translated, I shall say
for now on this side,
and when they are experienced by those
that are not as experienced in
understanding what you actually mean by
what you say,
well,
I will not say that they laugh a lot,
but there is a great deal of blinking.
And a lot of I shall say blank
expressions
because many of the terms any society
has do not as you know translate very
clearly into the terms another society
may have. When someone said in your
society, "Where am I?"
"Where am I?"
That gave us no end of confusion for a
while. For we could not even conceive how such
For we could not even conceive how such
a question could be asked,
how you could not know where you were.
Bit by bit, we then decided that one of
the easiest ways in interacting with any
civilization would be to have members
choose lives in that civilization. And
having lived those lives, they would
then have a model, a representational
model through which they would have more
understanding of your nomenclature and
your idioms.
The channel before you is my model and
represents the past life, the only past
life I have had on your planet for the
purpose of creating a model through
which I could relate to you. Because
without the model, you and I would be
far too alien to truly speak on the same
level. in that sense to aid in the
in that sense to aid in the
clarification of this terminology and to
further promote the idea and
understanding of simultaneous lives. I
am the channel's future like one of them
do. Uh anyway, I
Uh anyway, I
this relationship that you are in sort
of
No, I'm in the relationship.
Oh, hold you. In actual fact, if I may
interrupt you briefly once again, the
way it would actually translate in our
society would be as follows. I am the
relationship of of
continue.
uh my terminology of it or my expression
of of how I see this is a very negative
relation right right
and
why so how so
well because it doesn't excite me number
one oh then why are you in it
oh then why are you in it
that's what I that's why I'm asking this
question because I just don't understand
why I'm choosing to stay in this
relationship I see well what are you getting out of
I see well what are you getting out of
staying in it
anger is that what you want
is that what you want
no
all right how does Does it serve you
then to experience your own anger? Now,
do you know what natural anger is? By
the way,
thank you. Most of what on your society
you call anger is not actually
representative of its natural purpose
because usually what we call natural
anger only lasts about oh say 10 to 15
of your seconds.
Beyond that, it's invalidation,
judgment, guilt, frustration, hatred,
rage, jealousy, envy, all these
different ideas and classifications of
negativity that are not truly the
original natural energy that you typify
as anger. Because in a sense, this may
seem to be a contradiction, natural
anger is not experienced in a negative
way. Natural anger is as follow. When you see
Natural anger is as follow. When you see
something in your surrounding reality
that polarizes you and aligns you and
creates that rush of recognition of what
you believe most strongly as compared to
what you are seeing.
Anger then can be understood to be a
natural alignment by a reflection of
seeing something you know you are not.
That helps you understand more strongly
what you are.
Now the idea of what you typify as
anger, all the negativity that seem to
naturally, it doesn't naturally come as
the result of these types of
interactions, all of these things then
are your invalidations
of what you are seeing both outwardly
and inwardly. That's what you typify as
anger, invalidation.
But the idea of natural anger is simply
that when you are in a circumstance and
in a situation that you have created and
something occurs that is not
representative of the vibration you
prefer to represent yourself at, you
have the rush of alignment that reminds
you this is what I am that is what I am
not. But there is no reason to carry it
into invalidation and negativity from
that point forward. The anger quote
unquote is there to show you who you are
so you can then choose the reality you
prefer. Not believe that you have to
remain quote unquote stuck in the
situation that showed you who you were
to begin with. It's there for you to
make the change if you want to make a
change. So that is how anger can serve you in a
So that is how anger can serve you in a
positive way.
So if you are willing to learn that from
the circumstance, then perhaps it will
put you more clearly in touch with the
definitions you prefer to be. And by
simply acting
with conviction like the definitions you
prefer to be, acting like the person you
say you prefer to be, you will then
change your energy and your emotions and
your reactions so abruptly and so
strongly that you will no longer even
begin to be able to relate to someone
who is not of your frequency.
understand. And so if you do not relate to someone
And so if you do not relate to someone
who is not of your frequency, to put it
idiomatically, they can't push your
button. Understand?
Understand?
They will be a complete nonsequittor.
Understand? So if you use the idea of what you are
So if you use the idea of what you are
learning by being in the relationship in
a positive way, then you will simply
take yourself to whatever level is
representative of who you want to be.
And no one else who is not on that level
will be able in a sense to interact with
you in a negative way. Remember no one
no one no one ever actually directly
affects you. You have to choose to be
affected which means you simply willing to relate
which means you simply willing to relate
to the other person on their level.
That's why I asked the question because
I don't understand why I'm choosing to
relate to this person on his level. Let
me ask you a question in return if I
may. Do you really believe you are capable of
Do you really believe you are capable of
being the person you say you ought to
be? Yes. Yes.
Absolutely.
Yes. All right. Do you believe you need
All right. Do you believe you need
someone else in order to be complete?
No. All right. Do you have a definition of
All right. Do you have a definition of
who it is you would prefer to be?
All right. Are you willing to attract
individuals in your life that may not be
on the same level to reflect to them
ideas that may allow them to choose to
change if they want to without
necessarily taking it upon yourself to
be negatively affected by the things
they are going through?
Would you repeat that?
I rephrase it completely. In other
words, sometimes individuals that do
have a very clear understanding of who
and what they do want to be will still
allow through agreements they have made
other individuals into their life to be
attracted in their life that may not be
on the same level. Not so that they in
your terms can get sucked into their
energy, but so that they can see
reflected from you the conviction and
the certainty you have about who it is
you do want to be. and let them know in
no uncertain terms that you living your
life will offer them an opportunity to
match your frequency if they want to.
Not that they have to, if they want to,
but that what they choose will in no
way, shape, or form impede your desire
to be who you want to be. Now, all in a
sense you are doing is creating an
assumption that just because you
attracted that person into your life
that you have to match their frequency
in order to interact with them in the
way you agree to. But you don't. Many
times you will attract someone in just
so they get the opportunity to see the
reflection of what actually concerns
them best when they see in you the
willingness to live the life you really
prefer to live. In other words, to put
it on a very simple level, the way you
very often will help someone else the
most is by being mostly who you are the
best whether that goes along with what
they want or not.
Understand? Yes, I do. Um but the fact that I'm
Yes, I do. Um but the fact that I'm
still being charmed negatively by this
person means you're still accepting the
means you're still accepting the
offering.
Now examine simply for yourself. Does it
examine simply for yourself. Does it
serve you to do so?
Yes. No.
No.
All right. Remember this and perhaps
this will unlock.
And I
feelings. All feelings. Feelings.
Feelings. Feelings. Feelings.
All feelings are reactions.
reactions to something you already
believe to be true.
So if you find yourself feeling a
negative charge from someone, it's
because you contain a belief
that something is negatively charging
you. Change the definition and you will
Change the definition and you will
change the reaction emotionally.
Again, if you understand they have
nothing at all to do on certain levels
with the reality you prefer to be, if
you really rewrite the definition of
what your interaction is, then you will
understand that you will have the
emotions that follow suit to the new
definitions you have written. All
emotions are reactions. So you have a
choice in that sense to act as you
prefer to or in a sense to react as you
understand. Yeah. So if you are feeling negativity
Yeah. So if you are feeling negativity
because you are choosing to feel it, ask
yourself what would I have to believe in
order to choose to feel the negative
charge. Find what that belief is, what
that definition is that allows you to
accept the negative charge.
Once you find it, rewrite it in whatever
way you prefer to represent who and what
you are. And once you rewrite it and
start acting like you really believe
that, you will no longer have a negative
charge. It will not be part of your
makeup. Got it?
Got it?
Because you will be a different person.
Literally, literally.
Literally a different person.
Mother. Yes.
Yes.
Is this assisting you?
Oh, absolutely.
Oh, well, thank you very much.
You're welcome. Yeah.
Yes. Speak up. Speak up so that all may
share and I want to know her name and so I can
and I want to know her name and so I can
get in clear communication with
clearer communication with guys.
Very simple. Very simple.
Are you ready?
Are you sure?
All right.
Close your eye. Are you comfortable?
Take three deep breaths. Slow, easy,
restful, relaxing deep breath. Let me
know when you are ready.
Allow yourself now to simply drift for a
moment. Just daydream if you will.
Just daydream if you will.
And now I am going to suggest that you
in your mind ask
a series of questions or make a series
of statements.
When you do so, I want you to tell me
out loud
the very first thing, not the second,
the very first thing that pops into your
mind without thinking about it at all.
Understand? Without analyzing it and without needing
Without analyzing it and without needing
it to make sense.
Understand? All right.
All right.
Are you ready?
Now think of the idea of your guide.
Just think of the idea. Think of the
feeling of the vibration that to you
represents the idea of your guide. Have
you got it?
Oh, what does it feel like?
Describe it.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Expansive. Yes. What
else? Is there any physiological
sensation? I see eyes.
I see eyes.
You see eyes. All right. Very good. What
do they look like? All right. All right.
Now
know beyond a shadow of a doubt at this
moment that you are on the frequency
level through which you are in open
communication with your guide. Do you
understand this?
Now in your mind simply ask the following
in your mind simply ask the following
question and when I ask you a question
answer me as quickly as you can without
thinking. Ask now
Ask now
guide is that you
and tell me immediately what answer you
get. All right. Say guide how are you?
All right. Say guide how are you?
What did the guide say?
Fine. All right. Say guide where are you?
All right. Say guide where are you?
What did the guide show you?
Behind you.
All right.
Say guide I love you.
What did the guide say?
All right. Say guide. Why are you here?
Say guide. In what way?
What did the guide say?
All right. Say, "Thank you, guide."
What does the guide say?
You're welcome.
All right. Now,
take three deep breaths.
and open your eyes and become still
comfortable. But re-engage me in
conversation.
Are you ready?
All right. Now
understand that we took you through what
is simply called a very simplistic
conversation that many of you will say well I can
that many of you will say well I can
have a conversation with myself on that
level I could have invented that conversation
I could have invented that conversation
there was no meaty information in that
question why does there have to Yes.
Yes.
You see, your guide has a job
to guide you by being behind you. And
what that means is you're leading the
way. Your guide told you in no uncertain
Your guide told you in no uncertain
terms that the guide is behind you. And
that not only meant that the guy could
in a sense physically be behind you, but
what it means more appropriately is that
you are always reminded by the guy that
you are the leader. You are the best
guide. That's what a guy's job is, is to
remind you that you're in control.
Now, you can easily have conversations
and very often do have conversation, all
of you, with what you call your guide.
However, the information sometimes
appears so obvious to you
that you think, well, that was just me.
And in a sense, that's true.
Very often, the information you get in
your own conversations with yourself is
a conversation you are having with your
guys. But the point is, you are not
always supposed to, nor do you always
need to know the difference. because it
is not the guide's job to stand out as
different. Now, this can occur from time to time,
Now, this can occur from time to time,
and there is nothing I'm saying wrong
with it,
but the guide job is to do the job
unobtrusively. More often than not, communication with
More often than not, communication with
your guide will actually take the form
of some of the coincidences and
synchronicities that actually occur in
your daily life. The guide is
suggesting, guiding, showing you look
here is something that can serve you.
Now it's up to you to act upon it or
not. But the guide does not lead you by
the hand. And very often in that sense,
the guide does not initiate or instigate
what is perceived by many of you to be a
vocalized conversation. It can happen,
but more often than not, it won't
because the guide's job is more often
than not to be done quietly,
suggestively because you are supposed to be in the
because you are supposed to be in the
driver's seat. You are your own best
guide. So, the guides remain behind you in the
So, the guides remain behind you in the
background for the most part.
Now also you can create within your own
feeling a name for the guide. The guide
doesn't care.
The guide may have had at many points in
its life different names,
but it doesn't care. Give it whatever
name you wish. It will work. If you even
need to give it a name at all. The idea
simply is that if you know the feeling,
if you recognize the energy in and of
itself, of its own accord, then you
really actually have a more precise
representation of the guide name than
any label you could invent. The feeling
is the guide name, the guide's true
essence and being, the feeling you get,
the energy you send, that's the guide
name. That's why we no longer use names.
We know ourselves by our energy, by our
signature vibration itself.
And we know everyone else in our society
in the same way. So if you feel the need
to invent a name, it will be the guide's
real name because any name will do. If
you feel it is representative because
you're in control, the guide says, "Call
me what you want, boss.
You're the bos. I am here to guide you
because I love you. And because I love
you, I will always remind you. You're
the B.
So if you want to give me a name, I'll
love it. And I'll cherish it as my own
because it will be my own because you
have said so. Because you're the boss.
Understand? These ideas
These ideas
are very valid in terms of the way many
of you approach the idea of God. Lord, I'll kill
When you or if you should at any moment
choose to create what would classically
be called a misalignment with your own
energy, you'll know it. And the guide
will in no uncertain terms also let you
know it. But remember, you're equal to
the guide. You're a consciousness, too.
And you have your own say in these
conversations. The guide is not simply
there to say, "Do this, do that, do
this, do that."
The guide basically, if any conversation
happens, is saying, "Here's a
suggestion. What do you think? Here's a
suggestion. What do you think?" All the
suggestions the guide will make will be
representative of you being in alignment
with your own strongest intention. But
the guide will always say this is my
perception of your strongest intention.
But what do you think Bob?
Understand? That's why very often it seems as if
That's why very often it seems as if
connections and conversations and
communication with your guide is very
very flimsy because it is meant to be.
It will be strong at times but for very
specific purposes and only when you
yourself create a vibration of equality
that allows you to perceive your guide
as an equal.
Understand? So know the guide is there
and not only one that are usually many
and sometimes they take two.
Remember even though they have chosen to
be your guide, they also do have other
things to do.
Now, I'm not saying this is the case
with you, but we have perceived in our
conversations with many of you when you
start talking about the idea of
non-physical entities, especially people
that in your terms have physically died,
sometimes we are left with the
impression from you that you think they
have nothing better to do than hang
around waiting for you to contact them.
They're busy. They have lives to live.
They have things to learn.
very often they take almost no note of
the physical idea they have left behind
or even when they choose to time for
them is not what it is for you at all.
And sometimes when an individual after a
long let's say set of physicality
experiences all of a sudden again finds
themselves non-physical. I say again of
course speaking in linear terms
very often because they're so
overwhelmed by what seems to then be a
new understanding a new expansiveness.
Sometimes even just the shock that
they're actually still aware and not
really snuffed out will focus their
attention so strongly in the
non-physical plane they may think in
their old terms of thinking that they
have spent oh say 5 or 10 minutes
examining their new surroundings and
they turn around and look back at the
physical world they have left and oh my
goodness 3 years have come and gone.
No, no, no. for 10 minutes but 3 years
it can happen that way.
So the idea once again is to understand
that even the best of guides
is still working with the differences of
the definitions that you have created
between what you call physical reality
and non-physical reality. So in a sense
they have to be general. They have to be
subtle. They can at times be precise but
if they try to be very often they will
miss the mark because time for them is
not what it is for you. And that is also
why many times especially when
predictions come from guides or
non-physical entities the time frame may
be very wildly off the mark
because their sense of time is
completely I will say and not meaning to
be derogatory out of whack with yours.
So continue
experienced a lot of questions. Yes,
very good. Now again,
very often that is simply your awareness
of the fact that you are opening up your
senses and you are feeling the flow of
more energy. And sometimes
in a very literal sense, you are
actually feeling the touch of a guy.
That's what the original meaning of your
word touched means.
that sometimes the dye literally does
touch you on its own level and sometimes
you can feel it as an increase in the
pressure of energy in a particular area
of your body. And that's why because of
what many in your society have labeled
the idea of dealings with the
non-physical to be. That's why many of
you have said that the word touched
means out of your mind
or crazy because it deals with the idea
that you are literally touched by
something that your immediate physical
senses do not perceive.
I don't know if I'm going crazy. Yes.
Yes.
And what is that?
Did you notice the actions of the
physical channel as we merged our energy
with it?
Did you notice the head snapping?
The idea simply is is once again there
are certain areas, energy areas, energy
gates, energy doors upon the body within
your body. And as energy flows through
these areas, it may cause a
physiological reaction simply because
that area is not used to handling in
what you call a normal daily routine the
level of energy that is being poured
through it now and it will cause a
physiological reaction. Much in the same
way that if you have a conduit of some
sort and it is used to handling a
certain amount or trickle of fluid
through it and all of a sudden you pour
a great deal of fluid through it, it
will in a sense change its shape and
move around abruptly because now it is
handling a flow that is in your
terminology something greater than it is
used to handle. And that's simply for
now a habit and a reaction in many
members of your society until you
completely acclimate to that flow of
energy. Then the idea will settle down.
Understand? Yeah. Another thing
Yeah. Another thing
I had really bad dream or a dream. I was
doing meditation.
Yes. And there was insects all over.
And there was insects all over.
I see.
Yes. Yes. Stop.
Some of this to some degree is an
indication that some of the guides you
are in touch with are literally
extraterrestrial in nature and your mind
is interpreting them as insects. They're
not. But their energy comes across that
way. Understand?
Understand?
Your mind will create pictures to best
understand the experience that you have
had. But your outer aare mind only has a
few pictures to draw from. Whatever
feeling it gets, it will do the best it
can to match a picture to the feeling.
Some ideas of what you refer to as
extraterrestrial consciousness,
especially those that function in what
you would call a hive mentality, will be
interpreted by your mind as insectike
in their activities.
Understand? So some of the guide energy you are
So some of the guide energy you are
feeling has to do with extraterrestrial
connections as well.
And also how I develop my more
class and I started seeing rainbows and
I feel really
grounded and I just feel far away.
All right, then with your imagination
visualize a very strong beam of energy
going directly from your heart to the
center of your earth. your ground.
Understand? And the way you can allow it to expand
And the way you can allow it to expand
at the same time is with two words.
Unconditional love.
Trust that you are proceeding at the
proper pace. You are never going to go
faster than you can really handle.
Understand? For that would serve no
purpose. The only reason sometimes you
create the feeling of spiness as you say
is because you are simply not used to
that type of disorientation.
To some degree that is also what is
symbolized by the turning of the head,
an immediate reorientation to a
completely different level of reality.
Understand? Relax. You're doing fine.
Relax. You're doing fine.
All right.
Thank you. Yes.
Thank you. I have been experiencing
symptoms. Yes.
Yes.
Which are uncomfortable. They're
painful. Oh. All right. List define describe.
Oh. All right. List define describe.
Well, I have pains that I am
experiencing throughout the muscles and
sometimes joints in my body.
Yes. in my legs and my hands and my
wrists. And I feel um symptoms in my
lungs such as out of breath and being
wheezing. Uh I also experience those
pains in the side of my head. I'm
wondering what all these symptoms are
pointing to where they're coming from.
Have you at this timing already availed
yourself of what you simply might call
the diagnosis of your own medical
practitioner? Yes. And
Yes. And
they have not been specific. They think
that it might have something to do with
the immune system.
One more.
How is your diet?
I have changed it and I have become more
aware of what I'm eating so that I'm
eating more whole foods and I'm also on
mega vitamins right now.
One more.
Is there any particular
physiological local you would rather be
in than the one you are in now? Physiological local. Physiological local.
Yes.
Can you explain that a little bit
further? Area on your planet.
Area on your planet.
Would you rather live somewhere other
than where you are living?
I don't think so. But I would like more
peacefulness in my life.
More peacefulness. All right. Define the
idea of more peacefulness.
Less noise.
Noise. Struggle. Less strife.
Struggle. Less strife.
Less strife.
More harmony.
More harmony. All right.
Next is the obvious question.
Are you
are am I living in harmony?
Are you doing what excites you the most?
Yes, I am trying to
trying. Do you have a definition of the idea
Do you have a definition of the idea
that excites you the most?
Learning about yourself.
Learning about yourself. Well, that
comes naturally.
I am talking about outward expression.
Is there anything you want to do in life
that you're not doing?
Is there anything that excites you more
than anything else that you could be
doing in life that you're not doing?
Well, I would like to do more of my
artwork. Artwork?
Artwork?
All right. What type? What style?
Painting. Painting.
Painting.
This excites you?
Yes. A lot.
A lot.
Creating. Yes.
All right. Do you do a lot of it?
Not a lot.
Why not? If that's the most exciting
thing, why do you not do a lot of it?
I am a student that tries to learn about
my own development, about my spiritual
development. Are you saying you cannot paint and
Are you saying you cannot paint and
learn?
I'm learning both at the same time.
All right. But are you painting as often
as you would care to be?
No. Why not?
And when will you?
Because I'm doing other things.
But you said they are not as exciting.
You're right.
Well, then why are you doing them? Why
are you rigidizing
yourself? Why not create some flexibility? Why not
Why not create some flexibility? Why not
loosen up
your joints?
Okay. Are you under the impression that you
Are you under the impression that you
have to be the
student of discipline?
Sometimes I think.
Oh, I see.
Yeah, I think that.
Well, that's a very aging thing.
When will you do more often the thing
you would prefer to do?
As soon as I can,
which will be when?
The day after tomorrow.
Oh, all right.
Begin to express yourself and channel
yourself all ideas, positive and
negative, out into your paintings. All
the things you may imagine to be the
negative things running through your
system. Put them out on your painting.
Channel them through you. Process them
with your painting
and then see how much you lighten up and
how good you feel.
Understand? Yeah.
Yeah.
Would this simple?
I think so. Very definitely. Has this
happened in the past for me where my
paintings have definitely
You have been an artist many times.
Yeah. Well, just more recently, I feel that my
Well, just more recently, I feel that my
artwork has been a way for me to channel
certain energies that were not helpful
to me, but to give them an outlet.
Yes. And that sometimes it was a very
And that sometimes it was a very
positive
Yes. imagery that also fed my system.
imagery that also fed my system.
Yes. Yes. Yes.
Was that part of my guide?
Well, in a sense. In a sense. Yes. There
was involvement. Yes. But again
remember, do not relegate these ideas to
the power of your guide. They are
expressions of your own selfmpowerment.
How else can I help? Is there something
else that I could be doing?
Oh, now she's looking for the exciting
thing. Well, my artwork, is there something
Well, my artwork, is there something
else that can accelerate the
um process of healing within?
Well, you tell me. You have an
imagination. In your imagination, is
there anything else that excites you
more than the artwork?
And that's your answer, isn't it?
Whatever your strongest intention is,
whatever it is that excites you the
most, do it. If something else then
occurs to you, do that. But whatever the
strongest thing that excites you is at
any given moment, that's all you need to
know. Act on it. Act on it. Act on it.
That's the key.
Trust it. Flow with it. Let it support
you. It will effortlessly
let it. The things that excite you the
most are there telling you that they
excite you because they are the things
that can support you the easiest
and can let you express yourself in the
way that you can be of best service not
only to others but to yourself. That's
why these things excite you. Act on
them. They're there to be acted upon
because they represent who you are and
who you chose to be. Don't shun them. Do
not relegate them to a few moments of
your time.
If they are the thing that excites you
the most, express it as often as you
really want to.
All right.
Thank you very much.
Well, thank you very much.
you we have been talking about guides and
we have been talking about guides and
and entities that can help us.
Yes. Are you aware of an order of beings
Are you aware of an order of beings
called the order of the book I believe
are the eagle eagle eye the depths.
I read something about them and I would
like to know if you are aware of their
existence. On one level, yes. But we find that for
On one level, yes. But we find that for
right now there is not very much we
could say about them.
For what reason?
You don't have too much to say about
them. For right now, it seems that our access
For right now, it seems that our access
into information about them does not
immediately serve the timing of this
interaction. We will always impose upon
ourselves inhibitors to information when
that information either does not serve
the immediate timing of the interaction
we are having or in some way, shape or
form would actually create what you
would call an interference in the
process of certain individuals present
within the interaction to reveal the
information too.
So for right now we can perceive the
idea. We can perceive its existence
within the matrix of your collective
consciousness as a world. We can
perceive that they do perceive
themselves to be a fragment of your
consciousness to some degree and that
they do in a sense interact on certain
levels but for now we cannot perceive
but for now we cannot perceive
specifics.
All right. Yes. Are these beings from
the planet Venus?
Not directly. There is an association in
a tangential way in another dimensional
level. Not directly.
Will this do?
Sure. Thank you very much.
you um
um
we have at home some copper various
geometric forms for healing and raising
consciousness. Would you explain to us
in your words how they work?
They are in a sense being conductors,
focuses, lenses for electromagnetic
energy in much the same way that what
you would call a piece of glass focuses
light if it is curved the right way.
There are many such ways you can bend
the electromagnetic field and focus it
and direct it to create certain
vibrational states that can be conducive
to changes within your physiological
form. Making them out of conductive materials
Making them out of conductive materials
such as your copper can aid and assist
in their ability to focus that energy.
Now that your society is also
discovering materials that you call
superconductive, you can accelerate this process many
you can accelerate this process many
many many times over.
Understand? But they are lenses if you will to
But they are lenses if you will to
divert the flow and focus the flow of
the electromagnetic field in ways that
are representative
of the strongest vibration of the
intention that was present in your
imagination when you designed the
device. This was designed by another channel.
This was designed by another channel.
Yes.
So it's the strongest vibration that was
in the mind of the other channel is
present then in these devices
and yours as well because it is a
co-creation. Oh you mean because we have it in our
Oh you mean because we have it in our
home and it reflects the energy level
that we're at as well.
Yes. Of course. So you could not have them.
Of course. So you could not have them.
Oh. So then as we raise our energy
levels then they even become more
effective as well. That also
Yes. And also as you raise your energy level
And also as you raise your energy level
more and more and more as a society, you
will also no longer need as many
physiological manifestations of these
ideas. You will simply be able to direct
the energy yourself.
But they can serve again as catalysts
and triggers for those that are more
physiologically oriented at this time.
Certain shapes, certain ratios are in
your terms mathematical fundamental
constants that do accelerate the focus
and direction of the electromagnetic
energy. Some of these are already expressed in
Some of these are already expressed in
what you call some of the pyramidal
forms around your planet or the natural
crystallin forms that exist within your
world. These ratios are already
representative of the ideal ratios to
direct and focus the electromagnetic
field. And you can create them out of a
number of different materials. And each
will have particular purposes. And
again, copper is
especially good in your terminology to
represent the electromagnetic flow in
ways that are beneficial to some of the
biological alignments necessary in your species.
Well, this excellent. Thank you. Which
one are you?
Female. All right.
All right.
We talked about extraterrestrials.
Yes. It really gives me a face.
It really gives me a face.
Creeps.
Is that another attribute that you give
to insects?
Just get all these scary feelings. Yes,
I understand.
But it's simply because you're not used
to the idea yet.
What is it?
It's your own fears. The fears you have
been taught. The definitions you have
been fed by your society that teach you
to fear the unknown.
What are the hive hive type
extraterrestrials? What are they?
They are your friends.
What do they wish to communicate with
you? They are assisting you in creating
They are assisting you in creating
changes within yourself to assist you in
the things you want to do in life.
So how can I let go of the fear when
they want to contact me? And I mean it
really does frighten me.
Do you remember what we said about the
idea of emotions being reactions to
beliefs? Yes.
Yes.
Do you really believe they will harm
you?
No. That's very exciting.
Do you really believe they will hunger? I guess.
I guess.
All right. Why?
Why do you believe that you might come
to harm?
This is basically what is happening.
The changes that you are being assisted
with are changes that are allowing your
are changes that are allowing your
consciousness to change in ways
that your normal daily ego structure
mind finds panic causing.
Because your normal daily ego structured mind
your normal daily ego structured mind
has been taught that only certain things
and certain perspectives represent
stability and ongoing life.
and ongoing life.
The types of changes you are making now
are completely as you say pulling the
carpet out from under the feet of your
daily ego structured consciousness. It
is panicking because it thinks that the
changes you are making represent its
death. It hasn't learned that that's not
the case.
How do I do that or
mitigate what it's going to
talk to it?
Let it understand it is a part of you
and that any changes you make include it
because you are now learning to function
as a whole idea.
You see,
for many of you, the portion of your
consciousness that you call the ego
structure, and I do not mean this in a
derogatory sense, for the ego's job is
simply that portion of your
consciousness that keeps you focused in
the physical reality you have chosen to
be born into.
But you see, you have given throughout
your recent history, thousands and
thousands of years, your ego structure
an unfair job, an unfair burden.
You have constantly as a society over
and over again told your ego structure,
you're in charge.
You are the one responsible for
everything that happens. You are the one
with the total burden on your shoulders
for what happens in my life.
Don't fail me.
Keep me focused here. This is where I
want to be.
And so now as a society you are changing
your idea of what type of focus you want
in a sense. Therefore, your ego is
interpreting this change as being put
out of a job
because for so long it has been told
that it's in control and now you are
telling it no
you do have a job and you do control the
flow of certain perspectives but the eye
that I am is actually the creator of my
reality and in fact the eye that I am is
actually the creator of the ego.
So the ego in being told now that it has
to not stand out in a solitary fashion
but now can come back home and blend
with the rest of your consciousness only
has one way to interpret this at first.
I'm being fired. I'm being killed. I'm
dying. I have no purpose anymore.
That creates the panic you are feeling.
So if you can remind it, no, no, no, no,
no. I'm redefining your job.
And now you don't have to do it alone.
Now you've got friends, the rest of me,
to share the idea of creating my reality
with you. Oh dear and loving ego, thank
you, ego, for having stood at the pillar
of my uncertainty for so long.
Thank you for having stood the lonely
vigil for so long.
Now you don't have to take the full
responsibility. It doesn't have to be a
burden to you anymore. Now you have the
support of the rest of me. You're not
dying. You're being promoted.
You're now finally coming fully alive.
You're not cut off from the rest of me
anymore. That's what you tell it and that will
That's what you tell it and that will
soothe its panic and that will give it
joy and then you will understand the
following thing.
Your panic, your fear, your anxiety is
simply the negative pole of your joy and
your ecstasy because excitement and
anxiety are the same energy. One from a
positive and trusting point of view and
one from a fearful and doubtful point of
view. Trust yourself. Trust them. You made
Trust yourself. Trust them. You made
this agreement.
You know what you're doing, but now
you're doing it as more of you. You are
not allowing yourself to remain as a
collection of parts.
So simply allow your ego to know all
you're doing is bringing it home. You're
not killing it off.
Understand? Or pleasant dreams on that level. You
You
is it possible that
you are channeling you are one of
Daryl's present or past lives
in your terms future
or future
but again simultaneous
okay rather than being from a
civilization or is there a difference
now I am a being from another civilization
I am a being from another civilization
and I am at the same time a future life
of the channel we are aspects of the
same oversoul consciousness.
So in our in our terms then are you one
of Daryl's lives in a sense? Yes, you
can look at it linearly. At the same
time, there are other connections that
make it seem as if I am not connected at
all. In other words, the channel has had
many lives on your planet,
but he is the only one I have had on
your planet. I have had many lies on my
planet that are in your terms separate and
that are in your terms separate and
distinct from the lives he has had. And
yet he is one of my past lives where we
junction at that one point that
represents the service we agree to do
with each other.
If this making any sense,
a quick question. Yes. Could you uh
again in our physical terms define your
beings how they look like in our
language and also give us an example of
some of your speech if you still use
that. We do not use it but I can give you some
We do not use it but I can give you some
examples. We are now telepathic and it
is an ancient language to us. We are of
average 5t of your height white whitish
gray skin coloration very wide upturned
eyes not exactly like your friends.
The idea will be similar. The males have
no hair. The females have hair, usually
tending to white, although there are
exceptions. If you wish any kind of a
similar representation to a racial type
you are familiar with, you would
probably classify us as something akin
to Mongolian, but it is not exact at
all. We are humanoid, not human. In your
terms, the idea is that we will be very
slender. We will be relatively small of mouth,
We will be relatively small of mouth,
small of nose, small of ear, relatively
slender. The head will be slightly very
slightly more enlarged in ratio than the
size of your own head to your body.
The idea primarily is that we are now in
our transformation going from a fourth
density physiological state which is
what you are going into
to a fifth density non-physical state
entirely. That is our transformation.
And we are assisting ourselves by
assisting you in going through your
transformation from a third density
state to a fourth density state similar
to what we have existed as for what you
would call several thousands of your
years. Our planet is not too dissimilar
from your own in the sense that with a
very slight adjustment you would be
comfortable there. It is very green and
parklike in that sense. There are no
major structures built up about our
world as you call your city. At any
given moment, the majority of our
population exists in a different type of
city, our spacecraft. For many of them,
in your terms, are many miles in length
and carry many tens of thousands of
individuals. And it is within these that
we do much of our exploring for now.
The idea simply is is that also our
planet is a very temperate climate.
There are no wide range of seasons upon
our world. There is a lot of ocean and
not as much land as your own world
possesses.
In what you would call our ancient
language, the name of the people is Casani which
the name of the people is Casani which
means living life and the place the
planet itself
place of living life.
In this way, we have emerged from the
ancient language into a telepathic race
because of our unconditional love for
each other. Because when you express
unconditional love, you begin to operate
on the same frequency as everyone else
around you. And you can know the same
thoughts that they know because you are
creating the same thoughts they are
creating, not because you are literally
reading each other's minds. That is why
individuals on your planet that you call
lovers or individuals in love seem very
often more often than not to know each
other's thoughts. It is because they are
in love and matching their frequency
in what you call a remnant language.
Allow us once again a small sample.
There will be two two
shimmy
kashimi gets row shim.
That is 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10
chari
kashimi row shim.
There are phrases that we have shared
from time to time with your
civilization. A primary one being
which basically means I love you.
Although it more literally represents
this statement,
the mirror of the infinite in me
reflected in the mirror of the infinite
in you.
Sa as in society
is the primary form of the word that
means life. Sha means the exalted form
of light, the creation light. And that
is why our central sun, our star is
called sha rather than sa which is
simply the fundamental form of light out
of which everything else is created.
Will this do as a language lesson for
now?
There will be in your terms of counting
but a few moments remaining for this
interaction this evening of your time.
Allow us at this time to remind each and
every one of you individually and
collectively that conviction is the key.
that conviction is the key.
conviction to the things you know excite
you the most will always serve you.
Remember remember remember it is not a
matter of having to use more conviction
than you have ever used. It is not a
matter of having to learn to do
something you have never done. It is not
a matter of learning how to trust when
you have never done it before. You have
always had ultimate conviction, infinite
trust. It is simply a matter of choosing
the definitions
that you prefer to have conviction
about. When you give them the same conviction
When you give them the same conviction
you have always given any definition,
you will get the result of that
conviction. Remember, all circumstances
and all situations in life are
fundamentally neutral and do not have
builtin meaning.
You give them the meaning you have been
taught to give them. Positive meaning
in, positive effect out, negative
meaning in, negative effect out. It is
simple physics.
We thank you for the creation of this
interaction, for the creation of this
dream. And we remind you that you are in
fact dreaming right now. So wake up and
live the dream you prefer to. You might
as well. It's your choice. And you have
the ability to choose.
Once you decide,
then that sticks until you decide
differently. The decisions you make
The decisions you make
do not have a mind of their own to
change against your choice. If they
change, you have changed them.
Bring what you call your unconscious
beliefs to the conscious surface
and choose with your eyes open the way
you prefer. That's all it takes. You are
made in the image of the infinite. You
are multi-dimensional creators.
Act like it.
We thank you. Our love to you for
remember this. No matter what you choose
to think of yourselves, we always will
believe in you.
But the important thing is whether you
believe in yourself.
That's what will change your world.
Our love and the bond with them.
Let it go.