s good day to you this day of your time
as you create time to exist how are you
all this day of your
time allow us to begin this interaction
in the following
manner first a statement of the purpose
of the
interaction the idea that each and every
one of you being an aspect of creation
being an aspect of all that is are also
Co creators have that spark that desire
that drive that momentum within each and
every one of you that seeks to go from
within to being manifested as you say
externally in your physiological reality
so that you see as you say the fruits of
your labor
the idea is to First understand that
what we will be discussing
today though the words though the
technique may be somewhat new to your
ears maybe
not the mechanism itself of creation is
very second nature to you very natural
we will not be teaching you a new
mechanism per
se what we will be discussing our ways
to realize to rec recognize the
mechanism that you already use all the
time automatically so automatically that
you have been able to create the ability
to forget that you're using it because
it is so smooth operates so
automatically you do it all the
time to understand how you do it all the
time let us lay a little bit more of a
foundation about what it means to exist
in physical
reality now you all have begun to
understand as a
civilization that you generally speak of
physical reality as meaning the solid
matter that which is perceivable by your
physiological senses that which you call hard to the
senses that which you call hard to the
touch or discernable to your conscious
outer aware
mind but you also know
now through your own discoveries that
matter and energy are
synonymous are in a sense manifestations
of what you may call a primal energy of
some sort a primal idea a matrix a
template and this template gives rise to
the concepts of M and
energ I would like you to consider a new
defition definition of matter a new
definition of solid
reality are you paying attention oh all
right just
checking matter is a
matter is a
behavior it is a behavior of creation
that is all a
behavior he's not immutable he's not
unchangeable he's not EX in stone as you
say it is a behavior it is an idea it is
a
notion it is a
circumstance a collection of
circumstances that meet at a particular
point and as they
cross they reinforce each other these
Notions and as they reinforce each other
in a particular
way you then perceive them as immutable
matter but it is simply a
behavior of the universe that is
all now you each and every one of you as
a personality you know you each have a
behavior a style of presentation a
Persona construct there really isn't as much
construct there really isn't as much
difference as you might think between
what you might call a personality
behavior and material Behavior
because both the personality Behavior
and the material Behavior stem from the
same template that which is called
Consciousness itself
itself
Consciousness that which you label
Consciousness is the very fabric of
existence itself that is the prime
template out of which energy and matter
and personality are built are
constructed out of various conceptual
components arranged in various ways and then
arranged in various ways and then
perceived and
reflected as it is
arranged but it can be
rearranged you rearrange it all the time because
because
matter in a sense physical reality is
created only
as a
reflection of the behavior of the ideas
of the
Notions out of which your personality is
constructed to put it
simply what you are is what you
get this is the only basic law of
creation what you put out is what you
get back back
everything is
vibration of of the template of the
Consciousness various
frequencies because there is this
frequency and because there is that
frequency you get what you call two
different situations two different
circumstances or if you wish two
different objects in space
time which is also simply a
concept now we do not mean to imply that
these concepts are not real we simply
are saying that that is what reality is
it is substantial when you create it to
be it is very solid and substantial when
substantiality is one of the components
of the model of the
notion but when you begin to
redefine the concept of
substantiality of permanence of momentum
of inertia of continuance when you
redefine that idea recognizing that it
was a definition only to begin with you
can begin at whatever Pace you are
comfortable with you can begin to see
what was here to for considered to be
the solid unchangeable physical reality
begin to shall we say dissolve a little
bit soften a little bit concepts of
space time materiality energy shift a
little bit become
interchangeable a little bit remember
remember it is one of the primary
tenants even of your own physics that
matter and energy in that sense are
inter shiftable that space and time are
interchangeable that they are all simply
different manifestations of one primary
concept therefore it means any of them
can dissolve back into that primary
dissolve back into that primary
Consciousness that primary concept
anytime at all the only reason you see
continuance in your physical
reality one moment to the next moment
inertia day today is because you create
the idea the concept of automatic
continuance it is a
definition that is all it is a
definition but but but but big but that
is how strong your definitions
are as soon as you believe in that
definition as soon as there is no other
choice for you that's the reality you
get instantly no lag time none
zero so quickly does it manifest before
you around you within you of you from
you that it seems to be not of your
doing it is such an automatic function
it seems to be coming from somewhere
else therefore you have been able to
create the
notion you have been able to believe the
illusion that you exist in a universe
which surrounds you and that things
happen to you in life instead of
understanding that what you see around
you is simply a metaphor for what you
believe within
you and instead of saying that things
happen to you you can understand that
things happen from
you now many times in your reality
you see manifestations that well you
don't particularly care
for we are not implying that these
things come from you so that you will
say well then I must be a rotten
scoundrel I must be a terrible Creator I
must be a very bad manifestor I must be
a wicked person to manifest these things
I don't want if they come from me if I
responsible for creating them what does
that say about me all
right we are not bringing this idea up
so that you should blame yourself in
that way because the idea of judgment is
still the idea of more
separation more ideas of guilt create
more time more space more
details the
idea is to take it as your
responsibility but not as your blame in
that sense to understand that if you are
creating everything even the things you
don't prefer that that gives you the
clue that the reason you might be
creating things you don't prefer is
simply because of definitions you have
been taught about what you think that
thing ought to
be and in seeing it manifest in your
life and in knowing that you do not
prefer it to be that way you can then
with a new understanding we are
discussing today take it a step back and
say all right this must be from a
manifestation of a belief of an idea of
a notion of a
template that I no longer prefer maybe I
bought into it once maybe because I
needed to to survive perhaps maybe I had
to believe as this person believed maybe
as a child I had to believe as my
parents believe because they were
responsible for feeding me and if I
didn't believe like they did they would
have kicked me out I would have died I
had to rely upon them for sustenance and
support and so telepathically I had to
buy into that family idea that unit that
neighborhood that City that state that
country that
notion now we are not necessarily saying
that you will give all of these up that
you will change them all all these
Notions but you may find that along the
way you picked up a few bags that aren't
necessarily your style anymore aren't
necessarily your exact shade aren't your
your preference don't hold the things
you prefer to have them
hold this is because
now your
Society has allowed you to get to a
point in your life where they finally
tell you well all right I am sick and
tired of you get out and make your own
life learn how to do things for yourself
and yet all that while up to that point
sometimes almost to the very second they
were saying no no no rely on me I will
take care of you and then all of a
sudden you say oh no no no get out I
can't take care of you anymore you're on
your own but there is in many cases no
own but there is in many cases no
preparation no understanding that you
have the power the true power to take
any of the beliefs that they have given
you and rearrange them in ways that beit
you the idea that is you the person that
is you the person that is no longer just
a reflection of your parents no longer
just a reflection of your friends but
you and that is why many of you
all throughout your Society all
throughout many different times arrive
at a point in life which to us and I do
not say this in your terms to put you
down but which to us is inconceivable
not that we know everything but this
state of mind most mysterious to us that
you as a civilization have so many
members that could arrive at a point in
life where you actually have to stop and
look around and say who am I I don't
know where am I I don't know what do I
want I I don't
know these things to us are most
mysterious that you could ever arrive at
a point where you would ask yourself
such things perhaps in our civilization
there are many things we discover that
are new about ourselves perhaps we
surprise ourselves by ideas that we did
not here to for think
about but we always
know not necessarily in specific
definition but in general definition who
we are as far
we are aspects of the universe we are
reflections of the infinite we are who
we wish to
be so all that leaves is answering the
question who who do you wish to be what
do you wish to
be now there is a very simple way to
find out we have discussed this many
times with many of you we never Tire of
discussing it because it is a most
exciting concept it is the concept of
excitement itself many of you ask well all right
itself many of you ask well all right
how do I know who I am how do I know
what it is I'm all about why I'm here
what my purpose is how do I know these
things if I have been fed a diet of
ideas that is not me how can I discover
who I really am without a long involved
Journey or
process all right fair enough very
simple at any time at any time anywhere
all you need to do is sit yourself down
or stand up however you're
comfortable ask yourself with honesty
with Clarity and please with
Clarity and please with
relaxation ask
yourself what in my
imagination is the most exciting thing I
could think of to do what is it in life
that excites me the most either
immediately right now or if you wish as
a longer strange project doesn't really
matter whichever is more honest for you
what is it that excites me the most what
makes me
tingle what gives me strong emotional
desire yes yes this is it yes that's
what I
want what is it that gives you that
feeling of all if only I could do this I
would be the happiest person
alive find that
is simple because if you pay attention
to the feeling
itself as you scan through the library
of possible
realities one of them or a few of them
will hit you with that feeling you'll
feel the
twinge you feel the excitement as you
call them in your world the
butterflies now you may have many
reactions at this point some of you may
even turn away from it oh no no no I
could never do
that but that's not possible for little
me I'm not qualified I'm not experienced
enough I'm no good at that I'm not
creative enough I really don't have the
imagination for that that's very
childish I would be a very childish
person if I did that I have to be
responsible and act
responsible I have
obligations I have duties to perform and
this would take me away from that
everyone knows I wouldn't be living a real life
knows I wouldn't be living a real life
if I did
that you can't make money at
that that doesn't support
you how dare you have an idea to do this
when you're supposed to be supporting
your family how dare you be so frivolous
how dare you be so
unthoughtful how dare you I'll tell you
how you dare you dare because you know
this that whatever it is in life that
does excite you that
much is the signal from the universe is
the message from the universe that
that's who you are that's what you're
all about that's what will support
you many of you when you get to that
point who am
I you ask for signs you ask for help you
ask for
signals but you always get an
answer it's up to you as to whether or
not you have been taught to ignore the
answer a lot of of you ignore the answer
the answer always is what excites you
the most because excitement what you
call that feeling of
excitement is your physical Attunement
your physical alignment to the concept
that represents your highest
ideal if you align yourself and follow
that excitement you will be fulfilling
your purpose in life at that moment if
it changes follow it flow with it no one
says it has to be a static thing change
is the only constant in creation go with
it that's
stability moving is stable attending to
stay in one place all the time on one
foot that's when you fall over movement
is
stable movement is
balance balance is
movement now many of you are under the
assumption that equilibrium means you
just stay in one
spot equilibrium is being everywhere
equilibrium is being everywhere
equally is being balanced As you move as
you create the idea of creation within
you as you expand as you flow as you
grow you follow that thread of
excitement and it is connected all the
way all the way through your life and in
many cases beyond your physical life
excitement is the path you're all
looking for whatever it is in your
particular life that really motivates
you at any given moment with
Integrity act on
it let me digress for a
moment because there's a very fine line
in your Society between the idea of
finding something that excites
you and doing something from nervous eny
energy many of you interpret anxiety as
excitement it is a simple thing to do
because anxiety and excitement are the
same energy but one from a positive
point of view one from a negative point
of view it's the manifestation of the
polarity of the same idea the same
concept excitement
anxiousness many of you will do things
from anxiety and call it excitement oh
I'm very busy busy busy busy busy very
busy yes you see I'm very busy doing
what is I want to do very busy it keeps
me very busy all the
time when in fact what you're saying is
it keeps me so busy I can't really look
at the fact that I'm afraid that I can't
really do what it is that really excites
me the idea is to people watch on
yourself in that way not too hard not
too severe but to be honest with
yourself as to whether what you're doing
is from
anxiety that you are running from
something else or whether it is
excitement that you are flowing it
through you in an
manner when you function in an
integrated manner you realize a very
important Point very important perhaps
one of the most critical of
all every single person every single
individual is already as powerful as he
or she needs to be to create anything
they desire in life without having to
hurt anyone else or themselves in order
to create it that's how powerful you
are honest you are that powerful
everyone is because everyone is a
reflection of the
infinite all right some of these terms
they may not feel familiar
but the idea simply is to understand
that when you function in an integrated
manner when you know you are already a
whole idea not that you will not learn
not that you will not grow but you are
at any given moment a whole idea
anyway you can move on things act on
things do things without
worrying about whether it is the right
thing for you to do as long as you
understand that you are doing the best
you can in in the most integrated way
you can and the thing that excites you
the most of all you are doing everything
you can do and everything you are
supposed to be doing to get you to the
next place keep it simple it doesn't
need to be
complicated not at
all for the purpose of this Workshop we
will break it down a little bit
further step by step so that you can
understand how to take
yourself from a place you do not prefer
to be to a place that you
do there
are basically basically three overall areas
basically basically three overall areas
three basic functions three basic steps
that are
involved the first one has to do with
definitions and
beliefs the second has to do with em
emotional connections and the third has
to do with physical
activity that
Trinity when balanced in equilibrium
will allow you to be a Gateway through
which anything you desire will manifest
very rapidly very clearly clearly
now first
idea definitions and
beliefs before we proceed is everyone
clear so far about what we are
doing definitions and
belief what are they they are
words they are
Concepts they can be very
multi-leveled sometimes one belief will
ride as you say horseback on another
belief and you do not even know that it
has come along for the
ride it is there because you have been
taught to believe that it must be there
that this must go hand in hand with that
and therefore no matter how many times
sometimes you attempt to do this you
also always get that and sometimes this
is what is responsible for what you call
blocks now there really are no blocks
none zero you are never blocked because
you are always creating
something you're always creating there
is never a void a true void in creation
you already know nature does not allow a
vacuum in that
sense so you kind of create the illusion
that you're not getting anywhere you can
create the illusion that you're not in
touch with yourself but you are still
creating that scenario and that is a
very creative thing to do so first and
foremost let's shall we say dissolve the
primary block what you would call The
Catch 22 block and that is many of you
when you catch yourselves blocking will
block yourselves even further by be
waiting yourself for being blocked to
begin with oh no I now find I have a terrible
with oh no I now find I have a terrible
big block that must mean that I am
simply the kind of person who ought to
be blocked who has been blocked forever
I've wasted a lot of time being blocked
on and on and on and on all the ideas
that keep you from looking at the idea
you call the block all the ideas that
keep you rotating right in front of the
idea called The Block but keeps you
afraid to go into it or if I examine why
I'm blocked I'll probably find out that
what I've believed all along is true
that I'm worthless and I can't do
anything anyway and that's probably why
I'm
blocked if you were truly worthless you
wouldn't exist because creation creates no
exist because creation creates no
worthless things no pointless things
there are no extraneous Creations
anywhere if you exist you belong you fit
a part of the overall scenario you
cannot exist if you
don't therefore first and foremost be
kind to yourself be nice to yourself
treat yourself with respect you deserve
it
and you don't have to say well all right
I'll treat myself with respect because
Bashar said I deserve it I believe
Bashar I do not want you to believe
me I do not want you to believe one
thing I say if you don't choose to
believe it for
yourself if your beliefs and my belief
coincide that's because you choose to
believe that what I believe happens to
work for you as well not because I said
so not because I said you deserve it but
because you say you deserve it it won't
St unless you say it anyway I can say it
all day long you deserve it you deserve
it you deserve it until you believe it
my words are simply
words now I may feel greatly very
strongly about the fact that you deserve
and I do as a matter of fact it's more
than a belief I know you deserve it
beyond the shadow of a doubt I have no
doubt in my mind you deserve anything at
all but again until you believe it you
won't see see it so the idea is to first
of all give yourself as you say a break
please give yourself a rest from the
cycle of hitting yourself over the
head now when you come up with what you
think is a
block allow yourself without fear
therefore to dive into it to explore it
see it as an opportunity
before we continue I would like to
remind you of something very critical as
we discuss these ideas because of the
upbringing that many of you have had you
will hear these words as
philosophy well it's a nice philosophy
it's a nice attitude those are nice
things he's saying too bad they're not
really indicative of the real
world I wonder what he means by how you
actually go about doing these things all
he's doing is talking about nice
Concepts about exploring about not being
afraid well all right that would be nice
I'd like to have the attitude but having
that attitude doesn't mean that that
block is not to be feared what I would
like you to understand is that every
single thing I am saying as far as my
civilization is concerned is an actual
physical concept a mechanical concept
because again remember the vibration you
are is what you get back
attitude is
everything everything Whatever frequency you give
everything Whatever frequency you give
off that's what you see in the
mirror that's what you get reflected
back to you therefore when I say all
right see that idea and treat it not as
a block not as a fear but as an
opportunity I am not just using that
word lightly I mean it in every sense of
the term it is your gateway it is your
door way to learn more about yourself
and to get closer to what you want the
more you turn away from the idea of that
block the more you are afraid to explore
what is in there the farther away you
take yourself from what you really want
those things are given to you by
yourself so that when you explore them
you discover more of who and what you
are because if you think about it
logically as you say only by being more
of who and what you are will you be the
kind of person who will be able to do
that thing you say you want to do if
you're not acting like that person you
can't be that reality and we'll get to
that later but first of
later but first of
all again seize that idea as an
opportunity rather than
reacting act div in oh goody a block an
act div in oh goody a block an
opportunity oh goody I'm going going to
discover something new about myself now
all right all
right first state definitions
definitions now as we're going along
with this all of you as part of the
meditation as part of this exercise get
something personal in your life and use
that as we go along there will be time
enough and if there isn't time now there
will be time later on your own time but
use it as an example have an example now
of something you feel is blocking you of
a concept you feel that represents the
opposite of what you want that you feel
is a block that you feel you can't get
past can't get around can't get over it
can't get under it can't get through
it and look at the definition of what it
is Define what it
is it is this it is I haven't got enough
of that it's I have too much of this
it's I'm not getting any help here I
have too much help here I don't have
peace and quiet I don't have enough
noise whatever it is Define the main
idea you would perceive as a
block that of course assumes that you
have already decided on what it is that
you would like to do then again just to
help you when I say find the thing you
would really like to do most the thing
that excites you the most I don't
necessarily mean you have to have a
lifelong project in mind I just mean the
next thing you would like to really do
really excitingly Moment by
excitingly Moment by
moment if you feel that in any way shape
or form you are blocked from that then
Define that block now see it before you
now understand again that all you are
doing is discovering parts of yourself
because you as a society in being so
physically oriented have fragmented
yourself into pieces you're not
functioning as a whole whole
being therefore as
therefore as
you go along this path of self-discovery
what you're doing is picking up the
pieces pulling them back together
pulling yourself together so to speak
literally your Consciousness has been
fragmented now when you find what you
desire most that's the beacon to get
back to your centered self your God
child self in a sense for your
civilization colloquially speaking when
you figure out what it is that excites
you the most and you go for it you're
actually going quote unquote back to
your original state yes you're
progressing ahead but you're actually
going back to your original state your
natural state of Creator Hood so as you
go back to your original state you find
all the pieces you left scattered on the
path as you were growing up all the
fragmented beliefs all the ideals that
were beat out of you and you pick them
up and you examine them now sometimes
the reason when you find a piece you are
afraid look at it or it appears as a
block is because as we said many of the
beliefs you have been brought up with
many of the things that made you drop
that piece of yourself to begin with
sometimes comes with little Catch 22
beliefs riding
along such as if you pick that up you'll
be
sorry if you pick that up you might find
you really can't do it and then you'll
be a
failure if you pick that up and you do
this then you have to act this way too
and you know you don't want to act that
way too if you pick that up if if if if
if allow yourself when you are creating
a definition of what this piece is this
block is allow yourself to recognize all
the beliefs within it don't just allow
yourself to lump it all into one thing
see it for all the different ideas that
it is look at it from all different
points of view as an example we have
used this many times because we know
many of you are focused in this area
what you call abundance what you call
being rich physically
wealthy many of you oh yes yes yes you
say I would love to be rich I would love
to be abundant infinitely abundant
staggeringly wealthy all right that's fair it is a
wealthy all right that's fair it is a
way to be however beliefs that hit your
ride onto things like that that
sometimes you think are all one belief
but AR are beliefs such as yes but to be
staggeringly wealthy you have to stomp
on everyone in your path and I don't
want to do that many of you think that's
one belief to be wealthy is to be
inconsiderate many of you think that
automatically because that's the way you
were taught many of these beliefs in
your terms may be unconscious may be
subconscious but as you grew up you have
been shown examples sometimes physically
sometimes telepathically
see that Sunny see that daughter that
man over there he's stunningly rich but
you know what he has walked over so many
people to get there that no one likes
him anymore maybe he doesn't care he's so
anymore maybe he doesn't care he's so
rich I don't
know that made an impression on you
somewhere and then you may have
forgotten the incident but then
somewhere down the line when you are
attempting to be an adult and you say
well now
an adult thing to do or to be to be
staggeringly wealthy and somewhere in
the mind it goes yes but how many people
do you have to walk over to get
there and you don't even hear it
necessarily because it's buried so deep
but something in you
twists and something in you holds you
back from knowing you can be
staggeringly wealthy because ideally you
don't want to walk on anyone ideally you
think I'm a nice person I don't want to
do that if that's the only way I can be
rich I don't want to be rich so all the
opportunities for being wealthy stay
away because I'd Rather Be
Loved You may be telling yourself these
things all the time and not hearing them
that is why it is very important in
quiet relaxed silent
personal thought and meditation to get
honestly very honestly in touch with
what you really believe about this or
that what are your absolute
what are your absolute
definitions play the game it's all right
it is a game have fun with
it don't berate yourself for discovering
that you may believe a certain way that
you find distasteful or non-
preferential it doesn't have to be the
way you are but simply accept that it
may be the way you are now if you don't
prefer it then you can change it but how
are you going to change it unless you
are allow yourself to discover that
right now you believe that way unless
you take responsibility for it right
now there's no way you can change it
into what you prefer it to be because
you cannot change what you do not
own if you shy away from that
exploration no no no I don't want to
find out I don't want to find out that I
might think I'm a rotten person for
believing this I don't want to find out
that I have to walk over a million
people to be rich that's not an absolute
but you may believe it is that might be
another belief that's riding along that
you can't change the belief that that's
the way it
is all right now you found out okay you
want to be staggering wealthy now you
found out that you have a belief that
says you have to walk over a million
people to get there and now you also
found out you have another belief that
says you can't change that
belief you are not yet reaching true
foundational reality they are still
beliefs but they seem so grounded to you
so fundamental to many of you that you
don't even question them you say yes
that's the way it is I look around and I
see that all the people that have become
staggeringly wealthy they've all stepped
on everyone to get there I see that
reinforced again and again and again and
again of course that's the way it is
look around you everyone who's Rich has
been that
way but you see what you are forgetting
is
this and every
belief by definition in order to be
experienced as real has to be self
perpetuating has to be
self-reinforcing so anything you believe
is going to radiate out and is going to
attract examples into your life that
reinforce the belief you have so that
that is all you will
see of course you only see rich people
who walk in other people because that's
the way you believe it must be therefore
that's your reality therefore that's
what's reinforced so that you can
perpetuate that reality
or or and here is the doorway through
or instead of reacting as we said to
that reinforcement to that
reflection you can say
or I am being shown all these rich
people who have stepped on everyone else
simply to reflect to me that that is the
way I believe rich people must be
doesn't mean that's the way it is it
means that's the way I believe it must
be now wait a minute if that is simply
the way I believe it must be how would I
prefer to believe it is ah so now I can
see that instead of seeing all this
reflection as an indication that I am
stuck in that
reality it's now a reflection of
opportunity it is an option now now I am
being shown what I do believe so that if
I want to I can decide to believe
something else because now I'm aware of
what I do believe because I can't change
it if I don't know what I believed
before so what you
see in your reality around you day to
day everyday occurrences all the things
that happen to you what you see around
you are opportunities being offered to
you constantly this is a belief this is
a scenario this is what you now hold to
be true do you like it do you want to
change it do you want to keep it the way
it
is because you have been taught for so
long that physical reality is immutable
when you are usually presented with an
idea like that you don't even question
that it can really be changed on a
fundamental level and you accept it and you find
level and you accept it and you find
ways to settle with
it to settle for something that is not
you to settle for
less well all right if I can't have it
that way that's the way it is I guess
I'll have to settle for this maybe I'll
just be moderately
wealthy maybe I'll just keep struggling
to be
wealthy maybe there's a chance I might
get wealthy but well you know the
odds are
overwhelming you will justify these
ideas in any way shape or form you have
to
to prevent yourself from feeling badly
that you believe it can't be
changed don't believe it can't be
changed that's where you settle for
less when you believe that you have to
because it can't be
changed because you are dealing with
fundamentals and you can't change those
there is only one fundamental in
creation just one wasn't that simple of
the creator wasn't that nice of the
Creator the Creator said all right there
will only be one law not 10 not 50 not a
th000 one and it will be the same law
for everybody wasn't that fair wasn't that
everybody wasn't that fair wasn't that
simple wasn't that nice how much of a
head start do you
want there is only one idea and it isn't
even really what you might call in your
classical a law it is the structure of
existence itself simply put it is what
you put out is what you get back that's
it that's all there is to it that's all
there is to Creation what you put out is
what you get back what you put out
depends on your definition of who you
think you
are so who do you think you are who do you
so who do you think you are who do you
believe you are and sometimes you get
that as a negative too who do you think
you
will accept it as an opportunity to
answer well I think I'm a wonderful
creative being who can have anything he
or she wants that's who I think I am who
do you think you
are oh well that's just nonsense how
childish or grow up join the real world
get a clue wake up smell coffee and all
that all right all right fair enough
remember remember that in responding to
other individuals as well
we're not saying that because you may
find that your preferential beliefs are
different from theirs that you should be
r or be little theirs because in doing
so that puts you right back on the same
vibration that you want to get out of
remember your biblical phrase judge not
lest ye be judged doesn't mean you're
being judged from outside it means as
you judge others you become the
vibration of judgment as you become the
vibration of judgment you go to that
realm of judgment and as you are in the
realm of judgment all you can receive is
Judgment against you it's a reflection
it's simple physics simple mechanics
what you put out is what you get back
judge others you get
judged keep it
simple so definitions definitions is the
first step what is it you do believe
about this or that find out what excites
you the most and take some time to find
out what you believe are all the aspects
you can imagine of that thing that you
say excites you
you may find sometimes again that if you
chose the idea from anxiety you may find
that when you do examine all the things
you do believe about what excites you
that you may actually have chosen it
from anxiety rather than excitement you
may find that you're not willing to
really believe in this you're not
willing to really be persistent about
having this thing because maybe this
thing isn't really what you're all about
or maybe it is and maybe the whole issue
of why you're not willing to believe in
it and be persistent is the thing you
need to examine but that's up to
you theoretically you will find out what
it is by examining your definitions of
Life all the definitions are your own
regardless of how many of them your
society says are shared by so many other
people so it must be true for everyone
you do have Collective Realties yes but
you agree to have Collective realities
telepathically all right all right I'll
say there's a chair in the room and
you'll say there's a chair in the room
because we both want to agree that when
I'm at rest I will appear to be sitting
in what you call a chair it's convenient
it's automatic it's a definition it's a
symbol that we can both use maybe my
chair is a little bit different than
your chair it doesn't matter we both
agree enough so that we can get along in
one particular idea envelope or bubble
but remember there are literally as many
chairs in the room as there actually are
people in terms of a whole set in other
words you have your chair but you are
also creating everyone else's chair your
version of everyone else in that chair
your version of the room every one of
you so how many people there are that's
how many rooms there are and how many
versions of all the chairs there are
overlapping and
intertwining agreeing with each other on
enough points so that you can have what
you call a common experience
a common experience is simply playing by
the same rules of a particular game at
one particular moment individuals that
do not agree to share common experience
with you or at least not very much
common experience with you you call
insane they see things you
don't and sometimes you see things they
don't it doesn't mean that what they are
perceiving is less real it means that
they are choosing with a higher
percentage rate to see another
definition of reality than the one you
massively agree
upon now get in touch with your
definition understand that when you do
see the thing that excites you the most
that is the signal for who and what you
are Define the reality you prefer how
would you like your reality to be if it
isn't this definition the one you don't
prefer create the definition you do
prefer this is the two step of the
defining process part one A and B Define
the reality you have Define the reality
you want
now this does not necessarily mean that
you have to spend the next 200 years
defining the reality you want before you
do something about it that's another
fear mechanism to stay in your
estimation beyond the necessary time to
continue to break it down into further
and further analytical definitions never
really doing anything about it because
once again it gives you busy work to do
gives you something to do and you think
you're doing it but it's actually
keeping you from doing it it keeps you
thinking about doing it but it keeps you
from doing it because again you may have
another belief that says if you ever
ever ever ever got around actually doing
it you might fail you might not succeed
you don't ever have to have that belief
if once again you
remember whatever it is that excites you
the most is who you are you can't fail
at being you it is the one thing you
can't help but
be where you quote unquote
fail is when you try to be everyone else
thinking that this being everyone else
is actually being you because of what
you have been taught to believe you
ought to
be you should do this you should do
that then that at some point in your
mind may be who you think you are if I'm
not doing this I'm not being me I'm not
being the person I'm supposed to be
you this does not mean you have to be
selfish does not mean you have to turn
to other people say I don't care about
you I'm only concerned about me that's
not what I'm
saying because when paradoxically enough
this is the beauty of creation Paradox
the beauty of creation you know you're
dealing with your higher self when
you're dealing with
Paradox when you are most completely
yourself that's when you can help other
people that's when you can really care
that's when you can really love really
have compassion really be of assistance
how can you be of compassion how can you
be of assistance how can you really love
when you do not allow yourself to be
you who will there be to love if you are
not complete enough in your own mind to
do the
loving so paradoxically being absolutely
complete for yourself means you will be
able to
effortlessly be there for all other
people and help them be complete as well
now everyone is complete but you have a
notion that you're
not and many times you put it on to
other people other circumstances beyond
your reach and imagine that until you have
reach and imagine that until you have
those circumstances you are not
complete it is just the other way around
when you know you are complete and you
act like you're complete you have those
circumstances because that's who you are
and that's what gets attracted to
you this ties into the idea of the
second and the third portions of
emotional identification and physical
activity now before we go on to the
second part each and every one of you
become as relaxed as you can be
comfortable position close your
eyes and take three deep
breaths and no just no no matter whether
your mind remains chattering or not it
doesn't matter your style is your own
release all of the ideas that you have
to do it this way or you have to do it
that way you will do it correctly for
you just know beyond the Shadow it out
now that as you take these breath keep
breathing deeply slowly let it out take
it
in feel it for what it is feel the
breathing itself for what it is it
doesn't have to have any other purpose
just feel
it and simply allow allow not make not
force allow yourself to know right now
that as you
breathe you are breathing out the old
definitions and you are breathing in the
new definitions those that are far more
definitions those that are far more
representative of who you prefer to be
the old definitions going out that are
representative of who you do not prefer
to
be without judgment they served you in
the past you do not need the old
definitions now but they did serve
you they are still a part of you you're
not getting rid of them you are simply
letting them know their job is
changing and now their new definition is
to turn in the direction of who you
prefer to
be who you prefer to
be and as a segue from the section where
we Define our beliefs to the section
where we emotionally identify
remain in the meditative State and begin
now to actually visualize to see the old
you and see the old you dissolving or
coming apart or disassociating or
breaking down and see a new you with every breath
down and see a new you with every breath
in building up
crystallizing clear and
bright transparent brilliant
transparent brilliant
white light see the new you see now a
picture a picture of the you you want to
be doing the things you say are the
things that would excite you more than
anything else to do see yourself doing
them see
it take a moment and just play a
scenario out if you wish if it makes it
easier as if you are watching a stage
play see you on the stage then new you
on the stage going about a day in the
life of the new you what are the kinds
of things the new you is
doing pay attention if you catch
yourself doing things that the old you
did correct the play rewrite the line if
you said it the way you didn't want to
say it rewrite it and say it the way you
wanted to say it if you saw yourself
doing it not the way you wanted to do it
rewrite that action and see yourself
doing it the way you want to do it it's
all right it's not a mistake make just
because you may have done it the way you
didn't want to do first doesn't mean
you're stuck with that you are the
playright write a new play rehearsals
are now in session you are rehearsing
yourself to be the character you want to
be so take your time just play it
through sit back in your chair in the
auditorium and see yourself on the stage
becoming the new you doing all the
things only only the new you would want
to
do if you catch that you doing something
that is representative of the old you do
not chastise
yourself laugh Let It Go say oh I must
be remembering another play I used to be
in and then say ah yes here is the
script for this play this is now what I
am doing this is the character I am now
being and then see yourself being
it as you do this more and more you
should begin to notice something
happening within
you you should begin to feel how much
joy you're beginning to get out of
watching yourself doing the things you
really like to
do let yourself start to feel the joy of
watching a good play one that makes you
laugh it is all right too if it makes
makes you cry nothing wrong with that
that's a
release but feel the emotionality of
seeing the character change into the way
you prefer it to
be start feeling the vibration under
your rib cage in your solar plexus all
the way through your
body anywhere you wish to feel it in
your feet in your fingers feel the
tingling feel how delightful it is to
see someone that is doing what they love
to do isn't that
inspiring yes doesn't it just make you
want to get right up out of the
auditorium and do something like that
yes but it's all right stay there watch
the play for a
moment feel even more excitement with
every new line with every new
action it's all right it's all right
it's a beautifully unfolding play
beautifully
unfolding and now the play comes to its
Climax and you see the character
standing center
stage and they deliver the last
line and the curtain comes down and the
curtain goes up and they take their bow
applaud if you appreciated
it and you can do it physically if you
wish you are applauding that you all
right you are applauding the boldness of
how that you that actor actress that
character allowed you to feel you
identified you felt the compassion the
passion the emotions swelling within
you now that's being
alive that's feeling that's
being so
take that cue that emotional cue you now
just gave
yourself and just feel it for a moment
just feel how it feels to be that you just
feel how it feels to be that you just
feel
it this is the whole idea of emotional
identification part two the Second
Step as you sit there and feel it you
remember back to the idea now that the
first step was beliefs identifying
defining the belief and now you're in
the second stage you're feeling the
differences between the old and the new
you you are feeling the way it would
feel if you were the you you wanted to
be feel it it is you it is not an
unattainable goal it is not an
unreachable concept it is you right now
if you feel it right now that's you
right now right now that is
you take a deep breath and give a big
sigh one more
time and a third time deep breath deep
breath hold it hold it hold it hold it
[Music]
now stand up and Shake Your Body
Out Shake It Out Shake It Out loosen up
loosen up now be
seated Now understand something all
right I'll say it this way very
[Laughter] profound you are a new
profound you are a new
audience you are not the audience you
were when we quote unquote began this
interaction you are a new audience you
are a new you you have begun to redefine
the person that you
are personality is your construct is
your
creation it is your
invention it is your device to represent
an
idea it is composed of three things like
a prism
thought emotion and
belief change any of those you change
the prism change the prism you change
how the light passes through the prism
and the type of spectrum you get you are
a personality construct in physical
reality you are Consciousness
representing itself in a particular way
you are an idea you are a notion you are
a behavior
so literally literally take this to
heart I am not beinging in this sense
metaphorical take it to heart when you
change any aspect of your persona you
are a new person
literally yes yes I know you'll run out
of here and look in the mirror and say I
don't look any different although some
of you
might sometimes you get the feedback
from friends maybe have Haven seen him
in a while they say I almost didn't
recognize you you look so different I
don't know
why they look like a totally different
person and right there it can hit you I
am I am a totally different person
really a different person you see again
many of you are taught to believe in the
limitation of Change Change is a limited
idea the idea that okay well I made this
change but it's just a small change in
the person I always was
change anything you change the whole
equation you know your algebra what
happens when you change one
variable is not the answer different
completely of course you are the same
you are energy equations you are energy
frequency variable equations change one
component one frequency even an
infinitesimal bit you are a completely
different equation a complet different
person now do you understand what that
means it means anything you used to be
no longer applies to
you anything it means you don't have to take
anything it means you don't have to take
forever to change something you don't
prefer it means that if you are willing
to understand that any change is a total
change you can make an instant change if
you wish now if you decide to take
time that's all wrong
right it's a part of your process
perhaps you feel there are certain
things you don't want to miss that you
need to learn however the path goes
that's the way it needs to go remember
again don't berate yourself for the way
you are to begin with because the way
you are is the only thing you have to
work with to get to be something else if
you discount the way you are you don't
give yourself the tools to work with to
become what you prefer to be so do not
discount what you are first of all
at the same time if you understand that
any change is a total
change then you can be as different as
night and day in one split wink of an
eye literally a different person allow
person allow
yourself again not to quote unquote be
dishonest with yourself and pretend in
the classical sense of the term to to be
someone else when you know you still
believe in a way you don't prefer do not
ignore what your true beliefs are and
try to gloss that over with a
personality you think is the new
personality but which you know in your
heart you haven't dealt with the old
personality yet there is a fine line in
there be honest with yourself about
whether you really know you're new or
whether you really think think you're
new but act like the old person
that is the real clue how do you still
act how do you still act that is the
third phase your actions
phase your actions
themselves we will go on to that again
in a moment but first let us remain in
the idea of emotional
identification it is a very very very
strong tool emotion listen to the word
you have created in your language e
motion energy motion it is the
engine desire emotionality is the engine of
desire emotionality is the engine of
manifestation emotion is what gives the
picture in your
mind the energy to become
physical I'll say that again the
definitions the picture in your mind of
who you prefer to be that's the
blueprint the emotions are the
builders they look at the blueprint they
take the material of your thoughts and
they build it into the physical
manifestation your strongest belief is
what determines what they have to work
with and what the house will look like
when they're through with it if you
don't like the way the house is coming
out go back and change the blueprint let
the Builder rebuild it and come out with
the house the way you want to be it's as
simple as that emotions are the builders
the manifestors all right all right let's be
manifestors all right all right let's be
equal they are woman festers
too the idea is to Simply understand
that they are the true movement they are
the bridge from what you call the
concept into
realization
realization so it is of key importance
that when you have a picture in your
mind a
visualization of the you you would
prefer to be that you spend some time
feeling that as you say in your language
getting into it connecting to it with
all of your senses physical senses all
your emotions really identify with it take
emotions really identify with it take
some time how would it feel to be that
person would you taste things in a
different way would you have a different
appreciation of something would would
you hear things in a different way would
your taste and music
change play it all
out become thoroughly
involved as you say lost in a daydream
be dream that you feel
it don't worry if someone comes up and
sees a silly little smile on your face
and a vacant stare in your eye that's a
part of the process you are
disassociating from an old idea and you
are reassociating to a new one now
there's a vital clue in those words as
well you don't have to walk into them in
a negative way
remember disassociation disassociation
disorientation
disillusionment are literally what those
are you are detaching from an old idea
and allowing yourself to scan all the
probable realities you want limbo State
some of you feel up in the air nothing
under your feet foundationless when
you're in that state limbo State it's a
natural state of
reassessment when you judge it to be
negative that limbo state of scanning
reassessment turns into what
depression it is actually more precisely
compression you are going to the center
of your being where you know the answers
are and you're coming out with a new
idea a new
personality that's what the process is
for you don't not have to take it as
depression in a judgmental way let
yourself go through it as a natural
state it is a redefining time use it as
such and then when you have redefined
who you prefer to be bring those
emotions all the way up feel it as
strongly as you can taste it smell it
touch it see it hear it feel it with
your heart feel it with everything
physical emotional feel it identify with
it yes that's who I desire to be yes
that's who I am that is who I
am remember just as an aside that
sometimes when you say that's who I
desire to be that that can keep it in
the future understand right now that
when you feel that that is who you
are you couldn't be feeling it if you
weren't
so allow yourself to take a moment
now really feel the scenario get the
scenario now of the thing that excites
you the most and let yourself feel it as
you see
it if you find that your body
automatically wants to kind of twitch
and go along with what you feel let
it do not restrain yourself in that way
let your body move and sway play it out
it is an orchestration as if you were
truly listening to music let the music
of your soul vibrate and resonate Within
You Feel The Joy the unbridled Freedom
the passion and the compassion be a
child of
creation feel
free to be whatever you wish to be but
feel it don't just think it feel
it as you feel it take three deep
breaths and lock it into your
being lock it in
stand up and instead of jiggling and
shaking this time simply stretch reach
as high as you can and
stretch all the way up all the way up on
your toe
toe
stretch sure we are just about out of
time yes and now sit down
yes and now sit down
the third phase is the simplest in a
sense it is the quickest in a sense but
it is also the most powerful and the
most
profound the third phase physical
action phase one
identification phase two emotional
attachment desire phase three physical
desire phase three physical
activity that simply means if you have
defined what you want and you know how
good it would feel to be that person
then act like that person and what that
means is when you go out in your daily life
is when you go out in your daily life
daytoday
reality look at all opportunities
Through The Eyes of that person not the
old person act on those things in the
way the new person would act on the
opportunities that present themselves to
you most obviously most simply most
synchronistically take advantage of the
opportunity that are already around you
by redefining them look at something
perhaps in the way you used to and say
well I never saw how that could help me
before but now that I am a new person I
see something I didn't see if you see it
act on it physically act on it if you
have a
scenario in your visualization mind that
you believe represents the scenario that
would make you most
happy then as you did when you were on
the stage create to the best of your ability
stage create to the best of your ability
now I mean this literally physically
create with props to the best of your
ability that scenario find a space let a
friend give you a space rent a space go
to a space something that represents
what you
want make the props buy the props borrow
the props do it physically however something
props do it physically however something
as a standin prop not just what you call
non-physical imagination actually have some physical
imagination actually have some physical
representation of the things that you
would have if you were in that scenario
as that person and put them in the
places they would
be as we used our example before if you
believe that you are going to be a
staggeringly wealthy person then you
would have perhaps something like an
absolutely beautiful piece of art on
your wall well if you can't go out and
buy it right now create a standing put
it on the
wall put it on the wall where you would
put the other
one if you have to go through the whole
process of papering your house to look
like the house you would rather have do
it surround yourself with a physical
prop play in it for a while even a whole
day even a whole week who cares what the
neighbors say till I'm
say till I'm
redecorating I'm laying out some ideas
for how I would prefer things to be but
surround yourself as much as you can
with the actual physical problem with
the actual types of scenarios with the
actual people you would be dealing with
if you were the kind of person you want
to be and get used to it that's the
strongest physical Factor because if you
have those props around you'll start
reacting to them as if they were in your
terms the actual things and as soon as
you start reacting to them as if they
were you are training your physical form
you are training your biological
Consciousness how to act in a new
scenario soon you will know nothing else you have
soon you will know nothing else you have
a new habit and when you have that habit
you'll radiate a new frequency and as
you radiate a new frequency you will
start to actually attract either those
literal objects or representations of
those objects
because there can be no vacuum in
creation and if you truly with your
whole Essence your whole being your
whole mind your whole soul your whole
emotion your whole belief are acting as
if that is a real thing for you and your
body responds automatically in second
nature the universe must provide you the
actual other end of the interaction it
must you will automatically Attract it
and I predict you will be astonished at
how quickly and easily you do
it but not for long soon you're
astonishment will be replaced by
easy nothing is too good to be
true that's what I prefer to
believe therefore that's the way my life
is your choice but you are physical
beings so when you've defined it when
you have identified with
it act
it be it for sure yes I have a question
about instead of physical things what if
you wanted uh a higher Consciousness
ability such as remote viewing or teleportation
such as remote viewing or teleportation
how go about that all right first of all
understand that those kinds of things to
some degree are almost
automatically grown when you do expand
on every level in other words when you
truly allow yourself to be free on a
physical level you will automatically
find yourself being what you call more
psychic however you can set a scenario
if you wish where you will feel what it
would be like imagine what it would be
like to do those things to have those
senses to have those abilities what you
do play the scenario through if you can
get a friend to help
you we are not saying that you deceive
yourself we are not saying that you tell
falsehoods but the idea is that if you
can have a friend simply take you
through the exercise or the experience
of confirming in what it is you want you
will find that very soon you will begin
to develop a sense of when you are on
Target and when you are not so the idea
can be to begin with at first knowingly
in a pretend sit down imagine you're
going through the scenario say this is
such and such and have a friend say yes
you're right and get in touch with what
that would feel like to be correct that
way find out what that vibration is then
do a scan
quote unquote for real and when you feel
that vibration you will know you're
right you understand yes and how does it
get to like a a television Crystal
Clarity like say you call someone on the
phone and you just want the psychic
ability to just see the face inside the
room what you must understand is that
you may have many reasons for why you
would want that and you must be very
honest and examine what the reasons are
because many times you will find that
when on the surface you think this is
what I want you know the whole picture
you may find that if you had gotten it
it actually would have been detrimental
to your ultimate desire and perhaps
might have been detrimental to the other
person involved as well so you can
expect that you can do those things but
understand that it takes two or many
you're not just doing it by yourself it
always involves someone else it is a
whole idea of information and many times
when your expectations are not fulfilled
that doesn't mean you didn't get what
you actually wanted you must be very
very understanding about why you want
want what you want because many times
you may think you need it a certain way
when in fact that's actually
contradictory to what you really do want
you follow me so go with the flow
practice it as you will there will be
times when you find it will work
flawlessly there will be times when you
find in your estimation it will not work
but understand it isn't that that isn't
working it is that something else is
found if you had actually gotten what
you expected in the first place you
follow me the reason for one yes okay
and perhaps actually even more literal
information in another Direction because
remember information is the idea of psychic
information is the idea of psychic
sensing and information will take like
electricity and water the path of least
resistance therefore you may find that
it's actually more beneficial to the
overall idea whereas at first you may
think well I have to know it this way
but it actually may serve more people
for someone later on to come up to you
and simply show you the cover of a book
that has the information on it because
that may have actually been the path of
least resistance you follow me and it
may actually have served them by
allowing them to help you as well and
then they' learned something understand
you have to look at the whole picture
not just one little bitty well this is
what I would like to have happen okay
does that help you it helps well thank
you very
much yes yes
yes many
times no
right yes yes the thing that still TR me
and I
myself myself yes this isre yes let let
me change the scenario be brief theide
that you have decided who you are yes
that you like who you are you like what
you're aiming for you do understand that
there always changes yes yes all right
yes and one always yes you decided to
they feel good POS yes yes and so you
find that you're tracking on that
Vibrance that in that vibration you're
attracting other individuals to share
the similar you start to co-create yes
and then all of a sudden you attract
several individual
CC always always everyone fits yes
understand all right well let me ask you
a question if I may thank you can your
imagination or has your imagination come
up with a possible reason why that type
of an individual could be there yes and
let's say that you come up with a reason
yes you go with that reason you
understand that perhaps wory opponent or
person who being of service to you in
some come to that or you might be being
of service to them to teach them
something yes but as an individual yes
how does one in conscious awareness yes
cope La of a better cope may I ask you
another question yeah oh thank you very
question yeah oh thank you very
much why do you buy into their reality
to the point where you feel you are
losing touch with the one you prefer I'm
not then why do you use the term
Cope Let me put it this oh thank
you I mean I you know that I understand
the fundamentals all
maybe not very all right it exists
of the physical reality that we've all
sounds like an excuse no no I'm asking a
very specific question all
right some you have a situation
co-created with IND a situation that has
confin as a component of it One Moment
One Moment One Moment are you feeling
the conflict or simply recognizing that
they are recognizing the conflict that
they feel within a situation are you
saying you do not feel conflict then or
that you do no that I don't feel
conflict all right so you recognize that
they are feeling conflict indeed yes
inde and yet knowing that I prefer not
to spend my time and my that I don't
desire to put my energy into that area
into conflict into the conflict into the
promoting of the situation into and yet
recognizing at the same time yes that
there's something that I also desire and
out that I desire something that I
does the outcome have to come from
them not necessary well
then I guess this is a question that
bottom line yes oh all right bottom
line go ahead you
make it costs you
nothing and it never has and I thank
you um I the only area that I find that
I I come up against within myself in
this lifetime I love and enjoy most yes
yes yes yes is this area and I
just but it seems to be an area that has
cocreation it seems to be an area that
has to do with
time your time what about
it where's the bottom line you promised
me what am I asking yes yes what are you
asking me what I'm asking you is
me what I'm asking you is
that just one accept that life being the
process being the
moment AC that this moment I'm feeling
terrible or frustrated or something
about this and this moment I'm feeling
in and the next moment I may feeling
this and that one accept that one allows
it and then decides what one
prefers allowance is not necessarily
exactly the same thing as acceptance the
idea is that if you do for some reason
for whatever reason fine that you are at
one moment feeling terrible then allow
it in accept it only in the sense that
you admit that you are responsible for
creating that feeling that you have
accepted a situation on terms where your
reaction is one of a feeling you don't
prefer accept that take responsibility
for that but then you can use it in a
positive way you can examine all right
what beliefs that I have to have to have
that reaction do I want those beliefs
what beliefs do I want have those
beliefs and you will feel differently
and perhaps next time you will not be so
quick to respond in the
negative I understand that but but
yes I wish I could identify this dilemma
what dilemma The Dilemma that I'm I'm
attempting here to express it it seems
to me that your life that you describe
for examp live seems to me to be
life yes it's a life that that I allow
myself that I find myself living within
my own life many many
times and then there are these moments
within my yes that
AR all right now one moment do
understand that not making excuses your
planet is still different than our
planet your planet is still going
through certain changes that our planet
has long since ended you understand I do
you have agreed to be a part of your
planet otherwise you wouldn't be on it
you have agreed to some degree to be a
part in assisting your people and
yourself to change through those things
otherwise you would not be here at the
time of greatest change and Profit the
idea is to understand there will perhaps
still be times when you're going to be
able to relate and identify very
strongly with the idea of
sadness the idea is to let yourself feel
it and transform it not to ignore it or
wish it out of your life the idea is to
help other people to learn how to
transform it by showing them how you do
understand so sometimes it is actually
of more benefit to someone else if they
can at least see you go through the
process of transforming it rather than
seeming so
aloof from it you
understand you will eventually live
learn how to balance the idea so that it
becomes ultimate compassion so that
another individual will not think you
are shunning them if you do not exhibit
the idea of the same emotionality nor
identify strongly with them they will
still feel your radiant compassion and
know that you care but right now your
Society still puts much in the idea of
surface features and if misery doesn't
see you being miserable it doesn't think
it has any company now that is not to
say you have to be miserable but you may
still be required to show some of the
outward sign to show them how to
transform it is like leading someone
through a dark Valley back up to the
mountain you are being a guide it
doesn't necessarily have to affect you
as strongly as it affects them but you
may at least have to go through some of
the Motions knowing that if you're doing
it from Love and from compassion that it
really will not paradoxically touch you
as strongly as it is touching them in a
negative way you follow me does that
help you well thank you for being a Guiding
you well thank you for being a Guiding
Light and at this timing I'll me once
again to express to each and every one
of you our deepest appreciation our
deepest gratitude at being able to share
the gift of your Consciousness and the
gift of our Consciousness to blend it
together remember that what we have
talked about is a practical idea they
are tools that work use them if you wish
you will see the results I guarantee it
because you always are the creator of
your reality no matter what we thank you
we love you and we bid you good day
what time is it it's 10 10 okay I did
say he was
busy thank you all very much for being
here today