At first, it
took me a while to get used to the feeling. I'd
never done anything like that before, so it
was very interesting to see what I was doing in front of other people. It was
kind of a
separate experience of
IDE, but as I watched, I started to think about what my
consciousness should be controlling and
things like that.
But after a few years, my
consciousness and that of the other person gradually merged, and
people around me said that there wasn't as much difference as before.
My throat would sometimes hurt. How LIFE LIFE
after AFTER,
since I started channeling, I've
started to use the things I'm learning at the time and I've found a balance. My
emotional and logical parts, and my Noh-like
parts, have
all become balanced,
and I've become happier and easier than before. And
at the same time, I've started to see what's happening around me more clearly. So even when all sorts of things happen, I can see what's actually
happening better than before.  And
then there's the synchronicity that Bashar talks about, which is that the
right thing always happens at the right time. There are
a lot of coincidences like that happening, so it's become a lot
easier. Compared to before, I can now use my imagination more,
and I'm living a much easier, less effortful life.
How are you all feeling today in the time that you're creating?
Before we begin, I want to cover the basics.
Today's theme is imagination. I'll
also talk about things like being able to respond immediately to something. [Music]
[Music]
In this society, in your society, when something comes along, it's
hard to think that it's okay to just do what you want right away. Some people say they wish they
had this much inspiration,
but they don't have it. But there's no
one who doesn't use their imagination at all in creating
their own reality. Each and every one of you
creates your own reality. I've
said
this a few times before.  There's
no need to worry if you've never heard of it before.
Everyone here is here at the perfect time. So
even if you don't understand it consciously, everyone here is already prepared to get the most benefit from it. So
don't worry if you don't understand everything that's being said consciously. That doesn't
mean you shouldn't ask questions.
If you have a question, don't hesitate to ask.
But at the same time, do
n't worry that you might be overwhelmed.
You are already imagined to be
able to do many things on many levels. You ca
n't see all of the many levels in your consciousness, but you see this reality in an illusion.
You don't actually have a conscious, subconscious,
or unconscious. You've
divided many parts of your consciousness from one consciousness. But if you
do it properly, you can suppress
all of your fears and fears, and you can
also suppress the
unconscious part of your consciousness.
Depending on how much you absorb into that part, the things that come out will
manifest faster and faster.
So whether you're doing it consciously or
unconsciously, everything that comes in will
always come out.
However, on a conscious level, you
only know
how much you're consciously receiving at your own pace and what you can accept.
Everyone creates their own reality based on their own internal definition,
and up until now, when I've said this, I've
usually said it as a conclusion at the end of a workshop.
But today, I'd like to briefly explain it again,
and then, starting from that, I'd
like to go further. I would
like each and every person here today to remember the following information.
First of all, I want to say that
all situations in this reality are everything.
[Music] They do
n't come out of the blue with a negative or certain meaning.
But as you've grown up, you've learned that
when something happens, this is what it means.
When a neutral situation occurs, you
consciously, subconsciously, and/or
unconsciously assign meaning to it.
If you give that neutral situation a positive meaning, you can only get positive results from it. If you
give that neutral situation a negative meaning,
you can only get negative results from it.
As I always say, this is
n't philosophy; it's really just physics or
mechanics. But what I
'm saying here isn't that you should pretend that something is
positive when you think you're seeing something negative. I'm not saying you
should deceive yourself. I
want you to be honest with yourself here. Look honestly at what you've learned so far.
We know that no matter how much you tell yourself
in your head that this is positive, this is positive, this is positive,
if your legs are shaking even though you're saying it's positive, then
in your mind it's saying this is negative,
this is negative, and you're just telling yourself that it's
positive to counteract that. No matter
what the situation, when you feel like you have to protect yourself with all your might, you may
believe that you have negative power within yourself.  If
you can tell yourself that this is truly positive
and let go of your attachment to it, then
then
negativity cannot come out of it. You
just have to make a choice again yourself. If you make a choice
somewhere, negativity will come out.
Your reality does
not have its own consciousness within it. If
you don't give it a choice, it will not
change on its own. Reality does not
change on its own.
Well, that's not actually the case. I do
n't know anything about it, but it's
not really possible for something to just happen.
Life is not something that happens to you.
Life comes
out through you.
Each and every one of us is a unique set of eyes that can see things from different angles, different levels,
different perspectives.
You are simply eyes with free will.
So you can decide from what angle you want to see the imaginary thing,
and you choose for yourself how you want to see it.
Many people have learned to see reality using their own senses. They say that
their senses are like windows through which they can see the universe.
That's how I learned it. And
in a sense, that's true, but on
the other hand, it's
more like a filter than a window. It does
n't let through about 99% of what you don't want to feel or see. Your senses
Your senses
only see the reality you want to see.
But if you broaden and expand your senses,
things you couldn't see before can
come in.
When you think of yourself as a product of this physical body, when you think of this body as your only self,
what you can sense through your senses is limited. [Music] And so,
And so,
even in the real world, you can see and feel, but
when you focus only on your physical body,
about 99.99999% of it doesn't pass through.
So, as your physicists often say,
even in this real world, even in the material world,
even when we're only talking about the material world, we
don't see 99.9999%.
[Music] So
what I mean is, you can only see about the wavelengths of light, but you can
only hear a limited range of sound.
When you increase your sensitivity and your senses, you can sense
more of what's around you. By strengthening your
physical senses and
at the same time expanding your insight, your
inner eye, you
can gain access to more information. [Music]
So in this time of change, many
people are
already beginning to see things that aren't there, to hear things that aren't audible.
But these things are actually there, they're just
at a different frequency and vibration than you normally experience. [Applause]
Everything is just a different frequency, a different vibration that
comes from the basic energy that the basic universe has imagined. [Music]
Other realities and other dimensions are all here with you right now, they're just
emitted a little
differently, so you can't feel them.
When you let down your defenses a little,
even for a moment, you can become aware of these things. When you have expectations that things have to be a certain way, that
what you see should be a certain way, you don't
panic when you see something different.
They close that door.
When they don't close the door like that,
even when they see something else, they don't close the door. You call those people lucky.
But what they
see is just the same as how you normally see things. They
just see something that is not collectively agreed upon by everyone.
When they see something different from the reality that most people see, they don't know how to express it or position it within this reality. The
difficulty they have is not
where the reality they see comes from, but the difficulty comes from not being able to communicate what they see with
other people.
Sometimes there are people who can see other things in this way,
see other realities, and communicate that to the people around them well.
When they can smoothly communicate this different reality to the people around them,
people don't call them mad or crazy.
They are called geniuses.
People who can see such things in a slightly more artistic way.  We
call them visionaries. The
difference between visionaries and visionaries is that visionaries know
how to understand, at least in part, as well as all of us.
From our perspective,
every single person here is a visionary. And we're all using our imagination right now. We're already using it to create our own reality,
using our imagination. We haven't been taught how to use it to
create our reality, so we're not using it to its full potential.
And a lot of it is done with the conscious mind, but we're
just letting the unconscious mind do the work. You can expand that imaginative, visionary part
of you by using the following meditation.
So now, sit comfortably. Here's a
simple way to create your own image. You can do it with your
eyes closed, or with your eyes open, however you
like.
And there's no right or wrong way to do this meditation.
Everyone, your own vibrations right now. The
best way to use them is through
your imagination. They're
used naturally, so there's
no right or wrong way. So you don't have to follow along
as I lead you;
even if your imagination
starts to run on its own, that's what's best for you right now.
While you're relaxed,
before we move into the actual meditation, I'd like to give you one more example.
And so that it can softly enter your consciousness.
But before that, take three breaths.
[Applause]
Feel every part of your body relax.
Feel all your worries melt away. If any
part of your consciousness
says it doesn't want to let go of that tension, that's
okay. You can get it back in a few minutes. Let's
talk a bit now.
Relax and play.
We're just learning how to play now.
When we're playing, we become very imaginative.
So, as you continue to relax
and continue breathing, listen to the next example. We
've talked about alternate realities, but I'd like to
talk about here and now.
Something like this would be good.
This is called a radio. I
think everyone here knows about this device called a radio, which is used on a planet on this planet. I think everyone here knows that using this device, with its dial, you can
tune to your favorite program. Just because
because
you're tuning to one program,
no one would think that all the other programs, other songs, have disappeared.
We all know that all the other programs are playing. However, the reason you
can't hear it, you can only hear that one program, is because
you're tuned to it.
All the programs are playing at the same time. There's something
similar to that in film, as you
probably know, and it's a long "hmm."
It contains all the different things that are going on there. The person inside
only experiences what's in the piece. The part in the next piece is
not experienced by the person in the piece before that. If the person
inside wants to experience any movement, they have to
move the film.
All the clouds are right in front of you now,
existing simultaneously. If you hold the film in front of you, you
can see it all from beginning to end at a glance. You can see it right in front of your eyes, but you
but you
can't experience the characters in it unless you experience it.
This material world, the physical world,
is just one part of this film. The higher consciousness within you, the
part with the vision, is
like the one who moves it. You
can see it all in front of your eyes now, from the beginning to the end. I
want you to remember again that
situations are always neutral. You could
look at one part of the film and not understand
what's going on or what's
being said. In fact, you would
n't
understand it until it actually
starts to move and multiple parts start to move, and then you'll
understand the content. The various situations in life
are like a film. A story is created from the meaning you give to each part.
What I want to do here is for you to
look at the various situations in your life in the following way.
Imagine you're sitting in a theater,
and a play is about to begin.  The
curtain has just opened.
The character has
just opened, and they're still standing there, still.
All the props, stage equipment, and stage equipment are
there. Now, let's
say you haven't read the program yet. Let's say you haven't
heard anything about this.
So you don't know anything about
what the characters are going to say, what they're going to do, or who they are. You have
no idea what they're going to do.
Maybe one of the characters is
standing on the sidelines, making a gesture. You've
seen a lot of things in your life. Some people
immediately think, "That must be bad."
Or they might see someone who's done that and think, "He must be a
good person." Or they might see someone who's bad and think, "He's
doing something bad." So
what appears on the surface
doesn't actually mean anything.
All the situations that exist are simply neutral situations. The characters and props that exist don't mean
anything.
So I want to apply this principle to your everyday life.
Take three breaths.
And with each breath, feel yourself going
into a deeper state of relaxation. You'll feel
more self-acceptance and self-
love as you breathe. You'll
regain deeper wisdom in exploring who you are as a person as you breathe. And you'll breathe more deeply into the belief that everything that happens in your life
can be turned into something positive.
Now, as you breathe at your own pace, I'd
like you to visualize the following: Imagine something that happened in your life, past or present. For example, a
situation where you were treated negatively in your own eyes, or where you received negative emotions from it, or something that really
stuck with you.
Don't be afraid to choose something like that, something that made you feel
regret, guilt, or fear. Or a
situation where you wanted to do something but couldn't move forward because of something that happened.  It
's okay to be in a situation you don't want to be in. [Music]
So, try to imagine that situation as vividly as possible in your
mind. Everyone there,
Everyone there,
everyone in the situation. Do
n't let anyone get you down. Imagine everything in it. [Music]
As you look at the situation,
gradually feel yourself drifting away from it. Immerse
yourself in the situation. You're
so overwhelmed by it, your eyes gradually
lose focus, and you start to feel dizzy. That's a
good feeling. It
's like you're entering a light trance, a meditative state.
As you do this, the people there and the
situation gradually lose meaning to you, and it
just seems to move along. The
words being spoken also lose meaning and
become just sounds. They
sound to you as if you're listening to a foreign language and you don't understand anything. It's
like a play has just begun. There are
people, characters, and
props, but I don't understand them.
And in this light meditative state,  You're
looking at that scene. The
script seems very distant from you. It
seems unrelated to your life.
So, look at that situation as if it has no meaning to you, as if it were
completely blank.
Now, fully utilize your best side and think about
what you want to see from that scene.
Create that script. [Applause]
Forget what the meaning was originally and add your own flavor to it.
Add flavor to it within the situation. You
don't have to believe that this is what it is. Just imagine that, while looking at the same thing, you
can see this new way of looking at the same situation.
Believe it or trust it. You'll become confident
in it, and it's up to you to trust it, to believe it. But
for now, just play around and see if you can come up with a new definition or a new
ally for that situation.
And see for yourself
that you can see the target. And
see the target within it. So listen to the advice of others.
[Music]
Only, but when you decide what kind of reality you want to create,
take only what you want from that advice. And the
final decision is yours.
For example, let's say the situation you're looking at right now is
one in which someone said something negative to you in the past. You
look at that situation and
realize that you attracted
it to yourself. You have to
realize that you attracted it to yourself, because if you
don't, you ca
n't change it unless you know that you did it yourself.
So, decide that everything that happens in your life has a
positive reason.
You make that decision. You decide
how much of what that person said can be used to help you become the person you want to be, and which
and which
parts can't. You don't need to
judge or define any part of it yourself.
Love. What I want you to do now is to
shine in that situation as impermanent, unconditional love. Life.
Life.
You can shine like that because you
already know that everything that happens in your life has a positive meaning and comes to you for a
reason.
And then, give that situation the following:
That person is just yelling at you.
If that person wasn't yelling at you,  If you
know that, why do you
need to see that in your own reality?
Yelling at others,
getting angry, generally
when they feel they don't have power within themselves. When you need to
have that power and
appear to be no less than others,
look at the powerful parts of them. Trust them.
Redefine the way you want to be.
Remember, there are no obstacles in your life.
[Music] Learn to use things
yourself. Use them in situations.
Use them in situations.
[Music]
People who don't use those things themselves
often don't know that they're positive and
don't use them
because they see them as obstacles. The path that works is
not one that you walk on. You are the path. You can't
deviate from it, because you are the path. So everything
in your reality,
everything that happens in your reality, fits into that reality.
But that doesn't mean you have to love everything in your reality right now. [Music]
But if you
don't know that you created it yourself, you can't change it the way you want to. The vision
comes from have. You can't
reach your vision or imagination by denying what you have now, so
give yourself permission to do the following.
Use the method you just did within yourself and feel your energy expand and spread into the past,
present, and future. As
this wave of energy
permeates and passes through, all situations
become neutral. Then,
gradually, this wave of energy stretches out to infinity.
Feel the excitement and the energy of knowing that
your vision is being fulfilled. Feel that energy,
knowing that your vision is already being fulfilled, or
how it would feel if it were fulfilled.
Feel that excitement growing within you. Feel
your body now filled with a pale blue light.
Imagine yourself becoming extremely radiant.
Now see your body radiating extremely brightly outward, and
going further and further outward.
And as this wave of light spreads, it is coming in, transforming
previously neutral situations into more highly positive ones. Remember, situations
Remember, situations
don't have to look different from the outside.
But right now, you already
know that every situation that comes your way
has a positive meaning.
You are now in an ocean of light, right in the middle of it.
cannot go anywhere that is not positive energy.
This image is an infinite imagination being
sent to you now.
Light fills the universe,
and you are made of that light.
Take that light in, breathe it in, and
feel it within your heart. Your heart
Your heart
is burning away old beliefs, and they are melting
melting
away into golden light.
And from within that, the light dissolved in the yellow liquid will
emerge in a new form, the shape you desire.
As you exhale, your breath comes out of your mouth as electromagnetic pale light. Your pale
breath
falls on the bubbling golden liquid as cooling air. As the golden liquid comes into contact with the flame, the light and pale
breath emerge. A reality of the shape you desire will
emerge. From this moment on, what I will say next is
already yours.
From this moment on, what I will say next is
your vibration.
From this moment on,
what I will say next is your choice.
From now on, with every breath you take,
old ideas, old definitions will be dissolved within your heart.
With every
breath you take, you are
crystallizing Clear
Bright New realities
of positive Light. And with every breath you
exhale, new, desired
realities will be finalized. So with
every breath you take, your reality is changing.
You are walking from one reality
to the next reality to the next reality,
forever and ever,
endlessly.
Filled with inspiration and
filled with the support of those around you, you
see perfection in every situation and every event you encounter.
[Music]
Nothing is real to you. Nothing
comes to you except your own vibration, which you have decided to make your own.
Your breath is now the breath of life, and you
are now a pulse. You are all one energy. [Music]
[Music]
You are one infinite crystal, with
many facets. Choose the
thing that excites you most, and
when you do that with faith, the shadows
disappear. The more you shine, the more the shadows of doubt
disappear.
Remember, you have always had
faith. You have never lost infinite faith in your life.
In the past, you may have seen doubt as a loss of faith, but the
definition you choose is to
see doubt as having faith in a negative way. You
can direct that faith in a positive way, and you will.
You have that right. The universe will not deny you anything,
but it will always support the strongest vibrational frequency you choose.
So, take three more breaths. You have
already begun to walk in the direction you want.
Be being, be
being of vision.
Be being of inspiration. You
are truly already that. All you have to do is actually be that.
You already are that.
So, come back to the reality of your desired reality. You
can open up, but
remember one thing, and this is very important. You are already a different person. You can
look in the mirror and see how you look the same on the surface,
but you are
already a different person.
You are now the
person you want to be. You can do it
whenever you want. It's
that simple. It's
effortless. It's
a lot of fun. Thank you so much for
joining me today.
Thank you for your faith.
And thank you for your John.
Now, enjoy a short break. I'd like to ask
you to do the following. If you
feel like you're feeling a higher energy level than usual,
please do the
following.  If
you feel like you've seen energy,
use that as an actual action in the physical world.
Absorb as much energy as your body can comfortably absorb.
BREAK YOURSELF OUT!
MOVE YOUR JOINT and feel the connection to the Earth. During this break, you can stretch,
move your body,
and feel your feet on the ground.
This will help those of you seeking spirituality to remember to
include your body in that spirituality. No
level should be denied.
All, because everything
is one. So, we'll start again in about 15 minutes of your time. I'm going to talk about something that
allows you to react immediately to something that comes your way.
Doing it in a negative way to force yourself is called bracing. That's
not what I'm talking about today. I just want to give
you a perspective, so I'm
going to talk about the following: being able to
react to something.
None of the things I'm talking about today,
from the beginning to the present, have been planned or implemented in any way.  I did
n't have anything to talk about. I did
n't know what to say until you asked me. You
just need a general understanding and a general direction. With
your imagination and that kind of vision, you
understand: You know
what to say and what you need in each moment.
[Music] You do n't
have to worry about remembering, memorizing what you're going to say, or forgetting it. In that moment, inspiration
gives you what you need.
People who do similar things
realize that even if you do one workshop and then another, they're not the
same, and there are different elements. So we
choose the leaves, and by doing that, we
're not forcing you into our own direction. We speak
in a way that suits the moment when we're with you.
And by doing it this way,
I have a lot of fun. By doing it this way, I don't have any expectations of
what I expect from myself.
So every week, I'm surprised by myself. I look forward to
what's going to come out of my mouth.
So by having this flow with you, I've
discovered a new side of myself.
Thank you for helping me find it.
Your energy state
fluctuates with each energy. Acceleration doesn't mean you have to rush forward all the time.
When you become aware of something, you
react to it instantly. But that does
n't mean you can't do it slowly.
Imagination is about
feeling the energy of the moment. It's
like playing in an orchestra.
Sometimes the energy is very relaxed. [Laughter]
And sometimes it becomes very fast and everyone
does it in a different way. So, with
all of that, I want you to
understand that you can be imaginative, and you
can react in an instant. And the more imaginative you are, the
more you can create in your life. So, something [Laughter]
[Laughter]
NEXT is in. Memories are
created in the moment. So, we
want to recognize the imagination of your planet
and choose something.  I
think you're choosing something from the following
because your planet is very
imaginative, and I've
imagined a lot of very interesting people.
Some of the people on your planet have
created the following meditation,
and I'm going to
respond to some of the things we talked about earlier today.
Imagination is about
how you actually apply what you've learned.
And there are all these different areas of your personality that you've created, and it's important to
communicate with them.
Like, maybe you should drink some water before you start. And this
this
is a meditation called a walk the forest.
All
more. So, again, take three deep breaths
and relax.
If you want to close your eyes, do so.
And I'm
going to use my imagination to visualize the following.
Now, what I'm going to say next, just
keep it simple. I want to remind you again that there is no
right or wrong way to do this.
Just imagine the forest as best you can, the kind of forest you would want to enjoy.
Embrace it in a way that's right for you.
Imagine a forest where you can see the trees.
[Music] As you
look at that forest, observe the following:
Look at what time of day it is in your forest. Look at what kind of day it is in the forest you are imagining,
what kind of forest it is. And
while you're doing that, I want you to think about one more thing: I want you to
think about how you would get through that forest.
What I mean is, is there a path? Is there a path?
What kind of path is there? And how would you get through that
forest? Whoever you are,
start making your way through the forest in the way you imagine it. Start walking, and
observe carefully what kind of trees you imagine.
Look at the surroundings and the overall appearance. [Music]
[Music]
If you live there for a long time, there will be some kind of
wall. What
kind of wall is it? And what would you do to that wall? Take a
moment and think about what you would
do to that wall. If you have decided that you would do something about it,
And if you decide to go through the wall,
continue down that path again.
If you just can't get through the wall, just
decide what you're doing while you do the rest of the meditation.
For those who keep walking, I'll continue on. Continue walking further into the forest.
As you go, you'll come across a bear.
What kind of bear will it come out? And what will it burrow
into? And what will you do with it?
Just watch what you're doing with the bear.
And when you're done, continue on through the forest.
Inhale at a speed that's natural and comfortable for you.
You'll come across a box.
What will the box look like? And
what will you
do with it? Decide what is natural for you to do.
Continue breathing, staying relaxed. If you
find yourself taking a breath or holding your breath, just keep breathing. [Music]
Now think about the box and what you're doing.
When you're done, continue on through the forest. [ Music]
Music]
And as you go, you'll find the key.
What does that key look like? And
what do you do with it
? Just watch what you do with it. [Music]
[Music]
And then we move on, and now we
come across a drinking vessel. What does it look like? And what do you do with it?
Just watch what is natural for you. [Music]
And then we move on, and now we have water. And what kind of water is it?
And what do you do with it?
Just do
what is natural for you with the
water. So now we leave the water and move on, and as we
move on, we focus our attention on everything we can see and hear, and we find ours. A Deeper State of Rest That Sound Needs To Be.
And as we
focus our attention on everything we see and hear, we
move into an even deeper trance state, trying to include everything, everything we
see, everything we hear,
without excluding it. [Music]
And then as we move on, we
come across a building. What kind of building is it?
And what do you do with it?
Just a moment.
Then take three deep breaths.
As you breathe, gradually
emerge from the forest. Then come back into this room,
open your eyes,
and honestly recall how you responded to each encounter in the forest.
This forest, which you saw at the beginning, is you.
[Music] How did
you perceive life as an environment?
What were the trees like? Were they tall
or short? Were they
green or dead? It's not
good or bad,
but it allows you to see how you view life. If there's
something you want to change in this meditation,
just change it.
I asked what time of day it was, and that
means the following:
Where are you on your own growth stage?
Are you at dawn, or midafternoon, or in the
sunset, just settling into understanding and wisdom?
That
's what I mean. I
then asked about LIFE, and whether that's how
people perceive you.
Does it feel cold?
Or is it red
? The whole forest I just mentioned, and that time, what kind of day it is? These
three things basically represent the kind of life you have.
And how you want to go through it is how you
want to move through your life.
Or, whether you like it or not, this is how you're
living your life right now. Have you ever
had a curved path? It was a path that allowed you to look at and observe the
various things along the way as you went along it.
[Music] Perhaps you and your friend were passing by,
passing by,
not even noticing the trees around you, just going at your own speed. There was
probably just a
gap between you and your friend. Try to use
that as an example of how you want to move through your life. Sometimes a
slightly curved path is good, so you can really experience and enjoy what's around you. Sometimes a straight path
can accelerate your growth faster.
Decide which is best for you, which is the most enjoyable. Which one is the one that
truly makes you enjoy it the most?
And now the following wall
following wall
symbolizes how you see
obstacles
and challenges in life. It might be
something
low and short, so you
can jump up, jump over it, and go around it.
Or it might be wide and long, so it took a long time to get to the other side.
Or it might be taller than the trees and
bigger than the forest itself, so you
couldn't get around it at all. Was it made
of natural materials, or
man-made materials like steel, or
very dense and hard, or
transparent, or a
wall with a door that allowed you to get to the other side,
or you had no choice but to stay on this side, so you could jump up to the other side, or climb to the other side, or just walk through. These various perspectives
symbolize how you overcome challenges and obstacles.
Now, when we talk about symbols like this, and
look at things as symbols, we can see them the way we want to see them,
and then
from now on, we can make our life the way we want it to be.
This person who walked through the wall and met the bear was like
this. It
symbolized how we deal with various situations and our relationships.
Was that an emotional way of coping, and also
our relationships? Was there a big fear there?
Or a
cute bear that you really wanted to hug? Or a bear that
you couldn't help? Or a
cloud that you could communicate with? Was it from a
bear that seemed to be naturally in the forest?
Or a bear that seemed to come from a completely different place, even
though white doesn't suit the green forest? Did you
avoid the bear and breathe it first? Or did you
walk hand in hand with the bear? Or did you
just accept that it was there and
move on? Did it
become your friend? And then
you gave it back?
Think of this symbolic part as the emotional part of your life, your emotional responses, and your relationships.
Going further, I
found white.
The box represents something undiscovered, something full of wonder, in your life. Was it
simple on the outside and had something
wonderful inside? Or was it the
complete opposite? Was the
box dark and heavy and scary?
Or was it a beautiful color and very bright?
Was it a single large container? Or was it
filled with lots of tiny little things? And from
there to the key, that
was your blessing. Was it old and rusty or
new and shiny? Did you
pick it up and bring it with you, or did you
leave it there? Was it
very heavy and big? Or light and small? Or small
but heavy? Or large but
light? And I
went to drink from it. It
was a container for drinking, but it represented
how I wanted to express my life.
Was it a beautiful cup? Was it
empty or full? Did it contain
water? Or was it
something else you loved? Was it a cup that
each of you could drink from individually? Or a cup that everyone could drink from? Did
you bring it with you or
leave it behind?
This symbolizes how you see love in your life.
Then came water.
Water represents your emotional or sexual side. This is that side of you that you
have in relation to yourself
and to others. Was it a
very shallow stream
or a large, deep river? Red
water, cold water, dark water, clear water. Were there living
creatures in it? Or was there nothing there? Did
you jump in or just
stand there and watch?
And as you continued, you were surrounded by all sorts of
sounds, and your ears took in all of these. Those who do
n't listen and don't close off those things
are like this. You will be able to receive all kinds of information more easily and simply.
Did you learn from the natural environment around you, or
did you shut it off? Did you
make your own decisions about what was relevant to you and what wasn't?
Then you came across a certain kind of building.
This is how you view physical death—a
temple after death, a temple after death—how you view it. Was it a
small, old, rusty building? Or a
hut like that? Or a very
comfortable red one?
Was it a house that belonged to someone else? Or
was it yours?
Was it a building you didn't really want to live in, or a building you'd
like to move into and live in?
Was it underground or above ground? Did you
have any experience? Did you bring
all these things
with you and use them when you wanted?
For example, did you use a key to open the gate of the building?
Or did you go back and
open a box with the key? Did you
find a lake or a river? Did you go
back and pick up a cup and put it back together?
Or when you needed a cup, did you ask for it and draw it
closer to you?
Open your heart and have honest communication with yourself.
Look honestly at what you have done and what I have said so far.
Now take three deep breaths and inhale as much of
this beautiful forest air as you can.
Reconnect with the ground. Reconnect
with the sounds, smells, and all the sensations that are being created there.
Feel, see, hear, taste, and smell on all levels.
The world of
nature, the soil and
stones, their cold and warmth.
Feel their consciousness. More
More
refined forms, such as metals, and
more refined forms in minerals, like quartz.
All Green FL. Use all your senses to
feel the plant world. Feel the
green of the plants.
Feel their radiant energy. As the
wind blows through their leaves,
listen to their quiet, gentle conversation. The
king is the animal part. See
all the eyes of the animals, from the smallest to the largest, looking at you with such gentleness and love.
See where they are doing and guiding you,
and send them your unconditional love. All think, then,
think, then,
all living things, regardless of form or appearance.
Feel it. Feel all of the web that is a part of you.
Feel all of it.
Feel all of the extensions. Feel
all of the parts of consciousness, the
network of consciousness that is within you.
Imagine it in the way that is most comfortable for you. Most importantly,
Most importantly,
feel the unconditional love pulsating through that network. Feel it. [Music]
Feel the absolute whole, the infinite. Feel the love that the
infinite is giving you, the support and love it is sending
you.
Feel the gratitude for being given life.
Feel the infinite love, the infinite love for the absolute whole, for the absolute whole. All things
all. You are all of this, on all levels.
You are in it, and it is
in you.
Breathe that in now. Feel
how it loves you as you breathe.
Feel how loved you are. Feel how worthy you are of love. And as you
exhale, give all that love back,
because everything is worthy of your
love.
Now, take three breaths and come back to this reality.
You are not the same person as you were before.
No, this is not an analogy. You are
not the same person with differences. No matter how you think you are, you
are different when we say you are.
Personality is very artificial. It
can change every time,
but that is just a
reflection of who you are. You
are simply projecting a certain idea inside of you. If you
change your thinking, you
become a different person.
Every week, in fact, you are a completely different person. Say, "Who am I?" You might
say, "You are a different person every week, and then
who am I?" And my
answer is, "I
love who I am,
now and forever."
So, please stand up for yourself.
And stretch your body, sway a little, and feel
how good your body feels
with your physical awareness. Feel
this new body. Feel this body that is you. And remember,
And remember,
your consciousness is not in your body. Your soul
is not in your body; your body
is an expression of your soul.
Stretch your body, stretch your soul.
[Music]
Feel how you are connected to the ground through your feet, and how
you are connected to the stars through your head. Once you
feel that connection, the
next thing we'll do is talk about how to awaken,
how to awaken in this dream of this material world that you're experiencing right now. [Music]
Everything that's happening right now is a dream, and
dreams are reality. Reality is all a
dream. The
reason we can communicate so easily in your dream state right now is because what you
call the dream world is the most real world for us.
Your dream world is
our physical world to us, and your
physical world is our dream
world. For the past few thousand years, you have been walking through your dreams.
Now, within this dream, you can
wake up to the dream world you want to see. You
can do this in the following way.
Remember, this is just one
way; there are actually many ways.
Your imagination will
give you everything you need, so it is
your imagination,
not someone else's.
For this reason,
there is your imagination, your personal imagination.
So, in your imagination, do the
following. I told you that
all situations are neutral from the beginning. You can
close your eyes or open them. I
want you to imagine something like this in your mind. Now, look. You can see all dimensions,
all of yourself, everything symbolically in a way that is easiest for you.
See everything in the way that is easiest for you.
Take a moment to create that image.  The
most important connection
is when you feel it rather than see it. Try to grasp that connection you feel. Try to
feel that absolute wholeness for yourself. When
you yourself are that absolute whole, that
complete whole, what would it be like to become complete? Try to
feel it for yourself. When you become complete,
absolute whole, when you become complete,
what would your surroundings look like?
Wherever you look, there is a part of you. There is
nothing outside of yourself. Everything
you can do becomes reality.
Everything you can create exists. Everything
you can see exists. Everything you can create is something
you can create. The
source is like being surrounded by countless mirrors. No matter
what direction you choose, it will always be the
same. You can search for another reality. No matter
where you look, no matter what door you
open, you will always find reality. There is
no end, so no matter
where you are, you
can see yourself as the center now.
Because no matter which direction you go from you, there is an
infinite distance.
In other words, everyone is the same distance in the end. So no matter where you are, you
can be more centered.  There is no
such thing. You
can't say that
one reality is more real than another. It
all comes out of the center of your consciousness,
blossoming like a flower.
And it shows you mirrors in an infinite number of ways,
reflecting them back to you. Every One
Every One
Thing is one and the same thing, just one thing in many variations. There
's no reason for it to do this; it's the
very nature of existence that makes it so. The nature of creativity,
one of its qualities, is to simply create forever. There's no
beginning, no end; it's
always here, always now, forever. But
when you choose one reality, that's what you take with you. It
's not that it can't be controlled or anything like that. It's just that the choices you make make it
seem more real than other realities.
[Music]  You can come
back to this state of faithful presence whenever you want.
That's where all reality
is, where it's meaningless and opposite.
[Music] And then you'll understand this:
You were created to co-imagine with the infinite. And
how you imagine is by
giving meaning to neutral situations that already exist.
You, as a unique person, will give
unique meaning to those situations, and the
imagination will continue to flow.
That's how imaginative you are.
And you will never, ever, ever
run out of ideas. You don't
have to worry about running out of ideas, or about using your imagination,
or about creating new things, or exploring new levels. You do
n't have to rush to experience it all now. [Applause]
Because you are eternal beings. So relax,
enjoy the present, and you won't drift from positive reality
to negative reality entirely. You can't choose to do it
out of fear, or doubt, or guilt.
You can choose negativity or doubt. You
have the ability, but you don't deserve it. So
even if you choose negativity, you made a choice, so at the very least,
enjoy it.
Everything you do
is a reflection of your own perfection. Just because you think you're perfect does
n't mean you can't change anything or learn something new. Whatever you're
doing right now, in this very moment,
you're doing something perfect.
And even if you're in a terrible state,
that's still a complete disaster.
What you're doing is
perfect. Just by making a small change, you
change, you
can create a completely different reality.
Every little element is in the equation, in the
math equation, so
just by changing that variable, the
entire equation
changes. Let's say you have a cube. Just by
changing the color of one face, the whole thing changes. You've probably
learned about physics and all that, and you've learned
about continuity and all that, so you might
think, "Well, that
's just a change in the color of the cube, and it's still the same cube." But
no, that's not true.  Just
by changing your emotions, your feelings, your beliefs, your ideas, and your concepts, not only will you change, but the entire universe will change. Even a
small change can completely transform the entire universe.
Make the change you want to see,
and you will create a better universe you want to live in.
Conversely, if you want to make a difference in your reality,
change yourself. If you want to change,
act on that changed you, and
by doing so, you will
become that person.
Remember this: Do
not create a reality that is not your vibration. Awaken and live the reality you desire.
You are a consciousness. You are a conscious being with a conscious
mind.
[Music] The subconscious and unconscious
unconscious
mind are convenient names you use because you don't want to face them.
But if you know this, there is no
need to fear the unknown. There is nothing you can put
into life that you cannot use positively, if you choose to. There is
nothing you can't apply positively to any new discovery you make. The
eternal imagination will show you
what you can do.  You were
created to be able to express yourself in this way.
If that wasn't the case, you wouldn't be here now. The
universe will support you in any direction according to your free will. There are
only two foundations.
One is that you exist now.
The second is that what you give comes back to you.
Life is that simple. It
's your choices that make it complicated.
Allow yourself to see that you are waking up to a new reality. In fact, you are now awakening to a new consciousness. And
as you are doing so, plant that firmly within yourself.
[Applause] You have
now broken through all the realities you didn't want.
YOU ARE BORN and have been
reborn. Happy
birthday.
Now, take three breaths and
feel the life force within you.
And when you're done, if you have any questions, please
ask. All
All
have. Have you understood enough yet? Are there any questions? Yes,
please. I felt a pressure while I was doing this. Is that just from the heat? Is it an imaginary pressure? I felt an accelerated energy within me.  You're trying to
go beyond the church you built in the past, and expand beyond it. You've
You've
changed your focus.
[Music] So breathe into that.
And do some
physical activity that you enjoy, get your blood on your feet.
Move your body without thinking too much.
[Music] There are times when you
completely ignore your conscious filters and absorb this information. There are
many people like that. There are many people
in your species who
fall asleep while doing this kind of thing. This is
the world where the vibrations are the strongest in reality. In
places like this, we can communicate with you very easily.
What do you think? That's fine. I was dreaming,
and I was walking through a forest. And
each one of those things
was all about what I thought it was, but the last one, it
was like a huge building that couldn't be expanded, but had many levels. It was based on experiences like that, and it connected various sources. You could take the elevator to any floor you wanted.
Thank you very much.
For me, and for the planet right now, a
big problem is things like illness,
like cancer.
Personally, I feel uncomfortable
all the time.
And as a planet, we have issues like war and so on. But what I
'm talking about here is,
through those things,
if you want to do it yourself, look beyond that.
Look at the reality you want to live in. And
And
when you act as someone who already lives there, you can see it
as a model for others to aspire to. By doing what
excites you the most, you
shed light on those around you. [Music]
And again, my illness,
all of those things are resistance to my natural self.
[Music] There's one thing
this society needs to teach us: if we
do it this way, all the conflicts and polarities we have inside us
can come together and be balanced.
Every individual already has the power to achieve what they want
without harming others. I
think I can say it all in one sentence this time.  It
seems like you're also working hard to stretch yourself. It's
not just about focusing on the negative, but about acknowledging that it exists,
acknowledging that there is change, and turning your eyes in a different direction.
From our perspective, we
connect with the self that is already like that, and then we
act and model how we would act if that were already the case. Is that
okay? Each and
every one of us is characterized to a different degree. An
image is created.
Many people
seem to panic, saying they can't see the image.
But I hear this over and over again: "I ca
n't see it, I can't see it."
Each and every one of us is properly characterized.
Seeing an image that can be transformed doesn't mean you
have to see a picture in three dimensions for three or five hours straight. In some cases, the
image may only appear in a book, so quickly that you don't even notice it.
By exposing yourself to negativity, something like that will arise within you.
That's why I took the time to talk about it at the beginning: Your
own image will develop.
So I said that your own way is the most appropriate just the way it is.
So trust yourself.
Trust your natural self. If
some kind of change is necessary, any kind of change, and you
trust yourself, that
change will
come the fastest. I get it. It's fun, is
fun, is
n't it? It's emotions. It was like ecstasy.
like ecstasy.
Was it ecstasy? Thank you very much. I
felt like I was in control. That's
good. It's like getting closer to a higher consciousness, or something higher.
Ah, I asked you about a way to use your own imagination. Just somehow?
By just somehow, isn't it similar to the ecstasy I mentioned earlier?
Where is your belief?
Use your imagination. It will
surely take you in the direction you want to go. You can do it just somehow, or you
or you
can just do it simply. If
you do it just somehow, you'll only get some results. If you do it, you'll
get results. You can go
beyond the answer and be persuaded to believe.  I can't help but
feel like I'm talking about this.
What's needed is honesty with yourself.
Honesty, at least for us, is
very enjoyable. So, the
idea of ​​doing what you want to do comes up. [Applause]
[Applause]
At times like that, using this position of belief,
this tool, you
can know when it's time to do it.
Look at the ideas within yourself that are preventing you from doing it.
Ask yourself, "Is 20 years enough for me to be this way, and this way,
and this way?" [Music]
Or, "I think I need this much time to get to that point," and then
add that to that and do it first.
Then you can say, "20 years is
enough," "20 years is already enough," and you'll be completely
there. Then use your imagination. So, what about 10 years?
See how you respond.
10 years is
enough to
become the person you want to be. What about
five years? No problem. Five years is fine. Let's say I
say three years.
You'll probably say it's easy.
So, what about imagination?  I
say one year. [Applause]
Maybe that's when you first start to hesitate, and that
's how long it will take. But now you can ask yourself,
what definition, what insinuated notion do you
have inside you that makes it take that long?
Look at it. And
And
find that notion, and if it's not what you want,
redefine it. Change your notion.
And then try again with a new notion, and
see if that shortens the number of years you mentioned earlier. You hear that your imagination takes three years.
You
say that's fine. Let's say your imagination takes one year.
But with a new understanding,
you might say that's fine,
because if you use this new notion, it's
very simple to do it in one year. So how about
six months of imagination?
So you look at that definition, the notion inside you,
and then you
can do it again just like before.
Nothing
invented.  There is
nothing that you cannot actually manifest in some way within a maximum of three months from now. Even if you can't actually do that, the first
step can definitely be realized within three days to three weeks.
Well, that concludes the sing.
I would like to sincerely thank you for your kind words
and extend our love to you all.
All beings who are connected to me telepathically
extend their love to you. Thank you for playing with me today. We
are all children of the infinite beings. EX
LIFE Dream Sandam LIFE
To
All Exciting dreams and dream-
filled excitement. See you again
soon.
Yeah, how was anyone?
[Applause]