I I'll say good day to you this day of
your time as you create time to
exist allow us to begin this day of your
time with the laying of a foundation
that we may entitle
grounding now many of you have
recognized that what have termed a new
age has come upon your planet a new age
of exploring different ideas that have
to do with what you call the
consciousness of your being the
realizations of selfawareness and the
expansion of your senses in many
different Realms that for a long time in
your terms of counting have been
discounted upon your planet in your
civilization but now many of you more of
you than ever before are beginning to
become sensitized shall we say to the
idea that physical reality is but one of
the ways you as a being have of
expressing your
Consciousness as this becomes clearer
and clearer to each and every one of you
sometimes because of the old habits the
old approaches the old definitions the
old ideas you have been brought up with
that you have used used to define your
physiological reality up to this
point sometimes these old ideas will be
the way will be the methods that you use
to apply the new ideas into your
physiological reality and sometimes some
of you find there may be a great deal of
difficulty in allowing some of the newer
ideas to be applied through the old
belief systems through the old thought
formats sometimes therefore there will
be variety of reactions within many of
the individual members of your Society
all the way from a great deal of
negativity all the way up to
disconnection from your physiological
reality and this is why we would like to
address the whole notion this evening of
your time of what you colloquially call
grounding yourselves so that you can
allow yourselves to explore the vast
Realms of your Consciousness and yet at
the same time realize
that the exploration of these vast
Realms of Consciousness do not need to
take you away from the reality that you
yourselves have chosen to be born into
that you can blend the Notions of the
physical and the non-physical reality
very very well you can balance these
things together and create shall we say
a pragmatic approach to the idea of what
you have termed
metaphysics now the idea is to to
realize that one of the things that
causes the greatest amount of
separation of individuals when they
begin exploring metaphysical Notions the
greatest amount of separation from your
physical Society is the whole notion
that physical reality is somehow not as
spiritual as non-physical reality and
therefore when they've been exploring
the whole notion of spirituality they
begin to remove themselves
methodology wise as you said from the
notion of plugging in or staying plugged
into the idea of physical
reality both are equal Realms of
expression both are valid methods of
expression both are equally spiritual in
the fundamental meaning of the term
because both levels are created out of
your spirit out of your Consciousness
they cannot be otherwise there is only
one shall we say material out of which
any reality any experience any Dimension
can be created and that is in and of
itself the Prime energy of the infinite
Creator the spirit of the universe if
you wish to put it in those terms out of
that spiritual material out of that
Primal medium everything is created
physical reality non-physical reality
all the ideas that you can conceive of
are in a sense taking their sustenance
from the spiritual medium the Primal
substance of the INF Infinite Creation
itself therefore since everything is
made out of the same shall we say stuff
there is no need in that sense to create
one realm of expression one shall we say
crystallization of expression in the
universe to be any less valid than any
other just because it may happen to be
more dense or more shall we say refined
or more focused or more confining in one
sense of that term it is still spiritual
and all the confinement that an
individual May perceive in any one
particular level of reality usually
comes from their perception of that
reality anyway not the inherent quality
of the reality itself so there is no
need for the idea of individuals who
begin exploring the Notions of
spirituality and higher Consciousness to
become shall we say detached from the
idea of your physiological realm to
become Li headed in that way to become
Airy in that sense to make no sense
practically speaking to the idea of the
physiological realm these things are do
not have to be mutually exclusive as we
have discussed many times your Society
has been brought up with the notion that
it's either got to be this or that and
the idea simply is is that it can be
this and that that it can be additive
that it can in that way be inclusive and
enhancing rather than exclusive and
segregational this definition of making
it allowing it to be enhancing can allow
individuals to begin to see the
relationships between the non-physical
and the physical reality can begin to
create a new set of definitions in your
society that allows there to be
explanations and understandings even in
what you may call a scientific format
for the idea of what up to now seems to
be so
unexplainable as many various phenomena
in your reality seem to be nothing in
that sense is truly unexplainable there
may be different things which have more
or less applicability into your
particular dimensional realm but if
something can be experienced in your
dimensional realm if there is any way
shape or form you can have an experience
then to some degree that idea can be
understood by the inhabitants of the
realm that are having that experience at
least the portion of that phenomena that
is experienced in that Dimension can
somehow be made to fit or be allowed to
fit within all the possible phenomena
that are experienced or capable of being
experienced in that realm so the idea
simply is that just because someone
doesn't understand something first of
all because they may not see at first
how it fits doesn't mean that it does
not fit conversely just because someone
believes a certain way knows it fits but
doesn't also see how perhaps it fits
with other people's Notions do not have
to take the point of view that they are
beyond all that or above all that the
whole idea is that each and every one of
you individually chose to be born in
your reality and therefore whatever it
is you learn whatever it is you
experience in that reality in some way
shape or form can be applied to the
overall understanding of that reality it
does not have to seem as if what you
call science and metaphysics are truly
speaking two totally different languages
they do not have to seem mutually and
forever exclusive of each other they are
simply different perspectives of the
same one fundamental idea of existence
but with different definitions different
points of view different approaches to
the recognition of existence they are
quite the same thing just in what you
may call a slightly different language
but the idea really in that sense is
that you can apply and the idea is to
learn how to apply everything you learn
in the metaphysical structure of things
to the physical structure of your
reality the idea when you discover that
there may be the ability to reach what
you call Heaven is not to run away from
Earth to run away to heaven but to allow
yourself to realize that your
recognition of the existence of the
vibratory State you have labeled as
Heaven means you can create that
vibratory state of Heaven on Earth
itself and that's one of the reasons why
you have have created Your Existence and
your focus where it is in the physical
reality in which you now find yourselves
to
exist applicability is the key allow
yourselves to begin with the trust in
your grounding that everything you
experience must must must by definition
be able to be applied somehow in the
overall schematic the overall template
the overall definition of your
physiological reality look for that
application do not simply Let It Go and
say well that's just the way it is
that's the same type of things many of
you complain about when you discuss
these issues with your scientists they
say well that's the way it is but no
it's not you say well they have the same
point of view when a metaphysician says
well that's just the way it is and a
scientist says no it's not recognize it
is simply a reciprocal of the same point
of view nothing has to be left as being
just that's the way it is there is a way
to understand it there is a way to apply
and there is a way to treat even the
idea of such esoteric phenomena as
metaphysical studies into a very
pragmatic and practical application in
your physical reality that is why we
have for the years we have been
communicating with you always endeavored
to illustrate the idea of the mechanical
application of all the principles we
talk about for we recognize you do exist
in a physical materiality we also as a
civilization to some degree exist in our
own type of physical materiality and
therefore we understand the importance
shall we say of knowing that what you
hear and what you learn must also come
with a methodology must also come with
an understanding of how to apply what
you are learning into the idea of your
physiological existence so that you can
change the physical existence in the way
you prefer it to change so that you can
learn that the physical existence is but
an extension of your definitions is but
an extension
of your imaginations and your belief
systems so that you understand that you
are co-creators with the infinite and
what that means is that the physical
reality you experience is your version
of the infinite your version of creation
your exercising of your ability to
function as an aspect of the infinite it
is all well and good for individuals
that are exploring higher levels of
their Consciousness to say well
unconditional love is all all there is
is what it's all about it is a very
loving place to come from it is a very
very strong place of understanding but
if you don't understand how to apply
unconditional love in your physical
reality then no one is going to be able
to drive the physiological benefit from
your Revelations from your discoveries
from your awarenesses the whole idea is
to function as a living example in a way
that allows other individuals to know
that what you you have discovered is
something they can discover as well
something they can apply in their
physiological reality because remember
your world and having gone through many
thousands of years of learning
separation requires an example of how to
take what they already know and turn it
into a method that they can apply along
lines that they already understand there
does not have to be anything mysterious
about the idea of what you have called
metaphysical studies in your Society it
does not have to bounce against the
ideas and the Notions of what seems to
be common sense in fact it is based on
common sense in a very broad way and
sometimes in a very specific way but the
idea is to allow yourself to learn how
that is so to learn to see the
connections between the non-physical and
the physical to understand how the
physical is the product of the
non-physical and vice versa understand
how they are intertwined so that there
is no longer any separation upon your
planet between the idea of different
points of you now this does not mean
that you lose your individuality it does
not mean that you forsake different
Avenues of approach it simply means that
you understand all avenues approach are
valid are equal and in their own
self-created reality are true just as
true as any other approach just as real
as any other approach and that one can
be transformed into the other because
they are all aspects they are all
versions they are all faces of the one
infinite from which they have all been
created so keep your feet on the ground
even while your head is in the sky
always remember that you chose to be
physical it is for a reason it is for
allowing yourself to learn how to apply
what you are learning what you are
connecting into into the reality you
have chosen as your home for
now at this timing we will extend to you
as a civilization our utmost gratitude
in allowing us to experience all the
different ways you have chosen to go
through and co-create with us this
transformational age upon your planet
for us it is very exciting I know for
all of you it is very exciting too
although some of you sometimes don't
think of it as excitement the idea
however is that we appreciate deeply
this opportunity to reflect to you your
own power and to remind each and every
one of you that you do not need us but
that we simply desire to interact with
you because we love you and that if you
are willing to interact with us as an
equal then what that will mean is that
you yourself know that you are
responsible utterly for the Creations
you experience in your own reality and
that means you can do with it what you
really want to what you really desire to
we thank you for the opportunity to
reflect this to you to reflect back to
you what you already know to Simply
allow us to remind you that you are
aspects of the
infinite this is a gift to us and in
return for this gift I will ask you now
how is it and in what way may I be of
service to
you hello Bashar and good day to you I
have a very practical question for you
oh all right uh my step brother jacqu
has developed lumps throughout his lymph
system all right and I was wondering if
you could help me understand what he's
doing and what the family can do to help
him all right now I cannot necessarily
be too specific because we do not right
now function that way however the idea
to begin with the first step in any case
especially where what you call disease
physiological disease is concerned is to
allow the individual to get in touch
with himself in the following manner to
allow them to ask thems
what am I learning about myself by
having this disease what is this disease
what is this condition what is this
situation forcing me to face what issues
have come up because of this disease
that may not have come up if I didn't
have it now this is not to say an
individual has to have a disease no one
has to have a disease however because
your Society has taught you many things
that allow you to limit yourself in
various ways then many times many of you
are not willing or allowing enough or
knowledgeable enough to know that you
could get the information that the
disease is delivering to you in a more
beneficial way so the way to allow the
disease to transform into a more
positive manifestation if it is going to
is to begin to understand why it has
been created and one of the easiest ways
to do that is to understand what you are
learning out of being in the situation
what ideas allow you to integrate within
yourself a Fuller expanded awareness of
your abilities of your powers of your
connection to the infinite once you
understand what information the disease
is forcing you to look at then you can
make the decision that you will allow
that information to come through you in
your life in other ways other than the
idea of the disease which simply is the
idea of forcing you into a corner to
force you to face things that you may
not have been aware of within you
because you may have placed them in your
sub or unconscious strata that an
individual in your Society has created
so the first step is to remind that
individual that it is their creation Now
this does not mean that they necessarily
consciously chose it but it is their
creation based on the ideas the
definitions the negative ideas that they
have been shall we say spoonfed since
childhood and they may not see any other
way to get the information that the
disease is showing them other than by
forcing them to face it through the
disease if they can expand their
understanding of what it is that they
are learning learning they can learn it
in another way that is step one you
follow me so far yes the Second Step
that we would suggest is simply that you
remind the individual that they are
energy that matter and energy as even
your own scientists know is the same
thing and that the idea of any
manifestation any physiological
crystallization in your physical body is
simply the product of the arrangement of
energy patterns that are represent
presentative of the idea you most
strongly hold on to at any given moment
so they can begin in their own
imagination to create in relaxed States
a meditation a
visualization that is coupled with deep
and resonant breathing or toning to
balance themselves and place themselves
in that neutral state of vibrational
existence of neutral pitch so to speak
in that neutral State when they find
their signature vibration
the vibration that makes them feel shall
we say most alive most at home most
comfortable the one that really strikes
a cord within them when they rest when
they float in that vibration whether it
is mental or physical doesn't matter
when they float in that meditative State
they are at neutral when they are at
neutral they can begin to visualize
themselves as simply being constructed
physically speaking of electromagnetic
energy blue white light literally they
are made of blue white light see the
body in that way allow the body to
dissolve into energy and then see the
areas of consideration that you call the
disease see how they may appear
different than the idea of the blue
white light they may at first appear to
be a very dull gray but the idea simply
is is that if you can focus on those
ideas and learn the reason you have
created them to begin with then use the
knowledge you learn apply that knowledge
onto those areas of disease and see them
transform into the blue white bright
light so that the body idea the energy
idea becomes homogeneous so that no one
portion stands out any more than any
other portion this is a very strong
electromagnetically aligning idea and if
they are willing to continue to breathe
into it and feel that they are breathing
that electromagnetic energy in and out
suffusing every cell every molecule
every atom they can with that centered
State completely divests and transforms
into the idea of a balanced being and a
balanced being cannot by definition
contain dis ease now that is one
suggestion a lot of this in fact all of
it will have to do with whatever the
belief systems are that are strongest
within your acquaintance you understand
but get the ball rolling as you say
allow the individual to begin to examine
to discuss to discourse with the self to
know that answers can come from the
higher self to rest and relax in
meditative dialogue with the self and
listen to the answers he
gets ask have him ask how does it serve
me to have this disease what am I
learning by having created it then
listen to the information in that
meditative State I guarantee the
information will come and then he can
apply it and decide what to do with it
understand yes yes has this been of
assistance yes thank you well thank you
very much also on your behalf do not see
the individual do not see any individual
with a disease as weak see them as
having had the strength to allow such a
limiting condition to come into their
lives because they know they are strong
enough to learn from it support them
with a vision of the strength it took to
create the disease do not undermine them
by seeing them as weak and incapable of
changing it do not see them as a victim
understand yes so send your love in that
way knowing that they have the ability
to do with that disease whatever they
want to do it really is up to them and
also simply on your own behalf learn
from it what you want to learn allow
yourself to realize that sometimes
certain individuals will take on a
disease sometimes not so much for what they have
sometimes not so much for what they have
to learn about it but from what other
people around them can learn and
therefore they are actually performing a
service for many of the individuals
around them that they love you
understand yes he certainly facilitate a
lot in the family all this yes then
allow it to be obvious in terms of what
it is doing in terms of what the
individuals who are involved are
learning about themselves because in any
type of relationship any type of
relationship that is the bottom line as
you say what is it you are learning
about yourself by being involved that's
the purpose for that particular
situation understand yes thank you very
much thank you can I ask one quick
question very quick very quick time's up
all right go ahead um I was in Sedona
over the New Year's all right weekend
and did you have a good time oh yes
wonderful time uh we had visitors at the
house late one night all right and my
sense of them is that they were
reticulum is that true you have an
accurate sense but I will go no F
farther let us say there was reticulum
involvement in that area at that time
you were sensing an energy that was not
necessarily as shall we say close in
physical terms as you might have thought
it was but was permeating the entire
area and if you were sensitive to it you
could have felt that they were in fact
very close you understand yes thank you
very much thank you sharting
hello Bashar and good day to you my name
is Lori all right and uh I would like
you to explain for me and the people
here uh your connection with the
dolphins what exactly is that uh you do
with them if you work with them oh thank
you very much now and then we do the
idea is that the Dolphins what you call
dolphins and whales are from our point
of view first of all once again the
second shall we say alien to us alien
species upon planet Earth you have as a
planet two species that live side by
side that are aware self-aware species
land human water satation dolphin and
whale so your world has two
civilizations our connection to them is
simply the recognition first of all that
their environment has allowed them to be
more consciously telepathic than you
have allowed yourselves to be in your
environment up to this point therefore
they have been in communication with
what you have called extraterrestrial
societies for quite some time quite a
bit longer than your Society has been
they are very strongly connected to the
star system and the civilizations within
that star system of sierus because there
is a strong Affinity between their
energy we are connected peripherally
simply because we also belong to the
same Triad of Consciousness made up of
your Earth our essani and sisin which is
the name we refer to as the serious
system we are part of a Triad and
because we are all connected and all in
involved in that way in reflecting to
each other different aspects of our
Collective Consciousness the one
Consciousness that the Triad is then the
Dolphins are also a part of that and we
work with them to allow them to assist
you in dream realities more often than
not to teach you how to let go to teach
you how to love yourselves to teach you
how to play and to learn that ecstasy is
your Birthright this is one of the
strongest things we do with the dolphins
is shall we say I'll put it in a very
colloquial sense we work up programs
with them for them to introduce ideas in
your dream state to Aid and guide and
lure you into more love and more
allowance within yourselves that is one
of the strongest things we do with the
dolphin civilization upon your planet
since it is my function to contact
different civilizations on different
planets anyway I cannot leave the
Dolphins out in a sense when we are
dealing with your planet we must deal
with both of you but since both of you
your humans your dolphins are not yet
dealing as equals with each other then
we will use whatever means is at our
disposal to allow you to realize that
you can join them and join us in ecstasy
not because it is us not because you
need to but just because you in that
sense might prefer is not up to us to
say but you might prefer the idea of
unlimited ecstasy over the idea of
suffering that is our basic Endeavor and
our basic involvement with with the
dolphin civilization upon your planet
you understand yes um the reason I asked
I'm writing a screenplay called Call of
the dolphins all right and it refers to
the connection with
extraterrestrials and a young man who
helps uh who is an aonian manifest as a
man and uh he helps a young girl learn
about the full dimensions of her
personality by introducing her to the
world of the Dolphins right now um I was
wondering later on if you had the time
if um we could speak with
dreamer the
dolphin one
moment this will take place for various
reasons within what you would call the
next 3 weeks of your
time rather than this evening of your
time okay so you're asking that I come
that I come back with well I'm not
asking you that I am simply saying that
the idea of what you call the dreamer
Consciousness will have a particular
shall we say reason to interact with
your Society through this particular
Channel within the next 3 weeks and at
that time any and all other ideas that
you wish to utilize within that
conversation can also be shared along
with what dreamer also has in his mind
to share at that time okay thank you
very much we thank you sharing now one
more Moment One Moment do understand
once again that you have the ability in
your own dream reality to carry on those
conversations beginning this evening of
your time if you wish to you do not need
us nor the physical channel to
facilitate communication with the idea
of dreamer especially because remember
that dreamer is of your civilization
exists upon your planet therefore there
are no barriers to the communications
that you and dreamer can have beginning
either in your dreams or or even if you
wish to to Aid and assist the
facilitation to go into your physical
ocean and play with whatever dreamer
Dolphins come to you in your seas that
will accelerate the atmosphere around
you to begin to allow you to understand
the communications that you require you
will be given from the assistance and
the guides that you have whatever
information you need you do not need us
you understand yes thank you well thank
you very much and pleasant dreams
sharing yeah hi oh good day to you this
is my uh first time here here tonight
all right well this is my first time as
well as every time is right I don't know
if I should call you mister or captain
or how about friend friend that's good
thank you good or Ambassador too if you
wish but so are you thank you I I didn't
bring my list of questions today but I
did have one question I wanted to ask
but I like to give a little scenario on
something that happened to me prior
first all right be brief if you can I'll
make it as fast as I can yes that's
that's why my timing is off on Comedy
I'm too fast but um uh last Sunday I uh
went shopping and I bought a number of
things at the health food store and
while waiting in
line I bought I saw a package of cookies
they had on special sale I bought that
when I got home I'm taking things out of
my bag and I happen to pick up the sales
slip and I know I only bought three
things for over a dollar and and here
was a something for $139 I couldn't
figure out what it was and I kept
looking around couldn't find at all put
everything back in the shopping bag took
the thing went back to the store talked
to the woman she checked it out and she
says oh these were for the cookies I
says cookies that's right I did buy
cookies where are they she says well why
don't you get yourself another package
of cookies so I did put it in the bag
drove all the way home walked into the
kitchen and what's staring there right
in the face is a package of cookies ni
now what happened to him in the meantime
I don't know but they were not in your
creative reality that is true especially
because you are still dealing with the
it side of some of the other issues that
have been discussed regarding what
belongs to you and what doesn't okay
very good now my integrity was in on
cookies so I uh went back to the store
and there was a different saleswoman
there and I says I got these cookies by
accident would you take them back and
she looks at me like I was crazy all
right and she didn't know what to do
with them she called a manager and she
said there's a guy out here who's
bringing us back a package of cookies
anyway to make a long story short I just
said why don't you just put him back in
the shelf and she says gee you're an
honest guy but what she didn't know if
they were peanuts I would have sto them
cookies I didn't care about anyway all
right we thank you for allowing yourself
to reflect to yourself many of the
lessons that you say you have desire to
learn and now all you have to do as you
have already begun to understand is
apply those lesson across the board no
matter what the substance no matter what
the situation in that sense on that
fundamental level there is no difference
between what you call your cookies and
your peanuts well to me there was but
anyway I want to ask you a question um
we have a planet called Pluto and
there's a body of uh there's a mass that
moves around Pluto now what I want to
shut right now is that a moon of Pluto
or is that another planet well in a
sense the definition of what you call a
moon is simply anybody that orbits a
central body so in that sense by that
definition it is in fact a moon it is
rather small smaller than the planet you
call Pluto and your Society is now
beginning just beginning to discover
some very interesting things about that
binary system one of the things they
have begun to discover is that the very
fine fine fine atmosphere that exists
upon Pluto not an atmosphere as you
understand it that you could breathe in
that sense but the fine atmosphere that
exists upon Pluto they have begun to
discover actually envelops Chiron so far
out can it go they will begin to
discover also something they have not
seen yet that there is an actual shall
we say electrical potential between the
two and there is a great deal of
electrical arcing that goes on between
the body of Pluto and the body of Chiron
at particular times of alignment within
your solar system particular times of
buildup of ionic charge between that
binary pair in a sense yes it is a moon
because of the strict definition of what
a moon is very good are there any other
moons around Pluto there are other
debris but not anything of the magnitude
of
Sharon okay now in our solar system
other than Earth is there any other life
in the third dimension that we might
discover there will be discovered in
time certain compounds certain remnants
within certain areas of what you call
Mars there will be certain compounds
certain conglomerates of molecules
within what you may call a few or
several of what you call your gas giant
planets your Jupiter your Saturn your
Uranus your
Neptune these will be in your
terminology's primordial forms of
organic life but will lend you Clues to
the understanding of what you as a mass
Consciousness used and utilized to
create many of the ideas of life forms
upon your Earth there in time will be
seen to be interactions with other ideas
other levels of consciousness but in
your third dimensional State no there is
inhabitation to use the term loosely
with every single planet in your system
but not in the third dimension thank you
friend we thank you very much friend as
well
sharing good evening and to you good day
my name is Maran all right and I'm from
London England oh all right where I
think the quality of life is
deteriorating oh all right how so well
can I I I'll just proceed oh all right I
find myself increasingly uneasy and
uncomfortable at times all right when I
feel overtaken as it were by an alien
State of Mind oh all right and am then
appalled at what I see in here in the
world yes do you want to do something
about it uh most definitely what Ah
that's a good question oh thank you very
much but I an enormous question oh if
you say so I trust that this state of
mind will not lead to disease oh no no
no no no not
unless you do not recognize that it can
be used in a positive way if you do not
recognize that it can be applied in a
positive way if you become overly
concerned about it you can manifest it
in a diseased state but there is nothing
inherent within it that says it must go
that way it all depends how you apply it
very good now how do you you want to
apply it oh very positively all right
anything specific oh any particular
methodology any particular mode of
teaching of sharing of doing well I I
would need time to think about that all
right you have all the time in creation
I will simply remind you that when you
decide what that modality what that
methodology will be remember that
unconditional love will be the basis
that there is no need in attempting to
change in a allowing things on your
planet to change in positive ways there
is no need and in fact it would be quite
contrary to your desire to go about it
in an accusatory manner in an attacking
manner by shaking a finger at someone
else and saying you bad person you are
responsible for this all right they may
be very strongly connected to the idea
of what you call the dire state of
circumstances upon your world but to
pile on more accusation only adds to the
negativity the whole idea is to allow
them to change to create a situation and
an atmosphere in which it makes it
desirous for them to change by inspiring
them to change by being a living example
of what that change will result in as a
person by living in the world you
believe you want to live in now by being
a representative an ambassador from the
future Earth you say you want to live in
and treat them in that sense with love
opening up lines of communication
Avenues of communication with them in a
way that in inspires them to want to
change their point of view rather than
accuses them of what they have done for
blame will only add to the momentum of
the negativity that they're already very
familiar with in
creating thank you very much oh well
thank you very much it's your planet and
we thank you for being bold enough to
have chosen to want to be of assistance
in that way trust that whatever your
imagination comes up with in whatever
way you wish to apply those ideas will
be if it is something that really
excites you more than any other thing
will be the methodology that will work
best for you because that's what your
imagination has been designed to do give
you the methodology that will work best
for whoever it is you have created
yourself to be so flow with Integrity
with the strongest idea the strongest
method that excites you above and beyond
any other method you could conceive of
in terms of sharing your point of view
for creating a more positive Planet
thank you very much we thank you very
much for being a part of the entire
transformation hello up there or hello
over
there yeah um I've read about in
Atlantis they had a dome shaped building
many many many well this one they would
go into yes and it had crystals the
Temple of healing yes and it it said it
was be not the Temple of healing that it
was for uh them to like get direction in
their lives and to raise their energy
level is that not the same thing yeah I
suppose but it wasn't the quote Temple
all right shall we say more precisely
the Temple of centering
okay yeah okay so uh guys I was
interested in the energy they had in
there and they seem to have a system
where they would have crystals that were
fed by energy suppliers and uh by light
yes by light yeah and I'm interested in
creating that kind of atmosphere in a
room at my house all right go right
ahead I was wondering if you
technological uh insights into like how
I can get a crystal that'll Supply a
constant source of energy first of all
recognize that crystals in that sense
are simply a very basic form of
crystallized energy they are not very
far removed from the non-physical State
and why do you have to charge them
sometimes you do not necessarily have to
remember that a lot of the ideas on your
planet you have heard about what you are
quote unquote supposed to and not
supposed to do with crystals are simply
different belief systems about how to go
about allowing the idea of the crystal
to act as a catalyst and a trigger for
your own power because you in that sense
are creating the power of the crystal
the crystal is only functioning as a
remote amplifier for your own energy or
the collective energy of your entire
planet but it is in that sense activated
your energy it is only a trigger in that
way so the idea is in your meditative
state to find out which crystallin forms
attract you the strongest use those
crystallin forms in whatever Arrangement
your imagination says feels key Point
feels most correct and for you you will
replicate to the best of your ability in
your contemporary surrounding the same
idea the same effect that the atlantans
did in their civilization and I don't
have to like have us a generator Crystal
you can but you do not have to because
you are a master Crystal okay remember
that the idea of these crystallin forms
it is something you are discovering
shall we say again but the society you
are now is different than the societ you
were in Atlantean times and the way you
will use the crystals now will not be
identical to the way you used them then
because the atmosphere is different the
energy is different the Consciousness is
different the experiences are different
now is the time to use less
materialization now is the time to
simplify whatever inspires you whatever
you feel is correct for you to use by
all means use it but it is not something
that is absolutely essential and another
person may find that a completely
different approach will work for them
far more strongly than anything you
might come up with for yourself and vice
versa use your imagination to see the
arrangement that would be beneficial for
you or you can even allow yourself the
realization that if you fully fully
understand the idea that the crystals
are only symbolic in a sense of your own
energy you may not need the crystals at
all it is up to you however
quartz crystal is a very in your
terminology strong conductor a very
clear conductor you may if you wish
begin with that one thing that may be
extremely beneficial as far as
vibrational frequencies go as far as
vibrational affinities go as a reminder
as a catalyst as a trigger for blending
The Emotional Self will be the idea of
what you call Rose Quartz and
Amethyst also also very strong as a
magnetic ground for we have been talking
about grounding this evening will be the
substance that you call hematite mhm it
is very magnetically
orienting okay so perhaps if you wish
begin with this the clear the rose and
the Violet and allow there to be a
pattern of your own creation that blends
all three and then allow there to be the
small amounts of the substance of
hematite to act as a grounding so that
what you are actually doing is creating
in a sense a piece of inspirational
energy art that says that while you are
plugging into the Stars once again your
feet are still firmly on the ground mhm
okay I want to just reflect a couple
ideas off you Ahad I've had those are
the qualities of crystals yeah okay um
so you're Crystal too and reflecting off
you right yes
um okay one is that um if you if you
took a crystal to like a vortex in the
magnetic grid line and you put a crystal
there could that then relay that en
energy back to another crystal in your
absolutely and you will find in a sense
not exactly as you have said it that
that particular idea will revolutionize
within what you call the next 50 years
communication upon your planet because
you will find that there is such a thing
as shall we say sympathetic vibration
between similar forms of Crystal and
whatever type of vibration is shall we
say instigated in one Crystal can
automat ially happen at the same time in
another Crystal no matter how far away
that Crystal is simultaneous
Transmission in that sense so it's like
training wheels for telepathy or very
very good yes very good okay and another
idea I had is that I I made a pyramid
out of clay that's uh scaled after the
Egyptian pyramid Aisa yes and I was
wondering if I put a crystal inside of
that and then like had a quartz Rod
coming off that if that would bring the
energies through not quartz Rod I meant
copper that out um if that would carry
the energies that the pyramid is um
focusing it can
however is your clay model very very
accurately smooth it's very smooth but it's not
smooth it's very smooth but it's not
perfect but um I I made a point to uh
use exact measurements as much as I
couldn't it did shrink some when it was
fired as long long as the ratio is the
same it can do that yes okay and then so
if I if I took the copper line out and
then put it into other crystals they
would have the same energy as if I was
inside of the pyramid at that point
where the crystal it will be directed
differently the focus will be different
but it is the same type of energy the
pyramid simply acts as a lens for
magnetism focusing it in a very specific
way now one of the ways that we have
discussed that this can be shall we say
most efficiently drawn from is you have
a copper base with the copper Spike
coming up through the pyramid and
piercing a crystallin cap and coming out
the cap as an antenna oh really yes okay
great um as as one final thing I wonder
if you could tell us where there's any
major vortexes in the LA Malibu area
Malibu itself we have discussed many
times is the whole place is the vortex
yes for do understand the issue of
Vortex is not always AB absolutely
defined by a particular coordinate the
entire area as you understand that
notion shall we say
leaks into other dimensions in various
fluctuating ways depending upon the
alignment of your planet with your sun
and the alignment of your planet with
other planets the timing the seasons the
Tilt all the gravimetric information
upon your planet goes into creating the
fluctuations that happen in any one
particular vortex in any one particular
area but the entire area you call Malibu
leaks into other dimensions to some
degree all points do but there are
certain areas that you have called
vortices or Gates upon your planet that
are to some degree more aligned more
shall we say conducive to allowing them
to function as true tunnels from one
dimension to another Malibu is a very
strong area another very strong highly
magnetic area is what you would call the
area is what you would call the
perimeter of of your la centa la centa s
huh those Mountain areas around what you
call your law centa are very
magnetically strong okay great thank you
very much thank you very
much also your Palm
Desert
Shing good evening and good day to
you as I've mentioned before I have some
speak up so that all may share I have
some fairly definite ideas on how an
abundance could be distributed on this
planet without money when we get to that
point oh all right and I promised One
Moment One Moment uhuh remember that the
idea of abundance does not necessarily
have to forsake the idea of money it is
simply one of the ways abundance can be
expressed but
continue well we had talked sometime
past about that other planets had
eventually you will not need it and we
do not have it that is correct
uhuh it is usually a goet symbol for
something that could be a more direct
exchange or we understand what you are
saying we simply wish to underline that
idea so that individuals will not at
this point start throwing their money
away thinking that it is not
representative of abundance for it is
one of the symbols that still exist in
your society and is as valid as any
other symbol it simply isn't always as
necessary as some individuals think but
do continue
well the thing is as we move from using
money as a method of distribution and
and my understanding is that once we
have a true abundance of things on this
planet yes our money system will no
longer operate so at that point we could
have great dislocation unless we find a
way to phase over yes so this is this is
what I'm interested in this is the
concepts that I've been playing with and
I thought
perhaps and maybe not but if there is
something that we could learn from your
description of how other planets have
used money in a different way that this
might give me some ideas on how we could
phase over than yes one
intermediary format that was used in
civilizations was something that could
be for shall we say lack of a better
term as you say simply called a
universal exchange and the the idea is
that you may still have the
physiological representation of a piece
of money but it is based on services
rendered rather than the idea of some
physiological base such as metal you
understand right it is based on services
rendered so that individuals find
themselves exchanging the bills for
direct services rendered and for the
idea of
qualitative services rendered so that
one shall we say for now bill or coin or
whatever you wish to use is quote
unquote worth a particular section of
services a particular amount a
particular range of services it is a
broader definition of what you already
do but the idea also is that for every
single different service for everything
that is defined as a different service
another bill another coin is
exchanged there are still parameters to
work out within this idea of what one
coin what one bill shall be worth in
terms of a range of services but it is a
much broader definition as an
example one bill one coin could allow
you to exchange for an entire house not
many bills many coins one for one one
concept one coin you understand yes it
is based on the idea of Concepts in
terms of separating out what the coin is
worth and based on the idea of exchange
of direct service so that every exchange
that is made using the coin always
involves at some pre-arranged time span
a directly reciprocated service
by both individuals or both groups
making the exchange you understand so
it's sort of like a money combination
with barter system in a sense it is more
like a holding place in a sense or if
you wish an i you within a particular
time frame of an event so that when one
service is performed there is the quote
unquote guarantee with the coin that
another service of equal cost conceptual
range will be performed within a certain
amount of time for the original
individual that provided the first
service it is one of the ways that has
worked in some civilizations it can work
to some degree in your civilization but
there are still parameters to be worked
out but it is one idea so think in terms
of Concepts service for service and the
idea in and of itself of time segments
and concept segments and think of the
coin or the bill only as a placeholder
that says that some exchange is going on
and is still going on you understand
it's like an agreement has been made
within certain parameters yes how those
parameters shall be will be determined
upon the socioeconomic structure of the
society you prefer at the time you
invent that particular idea now it seems
as though it would work better that
system you just described if there were
an
abundance I don't know would it work
well do understand that one of the
things that will allow the system to
work and conversely one of the things
that will not allow it to work is the
whole notion of what you call on your
planet countries or borders those must
dissolve before the system will
work otherwise you do not have shall we
say an apportionment of abundance an
equal dispensation of abundance for the
only thing that creates an inequality of
abundance now is the fact that certain
areas are not allowed quote unquote to
share their abundance with other areas
because of the definition of what you
call governmental borders there really
is in an ultimate sense no starvation
problem no lack of anything it is simply
that everything is not equally
distributed and again this does not mean
that it has to come out to a mediocre
level it simply means that with the
efficient distribution and the equal
distribution of many different ideas and
we recognize right now that for your
planet this may seem like an
oversimplification but with an equalized
distribution of abilities there will be
a high level of abundance for all also
when you begin to rely on energy bases
that are different than what you are
using now when you begin to tap into the
idea of the electromagnetic field of
your planet for all of your power
requirements rather than what you are
using now there will also be more than
enough power to create the abundance you
require for every single member of your
community without the idea of pollution
without the idea of waste and without
the idea of limitation because there is
more than enough energy in creation for
everyone I understand that so I asked
you a while ago um if this gentleman
that I described to you would succeed in
getting his energy systems um put around
throughout the country and you said well
that depends on how much you help him so
anyway I have a shop in my garage and
I'm going to work at it so you know that
there are many that are involved in the
exploration of how to shall we say tap
the electromagnetic field of your planet
and transform it into all the variations
and forms of power that you require by
all means Follow Your Instinct do your
home fun as you say and do your research
and find out what are the principles
that allow your planet to operate many
individuals have done this and once
again we usually refer you to the idea
of the work you call from the individual
Tesla yes I have his books all right
then enjoy thank you very much thank you
Shing hello Bashar and good day to you
good day my name is Gloria all right I
have a kind of twofold question a kind
of twofold question yes go ahead unfold
it
the first is um a few years ago my
husband and I had an experience where we
were asleep in bed and um a woke with me
sitting on the bed a white light within
the room that created no shadows in
other words a very very bright bright
light and my husband rolled off from the
floor onto the bed into my arm I felt
absolutely no fear he was quite
frightened at that moment all right and
the light disappeared was that an
extraterrestrial there was connection to
what you may call extraterrestrial but
it was also mostly simply
interdimensional and also took place
mostly in an astral state or quasi
planar reality between what you would
call dense physicality and astral
existence that is the reason why there
were no Shadows from the light because
you were not dealing with a hard lined
hard edged physiological experience you
understand yes the idea simply is is
that light that recognition that
reflection is there to allow individuals
to key off of it to align as a
reflection within themselves the ideas
that are most true for themselves some
individuals have been taught to fear
many of the pieces they have created
themselves to be such as the case with
your husband in that sense simply an old
reaction to old definitions to Old
beliefs when shown what the alignment
what the light is that each and every
one of you are in a sense shall we say
graphically speaking what you are doing
is looking into a mirror and seeing the
reflection of your own light some of you
can take it some of you
can't understand yes absolutely I
understand but it was involving other
dimensions of Consciousness you can
colloquially say it was of also
extraterrestrial connection but for now
I would leave that has a very loose
definition right all right I would like
to
know since I I have a very strong sense
of the fact that I
am connecting on a constant basis
probably most nights guys
interdimensionally yes I would like to
know how I can activate my
memory in order to bring into the
physicality the information very simple
very very simple good are you doing in
your life what excites you the most yes
yes I am then that's how that's all you
need to do remember that the memory of
these ideas the memory of the
communication does not have to be
analytical and many times you don't want
it to be because in your terminology
will only get in the way of you acting
spontaneously right if you are doing
what excites you the most then you are
using the information in the way that
serves everyone else the best don't
worry about having an empirical
knowledge of all the specifics many
times the specifics will only allow you
to become overly analytical and in a
sense will trip you up will slow you
down perfect understand absolutely I do
understand wonderful and as my instinct
told me is so yes yes then you didn't
need to ask I know I'm very glad you
reassured me that there was nothing more
now one more little area and that is do
uh I am going to Bora Bora tomorrow and
I would like to know if is that any
everyone that comes back from there
talks about it being magical so I assume
that it got some kind of slightly
different energy why are you going for
the joy of it for the joy of being there
that Joy is what allows it to be magical
yes for that area shall we say is very
Loosely
structured yes when when you say that
it's very Loosely structured I imagine
that my entire vacation will be very
loosely structured quite spontaneous
precisely uh does that also have to do
with the density of the atmosphere
atmosphere vibration wonderful perfect
thank you bless for there are many many
many consciousnesses focused in that
area and the thickness of the air so to
speak is the thickness of the energy of
all the different consciousnesses in
levels and dimensions of reality that
are aware of that energy and also
sharing their Joy with it so in fact the
best way at all times to tune in to more
and more information is through Joy
absolutely because every time you choose
to lighten up you are enlightened
absolutely absolutely that's all it
means wonderful wonderful blessing thank
you we know that when you go there you
will be far from board
board sharting good evening Bashar and good
sharting good evening Bashar and good
day to you I'm going to ask my question
first and last first and last yes all
right my question will
be how does all of that seem to
you and I will weave a little story here
first Weave Away
okay um I've always considered myself to be
um I've always considered myself to be
an Explorer of
sorts an Explorer of sorts oh all sorts
how many sorts have you
explored Limitless all right do continue
all right last uh year in July I got
into something which I had information
on previously but hadn't done myself and
uh in that particular
experience um I began to
find that I was no longer grounded for
one because this particular procedure is
in a flotation tank all right um in this
intervening period of time I have spent
um 2 to three hours a week floating all
right literally not grounded all right
okay
um I went in with no
preconceived ideas of what I would
experience all right and so uh my
first 5 minutes in the tank was spent
laughing like a crazy person because of
this new float experience the um
weightlessness yes and many other things
okay going along into the story I
started seeing things yes as I went back
into the tank I saw more things and I
contacted people in different places
from that which I was uh familiar with
guys mainly um what I would call
Atlantis all right okay I met a group of
people which was a council they call
themselves a council of six yes this
Council of six people and I sat in the
room and they had bodies but they didn't
seem to have distinguishable heads their
heads glowed all right uh from there I
went on to four other people who showed
me through pyramids and have been
showing me in three different pyramids
um many different areas of atlon um
culture okay these people I considered
to be like guides to that particular
area very good yes now as I keep going
back to these people these Council of
six they say we'll let you keep coming
in to pull out information as long as
you pass it along to others yes okay
that is the applicability which keeps
you grounded okay now most recently uh
when I was in the tank uh which was
about a week and a half ago I came in
contact with these people and I this
Burning question had been arising um
because I would see these people of
these this Council of six suddenly go
into one yes and then they go back into
six they're playing tricks before me so
I said or I asked them yes where do you
come from guys like that we took off and
it was like um well in I don't suppose
you've seen the movie Star Wars but uh
it is within the memory of the channel
how about hyperspace okay it was that
fast travel yes okay and we they took me
or it took me or whatever to their home
and I
experienced that experience when I was
in the tank uh there was probably the uh
it could have been a tital wave because
my body shook so much and my hair and
the the tank the water in the tank is
the same as the temperature of a
person's skin and yet my hair was
standing on end it was an electrifying
experience I loved every minute of it
yes yeah yes yeah
okay so I've asked the question you know
and they told me they showed me where
they come from and they or when I was
there this name came through and I am
not um one to to read on names that
understand okay ashtar yes that's the
name that came through yes okay and uh
I'm saying why me why you know and the
answer is that's right you know because
you've been the answer was because
you've been doing this for a long time
anyway yes you are to some degree now we
have used this term now and then for a
few of you it does not always mean
precisely the same thing from person to
person but we use it as a general term
and we can use that term again now it's
because you are a pilot and you are
familiar with that idea of navigation
into different
dimensions all right now what they want
me to do is to
uh this this energy wants me to play out
the whole thing through various media uh
Avenues here I'm a physician I work all
day and this sort of thing in my office
I'm saying what the hell am I doing here
anyway you know yes and they said don't
worry you can leave your office and
we'll have somebody else there to run it
for you and you have plenty of income
and you can do your movies and write
your books and all of this sort of thing
as and so yeah I guess I'm supposed to
do this you know I I I I don't have any
disagreement with it all right it is not
a supposed to in the sense that they are
forcing you to it is simply what you
have agreed to do ex yeah it was uh it
was something that agreed to do and that
was the the initial contact was uh like
I said we'll let you keep coming back as
long as you agree to do this and I kept
wondering what the heck I had agreed to
do a long time ago what excites you the
most yeah while doing something like
this and furthering my Explorations yes
and also you will find that some of the
teaching methodologies that you also used in your
methodologies that you also used in your
atlantian incarnations were similar to
the the notion of the tank itself yes
the types of meditative States you would
allow other individuals to get into so
that they could under your guidance
learn to explore in that sense the idea
of different dimensions now the
nomenclature the vibration of ashar is
representative of a particular shall we
say faction of Consciousness it is not
as many of you think it to be a lot of
the interpretation many of you have of
the idea of ashtar is a physicalized one
that makes the most sense in your
reality they are not precisely what many
of you think them to be exactly in the
way you picture them also some of the
idea that you experienced
energetically of their shall we say home
also entailed being taken through this
is your experience being taken through
the doorway the Gateway of the star
system of Sirius and then shall we say
deflected on to the system of
Arcturus understand I do thank you now
always remember once again that you can
apply these ideas in very pragmatic ways
into your physiological reality through
the things you wish to give voice to
through the things you wish to give
picture to sound to through your art
through your
creativity and also you may find that
you may wish to it's up to
you re
create the idea of creating that
atmosphere for other individuals so once
again as you did in Atlantean times you
can allow them to learn to expand their
Consciousness to also explore those
different Realms again that exploration of sorts
Realms again that exploration of sorts
has to do with the idea of the fact that
you are a pilot and you are very
familiar with exploring different
dimensions of reality already now you
can simply apply that same idea in yet
one more way just in the same way as you
have applied it in thousands of ways
through thousands of lifetimes since
Atlantis it's up to you uhuh I feel that
I am um living many careers in this one
lifetime in this way yes you are
blending and therefore that is why we
are saying not only can you have the
creative expression you have talked
about in terms of a particular type of
format in presenting the information
itself but you can also recreate many of
the methodologies you have used in the
various lifetimes to act as assistants
as methodologies as techniques as
atmospheres as environments so that
other individuals may also take
advantage of that particular knowledge
and learn to expand themselves in
various ways as well you can do this to
the idea of workshops you can do it
through the idea of setting up your own
kind of meditative areas that people can
go into to get in touch with themselves
in a whatever way they want to it is up
to you as an analogy do remember that
from time to time the idea of our
communication with your civilization
through the channels we communicate with
to some degree is augmented by what we
typically refer to as our computer
Consciousness aboard our spacecraft and
you will find that I in many cases of
these Transmissions I'm in a state of
repose similar to the idea of you being
in your tank so that I am assisted and
augmented to be able to project my
Consciousness through my Dimension to
your dimension so that you can perceive
this interaction going on in much the
same way that you perceived visiting
that group's home world you understand I
understand there are on our mother ships
many cubicles that function as
augmentation Chambers they are not
filled with water in that sense but they
are very similar to the idea of being
placed in a chamber that augments the
Consciousness in a way that allows you
to know that what's going on in your
imagination as this conversation is
right now within mine is also
real understand oh I do
this is an interesting thing that I have
to share with you I feel like I'm having
a conversation with myself right now you
are yes I mean with what you're talking
about you are yeah okay you are
literally having a conversation with
yourself because now I am literally
having a conversation with myself right
now okay but what you're saying are many
thoughts that I've had about doing
exactly that for other people yes and I
didn't want to do something which
was a setup for example flotation tanks
as a center for doesn't have to be
precisely that way whatever inspires you
the most all right okay but I did find I
just wanted to share with with you and
the other people here that I found that
the environment of the tank was
beneficial not that it would necessarily
be for everybody but it cor was and uh
the other thing is I don't have to ask
my question again what do you think I
have a suggestion sure you can set up a
pilot training
course I thank you I thank you very much
for expressing your Stellar qualities
all right bye-bye at this timing you may
all enjoy a short break we will resume
contact in this fashion in approximately
10 of your minutes
[Music] [Applause] how's it
going I'll say
continue hello Bashar and good day to
you I've been learning for sometime now
or me too
too
about um what about the genetic
restructuring that's possible within the
body and also that's happening in
humanity at this time at least this is
my concept that there's a genetic
restructuring happening which is sort of
propelling humanity into the Aquarian
age well any sense yes and I'm
wondering two parts of this question the
first part is do you have any
information on the possible
stages of this transformational process
uh guys one of the things we can share
with you at this time is that your
genetic code is now allowing for the
creation of a higher concentration of
silicon in your bodies so that you can
become more shall we say receptive to
the same types of energy that crystall
and structures are sensitive
to thank you and um I'm also aware of a
connection between this genetic change
and what's called the 100th monkey
phenomenon and I'm wondering if you
could comment on
that this idea can cause what you call
Rapid genetic
mutation but it isn't necessarily
genetic mutation that has to happen in order for
mutation that has to happen in order for
a spontaneous change to occur in your
society when a certain number of
individuals when a certain percentage of
individuals know a certain thing if that
knowledge of those percentage of
individuals a small percentage of
individuals in your Society is aligned
with the
general idea of the direction your
Society is going in in such a way as to
Aid in the acceleration of that
direction then the remainder of your
Society will generally just through many
mentality just through telepathic
alignment fall into step with that
particular direction and add to the
accelerated energy whether is a genetic
change or not sometimes the genetic
change will occur because of that
falling into step because of that
acceleration but it isn't always
necessary and a genetic change
physiologically speaking doesn't always
happen at least not on that level a
change to some degree always happens
physiologically but what we are simply
saying is that it doesn't always
manifest in your terminology in the
genetic code itself in order that a
physical change simply does occur
because every thought you have changes
your physicality that doesn't mean that
the genetic code from one moment to the
next has to appear very different in
order for you to understand that
physically you have completely changed
with every single thought so it doesn't
always manifest in the genetic code even
though you have completely physically
changed from one moment to the next you
can't always rely on on the genetic code
to show you that you have changed
sometimes sociological events will be
what will show you that certain things
have changed the ability to talk about a
particular subject that wasn't there
before will show you that there has been
a change shall we say in the psychic
genetic code even though it may not be
apparent in the physiological one you
understand yes yes does this assist you
yes the last part of the question is
I have heard from a couple of sources
that there is an asteroid that is at
present heading towards our planet that
somehow left the asteroid belt and is
heading towards our planet and will
impact this planet in May of this year
no good I was asking if this was
accurate first of all there are many
asteroids and many fragments and many
debris which do approach your your
planet and many planets within many
systems quite regularly many of these
you do not even hear about because they
simply pass by now the
idea to some degree is mostly symbolic
what you call your May month is a highly
energized time of transition and of
transformation upon your planet it will
create a very large impact so to speak
but the the idea has simply been
translated into a physiological
circumstance that is not our perception
now we do not have absolute shall we say
ability to catalog every single spec of
substance within your solar system we do
not always know where every single idea
every single body is at any given moment
it is our perception at this time
however that the field of intersection
of planetary with your planet would seem
to be relatively nil as you
say thank you very much the idea of
associating it to an asteroid is simply
because many of you make associations
with planetary happenings to the ideas
astrologically speaking of the heavens
and therefore sometimes assume that when
you see certain things played out on
your charts on your energy agreement
charts you think that it absolutely must
must play out physiologically in your
surrounding solar system many times the
indications you get on the charts are
indications of energy events again the
analogy that a psychic impact will
happen that something will hit from one
dimension to another but not necessarily
that it has to manifest in your
physiological surroundings in again the
same way that there can be a psychic
impact without necessarily experiencing
it in the physiological genetic
thank you that's highly
preferable thank you very much for
creating the reality that you find most
pleasing we thank you for your
sharing sharing hello and to you good
day uh my question is are the pro speak
up so that all may share are the
pyramidal formations photographed by
Nas's Mars Orbiter artifacts of a
civilization or merely
mountains there is to some degree an
artificial construction to them a couple
of them are not
artificial but a few of them are and the
idea now as it begins to
unfold will lead many of you to
realize in what you call a very
scientific way within the next couple of
your decades some of the ideas about
shall we say the origin points of your
civilization or other points that your
civilization has been connected to in
the past how long ago was that a
civilization how long ago were they
constructed longer than what you would
call 100,000 years we do not have a
precise calculation from our dimension
of time to yours were they Homo sapiens
were they ancestors of ours they were
mostly tinged in what you would call the
blue skin range in that sense they are
not strictly human but they are and were
humanoid and there was in Early Times
upon your planet
intermixing a long time
ago I wasn't going to ask this question
but the physician mentioned the uh
goddess estar uh who I was studying today I
estar uh who I was studying today I
found out that she is the same as many
other what was mentioned was not ishar
what was mentioned was ashtar oh there
which is a different connotation
H well my question would stand at why
was the why is the U goddess ashar in
the Hebrew Old Testament at odds with
the Hebrew God
Yahweh the idea has to do and we will
not get into the details of this now for
it will take up quite a bit of time in
your terms of time but the idea has to
do with old belief system
influxes of old belief systems that re
re incarnated upon your Earth back in
those times and met face to face with
the systems that already existed the
systems of belief that already existed
upon your planet in the cultures that
already existed upon your planet when
that new reincarnational influx from
other civilizations came
in some of the definitional differences
that occurred as they existed on your
planet and as they came in from the
other civilizations caused conflict qu
to
occur and some of this is responsible
for the formation of some of the
religions that you now have upon your
planet these early conflicts these early
dichotomies in the belief systems from
one system to
another thank you thank you very much
there will be more on this at another
time we will
delineate quote unquote historically far
more information about those early
influxes later
on
hello Bashar and are you good day my
name is Moren midnight and this is my
second time here all right still my
first I'm a little nervous oh oh can you
say you are excited yes do you prefer to
be excited as opposed to anxious yes all
right do you remember that excitement
and anxiety are the same
energy yeah it's called Energy it's the
same energy excitement and anxiety are
the same energy one from a positive
point of view one from a negative point
of view that's all you get excitement
when you trust in a positive way you get
anxiety when you trust in a negative way
in other words when you doubt but that's
all it is don't worry about it you're
doing just fine we thank you for
co-creating this interaction we are very
pleased to meet you to us you are a gift
of immeasurable knowledge so do
share thank you
um well uh in a nutshell I should say um
three years ago I was um in my career
following my career and I had a
neurological um breakdown and my whole
body became semi- paralyzed how
exciting yes and
uh well the neurologist Di do me is
probably having multiple sclerosis I see
and uh I I kept it quiet I didn't know
how to deal with it I was under
emotional and physical and spiritual
stress from learning that cuz I knew
nothing about it all right and I I got
better and then 6 months later my father
passed away from a heart attack and then
3 months after that my brother died from
heroin and alcohol all right and I've
been dealing with my other brother on
drugs since then so with the fear he we
could lose him I see so a twofold
question also is that um I have had
periodic relapses with my own body and
uh I have I thank you for your an answer
to question number one because I have
done a shift of energy as of last year
and I've become strong and I've done a
lot of spiritual work and I have come a
long way emotionally spiritually and
physically and I have been learning a lot just like
and I have been learning a lot just like
you said and um so my question is um
what can you tell me further about this
and also anything to do with the deaths
and how to work with my brother now so
thank you some of what you are experiencing
you some of what you are experiencing
from our point of
view allow us to clarify that from our
point of view oh
has to do with connections into
agreements in other lives in past lives
that you are carrying over with your
family in this present life that you
have all made agreements together to
reflect certain things to create certain
apparent limitations certain High
degrees of focus to allow you to
expand in very different ways in very
bold ways in very energetic ways
now sometimes times individuals because
of what they are taught to believe
choose to create that expansion in
negative ways and sometimes not meaning
to be factious expand themselves out of
physical reality because they don't know
how to handle it they don't know how to
keep it within the idea of the physical
reality they chose to be born
in so the idea will be that they will
lose touch with their
self-empowerment and in that sense will
feel that they must start as you say
from scratch must clean the Slate and
reincarnate again going into the very
same scenarios to relearn the idea from
a position of power you have learned the
idea from a position of
power you are learning how to transform
the idea in a way that allows you to
idea in a way that allows you to
maintain your focus in the physical
reality and accelerate that physical
reality to create the Energy System the
energy atmosphere
that other individuals that have made
this agreement to whom you are attached
only believed was possible by detaching
themselves from the physical reality to
begin with
completely they found the expansion they
desired in the physical death they found
the relief they desired in the physical
death it gave them an opportunity to
refocus their thoughts so to speak
reassess their understanding of their
approach in that physical life and come
to terms with the realiz ation that they
can reincarnate create the same
scenarios generally not meaning they
have to experience the same ideas of
disease but the same ideas of limited
Focus so that now they can learn that
that idea of limited focus is only
because of the definitions they buy into
and that really life does not hold them
in check it is only their definitions
that hold life itself in check you are
beginning now to understand that your
definitions are responsible for the type
of life you live whereas simply their
belief did not allow them to break
beyond the notion that life in that
sense is responsible for their
definitions that life happens to them
you are learning that life happens
through you not to you now the more you
are willing to live as an example of
this idea the more you can act as a
living reflection for any other
individual who still remain in your
physical reality that have also agreed
to go through similar ideas of
limitation similar ideas of restriction
similar ideas of focus to some degree in
some of the other lives you have
functioned many times as a mother for
all these in other individuals that you
are referring to and to some
degree you have now chosen this life to
somewhat detach yourself from that
position to function more as an equal
yet you retained some of of the
qualities that they could look to if
they chose to but you made it less
obvious so that they would be far more
on their own now at first it may seem as
if they have not learned that they could
fly and have in a sense fallen out of
the physical Nest into another dimension
beyond your reach they are not beyond
your reach they are not beyond their
reach they are just fine they are being
assisted in that sense and have always
been assisted from the non-physical side
to reorient them to allow them to
understand what it was they were going
through in the physical life what the
lesson was they wanted to learn what the
focus was that they put themselves
through to learn that lesson and how
they can expand that focus when they
reincarnate if they choose to it seems
very likely that they will choose to
when they choose to reincarnate in
physical reality they can then go
through the same Exploration with not
quite the same degree of restrictive
feeling for the restrictions they create
you can learn to do this now you have
given each of you have given yourselves
a particular idea of restriction of
limitation according to what you thought
would represent the direction you wanted
to expand into so in other words you
chose a style of limitation that when
you broke through it would give you the
expansion the type of expansion you
believed as a spirit as a soul that you
wanted to experience you follow me so
far yes um I understand you're talking
more about the ones my loved ones who
have died rather than the on who is on
the drugs and dealing with the pain of
the living death he's going through well
that as well though uhhuh we are talking
about that as well because that is a
particular style of limitation and that
particular style of limitation has to do
with putting your power
into the objects around you that is the
whole notion of addiction is assuming
that the objects that the symbols around
you are what contains the power you seek
and therefore having to rely upon them
by not feeling that the power is within
you to change your reality that is what
addiction is all about understand mhm
now your particular idea of choosing
that supposed I will say alleged disease
for it is not something that really was
very strongly ingrained within you only
enough was it ingrained within you to
give you a diagnosis from an individual
that would allow you to focus on what
you needed to focus on it is not very
strong ingrained within you it is quite
malleable quite flexible in you because
you are still the mother figure in that
sense and you are still quite a bit more
flexible than your children they are
still learning and you can teach them
and one of the easiest ways you can
reflect to them one of the easiest ways
you can teach them is by functioning in
full capacity with the unconditional
love but not taking responsibility for
them being responsible to them by being
equal and allowing them to see how they
can be equal to everything in life
that's the key learning to know that you
are equal to everything in life because
it is a projection of your thoughts your
beliefs your emotions understand mhm so
your focus your limitation in no way
shape or form is as shall we say binding
as
theirs understand I feel that very
strongly and I feel that I've let my
brother go who is is now using the drugs
and I've let him do his thing and be who
he is and now this does not mean that
you cannot continue to act as an example
it does not mean that you cannot in a
sense share the idea that he has the
capability of finding his own power it
does not mean that you do not help him
but you do not force anything nor can
you force anything upon anyone else
understand what about um my physical
symptoms I I've been through a lot of
pain emotional as I said emotional
physical spiritual just a horrifying thing I've
spiritual just a horrifying thing I've
been through and I still have periodic
symptoms my eyes my neurological system
what is pain do you have a
definition my definition of pain is that
it um discomfort
I cause it's cause uhhuh what causes
pain what causes the sensation you call
pain um thank you well what's causing it is I
um thank you well what's causing it is I
feel maybe this is not what you want to
hear but I feel it's it's I know it's my
neurological system which is the core of
my being and I have become a lot
stronger but there still are VAR
symptoms that keep me from having my
career you know all right may I ask you
a question yes what is your career the
career you desire to have well the
career I did desire yes was to be
involved with um the public performing
acting well I've obviously it's thrown
me into um I have had a full life of
being involved with the metaphysical and
the do you still desire it oh of course
aside from the pain but I will tell you
Bashar that I'm I've through this I've
become much more involved with
homeopathics anding and nurturing and
mother what you're talking about and
working with people and the
most at the same time that you consider
that do understand that they do not have
to be mutually
exclusive they can coexist that's what
I'm looking forward to if these symptoms
will all so my basic question is if you
can tell me anything to do to further
the we're getting there we're getting
there first in a moment I will give you
our definition of pain okay but right
now I prefer to continue with the
questioning of the idea of of your
career um now you say the pain keeps you
from the career MH so performance all
right the next question I would ask you
is this do you have any fears about
succeeding uh no I don't feel I do and I
feel that I have fear of the stress any
stress that you see stress makes my
symptoms ignite more so anything thank
you thank you thank you now you are
hitting as you said L the nail squarely
on the head why do you define your
career as having to contain
stress I was under the assumption that
your career is something that would give
you Joy it does it does and it's also
lots of things that give you Joy give
you at our Str I your
pardon what an absolutely fascinating
and creative
definition however I choose not to buy
into it
things that give you Joy do not give you
stress I'll rephrase that the things
that give me joy do not give me stress
yeah things that give me stress in that
sense by definition are not the things
that give me
joy understand where did you get this
definition that the things that give you
Joy give you
stress well um and with before you go on
no no no one moment that may have been
the definition you had of course that's
what happened if that's the definition
you have of reality if the things that
give you Joy in your belief system give
you stress then you cannot possibly be
surprised but when you receive stress
when you attempt to do something you
enjoy understand of course that's what
happened because that's the definition
you have now do you prefer that
definition no then why keep it why not
allow yourself to prefer to believe that
the things that give you Joy give you
Joy Joy give you ecstasy give you health
give you
balance why should you assume just
because other people in your Society
have said this is the way it is that Joy
must bring stress where is that written
or chiseled into the fabric of existence
it's not a law of the universe well I
don't believe that I I think you're
coming at me very strongly because I've
it's a statement I said for instance
when I was sitting there I can perform
in front of a group of sitting over
there my heart was pounding 100 miles a
minute because I get very nervous why in
front of people why because I think I'm
afraid is judged and so
what you are the only one who is judging
yourself regardless of what they do the
only way you can feel their judgment is
if you accept it as true which means you
are the ultimate judge of
yourself understand right so you think
all of this emotional is creating my yes
a lot of your definition your belief
system is what is creating your pain
because here is our definition all pain
mental pain spiritual pain emotional
pain physical pain all pain is the
result of resisting your natural
self that's it so when you create a
definition that says my natural self is
this idea that would give me joy and
then add into that equation the idea
that Joy gives you stress you are
discounting your natural self you are
contradicting your natural self you are
creating friction with two contrary and
opposing definitions and forcing them
together and that friction is
experienced that friction of ideology
that friction of definition is
translated in your physical body body as
pain understand mhm so you do not have
to prefer to believe that what gives you
Joy should cause you stress I understand
the idea of the habitual rituals that
many of you have bought
into but examine your definitions
clarify your definitions for you see the
only reason that your disease has
manifested neurologically is because your nerves
neurologically is because your nerves
represent the lines of communication
within you and you have crossed your
circuits with contrary
definitions you have short circuited
yourself and it has manifested in a
disease of the nervous system because
those are the lines of communication
within your body mhm understand so clean
your lines of communication by
clarifying your definition what gives
you Joy gives you Joy what gives you
stress gives you stress if you insist
that what gives you Joy gives you stress
you are going to find yourself short
circuiting cross-wired understand mhm so if
cross-wired understand mhm so if
something gives me stress and I'm
fearful of it it really isn't actually
giving me joy obviously not at that time
you're not allowing it to no you are
interpreting the situation as a
stressful one and you are acknowledging
the idea that the energy will come to
you in stressful ways so of course
you're going to feel it that way you're
going to manifest it that way
physiologically because your physical
reality is only what you define it to be
remember your definitions are physical
reality physical reality does not have
an empirical existence apart from the
definitions you created to be it is the
definitions you created to be that's all
it is that's all physical reality is MHM
the only difference between what you
call physical reality and non-physical
reality is that you have defined
physical reality as solid mhm that's it
it's the only
difference therefore as you think it so
it is many individuals create apparent
disease and friction and blocks and
resistance in their life not because
there is anything empirically or
inherently Difficult about the idea they
have chosen but simply because of the
definitions they have assigned to the
ideas that they have chosen that's why
many individuals do not receive the
things they say they want to receive
because they have attached to it a
negative definition that at the same
time they don't want so it keeps
everything locked in stalemate and that
creates resistance it creates effort and it
resistance it creates effort and it
makes you
tired understand I understand so clarify
the definitions right and allow yourself
to realize that whatever definition you
determine is the definition you prefer
that's what will stick and you don't
need any more reason other than you say
so that's why mhm and being positive yes
attitude is everything many people think
well all right positive attitude that's
all well and good but how does it really
affect the real
reality that definition in and of itself
allows your positive attitude to become
impotent because you are saying there is
a real reality that your positive
attitude cannot affect
instead of understanding that your
attitude is the reality you experience
because it is absolute physics absolute
mechanics all circumstances and all
situations are fundamentally neutral
blank empty devoid of meaning no
circumstance has built in meaning from
the creation you are the assigners of
meaning that's what all the individuals
within creation do that's how all the
individual within creation create
cocreate with the infinite you take the
neutral props that have already been
created the potential realities the
infinite dimensional probable Futures
that have already been created and you
assign a meaning to it that makes that
particular future relevant to you and
therefore capable of being experienced
physically by you but the type of
meaning you assign determines how you
get to experience it so if you
automatically assign a negative
definition a negative meaning a negative
experience is all you can expect if you
assign a positive meaning with a
positive attitude a positive experience
is all you can get it's simple physics
that kind of reality that kind of
experiential reality does not have a
mind of its own it's absolutely at your
mercy understand mhm the reality you get
is the product of the way you have
defined it that's why when you see a
physical manifestation occurring that
you don't prefer it is there to show you
that you have a belief system A
definitional system that is at odds with
what you want use the fact that you are
experiencing something you don't prefer
to put you in touch to allow you to
meditate to allow you to examine
yourself and put you in touch with what
kind of a definition would you have to
have in order to create this kind of a
reality when you have gotten in touch
with what the definition is you can
clarify it you can say well why would I
continue to choose to believe in this
which doesn't reflect what I prefer to
believe in as soon as you understand
that all definitions are equal to any
other definition you will also
understand that the one definition you
have had has no more intrinsic power
than any other definition you could have
so you will say all right this is the
definition I have had now what's the
definition I prefer to have it's this
write it out spell it out see it in
clear letters burning letters whatever
it takes to get your attention see it
whatever it takes to get you excited see
it that way and then know beyond a
shadow of a doubt that what you now see
what you have now redefined is the new
reality no two ways about it no
dichotomy this definition is from this
this point forward your reality act like
that is true have the conviction to
understand that the new definition is
just as valid as the old one you got all
the old reality from the old definition
there were no gaps there were no flaws
there were no hesitations the universe
delivered instantly the reality that was
representative of your old definition
there is no reason why the universe
should not just as quickly deliver the
reality that is representative of the
new definition you have assigned to it
understand I understand does this help
you it helps and I agree with everything
you've said well thank you and um I have
come a long way my strengthening myself
and I plan on going a lot further and uh
thank you very much everything is
infinite in all directions you have all
the time in creation and all the
creation in time it's all up to you and
all within you and we thank you for your
exploration and we thank you for the
unfolding of the Persona you chose to be
thank you my mother's here too thank you
for the connections that you have made
and the connections and relationships
you allow to be reflected back and forth
to each other as aspects of the infinite
looking at itself from all the different
directions that it
can thank you very much our love to you
all we will take this
opportunity to
now shall we say
announce that we recognize as you have
been told a new cycle of our
interactions will begin with you in the
form of what is called your Workshop
format with regard to some
degree from what has just been
discussed the first shall we say title
and the first
Workshop shall be Persona
reconstruction wherein we will learn how
to define what you are as a
personality and step by step how to
reinvent how to
redesign the person you are into the
person you prefer to be with the history
and the future and the present that goes
along with
that
sharing hello Bashar and good day to you
I have a question about about animals on
our planet animals all right speak up so
that all may share and how how these
animals are in a way affecting uh some
of my personal pleasure which is that I
love to go hiking alone in the mountains
yes and so do they yes it's
true and up until recently um I thought
that was just really neat however
recently I was uh uh not in the
mountains but in the city I was attacked
by a dog by a German Shepherd all right
and I started paying more attention to
all the reports in the news about
attacks by Pitbulls and other dogs all
right it got your attention yes yes I'm
wondering why we're having so much
publicity about this now and thanu how I
can deal with my fear about fu fu first
of all generally now always there will
be many specific symbologies for all the
different individuals that exist but
there are also
General symbologies General meanings
that you have assigned as a society to
different symbols in your reality and
the dog generally represents service in
your Society the idea now is that your
Society the idea now is that your
Society is being forced by that symbol
to start looking at the whole issue of
service of being of service of serving
and automatically being served by
serving others in that sense that is the
general Foundation the idea of the lack
of willingness that has existed in
general in your Society to serve and to
support the whole society is now causing
to some degree a reaction in the symbol
that represents service so that it does
however it can Propel you towards facing
those ideas within yourself that allow
you to come to to terms with how you can
be of broader service not only outwardly
but in a sense in learning to love the
self so that in loving the self you can
be of service in the most beneficial
ways outwardly to all members of your
Society is there a specific meaning to
the symbol of what you have called the
animal German Shepherd to
you it's a very strong animal a very
strong animal all right do you believe
that your strength is
equal no why not not after being
attacked by one all right why
not because I approached it very openly
at first I thought he was just being
friendly with me and I love dogs all
right and I was very shocked when he
attacked me all right what did it get
you to
examine it did get me to examine the
issue of self-love all right right how
so I had been berading myself for a
mistake that I had made I see and this
happened at about the same time and the
the circumstances were very similar so
you are telling me that because you
poured out the love to that animal you
did not deserve to be
bit yes yes in the same light why do you
deserve to punish
yourself why do you not deserve absolute
selflove well I guess there's definitely
a connection there isn't there yes why
are you so hard on yourself I don't know
why am I tell me I don't know I've been
working on this for years years and
years and years all right may ask you a
question yes do you have in any way shape or form
yes do you have in any way shape or form
in your imagination a concept of what it
would be like to love yourself fully as
you can
unconditionally a very dim one I'm a lot
more able to understand loving everyone
else and having everyone else love each
other and love me oh all right all right
how is it that you can love anyone else
if you are not a whole
being how can you give love if you do
not believe you are complete enough to
receive love from yourself
if you do not think of yourself as a
whole idea how can you give anything to
anyone that follows and I have thought
of that and sat with that may I ask you
another question yes oh thank you this
is very much
fun it is for me too thank
you do you believe you fit in
creation often times I feel that I do
not fit in my environment all right may
I ask you another question please feel
free to ask any questions you oh thank
you very
much I'm attempting to be very polite
uhoh how is it mechanically possible for
something that exists in a certain
environment to not belong in that
environment well mechanically it's not possible is
well mechanically it's not possible is
it all right no therefore where you are
is where you fit you cannot be where you
do not fit and you cannot experience a
reality you are not the vibration of
conversely whatever reality you do
experience is what you are the vibration
of now
generally if you exist in a reality
where you have a desire to love all
beings where you recognize the idea of
love that you wish to share it that you
wish to give it that you wish to support
if you have been able to concoct that
kind of a notion if you have been able
to conceive of that kind of a service
how could you yourself not belong to
that energy how could you not fit in
that particular event and while you're
pondering that if you are talking about
being desirous of giving un
unconditional love how can it be
unconditional if you're not
included you're quite a logician aren't
you when I am forced to be by your
Society
yes do you have an answer no I'm
speechless that will
do many times simply The Knowing itself
is sufficient you don't have to say
anything if you understand what I am
saying well I'm feeling it so I must
understand it very good very good one
more time I am feeling it so I must
time I am feeling it so I must
understand
it I am feeling it so I must understand
it now that's
conviction and that's deserv ability and
that is self-love who says that you are
incapable of
self-love not you because you have just
demonstrated it fully I am feeling it so
I must understand it you believe in
yourself and that is
self-love see how simple it is you don't
have to work on it for
years well I had a feeling that was the
case and if I just talked to you about
it I could figure out how not to have to
spend more years on it have you figured
it out then well I feel it so yes I must
understand it yes you
do you belong you are made out of
unconditional love that's what
everything and everyone is made of
because unconditional love is the
infinite is existence itself it is the
prime medium unconditional love you must
deserve it or you wouldn't exist
obviously the Infinite Creation believes
you deserve it or you wouldn't have been
created would you have that's true
Infinite Creation does not make
extraneous and pointless Creations does
not create things that don't fit so if
you exist if you EX exist you must
somehow deserve to at least in the eyes
of the Infinite
Creation so why not treat yourself with
the same
respect Why argue with Infinite Creation
about your deserv
ability you always crack me
up well we thank you for allowing us to
also crack you
open does this serve you it serves me
very well bash sure thank you I thank
you for giving us such a gift of love as
your willingness to share and such a
gift as allowing us to see how deserving
all of you are of love because you all
deserve it thank you thank you again Shing
it thank you thank you again Shing
[Applause]
hello friend and good day to you I would
like you to tell me what is my true
place right here right
now thank you wherever you are that's
your true Place once again applying what
we have just talked about how can you be
anywhere else other than what is
representative of the things you need to
know about yourself right now you cannot
really be off your path because a path
is not what you are on a path is what
you are you cannot be off yourself the
idea once again is to Simply recognize
that if you do what excites you the most
with integrity and live in the moment
here and now you are fulfilling all of
the ideas and the Notions that you call
purpose and Mission and place because
the main purpose and Mission and place
of all of your lives is to be to the
fullest that you can whoever it is you
are because there is no one else like
you there never has been there never
will be and even though you are
reincarnational beings the you you are
now only has One Life to Live be that
you to the fullest and that will be the
Fulfillment of your place thank you
thank you very
much at this timing allow us to extend
once again and for the very first time
our unconditional love and our deepest
appreciation in allowing us to
experience and enjoy each and every one
of you individually and
collectively you have a very sweet
taste we thank you we remind you that
you are dreaming right now wake up and
live the dream you prefer to it's your
choice it's up to
you we will
extend to
you a most
joyous a most loving and the most
ecstatic good
Daye thank you
how to go
[Applause] sh