all right I'll say how are you all this
evening of your time as you create time
to
exist allow us to begin this interaction
this evening of your time with a
reminder that last time of your time was
the first part of a three-part summation
therefore the entitlement for this
evening is summation part
two and in the same format as last time
we will begin with an opening idea and
we will also end with an idea as well
now first of all before we begin with
the opening idea allow me to remind
those of you who are already familiar
with this idea that we have discussed
before that this is in a sense in an old
cycle of counting happy New Year for
remember this is your November first
date and in the ancient times of
counting in what you would call
atlantian times what you call your all
hollow's Eve Halloween was the day
before the destruction of Atlantis
November 1st today is the destruction
and tomorrow is the day after what you
call in some of your religious
vernaculars all hollow's Eve All Souls
day and All Saints Day translates into
these ideas of the destruction of your
atlantian land
mass this was brought forward to the
remnants that remembered the remnants of
your civilization that remembered this
idea this catastrophe as you call it and
it was passed through
druidic understandings until you now
have your present day recollection of
hallowen and the idea of the All Souls and All
and the idea of the All Souls and All
Saints Day therefore it is to some
degree in ancient times recognition of
the new year the New Beginning starting
over the new cycle the cycle that you
are in now begun on November 1st rather
than your January 1 so in a very real
way in terms of the energy cycle that
you are in now this day not your January
1st this day is New Year's Day so happy
New Year happy year um now as we spoke
last time we will to some degree
dialogue a little bit in a moment on the
concept of God seeds which each and
every one of you are one of a seed of
God or that which we call all that is
the creation but first we wish to remind
you that when we talk of things when we
talk of terminologies when we use
certain words in your
language many of you because of your
particular Focus because of the focus
that you bring to these interactions
will of course as an individual will
focus on one particular thing and
another portion May Slide by your
Consciousness or you may think that this
word means something but this word does
not now we do not mean this
egotistically but understand every
single thing we say has a particular
meaning and a particular reason for
being chosen all of these interactions
from our civilization to your
civilization are energy
orchestrations there is no accident in
terms of the way your language is
translating through the channel there is
no accident in terms of the pacing and
the inflections that you hear your words
come out in all of these if you listen
with a different portion of your mind
can be seen to be energy
orchestrations so that we may play upon
the particular
vibrations of the language the
particular cadences that your
subconscious and unconscious mind will
live listen to and so that these ideas
will sink most deeply into you where and
when you want them to so you do not
necessarily have to worry that a certain
concept may be new to you that a certain
word may pass you by all levels of your
Consciousness are being addressed in
these interactions and one portion if
not another will understand precisely
and fully what is going on so in other
words you will miss nothing do not worry
relax every single one of you that ows
yourself to be in a relaxed state of
high focus will simply absorb the
information we will share this evening
of your time in exactly the way that is
proper for the individual you happen to
be there is no right way and there is no
wrong way to have this interaction to
share in this exchange the more
excitement you have the more fun you
have the more relaxed you are the more
you will absorb and the more readily you
will allow that information to to come
to the surface exactly and precisely
when and where you need it to be able to
apply it in your physical daytoday lives
and that is another thing that we wish
you to understand many of you will hear
certain terminologies and think that we
are simply using these terminologies to
color or make more flowy some of the
concepts that we are discussing some of
these things only sound flowery or
imaginative or fantasy likee to many of
you because of the definitions your
Society has taught you to understand
many of the concepts that we are talking
about that to you simply sound like
philosophies are to us absolute material
physics and accurately describe the way
reality is experienced and created
physically concretely materially in your
daytoday living experience in your own
as you say down to Earth's pragmatic
day-to-day lives everything we are
discussing with you is not only about
the idea of allowing you to feel more
fully your own self-empowerment feel
more energetic and feel more happy but
to understand that those very attitudes
themselves are actually energy states
that profoundly affect the physical
concrete reality you are capable of
attracting to yourselves so that you can
realiz your dreams literally live them
manifest them physicalize them so you
can touch them smell them taste them
hear them be them and have them manifest
before you so that you know beyond a
shadow of a doubt you are the Creator
literally of your individual
physiological reality and that together
all of you are the co-creators of Your
World reality each and every one of you do
reality each and every one of you do
this automatically each and every one of
you do this because you are extensions
aspects seeds of God because you are as
you say made in the image of God and to
us that simply means you have the same
capacity on an individual level that you
ascribe to the infinite Creator on an
overall expanded level your individual
immediate personal reality is just as
much under your control as the entirety
of creation is under the awareness of
the infinite Creator you by being made
in the image of God you by being a seed
of God are planted are projected in a
particular aspect of the entire universe
in one particular dimensional reality
let us say for now your physical Earth
reality what you understand as your
physical universe is simply one of the
facets of a multi-dimensional infinite
Universe there are many many ways to
live many many forms of life many forms
of expression of Consciousness all of
them are equal no one is better than any
other they are all valid across the
board as you say but they are all vastly
different all unique each and every one
of you as we have said many times is one
of the ways that God has of looking at
itself each and every one of you are one
of the ways that God has of creating it
yourself into
beingness as a seed of God as you choose
to plant yourself in this reality as you
have chosen to project your
Consciousness into this physical
environment so you begin to bloom and
Blossom and stretch up through the Earth
to reach toward the Sun to reach toward
the light of creation and in so doing
you describe your unique floral pattern
your unique coloration your unique
Direction and attributes and talents
each and every one of you is a part of
the garden no one is less important if
you exist then you belong you fit in
nothing is extraneous there is no
leftovers in creation no accidents no
mistakes in that way there is nothing
that does not belong if you exist where
you are then you fit sit there you are a
part of the garden you are one of the
seeds that was originally planted in
that particular area and you are a part
of the color and the joy of that
particular Garden each of you have a
place each of you deserves all the light
in that sense that you can soak up but
you now can realize that you no longer
have to fight for that space only
flowers that do not believe they do not
belong in the garden believe they have
to fight for enough light to live if you
know that you are a part of the original
package shall we say then you know that
you belong and you know that that light
that happiness that joy that ecstasy
that fulfillment that realization that
manifestation is your Birthright because
you are where you are and there is more
than enough for everyone well all right
all right I'll be more precise there is
exactly just enough for everyone exactly
precisely just enough for every single
one of you that exists in any particular
dimensional reality now everything that
we have been discussing with you in the
many various forms that we have been
discussing it for the past 5 years of
your counting has all of course been
focused on the idea of allowing you to
remember that you have this power within
you as your
Birthright that we are only reflecting
your power to you we are not giving you
power we are not taking your power we
have enough of our own we don't need
yours you have enough of your own you
don't need ours and besides since you
are a complete idea in and of yourself
there is nowhere to fit our power into
yours since we are complete there is
nowhere to fit your power into our
reality anyway but as mirrors for each
other we can reflect what we have done
with our understanding of power and you
reflect what you have done with your
understanding of power now in observing
your garden our garden has come to
understand that there may be shall we
say situations that you have created
that you have chosen that would make it
seem as as if there are many weeds in
your garden and that living in that Garden is
garden and that living in that Garden is
a struggle that there's not enough water
not enough light and not enough soil not
enough nutrients to go around and
therefore you have as a civilization
started trying to uproot everyone else
and spread your roots out so that you
will have more more more more more me me
me me me but the idea you see once again
is that if you understand that everyone
by virtue of the fact that they exist
belongs where they are then you can
relax those definitions relax those
expectations relax those negative belief
systems and you can know that you and
they will spread your roots out and you
will intertwine those roots in exactly
precisely the type of tapestry that is
required for each and every one of you
to get exactly as much water exactly as
much light exactly as much nutrient as
you need for the flour you have decided
at any given moment that you are when
you decide that you are going to be a
different flower a bigger flower a
flower of another color then when you
live as that flower when you live with
that conviction when you change the idea
of the seed that you are then you are
automatically given the light you need
the additional soil you need in the way
you need it to be that flower while at
the same time excluding no one else the
garden is big enough for all and the
garden is big enough for all you can
possibly become remember that that the
idea of becoming is also a part of the
package you do not have to think in
limitation you don't not have to think
well there's just enough for what we are
now but what if we decide to change what
if we decide to grow what if we decide
we want more what if we decide we are
more what if we decide we must expand to
survive there is already in the template
of the garden enough room for all the
expansion you could ever do in that
Garden that was a part of the original
design the Creator knows what it is
doing trust that the template is
infinite understand what that means
infinite you will never never never
never never never never never never
never never never never never use it
never never never never use it
up never never run out never not ever no
never ever there is always enough always
ever there is always enough always
because it is infinite and I understand
I understand and I am not belittling You
by saying what I'm about to say I
understand that because of the way many
of you have been taught to think that
the idea that there is more than enough
for everyone no matter how much you expand
everyone no matter how much you expand
and that there will still be room for
everyone even if everyone expands to
infinite proportions and there's still
enough room I understand that that
concept doesn't always fit very neatly
into the third dimensional physical box
reality that you believe exists but you
are more than that you exist on every
level that there is to exist
upon your experience of life in the
third dimensional box reality is simply
one of your
faces one of your sides one of your many
aspects and the idea is to understand
that expansion is only the process of
expansion is only the process of
remembering more and more and more and
more of the garden that already exists
more and more and more remembrance of
the flower you already are on many
different levels and simply becoming
that expansive flow that expanded seed
which contains all the potential for
worlds and
universes take your lesson from the
physical seeds upon your
planet as many of you have already
pointed out over and over again though
many of you just think it's a nice story
look at the difference between the size
of a small seed and the tree it becomes
there are worlds inside every point in
space universes inside every grain of
sand it is literal it is not a poetic
analogy grains of sand universes in
grains of sand oh that sounds nice it
makes me feel expanded but it was simply
a nice analogy to get me going to make
we think nice thoughts and to have a
pleasant day yes it is for that too but this is
day yes it is for that too but this is
what I was discussing earlier many times
when you hear phrases like that there
are universes in a grain of sand you
think well isn't that nice that he said
that oh it makes me feel so very
pleasant it's a nice feeling warms me up
inside but of course you can't really
take it literally it's just a metaphor
it's just an analogy no it is
not every single
point in space and time contains the
totality of all space and time that's
why you can be whatever you want
wherever you want whenever you want
because you have access to all of it
wherever whenever and whoever you are
because each and every one of you is
such a point such a seed and you contain
the totality of all of it now that does
not necessarily mean that the totality
of the universe will be expressed
physically at every single point in a
physical reality it does not need to and
by the definition of your physical
reality you don't necessarily want it to
having every single thing you could ever
do it exactly one place at one time
would get a little shall we say
claustrophobic perhaps for you but the
idea is to understand that what
motivates you the strongest what excites
you the most is the light of your inner
being excitement is the inner light of
who and what you most truly
are follow that light reach for that
light go for that light let it give you
the Life Force to Blossom in that
direction it will always come into being
if you follow it always always always no
exceptions none never
ever you are not expected to struggle
you are not expected to
suffer that kind of a garden is one of
the gardens that can be experienced in
the infinite Garden of all that is it is
no more and no less than any other type
of garden if it's not the type of garden
you prefer you have the right to change
the garden the idea of the garden you
live in everybody
in everybody
wins you do not have to think if I win
you lose that is one type of reality and
you can experience it that way if you
want to if you believe you must if
that's the laws you set down for
yourself but remember many times when
you think this is a law of creation it
is only a belief it is only an
assumption that you are creating to be
solid because you believe it must be so
because you have been taught to believe
it must be so forever and ever and never
but there is only one only one law in
creation only one just one it's that
simple yes just one what is it I'll tell
you thank
you what you put out is what you get
back that's it it is the basis for all
reality physical non-physical all levels
of conscious
the vibration you are the beliefs you
hold most strongly the emotions you
exhibit most strongly the energy you put
out most strongly is the reality the
reflection you get back most strongly
you are literally what you think
literally it is simply that in physical
reality you have created a reality where
there is the concept of Space volume
Dimension and time so sometimes you can
create an experience where what you
think and what you experience may have a
lag time between it it takes time for
certain things to manifest in physical
reality and non-physical reality takes
no time when you physically die you
become a spirit form of Consciousness
you become a thought form and a world of
thought form and exactly the instant you
think of a concept that's the reality
you experience around you seemingly
tangibly solidly fully fully realized
physical Reality by definition contains
the parameters space and time therefore
what you think is still what you get but
you experience a slower process of
manifestation in a linear conceptual
form one aspect after another aspect
beginning middle ending these are all Concepts
middle ending these are all Concepts
they are all tools they are all
perspectives of physical reality because
that's the definition of this particular
reality that you have chosen to exist
within however now that you are speeding
up now that you are accelerating by
exploring what you are as a
Consciousness you are dissolving the
barriers the definitions that formerly
allowed you to compartmentalize your
physical reality into such a rigid
structure now you are beginning to
realize that all the platitudes and all
the ideas that you formerly were taught
were laws of reality and that's the way
it is and you must do it such and such
or you won't get this now you're
beginning to understand there are many
roads many ways now you're beginning to
realize that each and every one of you
is a different way to realize creation
through you you're a gate a doorway a
window an Eye of Creation and Eye of
Creation that sees itself in a different
way from that
eye but you have in your species two
eyes you have a left you have a right
the left eye sees things a little bit
differently than the right eye do you
rebuke the left eye because it sees
things differently than the right do you
rebuke and chastise the right eye
because it sees things a little bit
differently than the left no because why
because you know you need both of them
to gain perspective
all of you all of you are the eyes of
creation Unity on your planet will be
the result of respecting the different
points of view the diversity of
perception on the whole planet the
Gathering of all the differences the
respecting of all the differences is
what creates Unity many of you have been
taught to believe that Unity must be at
the expense of individuality you all
have to become clones robots mindless
automatons in order to have Unity you
must all think alike act alike never
vary that is not so Unity true balanced
Unity exciting effervescent energetic
creative Unity is the product of the
strengthening of all the individuals and
the equalization of all the individual
points of view you
are so
seeds grow up to be different flowers
even of the same variety the different
flower slightly different here one petal
facing this way one leaf cocked that way
and it is the variety that adds wonder
and adds Delight to the Garden you all
know this we know you all know this and
all we're doing is reminding you of what
you already know this is not boring for
us we Delight in it because we love you
unconditionally and because we desire if
you should ask well what do you get out
of helping us I'll tell you we get out
of it knowing that if any of you decide
if any of you choose to live the same
type of ecstatic exuberant reality that
we have chosen to live then you will
join the vibration of our reality and
there will be that many more points of
view in our reality that adds delight
and color to the Garden in which we live
that's what we get out of it and
expanded reality that gives us more to
explore forever and ever and ever so we
thank you we thank you for allowing us
to speak to you at this time we thank
you for allowing us to interact with you
we thank you for choosing that our
Gardens at least on some level should
blend so that the vast variety in both
Gardens can Delight the eyes of Creation
in all that it
is in return at this time for the gift
that you are giving to us of acting as
ambassadors and representative of your
civilization in return for the gift of
allowing me to function as a
representative of the many hundreds of
millions of beings in the various
civilizations of which we are a part I
ask you now in return for this gift in
what way may I be of service to
you tri treat sure and to you all Hollow
Z it's a pleasure to talk with you again
and you as well uh before we begin I'd
like to let everybody know what we've
been doing together for the past years
briefly brief three years ago Bashar
suggested a an experiment we might run
to approximate the method by which his
craft Works in our atmosphere uh and he
outlined a series of experiments me out
run and the result of it is back there
it's roughly our third model uh over
three years time and many hours of work
in the lab and in the shop Etc many fun
yeah it's been a jazz it's really been a
lot of fun and I thought you might
comment on it uh you've seen it as Daryl
at least I and uh you made mention to
Steve earlier my partner that uh it was
one thing and we had spoken as it was
another thing and uh I'd like you to
expound expound upon that all right
thank you very much now do understand of
course and again in no way shape or form
I know you will know this is not a
belittlement but we are starting with to
use an analogy the model te of
saucers absolutely because the
technology is to some degree new for
your Society you understand sure look
what Happ all right now there are many
different ideas that we now use for what
you would call propulsion and of course
as we have discussed what we use isn't
really propulsion anymore at all sure
the idea is that our vibrational
resonance changes the universal reality
that our spacecraft relate to and we
simply instantaneously retranslate
ourselves from Universe to Universe
without spending any time intervening
travel from one point to another sure
but the idea of what you have is a
generating device to generate a
particular kind of vibrational
electromagnetic pulse which can actually
have many different uses many different
applications some of which will actually
be Medical in nature by surrounding
individuals with a particular field by
allowing them to relate to a particular
vibration they can then key off of that
vibration and align themselves with the
electromagnetic resonance field of your
planet and so bring themselves back to a
zero rest balance point of perfect
health that is one of the things that
your device can assist people within now
one way to pick up upon the
resonances of the device that you have
is to increase its sensitivity in the
following way not that you have to make
any changes in the device per se but you
will find that this device will give off
energies that some of your instruments
may not be able to really read on all
levels you will get some readings but
not necessarily on all levels what you
can do if you wish to take a more
sensitive reading in is you can surround
your device with a series of very thin
walled highly conductive tubes of metal
have them
suspended on very fine string or wire so
they are not based on anything not
touching anything not held rigid in
anything in that sense and then you
can find that the electromagnetic field
that your device will generate will
cause vibrations to exist in those tubes
and then you will be able through the
tubes to have increased the degree of
sensitivity that your devices can pick
up upon by taking readings off the tubes
directly instead of readings off of the
energy field of the device itself you
follow me it's like a fine voltmeter so
to speak yeah sure
now in the central
disc when we first discuss the idea of
having the different areas around the
central disc that your brush would touch
MH we did if you will recall discuss
that there ought to be perhaps a few
more of those alternating areas than you
have constructed how many have you
constructed three on top and three on
bottom all right why not the original 20
that we talked about oh there are 20
coils I didn't realize you meant 20
segments on the disc
yes now you see the idea is because if
you refer back to the original
information we said that as those
different areas touch the brushes it
flops the field back and forth flops
poing it three times back and forth will
give you some effect but 20 times back
and forth will give you a much stronger
effect this just the function of the
angular velocity of the disc though if
you spin it faster you're going to get
that many commutations no because
remember you are fixed to a number of
revolutions and it is the idea of the
number of flops per the number of
revolutions that is important if you
have to speed it up in order to get the
same number of flops you are in a sense
counterbalancing yourself you understand
and making a new disc isn't that
difficult all right m we would suggest
that you will get a much stronger effect
if you have many segments at least 20 so
that you will get a much higher flopping
back and forth of the polarity mhm you
understand surely all right St do
experiment with what you have because
you will get some effect you will see
some reading and it can give you some
understanding of how to go and do
understand as we have already said the
device as you already have it
constructed actually will be of benefit
in certain ways because a lower
resonance device will be necessary for
certain applications where the higher
resonance device may actually be too
dangerous especially for biological
applications you follow me you don't
want to be too close to it anyway yes MH
one more thing U I had a dream just
maybe a month ago that uh I was in a
room with a professor and a number of my
associates and uh the room started
spinning the room started spinning so
hard I was clawing the walls yes and I
was trying to reach my hand out the
window I couldn't even get my hand out
the window and it was all all over and I
and asked my professor what was going on
he said well you found yourself in an
infinitely accelerating reference frame
very good I don't know how much you guys
know about reference frames and we talk
about them all the time and you talk
about the field as an isolation field a
removal from space yes as as you guys
understand it it is exactly the same
thing that's what I thought and in a
sense that is what you are building is a
generator for that infinitely
accelerating reference frame you were
attending a physics lecture on a higher
plane you were getting the answers that you
you were getting the answers that you
need learn how to translate the
symbology that you have learn how to
bring back that information you have
gone there many times and apply it to
what you are doing you are being given
all the information and all the answers
you require great does that help yeah
you're tremendous thank you very much
our regards to everybody over there our
love to you as well thanks bash
sharing hi there and to you good day do
speak up and be bold so that all may
share definitely okay I have one
question I just want to know what's the
lifeline between my mother Nicole Davis
and myself what is the life yeah past
life connections or anything many there
are many many many there is never only
one with anyone that you are very
emotionally close to in this life there
are many many many now again in line in
keeping with the idea of knowing that
you have your own power and that that we
are here to help you remember that you
have your own power I will tell you this
first as a foundation this goes for all
of you if for some reason your curiosity
allows you to drift into the idea of
past life
recognition allow yourself to understand
very simply first of all very easily
first of all any particular area or era
in your history when you think of
another person and you think where was I
connected with this person any
particular area that excites you the
most that comes up the strongest that
you have the strongest attraction to in
a sense is your general answer you at
least are that sensitive of a barometer
the areas you are most attracted to are
the areas of most significance for you
right now you understand mhm in other
lives other areas may have had more
significance or different significance
because that is a different focus at
that moment you understand the linear of
what you are calling reincarnation is
not exactly correct it is a mult mul
dimensional simultaneous Incarnation on many
simultaneous Incarnation on many
different levels at once it is all going
on right now all the lives are being
lived right now your perception that it
is a linear tracing backwards in time is
simply a perception of this physical
life in the way you have been taught to
look at space and time so understand if
you feel a close connection with that
individual you are calling your mother
right now then simply Main maintain are
you paying attention mhm maintain the
vibration that feeling you know what
that connection feels like yes capture
that feeling right now do you have a
lock on it I always do she's very close
to me all right feel the vibration now
specifically do you feel it I always
have all right do you feel it now yes
thank you as you are now feeling it right now
you as you are now feeling it right now
in the present let your imagination
rft and ask your question where are some
of the strongest Connections in other
lives that are going on right now what
comes into your
imagination I've been told that I was um
a princess back in Atlantis I not ask
you what you had been told well my my
strongest impression why is that your
strongest impression cuz I feel
real infinite just a real strong tie with
infinite just a real strong tie with
back then all right are you doing
anything in your life similarly now that
you know you did back then are you
repeating any Cycles in a different way
I want to be a singer I'm going to be a
singer so and you studied the idea of
tone and vibration back then more than
likely yes more than likely all right
does that feel correct to you yes it
does all right understand before we go
on this is the most important point of
the whole issue of past life reality
whatever it is that feels correct is the
strongest signal to you whether or not
you have an absolutely accurate fix on
the precise details of that life isn't
always that critical the energy that
feels correct the energy that you can
apply in the present life in a way that
excites you that is what the focus is
all about you understand yes yes just
sometimes sometimes I get mixed emotions
like one part of me will know the truth
One Moment One Moment I understand what
you are saying one part of me does this
one part of me does that mixed emotions
but let me rephrase this idea in a
different way okay you are not a
collection of Parts Waring with each
other for some form of
dominance that will then somehow
magically mysteriously balance out into
the truth you are at any given moment
the absolute result of the belief system
you hold most strongly to be true you
are not a part fighting with this part
you are at one moment perhaps the person
who believes more strongly in the doubt
in the negative in the things you don't
prefer and then perhaps in the next
moment you are the person that more
strongly believes in the things you do
prefer but those are two different
realities completely exactly now you may fluctuate
completely exactly now you may fluctuate
back and
forth and through that fluctuation and
through that exper experience come to
some form of balance that you then
prefer but if you consider yourself to
be at war with yourself like one parts
off here one parts off there it may
cause undue stress in your
system you understand yeah know I don't
feel that way all the time just once a
month all right I don't
know just trying to up the just trying
to break up the monotonous here I feel
like no you feel like what I just feel
great to be here I just wanted to say
thank you too for your sharing if this
came unexpected my name was dropped in
the Hat so it was like
yeah very good that is a very nice way
to create your reality EX full of
surprises exactly you know been having a
lot of that yeah all right especially my
dream and this dream of singing yes you
are a singer yes um yes I've seen it for
scene yes yes yes yes to sing yep yes
very much so and you are a singer yes
yes why because I haven't really got
into a band that much I mean I've had a
little bit experience band are you
talking about a particular frequency
no now I'm really diry ritten no a group
a group yeah musical performers stuff
like that and so you are saying that the
only definition you have of being a
singer is by belonging to a particular
group no not really I used to work for
luy and Safeway and I used to sing for
the customers and they loved it so right
all right you
know and so you are therefore definitely
a singer yes yes all right now are you
implying somehow that you are not doing it as
somehow that you are not doing it as
fully as you would like exactly when
will you soon soon yeah do you have a date no
you soon soon yeah do you have a date no
I don't not that atted dat no my first
priority is to move out of I live in I
reside in Lake Tahoe area Lake Tahoe
area all right your first priority is
move to move yeah why why because I
don't like being the cold spot of the
nation and that's what trecky is usually
it's um like 10 deg or so all right
sometimes not not often just a few days
Lake Taho
now now no a part ofy yes but part part
there go Parts
again I why do you keep leaving parts of
yourself all over the place I don't
know I don't know why is a part of you
there yeah because a part of me is going
to be looking for new housing here in
San Diego part of you I see yeah do you
sell a house to a part of you
I no may I ask you a question sure where
is your mother where's my mom she lives
right outside of Phoenix outside yeah
and she took me to sedon and St she
lives all right all right she's very
attuned what did you find was
strengthened in your connection by going
to the area you call Sedona oh I love it
it's a very very special to me very I
what do you find was strengthened in the
connection between you and your
mother um Sedona it just you know I have
I didn't see her for a long time so I
went up there because she's been ill and
um stop stop stop stop thank you there
was also a very strong life in what you
would call Chinese terms where the
individual you now call your mother
instructed you in the use of the temple
bells again a reference to the idea of
sound you understand okay yeah now the
vibrations that exist in Sedona are very
highly electromagnetic and also brought
up some of that
resonance is there a particular area
that you would like to move to from your
Le
Taho um anywhere except downtown LA I
just I prefer yeah I prefer like San
Diego somewhere warm oh right yeah I
have is that your strongest preference
your San Diego yeah I feel that's where
we're more of the business is as far as
music all right when will you be there
hopefully within the next month
hopefully yes I'm projecting it all
right one month is more than enough time
for your belief system to say that you
will be in San Diego unless I get snowed
in then I don't
know all right let us know up
there all right now
uh you feel happy yes always you feel
like you are doing what you really love
to
do once I start singing yes I've seen it
in foreseen dreams I all right then I
would suggest you start singing right
now yes
yes yes all right and I will give you an
analogy mhm you are a ship like our
ships many people have seen our ships of
various types of various civilizations
from time to time depending upon the
circumstances you will hear a harmonic
vibration coming from the ship many
people have assumed that this harmonic
hum is somehow a side effect of the
propulsion system of the ship it is
not it is what induces the ship to
move it is the harmonics of the
vibrational realities the ship is moving
through it is a side effect to some
degree what you are hearing but the
harmonic vibrations actually induce the
ship to go from place to place so when
the ship starts singing that's when it
moves you understand my meaning yes I
hear it a lot I always thought it was
Gabriel or something say down the horns
of Gabriel all right there is an analogy
in your Bible about that and to some
degree that is actually what they are
referring to are the harmonics of some
of our SP craft yeah cuz I hear it now
the idea is that as soon as you start
singing as soon you start being that
singer by surrounding yourself with that
vibration you will automatically slide
along the paths that are representative
of the vibration that you are through
your singing Do the singing and you will
automatically move you'll not have to
hope or worry about anything you will
just slide into the proper slot you
understand yes yes I do I think it's
more mainly getting the courage up to go
the courage up do it moment
why why do you need extra special
courage to Simply Be what the singing
tells you you already naturally are you
are down your own vibration I just don't
know how well I would react CU in my
four scene dreams when I was singing
there was a major crowd out there and I
just it just I don't know everyone who
chooses to expresss will always find the
audience that reflects who and what they
are on whatever level they are ready to
express thems remember remember what did
we already say the only law in creation
is what you put out is what you get back
so if you feel for some reason all right
all right I'm not ready for that big
audience sing on whatever level you are
comfortable and know that the audience
that will be representative of that
level of comfort will be there but there
really is no reason why you should fear
the larger audience because because if
and you can use this in a reciprocal
idea of understanding if you should
attract an audience that large then if
you have done so that must mean that's
what you're putting out therefore it's a
perfect match you will come up to that
level you will perform as you need to if
that audience is there you must have the
capacity to amuse them and please them
otherwise it would have been a smaller
audience you understand yes you only get
the vibration you on you cannot
experience a reality you are not the
vibration of so if you see thousands
millions of people there to see you that
must be representative of the level you
are capable of returning to them it must
be you cannot get something more than is
representative of what you're capable of
being you understand exactly sometimes I
just think a little doubt moves in there
and then I it doesn't matter if it does
remember doubt is not a lack of faith
is an infinite faith in something you
don't prefer you understand it is not a
lack of faith and it doesn't matter if
you choose to say it's there it doesn't
matter having a doubt doesn't mean you
can't still do what you
want unless you believe it must mean
that you can say all right I'm afraid
all right I doubt but I still want to do
it so I'm going to you can have a
reality definition where you say I doubt
but I still do
you understand yes you don't have to
have a reality that says the doubt stops
what I want you can say I doubt but I do
anyway I think it will get easier for me
once I start doing it and really
concentrating all on that quit bagging
groceries and give that all all right
you do remember you are a 100% being and
if you are doing something 30% that is
not who and what you are you cannot
expect the thing you really want to
manifest any more than 70 you want
understand exactly thank you very much
thank you too and thank your mother for
choosing in this life to create such a
beautiful resonance a beautiful song
between you that you support each other
in that way do not doubt what is obvious
within your own life do not doubt the
energies you know are there it is not
that she is there because you need that
support because you need that
encouragement intrinsically the
connection between you is there to let
you know that you created that reality
too and that all of the energy of that
connection is in your reality as well as
all the energy of the connection between
you is also in her reality remember you
are both 100% beings it's not exactly in
the way you mean it 50/50 I have 50% you
have 50% no a 50/50 situation is a truly
balanced situation when you are 100% and
so is she you understand yes this was
one of her questions she wanted me ask
you thank you very much and thank you
thank you too and I I got your whole
planet system down thank you too our
love to you you too byebye sh who's next
ahead hello Bashar hello to you good day
at our last meeting so number four be
number three all
right that's correct at our last
meeting I mentioned to you that um the
House of Lords St UFO study group in
Parliament yes had had a sickness of
their um leader yes and um you suggested
that I go over there because a new
leader will be found yes well I went to
Parliament and found a new leader yes
and uh was a little bit disappointed OED
with uh uh his approach all right he uh
heard me out and uh we've been
exchanging information for a
decade and um the new uh leader of the
House of Lords decided after my visit to
close down entirely the committee in
Parliament which represents 50 million
Englishmen what did you
say was it something you said
we we offered we offered to uh um make
an appointment for Bashar to speak to
Parliament yes and he declined on on the
on the um and the reason being that the
channel um was presenting the
information and not taking
responsibility for the content of it all
responsibility is taken but there are
different levels to the idea of
understanding what that means understand
the channel fully takes responsibility
for what the channel allows to come through
what the channel allows to come through
you understand that I understand it but
I could not make the point well that is
all right but understand also that is
not really the
reason there is much information now
that is coming to light about their
involvement in what you may call much
suppression of information yes the idea
now is that in their terminology in your
vacular things are getting a little too
for them yes so it is all right you
found a new leader I did not say the
leader would be compatible with your
desires no you did
not but the new leader is representative
of what you may call the dark before the
dawn they are now in a sense scrambling
around to some degree not to disparage
them they are scrambling around to make
sure everyone is in a safe position when
the information finally breaks they are
well now I will not be rude they are
covering their
[Laughter] posteriors you understand yes I do
posteriors you understand yes I do
understand um but it it Le it leaves me
um a sort of uh Cut Loose from the idea
of uh informing them of my knowledge um
of
UFOs understand we understand but do
understand also that the ones who have
actually caused the a of that department
in many ways obviously know just as much
as you do c certainly or they would not
be running around like they are so there
is really nothing you have to teach them
per se except now you have made them
aware you have done the service of
making them aware of the fact that there
are many shall we say leaks and that the
information is now coming in on them and
that they must do what they can to
create a system whereas when that
information is processed through will
allow ow them to in their own mind
survive as best that they can and come
up smelling like a rose you understand
yes I do you have to some degree
accelerated the process had they still
maintained the department in a sense it
would have been a sign that they still
didn't feel that you necessarily knew as
much as they did they would not
necessarily have felt threatened by it
they would not necessarily have felt
that the information break was imminent
but you have accelerated the process by
letting them know that there is now
information approaching them from many
different sources information that they
thought was secret that no longer is you
understand yes so you have provided that
service very well and in a sense you
have delivered the most important
message I could have delivered to them
anyway get ready you
understand thank you P oh thank you for
being such a wonderful Emissary do you
want to ask about Billy Myers please ask
yes yes if I may ask another question
you may ask I may not
answer um and this p um month I visited
a a Swiss citizen Billy Meyer who who
has had an 11y year ongoing encounter
with UFO contacts with the pleades to
some degree not as much lately as you
might think his last encounter was in
August of this
year and uh um his original Mission was
to was to make all the UFO uh contacts
and information known to the world yes
and it was done and it was done and he
has gotten nothing but has had nothing
but regrets for doing this yes because
of the reactions of your Society they've
been very bad he's had another attempt
on his life yes and he is in seclusion
but I saw him all right well that is why
to some degree not in a very strongly
accelerated manner but to some degree
some of the pleadians are also
contacting other individuals as well but
do understand that Billy as you say
chose to be one of the vanguards one of
the the forerunners and take the brunt
of the ridicule many things have become
Twisted much of the information is now
no longer reliable because it has been
interspersed with false information but
the ice has been broken the job has been
done to some degree and in a very real
way Billy can relax a lot more than he
thinks because now information is being
spread to other individuals he is not
bearing the brunt alone though he may
have created for himself a little bit of
a rut where he thinks he is burdened by
the entire weight but he is not some of
the things that he is experiencing now
are due to Simply his own reactions of
becoming caught up in the idea of the
Intrigue that he did to some degree
bring out in other people but he does
not necessarily have to be quite so
strongly focused in that area at this
time for he is no longer bearing the
brunt of the entire dispersal of the
information you understand yes but uh
very recently there was a 2-hour
broadcast which uh was on National
Television in this country and um the
the um program seemed to be uh very
informative on UFOs but the announcer
made a statement that of course Billy
Meyer is a hoax that statement was made
in your terminology based on certain
information that they did not research
thoroughly it was based on information
that has come to light to some degree to
discredit that particular idea
understand that they could say no more
than that because they had no more
information than that the purpose of the
program was to focus on the idea of the
interaction between your society and the
society that is called Zeta iul anyway
those were simply comments that were
made because they felt they were
necessary to add into the idea but there
really was no informational research
that was done and those statements that
statement in a sense was in your term
simply off-handed you understand yes it
was based on the idea and this does not
take into a fact all of the ideas does
not take into account all of the facts
but that statement was based on the idea
that at one point in the contact of the
pleadians with Billy Meer when some of
the photographs were taken Billy Meyer
constructed a model so that photographs
of the model could be taken to see if
there was any difference between
photographs of the model and photographs
of the real ships so that it could be
proven that photographs of the model
could be detected as such and that
photographs of the real ship were
photographs of the real ship because of
the difference in quality between the
two it's absolutely correct the model
was simply found and taken to be proved
Pro that Billy Meyer had faked all of
the photographs you understand yes now
the idea was simply based the statement
that was made on that program was simply
based on that and other assumptions and
that is why they could not really go
much into it because they had not really
done their research on that they were
simply throwing it in because they had
received the information but they did
not dwell on it the purpose of the
program was to more familiarize your
Society with one of the strongest
contacts going on now between your
society and that which is called Zeta
reticulum you understand yes we thank
you and there will be more information
on that now that so much is coming to
light now that individuals are willing
to listen to this dialogue there will be
more information forthcoming very
rapidly we thank you for the part that
you have played so far and the part you
will continue to play thank you
sh greetings p and to you good day I
have a personal question a personal
question all right if you could reflect
to me why I don't recall dreams that
seem to be full of conflict anger so
much so that I cry out at night and wake
my husband they have no recall all right
first I'll ask you a
question do you want to recall what
gives you such fear yes I do why so that
I can face it may I ask you another
question yes please you are saying then
to me that quote unquote knowing the
details will allow you to handle the
fear more readily I believe so all right
can you believe that the experiences you
are having quote unquote the having of
the nightmares themselves can you
understand that that in and of itself is
a process which is processing fear
through you that it is releasing that
fear that it is one way to deal with the
fear yes I understand that all right do
you understand that having those
nightmares then can be allowing you to
have less in your life to fear
about I understand that all right
now what to the best of your knowledge
as a conscious being as you are a
conscious being right now what to the
best of your knowledge are the things
that you are most afraid
of whether they have cropped up in your
dreams or not what are you most afraid
of not use your imagination now not
having a purpose in life not having a
purpose does that cause you to tremble
with fear no all right but is that the
thing you are most afraid
of it's a feeling that I I don't find
excitements in my life you don't find
excitements all right is there some
particular thing that you would like to
do that you are not doing no are you
doing everything that you can think of
that would excite
you to some extent to some extent I
don't have I can create more in my
imagination and in my mind yes and get
satisfaction from that better than I do
in the material world
why what do you think what definition do
you have about the material world that
says that what is in your imagination
cannot be manifest in
it because once I've done it in my mind
I don't need to do it in the material
world I've already experienced that
experience all right but what about the
idea of sharing what you have
experienced with others other s how can
you do that without some form of
material transference or do you not want to share
transference or do you not want to share
that idea with anyone
else are you wanting to keep all the fun
to
yourself no all right in what way do you
think would be the most exciting way you
could share what your imagination comes
up with that you enjoy so
much through verbal communication or
through writing well is that not one
form of material
manifestation yes all right would that
excite you to do so yes it would all
right do you see yourself perhaps in
that sense therefore giving imagination
seminars to help other individuals who
may feel that their imagination is
somehow poor to be able to enrich their
imagination so they can have fun in
their imaginations too what about that
idea without being imagination
director does that excite you no
no in what form then would the sharing
of what is in your imagination with
other people excites you through writing
or through personal one-on-one contacts
ah all right then it would be our
suggestion that you use the sparkling
imagination you have said that you have
and come up with some form of
advertisement to let other people know
that that service is
available and then do it does that give
you pleasure
yes will you do it yes I will when you
take even the smallest first step
towards exteriorizing what is within your
exteriorizing what is within your
imagination you set everything in motion
to allow what is in you to manifest in
larger and larger degrees materially
around you but the reason it's not
manifesting and the reason you don't
think it can be manifested easily in
your physical reality is you're not even
taking the first step you are keeping it
within you you are not letting it out
you're not letting anyone know who you
are what you are you're not sharing it
with your physical
reality remember as we said it's what
you put out that determines what you get
back not what you keep to
yourself big secret I am this big
energetic fun imaginative being and no
one else
knows that may feel wonderful to you but
as long as you have chosen to exist in a
reality where there are also other
people to share it with as long as you
have chosen to exist in a reality where
what is in you can manifest in an
exteriorized reflection give it the
opportunity to do so by sharing it
exteriorly in whatever way does give you
Joy you follow me yes I do and that will
set the whole thing in motion and it
will accelerate does that help yes it
does very much well thank you very much
when you start to get it out of your
system it will not block up and create
more and more and more fear to scare it
out of you you understand yes because
you see the idea of the nightmares with
no apparent way to understand it is a
pressure building up with no outlet and
when the pressure builds to a certain
point it must create an outlet now you
want to be in control of what that
outlet is you don't want to play the
game of being out of control break down
and have to pull yourself back together
to decide that you can create the outlet
now to release all the pressure the
outlet is simply doing it in whatever
way excites you the most use the
imagination you say you have and create
a way to exteriorize it that will
release the pressure and that will allow
you to sweeten the dreams you understand
yes I do thank you very much I thank you
forar sharing
good evening bash and to you good day
thank you for being here at this time
thank you for being
there may I ask you to uh please step
aside and allow the galactic
Consciousness to come
through second half all right sold so
I'll give my question to someone else
then the
idea is to understand first of
all that the
ways of
energy that will come through in the
second half that are more representative
of the galactic
Consciousness more directly
representative of the galactic
Consciousness will have a particular
frequency to them
long low strong waves I will let let you know
low strong waves I will let let you know
when they
begin when they begin as the galactic
Consciousness comes through simply allow
yourself at that time to go into a
meditative State close your eyes and as
the galactic
speaks you then will find your Affinity
with that vibration your connection to
that vibration your familiarity with
that vibration so that you can begin to
open up those doors and operate on that
level in a more precise
way and in opening those doors in your
own physical reality and in your own dream
physical reality and in your own dream
reality all of the answers will come
through in a very obvious and apparent
way you follow me yes thank you well
thank you very
much
sharing hi Bashar and who you good day a
couple of months ago you mentioned to me
that there were One Moment One Moment
be bold speak up all wish to share who
you
are two or three months ago you told me
that there were two females from esani
and two or three children that wanted to
work with me yes do you recall that
yes I'm having a little problem making
contact a little problem all right what
sort of little problem I have visual
contact but I don't have verbal contact
with two verbal contact with two females
yes can you help me visual
contact what do you see describe what
you see when you have this visual contact I
see when you have this visual contact I
only see two physical forms and two
female forms that's and how do you feel
when you see them I feel like I want to
talk to them all right and do
you do you do you talk to them you feel
like you want to talk to them yes but I
I don't hear anything back I don't I
don't get communication
back yes you
do it is simply that you have an
expectation that you ought to hear it in
a particular way and your expectation is
blocking out the communication you are
getting it is a lot easier than you
think and that's all you're going
through is you are creating it to be
more difficult than it
is now how do you think it ought to
sound
it's not that I think it has to have a
sound I because I have communication
with other energies from other
dimensions but this one this particular
one I don't seem to have clear
communication with all right I'll give
you a
technique are you ready yes and you can
do it right now if you wish all right is
there something you can choose a phrase
a question that you have already asked
them that you receive no answer to that
you can speak out loud right
now can you choose one of those phrases
yes I can say it now as if you are now
speaking to
them will you be participating with me
at the center on the beach all right now
I'll suggest this to you are you ready
yes if if if if if I know how many of
you like that word if if if it's a very
safe word
if not have to commit right now he said
if all play along
if if if if if you if you were one of
those beings how would you
answer how would you want to
answer what would you say yes or no and
what would you want to
answer I I don't understand that
question all
right I am not chastising you but don't
be
stubborn if you were one of those beings
put yourself in their position right now
play a game oh I see what you're saying
all right okay how would you answer now
be yourself again for the moment be the
you you're familiar with being ask the
question again okay you're in a play you
are one character now ask the question
will you be participating with me in my
Center on the beach now step over Dawn a
new costume you are now the being you
have asked the question of respond in
the way that gives you the most Joy what
is your answer of course now what's so
difficult about
that why do you think but that's just
me that's not really what they might say
that's just my wishes and my hopes what
makes you think that you would attract a
being to you that would be any different
from what you really desire why wouldn't
they why would they not participate with
you why not
okay oh so that wasn't a good question
oh it was a beautiful question and it
was a lovely answer and a true one why
do you doubt the dialogue is between
yourself and yourself even when it's
with someone else but I I realize that
oh you do mhm well then realize it for
me
now all right can you give me a name
for now a symbolic name okay
calet will that do that'll do fine why
will it do fine I like it why it sounds
nice sounds nice say it then Crystal it
Crystal say it again Crystal
it cryst
cset I I can't CL my teeth like that all
that all
right by the way by the way by the way
sometimes over the course of what you
call the Last 5 Years in dialogues with
many of you now and then you have heard
when we say certain things that now and
then the Channel's teeth
will to some degree it have various
reasons for occurring at various times
however I will simply tell you now that
there are aspects of our language that
don't translate into your language other than therefore
than therefore
cset is actually the trer vibration all
right but cset will
do
Now understand all right all right I'll
say it
please understand please understand
don't be so hard on yourself please
understand it is that simple simply
assume what you imagine Crystal's
identity to be and respond as cset
would do you understand I do you will
then build the Rapport between you it
will get smoother you will know the
difference it is going to involve your
Consciousness even though it's going to
involve her Consciousness too but
remember remember as is the case with
most of these connections you are
speaking with an aspect of your own
future self so why not initiate the
dialogue it's only you anyway you
understand yes makes sense thank you
very much thank
you Shing
good day Bashar good day to you thank
you uh specific disciplines and
techniques seem to work better sometimes
than just metaphor and philosophy yes
yes yes depending upon the vibration you
have constructed yourself to be
depending upon the beliefs you have
bought into of course one ritual one
methodology will work splendidly for
someone maybe not necessarily for
someone else
but if you find that a particular
methodology does work for you by all
means use it but simply we are saying
remember it works for you because it is
reflective of what you
believe understand yes continue what I
was referring to is that most of the
time we hear uh people like you and
other spiritual teachers tell us
beautiful things like your opening
statements were great but then the
application seems to be dependent on our
own ability then to take those things
and do something about it being
responsible for what we've heard yes it
is always your responsibility now from
time to time we have shared many dozens
by now of different techniques that work
better shall we say for some of you than
others but that's why we always share
new techniques because now and then we
will hit more of you with one than
another but yes it is always up to your
imagination to invent the technique that
works best for you because it is your
imagination we can't do better than your
own imagination at coming up with a
technique that works best for you
because we are not you that's why we
always tell you that the responsibility
ultimately is yours even though we may
nudge you in a certain direction with
our suggestions with our rituals with
our meditations that's why we always say
that even when we take you through an
exercise if your imagination decides to
change what we are saying let it because
your imagination knows what is best for
you it's always your responsibility it
has to be you understand yes does that
help with what you want to know
well what I'm referring to specifically
is now that you're wrapping this up in
the next two sessions is that maybe from
your point of view there are some some
oversight you could give us about one of
the distinct problems that I see in our
world which is physical health
well-being care for the body and
specifically I'm asking about what do
you see as the basic
diet exercise routines those techniques
that you would see for us to improve
prove ourselves you are saying generally
the things that would seem to work
generally across the board for most of
you within the collective reality that
you share as related to most people's
disease and distress and sufferings yes
well you have said it yourself have you
not stress the idea that many of you think
stress the idea that many of you think
you ought to be doing one thing when you
know deep down what you really want to
be doing is something quite different
it's not being true to yourselves that's
the root of all disease not being true
to your natural self not doing what
excites you with Integrity with
fulfillment and joy not being your
natural self will fragment you and
create you to be stressed and
diseased the idea generally generally
yes you will find the lighter your diet
the more symbolically lighter the
material is that you ingest the higher
the vibration of energy will be the
simpler the form of sustenance the
higher the vibration of energy the less
complex the form of sustenance the
higher the clearer the cleaner the
vibration of energy will be in general
there will be fluctuations in this and
exceptions of course depending upon time
mood attitude the idea in general of
attitude the idea in general of
breathing more fully breathing more
deeply and of course allowing yourself
to create energy systems that are
non-polluting will help you as well
obviously but these things are obvious
to you well let me back up a
moment I suppose I could say again
without meaning to chastise anyone that
if they really were obvious you would be
doing them but many of you are not many
individuals in your Society quote
unquote know how they ought to be eating how
know how they ought to be eating how
they really feel like they want to eat
many individuals in your Society know
they ought not according to their belief
systems to be pumping pollutants Into
Your Atmosphere but they do
anyway how can we possibly in any way
shape or form offer any kind of advice
or any kind of
suggestion in the light of the fact that
your people already know what it is they
need to do and yet don't do
it so the idea generally is that your
Society is already well aware of many of
the things it could be doing to allow
every individual the fullest reflection
of health and joy and you don't do it so
what could I say what could I possibly
say to fill that Gap except what I have
already said and that is that I simply
guarantee beyond a shadow of a doubt
that if you do follow your natural
intuition and do what excites you with
Integrity you will create a vibration
within yourself that will at the very
least act as a translation filter so
that even if all these things are going
on around you they won't affect you
personally in a negative
way and then bit by bit as more
individuals do that as more individuals
do what excites them you then co-create
an overall environment where you all of
a sudden say hey let's not do this
anymore it's not representative of what
we really want because we now know we
are whole beings and we don't don't
really have portions of ourselves that
want this and other pieces of ourselves
that still do this
anyway we are whole consciousnesses and
this is what we choose and when you
choose it that way with conviction and
when you act on your words then you will
be healthy because you will be
whole when you do not fragment yourself
into segments of Consciousness when you
do not war with
yourself then you will be whole and when
you are whole you will be healthy
because that's your natural state does
that help absolutely what's the answer
to the uh what I call the copout to
saying that's the way it's supposed to
be and it doesn't matter
anyway there is really nothing you can
say to change an individual's mind when
they do not want it to be changed
however you could say all right but I
know in my reality I personally if this
is true have
experienced certain things that people
have said this is the way it is but I
chose to believe something else I did it
another way and I still got a result my
reality reinforced my belief I know that
the same principle will work for you so
you can say this is the way it is and as
long as you do you will still get that
reality now I cannot prove it to you I
cannot make you change and I don't want
to you can say but you can also say what
I have just said I
guarantee guarantee that should you
guarantee that should you
decide to believe differently that it
doesn't have to be this way that it
might just possibly perhaps maybe be the
way you'd prefer it to be and you start
living as if that could be so I
guarantee you will get the result
because every belief system create a
self reinforcing reality that makes it
seem as if that belief system is the
only belief system that exists is the
only true belief that's the nature of
how you create your reality were it not
that way you couldn't focus on any one
particular reality but when you change
the belief you change the reality you
can't prove it to them if they want to
insist on being one way remember if a
person insists on saying I told you so they're
insists on saying I told you so they're
always going to get a reality that gives
them the opportunity to say I told you
so over and over
again that in my estimation is the only
thing you can say to them I guarantee
that if you change the belief the
reality will change but that's my belief
I've gotten the result it's up to you I
love you anyway because you are one of
the facets of all that is and whatever
you decide to do I love you anyway even
if you decide that your reality should
be one that lacks
Integrity I understand that loving you
anyway gives you the best opportunity to
change that reality should at some point
you decide to do so not that it is in my
estimation not that I am judging that
you ought to change because I am no
better than you and I come to decide
what is true for you but I love you
anyway unconditionally because by giving
you that mirror that reflection if you
decide you want to change the love will
make it easier for you to do so how's
that wonderful than just as a quick last
thing oh a quick last thing when you
talk about saky when you talk about
pollution and and what we're doing
polluting is it not the inner pollution
of the body that's the basic thing
course it is not the inner pollution
even of the body it is the conflicting
pollution of what you would call
negative beliefs first remember that
even your body is a result an
exteriorized result of what you believe
you are so the idea is the belief
systems first when you change your
belief systems when you know you have
unlimited access to power when you know
you're connected to the universe and you
draw power directly from the natural
universe that exists you do not have to
create it in a way that implies that you
are disconnected from it which creates
friction which creates all the excess
heat all the excess pollutants all the
side effects and derivatives they are
all representative of how you believe
yourselves to be you believe yourselves
to be in a sense contamin at with many
different beliefs many different ideas
you judge them some better some worse it
is the discrepancies within you that
cause the exteriorized effect you
understand mhm does that help you thank
you very much well thank you very much
and thank you all for coming to an age
of realization when you know you can
have a smooth transition from one idea
to the next and it does not have to be
in your terms violent nor
catastrophic but at the same time we
thank you for being creative enough to
be able to use even the violent and the
catastrophic pressures to allow you to
change by giving yourselves nowhere else
to turn
turn
shooting happy New Year and happy New
Year to you closer to the mic
please uh the question I asked Bashar
yes relates to something that happened
about 2 years ago all right my brother
was killed in mob Collision all right uh
since then through uh intense
astrological study
nice my excitement has carried me in the
direction in the Direction guys that he
was a strong serious connection all
right and this is reflected further by
the fact that he had served as somewhat
of a guardian for me he was my older
brother all right about four months ago
Bashar yes I happened to stumble across
an unexpected uh
unexpected thing
regarding well I met a very interesting
young lady well all
right and once again through the using
the astrological chart as an objective
tool for identity awareness yes I'd come
across the idea that something of a very
arcturian nature had taken place all
right and so oh months after that
Bashar carrying it out a bit
here in Her Dream she had she'd been
interrupted uh I was lying beside her
she'd woken up
and she was I won't say frantic but she
was really startled all right and she
kept saying is it you is it you and she
sat there for 5 or 10 of our Earth
minutes and I and I asked her what the
dream was about and she said that my
brother had appeared to her but sure I
had felt strong at lant and connections
with this woman ever since the first
moment that I'd met her all right and so
so I would like to know if this so some
kind of pre-birth between myself and her
between he uh myself and her or if you
had anything to say about this
uh all things are the result of
agreements yes generally pre-birth
especially with very strong momentum yes
of course but you know this yes I do you
don't need me to confirm this no I don't
the energy is strong you sense it
strongly you don't need my labels for
it my labels are not better than yours
all those things are done by agreement
all of them many times pre- birth yes
generally the timing of deaths the
timing of births generally are arranged
pre birth
yes on the intergalactic level of the
astrological work that I do I would like
to know something more about the arc
turth it is the gate through
which many of the individuals being born
on your planet now are passed to be
acclimated to the new vibration of the
fourth density Earth that you are
becoming so that they will not have to
forget as much of who and what they are
and will not have as many barriers to
work through they are being aligned with
a higher vibrational realm through the
Arcturus gate before they are born once
again as you would say reincarnated upon
your planet you understand yes does that
help you yes will that be sufficient for
now that will do thank you very much
stay where you are
what may assist you as your winter is
coming up in your segment of your planet
would be to focus upon the star of
Sirus and allow yourself to feel the
energy of its bright white
light and see what that vibration does
to help align you to the dream world
where you can have much stronger and
much clearer Communications with those
that you would say are now in spirit
form you understand yes if you think of the
you understand yes if you think of the
white light of Sirius and think of that
vibration think of that all-encompassing
white light out of which everything is
made it can help translate your
Consciousness into spiritual reality and
allow communication between your
physical world and your spiritual world
to go on more easily without a barrier
between them you understand yes thank
you very much thank
you sharing
hello Commander oh hello how are you
great great all
right my daughter nicoo was killed in a
car accident last year seems to be a
popular method of translation and I was
wondering what offense was what's going
on with her and will she
reincarnate back into a physical body
while I'm still in my physical body and
what specific lifetime we had together
that was so
significant related to this one all of
that yes all of
that an aspect of her Consciousness will
reincarnate but not the total idea
generally therefore to answer your
question most directly
no the being will function as a spirit
guide for quite some time perhaps what
you would call at least 80 more of your
years therefore you are more likely to
join her in the spiritual realm before
she chooses to reincarnate as the being
you understood you
understand yes one moment one
moment as
Grandmama as Grandmama Rosie in another
life very strong connection with this
being she being your grand mama in
another life Rose by name one moment
if you will send love as you have been
doing to assist this individual to learn
what they need to learn they can then
assist those that they need to assist
and assist you more strongly in learning
how to communicate directly with them
you understand yes send love you can use
the image of a cherub you understand yes
and that image will get
through you follow me yes and then
simply as you lay down to sleep think of
that image project the love from the
heart or perhaps the image of a heart
with wings will be symbolic or a
cherub and then simply relax into sleep
and know that when that
individual has the time shall we say
there will be communication however do
not assume as we know many of you do
that an individual who has died has
nothing better to do than to hang around
waiting to talk to you they are very
busy learning new things they still have
lives to live and also the time time
frame is so different that sometimes
they may think well all right I've been
dead sometimes it takes a while to even
realize that they are dead because of
the type of belief systems your planet
has fed them but if they realize it
right away all right I'm a spirit form
now and they meet other Spirit forms
whose job it is to instruct them in
acclimating to that world once again
sometimes they may feel that they have
been in conversation with another Spirit
form for oh what feels like maybe five
minutes but they turn around and say oh
my a year has gone by on
Earth I did not mean to be out of touch
for so long I just got wrapped up and
time here is not what it is there you
understand yes so live your life take
strength from the connection that you
still have with that individual because
no connection of that nature is ever
broken send love to help them learn what
they need to learn more quickly and they
will be able to return the conversation
when it is convenient and appropriate
for both of you so relax all right yes
thank you very much thank you oh One
Moment One Moment One Moment you can
find as we have now just received that
because of the nature of the vibration
of this individual because of the symbol
of the heart with the wings and the
Cherub the strongest day upcoming that
you'll be able to contact this
individual in meditative States will be
what you call your Valentine's Day all
right yes thank you very much thank
you at this timing you may all enjoy a
short break we will resume contact in
approximately 10 to 15 of your minute
how's it going
great uh there's Refreshments out this
door and if you want to order tonight's
tape just see Pamela straight back in
front of the control
Booth when I call you back please come
back cuz we can't start until everyone's
seated and quiet it'll be about 1015
minutes thanks what time is it uh what
time
is 10 10 on the button 10 yeah [Applause]
say before we continue with
question all of you become as
comfortable as you
can allow yourself now to do the
following thing though it may to some of
you seem a little bit silly that's all
right
either place the side of your hand or
your arm in your mouth and
[Music] hum all
hum all
right now the idea is to allow you to
Simply feel the vibration against your
skin to feel the vibration inside the
physical form of your body
because when
when you feel the vibration of the
galactic energy we desire that to have the
energy we desire that to have the
strongest effect to tap most strongly
into this wave of
energy that you imagine that this wave
is passing through you even as the
vibration of your hum passes into your
skin into your muscles into your bones
and that you realize that the idea of
the harmonic that you have called the
home the old
the that centered and balanced vibration
when you do it in a collective way or
individually personally privately is the
vibration that aligns you to the
Consciousness the fabric itself of
creation that's why it centers and
balances you so strongly and the
galactic energy because it is made of
the fabric of the consciousness of
creation itself when you vibrate in that M sound
itself when you vibrate in that M sound
will feel your vibration as if you are
literally humming inside of its body as
if you are a part of it it will feel
that you are coales crystallized out of
its own
energy that is one of the easiest ways
in that sense to contact or shall we say
allow yourself to arrive on the level of
the energy of the galactic to Center
yourself through that
M the idea is also helpful if you will
imagine in your mind's eye and an entire
galaxy of stars a pin wheel Galaxy
spinning in the Blackness of space very
slowly weighing
weighing
billions countless billions of tons of
mass spinning slowly turning and hearing
the Deep Rumble of that energy Infinite
Energy spinning that gigantic mass of a
galaxy there will be in time
through the channels project of what you
call Future Resort the idea being that
it is called Andromeda the idea being
that it is connected to the largest
galaxy in your
area a film that will be made for the
purposes of advertisement wherein this
spinning Galaxy and the appropriate
vibratory level that goes along with it will be
level that goes along with it will be
rendered and shown to people so that
when they view the image of the spinning
Galaxy and they hear the harmonic Rumble
of its energy they will immediately key
into the vibration of the Andromeda wave
because Andromeda is the central Galaxy
of this area and carries with it the
controlling shall we say wave upon which
and from which all other galaxies take
their cue that is why androma is even
cue that is why androma is even
recognized by many of you as being what
you call the central Council because it
vibrates at a particular
pitch that encompasses all other
galaxies in the immediate
neighborhood this Andromeda wave this
vibratory Galactic wave is most
accurately once again defined by the
oh that you create among yourself so
once again now if you wish you can put
your hand up to your mouth or you can
simply vibrate and feel it all the way
through you together now oh [Music]
that vibration in the very depth of your
solar plexus is the vibration that Keys
you into the galactic now remain relaxed
and if you wish with your eyes closed it
is up to you one moment
if you will now feel the vibration of
depth feel the wave after wave of
Consciousness that you are feel wave
waves of energy passing through you feel
the deepening of the vibration the Deep
Rumble of the central core of your being
feel the smooth warmth of energy passing
and radiating from your body feel the
energy that your body is the
masslessness it can become feel that you
are melting into an all-encompassing sea
of brilliant and warm golden colored
energy you are the substance of the
fabric of creation itself of which the
galactic Consciousness is made feel
wave after wave passing through you as
the waves of your own oceans your own
physical Oceans Rise to the shores of
your land feel
wave after
wave passing through you radiating out
from a central source of Galactic energy
each and every one of you is a beacon a
center of that
wave after
wave anytime you are so desired to feel
that energy with the m you have been
given or standing on your ocean shore
feel the crash and the vibration of the
wav in the pit of your solar plexus know
at that moment that you have connected
to the galactic vibration feel the
energy of the
wave take time time take
time take
time be space b volume B
time B
eternity B
Energy b
b
b b the heartbeat of life itself b b
B the pulse the warmth the blood
coursing through the vein the artery be
the cell warm connected touching all other
cell warm connected touching all other
cells be
rich be at
peace think of all individuals on your
world see them all in one room see them
all in light all in laughter all in love
be the heartbeat beating the pulse
beating coursing the
way after
way after wave of
energy feel your Consciousness Sinking
Deep deeper and deeper and more deeply
into Comfort into abundance into deserv
ability as you imagine golden
wave after golden
wave of brilliant warm thick
light passing through
you carrying you in the edies and
currents of energy of the fabric of
consciousness of space
itself wave after
wave after
wave of
unconditional
love take three deep breaths
breaths
you are the way
the
wave washing away all
fear washing away all
doubt you are
[Applause] alive you are made of life
itself flow on the Stream your natural
stream the
stream you know most
[Applause] true
true
love the vibration of infinite love it
is what you are made
[Applause] of our love
we thank you for allowing the sharing to
take place we thank you for allowing
yourself to Center within the depths of
your being we thank you for loving yourself
being we thank you for loving yourself
enough to
explore the depths of your
Consciousness and to know beyond the
shadow of a doubt that everything you
will ever discover will always be worth
discovering and only lead to more
discovery of Joy about yourself we thank
you and we now suggest that we may continue sharing all
sharing all
right perhaps in the interest as we know
you have been discussing the idea of
asking only one question maybe we should
only give one answer
and it will be straight as an arrow if
you wish
wish
proceed well there goes my list of
questions um if I only have one then do
you have a message for me do I have a
message for you
no okay was that straight enough uh now
I have have a
question may I ask it yes do you have a
message for
yourself yes what is it do share
well your friend is having a good
time what is your message for yourself
you you are among friends who love you
you can
share this the screen went blank the
screen went blank is it a very pretty
screen not blank not blank it is not
pretty why
not well sort of invisible sort of
invisible then how do you know it's
there it has an outline it has an
outline line all right is it a pretty
outline H it's pretty plain pretty plain
it's like a working screen a working
screen all right what would you like to
construct on that screen now that you
have cleaned your slate begin a new
begin a fresh what would you like to
draw on that
screen I would like to draw um the path
that's really next the activity or the
um career yes yes that I'm moving into
and what is it
what is it there's so many there are so
many then what category do they all fit
in what are the aspects of what is the
overall career that all the different
tools and all the different ideas are
aspects
of um when you mentioned that this was
the new year and Halloween and I had um
been struggling with this question yes
and the thing that changed it was when
it was time to get out the Halloween
decorations and the costumes yes and I
realized that that's the thing that
really excites me yes yes yes in what
way it's fun I like I like the
creativity yes and what do the costumes
do what do the masks allow you to be
change identities change your identity
into whatever you wish right and does it
allow you to safely get in touch with
what you may call the negative side of
yourself and have fun with it without
fearing it too much yes and does it
allow you to share that with other
people in a way they know is safe
because they know it's only
Halloween yes and do you think that some
sort of transformational interaction can
come of that yes do you think some sort
of transformational career can come of
that yes just because it's not Halloween
now doesn't mean you cannot put on those
costumes and play out some ideas with
other individuals right does that seem
like that would be a fun career very fun
would it be the
funest career you can think of well the
most fun would be if I could be the uh
first comedian on
esani you're already getting a big laugh thank
laugh thank
you you brought down the house
house
now remember that we are all always
tuning in the idea of course is to be what you
in the idea of course is to be what you
desire to be where you chose to be
doesn't mean that we're not receiving
you but do not focus on our civilization
as much as your own the idea is to share
joy in your own civilization so your
civilization can be helped by you to be
like what you imagine our civilization
is like and then we can blend because
we'll be on the same frequency you
understand got it and by the way you
certainly will not be the first comedian
on asani unless you simply mean from
Earth right in the physical right
because there are many of you that are
incarnated upon asani and a lot of you
are
Jokers that's why they need me all right
but let us shall we say for now stay
grounded down to earth how do you
translate what you just said into Earth
terminology what is it that excites you
the most that you would like to do on
Earth well I got the idea that there
might be a need for somebody to do uh
decorating yes for people for holidays
all right um their business their
Windows their oh and brighten the place
up liven them all up and put them in
good spirits right and would that be fun and
spirits right and would that be fun and
exciting and would it feel like play yes
when will you do it well I made some
calls today oh all right I does that
mean that you have already started to do
it yes and will you begin to do it more
and more boldly every day advertising
yourself in every way she perform you
think is fun to do so so that many
people will know that you are there to
take advantage of your service it's a
good idea oh thank you very
much will you do that yes then one of
the few predictions I can make mate if
you do that I predict your life will be
full of fun forever and it will never
end would you like that prediction to
come true yes then make it
so allow it to be so by doing it by
being that person and knowing knowing
what beyond the shadow of a doubt
knowing knowing knowing that when you do
what excites you the most you will be
supported and more quote unquote than
enough people will call on your services
to give you all the abundance you need
and allow you to have a good time doing
it sound like fun yes thank you for
brightening up your corner of the
universe was that helpful yes is that
sufficient I want to ask you one more
thing you little sneak all
right when I was doing some um
visualization and meditating um uh on
the my Essential crystalline structure
you essential crystalline structure yes
what I got um were two pyramids that
were base to Bas yes with a sphere in
the middle all right touching the edges
of the base all right and around that
was a nine-pointed star all right um I
think well I get I get the impression
that I understand the symbolism of the
pyramids and the sphere but I don't I
don't know the nine-pointed star and I
don't really get what it is Al together
to some degree it is what you may call a
mandala and it shows some of the
directions of other Universal Realms
that you are connected into it shows
some of the directions of guidance that
you can receive communication channels
that you can
receive from other places One Moment One
Moment One Moment if
you will also
understand that different points
sometimes our references to the
connection into different star systems
star systems other civilizations that
you have deep connections
to One Moment One Moment
nine in your case is important because
of the idea of being three Triads to
some degree is representative of the
connection of Earth as assani and
Sirus One Moment One
Moment think if you wish in what you may
call now I know this will vary for many
of you but your holy day of holy day the
idea Christmas and the idea of what you
call the Christmas star what you call
Star of Bethlehem think of the
nine-pointed star in that way as being a
symbolic representation of that
particular type of energy and you can
see that it may function as a lantern as
a guide to light the way and connect you
to the path that will give you the most
Joy you follow me mhm it is an unfolding
a particular type of Crystal and flower
that represents all the different
capacities and dimensions that you have
within yourself if you simply pick up
upon the vibration of it you really do
not need to understand it in your terms
analytically follow the
energy do what excites you there will be
synchronistic occurrences of that symbol
now and again in your life you can put
them in some of the decorations that you
create these stars and it will have an
effect on other people as well you may
wish to explore it three-dimensionally
geometrically build one out of some
substance see how it makes you feel as a
resonating vibrational tool you follow
me just the star or the whole structure
with can be just the star can be any
aspect of it any one of the structures
in combination all together does not
really matter even make a drawing of it
you follow me I just had a brilliant
idea oh what is it dou sh well a clown
hat sort of with a pyramid cone on top
and the star for the headpiece oh well
thank you very much for your
brilant idea star light star bright all right
idea star light star bright all right
very good have a good night good night
thank you I thank you I I would I would
like to know how about the whales in
point Barrel what about them well um it
seemed like a very unusual effort that
people made to try to get them loose
will not be so unusual in the near
future when you understand the
connection as those individuals did very
much your attempts your human attempts to
your attempts your human attempts to
help them out is very much a
representation very much a
representation in that sense of the
connection and the kinship that you are
now feeling to that form of life upon
your planet we were much in that sense
Overjoyed in watching that scenario much
Overjoyed for it shows that you really
are feeling that connection and we thank
you very much and so do
they thank you Bish well thank you
nothing to do that our love to you Shing
yes yes um hello V and to you good
day Mountaintop lady I don't believe it
what what what what what it's been 9
months how can you remember from just
hello oh please what am I saying what is
so difficult about that I came it's been
about nine months since I contacted like
this and I had about 20 30 million
questions I can't think of any I don't
know if they have that much
time I was trying to find the one and
did you succeed and I am so blown out
from the earlier part I'm trying I'll
think of something what where isn't pull
yourself together you have totally
totally it's all your fault you know
changed my life oh oh oh no no no no no
it's a co-creation thank you it's a
co-creation see how are it's your fault
too
when you say follow your ecstasy or
follow your excitement yes works for me
it works for me after I found out what
that entrance into the fourth density is
there is nothing this lifetime I have
found quite so exciting no thank you and
unconditional love for you is very easy
I think you know thank you easy for you
as well uh it's easier seems well
there's been a few areas of little
shakiness but I'm working on it that's
all right
all part of the
fun well barriers just as you know are
not there and it's a different Viewpoint
yes and it's very exciting to find every
barrier is of service thank you very
much for your sharing and your wisdom
fourth density because of the content
there's a lot of new people here and I
hope every one of them will take a look
at what the fourth density does
represent because it is very exciting
well thank you very much the question i'
finally I do have one it's a little one
now it's very little and it's not
serious they're all significant okay um
Mir mountain is finally getting off the
ground after I finally said to hell with
it it started working I guess thank you
very much after you let go all the details
much after you let go all the details
yes that's exact now other people are
doing the details all right uh I did
spend some time up there and because of
a gentleman that came earlier talking
about Billy Meer if you remember you did
send me to the ples thing and
it's a kind of know but I need a little
reassurance on what I think I already
know maybe okay while up there I spent
quite some time all by myself yes and
you know it's a plateau all by itself
yes and the Stars what I oh God yes and
it was so
beautiful he's been
there and go on go
on it's either four or five nights I
can't it kind of loses content of time
all right but
five five thank
you there was something that did come
into the vicinity yes and I can't say I
don't know I can't I don't know a word
vibration frequency resonance is the
best word I can think of yes it woke me
up in the middle of the night I don't
know 2 3 in the morning and it was so
strong One Moment One Moment always one
of the most receptive times in your
dimensional reality 3 a.m. be aware of
it
um I just would like some reassurance I
know it wasn't from this planet I it
feels five
civilizations yo-yoing in and out one
after another on five successive nights
five the number of Earth Humanity five
kisses to the Earth five
touches you
understand um five
blessings five consecrations
five acknowledgements five well
acknowledgements five well
wishes the resonance hell the resonance
as we have talked there will be
another I it's so funny because I don't
talk about this to anybody else you
think be real careful on all this and
here I'm saying in front of all these
people all what
people well I've been very careful about
the spaceship Landing as we've discussed
and you sent me to the pades thing and
it's like you either sound like they're
going to lock you up or put you away or
go through the threats that Billy Meer
has and what have you but I know they're
there I know they're there all right
remember again even though we are there
focus on the earth that's your home
that's doing your job and that's
allowing the connection between us to
strengthen in its full capacity staying
with your feet on the ground doing what
excites you honor and being of service
and we thank you for doing that we thank
you for your
persistence underly that word for all of
you persistence in what you believe it
does not have to be a struggle you don't
need stamina persistence is simply
trusting and having the conviction to
have the faith that what you know you're
all about you are all about and nothing
else will do
persistence what does amen mean say
again amen amen amen so be it so be it
so be it thank you for your help you've
carried me through many many times you
have carried yourself but I have been
delighted to walk arm in arm with you I
felt your energy and I think you I will
your energy has been there inist many
times one moment how are you
bodily are you feeling clearer after
tonight I don't think anything's going
to touch me I'm going for major surgery
on the 9th of this coming month but
since it's a brand new area brand new
time all right I was thinking after you
talk tonight about this new
transformation into into like out of
leaving the body it sounded really
exciting I'll have to admit who needs it
I know wait wait but the idea of the
fourth density is a little bit more
exciting all right but it is tempting
breathe through the ninth breathe
through it breathe and breathe through
it will you be there to assist little
bit I'll take
it there's no such thing as a little bit
thank you we all of you are completely and
you we all of you are completely and
totally
interpenetrated you understand remember
what we said in every point is the
totality we are there for you
completely as long as you are there for
yourself if you are not whole in your
space we can't reach you but if you are
whole in your space and true to yourself
and complete with yourself we are there
for you 100% not just a little a little
bit you understand yes the judgments
have been something to really work
through on yourself yes yes I'm sure
thank you for choosing the appropriate
idea and symbol of a mirror mirror
Mountain yes IL in our language IL
mirror IL AAR IL AAR
experience which literally translated
into a mirror image of the self
experiencing the self another face of
the self that's exactly what it does
thank you so much bishar we'll see
you in a different we will see you
physically someday you said Someday I'm
keeping it to your word all right will I
see you
physically I am holding you all to your
word as
well because remember unless you match
our vibration we do not cocreate and you
do not meet us halfway in that world in
which we both can exist so the question
can be said to you as well many of you
have asked over and over again when we
will see you physically when will you
all land when will we be able to touch
you but understand our reality your
reality are different frequencies unless
you meet us halfway I can ask you the
same question will I ever see you
physically will you ever
land all right then we will meet someday
I know that all right I thank you and
that day is today in the reality that
you prefer be that reality you prefer
and it will be today before you know it
and again do we not have to be a fourth
density view or frequency being the
reality you prefer to be is fourth
density o you understand it's new living
your dream is what fourth density is
that's the
definition because you know your dreams
are real and physical reality is but a
dream when you live like that that's
fourth density in which anything can
happen and which everything
does very exciting thank you very much I
love you
sharing hi Bashar and who you good day
I'm going to try to be as articulated as
you are but just relax you'll do fine
don't try speak up however so that all
may share okay um two months ago I had
an accident a motorcycle accident
motorcycle accident two months ago all
right yeah and something came off of a
motorcycle a piece of metal and hit the
ground and came full speed in my face
and I had like 15 stitches on my lips oh
W right it looks much better now I'm
thank God and
uh well when that happened I was
wondering where was my protective guide
because I always thought I had
protection you do you all do but again
remember you choose your reality you
choose to show yourself things in
certain ways you choose to get your
attention in certain ways if you will
not pay attention in other ways what did
you learn by going through that
particular type of experience I went
through a total change of Consciousness
in what way from what to what um I I
felt like I was reborn and I
was searching for other things that are
were more positive all right all right
very good now may I ask you a question
go ahead thank you what makes you think
you didn't have protection did you get
killed no perhaps it hit you just hard
enough to wake you up what makes you
think that that's not protection it
could have killed you that's that Mak
sense yes it does did you think about it
from that point of view yeah yes I did
all right then you know you had
protection because you were allowed and
you allowed yourself to go through what
you may call a very harrowing and very
quick and a very exciting and very
immediate experience and you in that
sense knew you would be all right in
that sense you protected yourself you
have the protection you had the blessing
you blessed yourself you knew what you
were doing and you did it just enough to
wake you up just to change your
direction by going very fast which shows
that you are a very accelerative person
understand yeah you knew what you were
doing now that's not the only way you
could have done it you didn't have to
get your attention by hitting yourself
in the face that could have done
it if you will listen to The Sounds if
you will pay attention to them when they
come in shall we say hey slightly less
hazardous form then perhaps you will
wake up with that if you hear the words
then you will wake up with that however
you might just be one of those bold
people that decides you just have to do
it in flare and Flash and that you have
to have a reminder a nice little scar oh
yes that's my badge I'm very proud of
that that's the day I changed forever
look at that what a lovely scar I'm so
precise you understand yes I did now how
do you feel um since the accident after
the accident for like 2 3 weeks I was
really scared and kind of uh good you
processed all your old fear I I I had
like paranoia and I knew I was not crazy
I was just going through change yes and
every night after that since two months
I I think so I think so oh I'm
[Music] V you sure sold me yes I think I believe
V you sure sold me yes I think I believe
that maybe I am doing what excites me
the most
perhaps yes or no yes you are doing what
excites you the most yes or
no I'm going towards that when will you
do
it before you answer let me ask you
another question just to give you
something else to think about if I may
may I may you may yeah thank you what
makes you think that the things you are
doing now are things that are on the way
towards doing it as opposed to things
that are a part of the doing of the
thing yeah you said the right way thank
you okay it is the doing of the thing in
all its aspects do not discount the
process the process is a part of doing
the thing
enjoy it learn from it it is bringing
you the knowledge you want to do the
thing you want to do more
gloriously enjoy where you are enjoying
where you are is what makes it easier to
get where you want to go deny where you
are and you remove the Stepping Stones
understand yes so enjoy and you will go
Full Speed Ahead and next time you will
not have to smack yourself in the face
to change directions you understand I do
relax the new energy coming through is
just to acclimatize you to your new self
you're feeling more of yourself more of
the energy you are it's a vibrational
feeling a vibrant feeling an exciting
feeling be that
you okay okay is it a deal it's a deal
it's up to
you does that help you yes well thank
you and pleasant dreams thank
you bye
hello shouting [Music]
hi Bashar and you good day um I'm going
to ask something for a friend of mine
who was supposed to be here for the
first time tonight oh um several nights
ago three nights ago she had an
experience in her excuse me in her
home and um she was woke up from her
sleep about about four times two times
the first time she was woke up by a
spiral of yellow light I second time was
a very intense bright yellow
light and it scared her so
bad that she got up and she went to a
bathroom to try to recover and she was
very dispersed um dispersed that's what she
dispersed um dispersed that's what she
said all
right um she also became numb in the arm yes
um she also became numb in the arm yes
all right her her hand would work but
she couldn't feel anything yes and what
else and then she became very sore from
the waist down yes and today she
couldn't even get out of the
bed and what I'd like you want a
medicine no a cure no a an a
climatizer what's that something to
allow her to get used to it perhaps
perhaps a a reflection from you as to
what is happening so that she is not so
afraid she's she's seen green energies
come through her room that disappear on
her side of the bed and she hasn't
talked to anybody about this but me and
now you've blabbed it to
[Laughter] [Applause] [Applause]
[Music] everyone
everyone
now did you hear that
yes it would have been good but it will
do if she would have been here to hear
that because that's what she needs to do
when this happens she needs to laugh
okay do you understand mhm that is the
most important thing she can do right
now laugh and let it through and she
will understand what is happening there
are some friends working with her okay
there are some guys working with her
there is to some degree
physiological interaction going on
between one level and
another all right
laugh and she will be given more
opportunity to remain conscious of what
is happening and to remain in apparent
control of what is happening you
understand okay so tell her if she goes
to the bathroom look in the mirror laugh
if she stays in the bed lie there laugh
okay all right yes what also something
else the same night
when I woke up the next morning I felt
like I'd been in a fight or something
all right and but I also had felt like I
had not
been where I woke up yes in a sense
there was astral projection is that well
I know I was busy doing something I
don't know what I don't know why I ended
up with pain at the base of my neck
going all the way down my shoulders to
some degree you were assisting your
friend to quote unquote wrestle with
self-created demons in the dream state
okay understand yes so you transfer that
idea to your physical body and woke up a
little stiff little sore yeah it was
yeah I had the half of the body hurting
that she didn't yes she had the lower
half I had the upper half you are
helping to support helping to support
that individual helping her through what
may be called a little bit of a rough
time she will stabilize you will
stabilize your friends you're helping
each other out it's all right you are
buddy Buddies in the astral realm what
you go through there you're having great
fun doing cuz it takes Great Gusto as
you say you're getting your teeth into
it you're rolling around and wrestling
with this idea wrestling with the
problem you will iron it out okay
understand yes laugh enjoy it is all in
good fun buddy buddies okay great thank
you and pleasant dream thank you Pasar
and thank you for all the years and of
sharing and it it was
very I feel like crying
better myself thank you very much for
all the Delight that you have given to
me and to all of us all of you thank you
thank you
sharing I'm sir and who you good day um
I know it's late so um I'll just make
this quick maybe you could I I came here
to talk about both the projects and also
a personal question yes um maybe you
could share a little bit about what this
device is I think both questions are are
related um I'll get to it real quick I
think uh not sure why but I have certain
uh deserv ability or lack of deserv
ability beliefs um I have a project I've
been working on 16 years with global
metabolics and it relates to I would
just say the well-being of our human
family but I do not either create enough
money or individuals to do what I know I
can do and I find it very frustrating
all right
also uh the same thing in creating a
relationship that is really whole and
complete with a female that has all of
the qualities that I feel I have to
share and um I would just like to get to
whatever limiting belief may have been
there I was very severely abused as a
child all right done the best I could in
my 37 years but I uh I'm not trying to
buy into I understand but I still feel
there's a pieace that holds back because
of all the things I'm involved in all
right I have one suggestion first off
yes have you ever gone through a
meditation where you allow yourself to
relive the childhood and build it from
scratch into the way you want it to be
uh not fully in many ways yes um that I
just all I can say is I keep sensing the
pattern I see is there's some piece I am
not able to access there are still times
I wake up and out of the blue I feel
very sad uh there's still something
that's hurt inside whatever you want to
call it something confused or hurt
little boy or holding on to some belief
and I really don't know how to quickly
access it all right all right One Moment
One Moment One Moment
good day to you my
friend hello my friend you may address
as anima the idea of the feminine energy
the counterpart of Bashar from you know
as the idea of feminine energy that you
seek within yourself the idea of coming
to terms with the idea of the feminine
energy within your being allow us simply
to
reflect that what you can do is
construct construct yourself into that
feminine version construct yourself into
that feminine ideal you know there have
been many discussions between Bashar and
yourself about the idea of already being
equal to that counterpart so that you
may draw into your life you already have
heard those discussions many times have
you not yes have you ever allowed
yourself in your imagination however to
construct the idea of your feminine
self no and I don't know what prevents
that when I try to allow yourself that's
what I know that's what it's trying to
express allow yourself the grace to do
so simply in your imagination to see the
idea of a feminine counterpart it is all
right to start out by allowing the
feminine counterpart to manifest itself
in whatever way she will you don't not
have to have any particular expectations
of what would appear to be feminine just
see a counterpart in your imagination
and know that it is the feminine idea
the feminine aspect of yourself for now
it can be a placeholder that is all
right you follow me so far yes allow
yourself to go through all the stages of
the idea of that feminine counterpart
allow it to be a sister experience that
allow it to be a daughter experience
that allow it to be a mother experience
that allow it to be a lover experience
that experience those four stages of
daughter and experience the idea of
sister and experience the idea of mother
and experience the idea of
Love experience all those counterpart
aspects of the feminine idea allow
yourself some time allow yourself some
conversations with them allow them
simply to discuss with you their view of
you allow them to discuss their
perspective of you sit somewhere and
have a very social afternoon with all of
them invite them in either one at a time
or all at once and sit and have what you
may call your te and discuss with them
just the various aspects of the Persona
construction that you are choosing to be
allow them to comment allow them to if
you will redecorate the idea of the
house that you are the house that you
have constructed yourself to be confer
as equals in the idea of why this ought
to be so or how that should be just so
and this and such take some time and
enjoy the exchange and enjoy that
communication give yourself time to
enjoy a creative field that you rarely
allow yourself to venture into the art
of artistic conversation with that
aspect of yourself for it is an art it
truly is an art and feel the warm
sunshine of the afternoon or the
introspective cloudy day with the warm
Hearth crackling away be in that Cottage
having tea with these individuals feel
at home feel that it is your home home
and that you have invited them in and it
is their home too but they are also in
your terms
consultants and they are helping you to
redecorate and redefine and redesign the
idea of not only your masculine persona
but the whole concept of the feminine
side the whole concept of the cottage
the whole concept of the home so that it
is the warm cheery and comfortable and
cushioned place that you desire it to be
that it is also what you call now your
information Cottage your idea of being
connected to the whole world the New
Concept of being connected through
information the whole concept of a being
a home Cottage so that it is homey even
while it stretches out to Encompass the
entire information Matrix of the
universe go through this exercise invite
them in and become delighted with all
that they have to
share very important very important
become delighted with their Delight in
you do not be shy do not be embarrassed
by their Delight in you you deserve to
be delighted in in that way relax with
yourself and begin to treat yourself
like dessert in that sense and let them
cherish you let them Delight in you let
them tell you how they truly feel let
them love you in that way and Learn To
Love Yourself from being a little boy on
up once again you know how to play in
certain levels but there are certain
aspects of yourself that you do not
allow yourself to Delight in just
because other individuals in your life
did not Delight in them allow these four
feminine aspects of the daughter sister
mother lover to now tell you how much
they truly Delight in you even as I have
taken great Delight in loving you with
my whole heart and cherishing that you
would allow me to have this interaction
with you if I could right now I would
smother you with
kisses understand understand simply that it is
understand understand simply that it is
always a joy for us always a delight and
never something we would refuse in order
to hug in order to cherish in order to
nurture all of you but truly understand
we are not given the opportunity to
Delight in you unless you truly Delight
in yourselves we thank you for allowing
us at this time also to share the
feminine aspect of the esani world of
which I am a part of which Bashar is a
part of which many millions of
individuals are a part both in feminine
and masculine aspect we thank you for
being bold and strong and willing to
blend these ideas within yourself it was
told to you many times before by both
Bashar and myself in various ways in
dream states and in physical
conversation that this idea was a
communication device understand that it is so polish
device understand that it is so polish
and finish put on the Caps be they
Crystal or be they other insulating
material does not really matter so much
as long as you have created it out of
the craft of your heart as long as you
cherish this idea and you put your heart
and your soul into it as long as it is
the symbol of your polished desire and
conductivity to all aspects of yourself
it will do the job and it will work for
you surely just as it will work for
anyone else it is in that sense your
magic b it is your magic gate your magic
doorway use it for it is your telephone
to the stars and your telephone to all
aspects of your Stellar qualities allow
us to cherish you by cherishing yourself
I only ask you this favor
do yourself the favor and allow us to
enjoy you in this way we thank you we
love you and we B you a fond and loving
good night I love you too thank
you we thank you for the opportunity to
share in that conversation as a little
bit of an Eevees
dropper you have done precise work and
we commend you in that way for the
Precision and attention to detail but as
was pointed out by anima it is your to
use for yourself as well you deserve it
it's your toy it is your present in that
sense give it to yourself as well as
making it for other people allow
yourself now allow yourself now to do
what anama has suggested in the comfort
of your own timing in the privacy of
your own home if you wish or out in
nature for the idea of nature being
surrounded by the trees and hearing the
ocean and sitting in the grass is a very
nice place as we see on your planet to
have tea and conversation
feel infused with nature for you know that
infused with nature for you know that
the spirit of the idea of the entire
Earth in your terms is feminine aspect
let it nurture you let it treat you as
the little child that deserves all the
love you know is at your
disposal enjoy our love to you we B you all at
enjoy our love to you we B you all at
this
timing to remember to remember that you
are God's seeds where you have planted
yourselves you will grow you are capable
of anything and everything positive and
negative but you always have choice we
cannot tell you that enough you are in
control you have the power be
direct not circumspect with yourselves
be bold be
clear take the step Act
you have also upon your planet many
individuals who have the resources and
the wisdom and the love and the caring
to share with you their
abilities from time to time we have now
and then recommended a few of your books
because we know simply that we wish to
point out Simply that you have the
resources on your own world to do what
you wish we have discussed last time briefly
wish we have discussed last time briefly
a work a book that is called
wishcraft we do not recommend this
because we in your terms own a
percentage of the
book we do not recommend it because we
wish to deny that other books have Merit
we have recommended many of them but we
do not wish to endorse because we know
some of you will still take our
endorsement as being a stamp of approval
and all other books go by the wayside so
we do it cautiously we call out things
cautiously but most importantly we wish
you to understand that when we recommend
something like that it is because we
wish you to understand you have the
knowledge on your own planet in your own
people you are a wise and compassionate
race of beings believe in
yourselves there is a segment in your
book of wishcraft that gives you many
examples of all the different ways you
can go about expressing your abundance
other than the idea of having to have
money yes you can have that it's a very
valuable idea it is not the only one you
can buy something
yes but you can also trade you can also
make it yourself you can also win it you
can also be given it as a gift you can
borrow it you can rent it you can do
many things with what you need acquire
the tools and the props of what you need
and use them act on them do not build a
prop and then sit with it wondering what
is going on apply it act upon it get out
in the
world and in that sense know that the
world will shape itself to what you need
and it will do so for everyone and there
is no conflict in this no one loses
because you win you all win because
there is enough for
everyone you are learning this now and
we thank you for learning this now we
thank you for being willing to learn
this now a very good suggestion was given by
now a very good suggestion was given by
a spiritual friend of us all and the
suggestion was was simply
this even if at some moment you may feel
that you do not have what you need that
you do not have what it takes very often
all that is necessary is to say I may
believe I do not have it now but at
least I am willing to have
it then act to the best of your ability
on what you can do use your
imagination and let the rest take care
of it yourself automatically because you
are effortless beings of creation
effortless easy enjoyable exciting be
bold no one will turn you away there is
always an appropriate audience for
everything you truly need to say and you
will find that audience for everyone who
wishes to be on a particular stage there
is always an audience to appreciate what
you have to say once again because
everything fits and everything belongs
and there is never never never never
never never never
never an actor that is born without an
audience that is born at the same time
for that
actor never it all works perfectly flawlessly
never it all works perfectly flawlessly
believe it act like you believe it and
you'll see the results guar guaranteed
can't prove it to you wouldn't want to
try but it works for us you are no
different because you fall under the
same one law of creation there is only
one what you put out is what you get
back see for
yourself our love to
you our thanks to you we will
communicate once more in this fashion
what of
your months from now in the third part
of
summation so that we may wrap up one
level and open the box to another so
that you may proceed more boldly in a
world more
open with all the potential right in
front of you yours for the
doing do think is
wonderful believe is wonderful feel is
wonderful doing is what creates the reality in
doing is what creates the reality in
your
experience our love to you
unconditionally our thanks to you for
the gift of sharing we bid you all a
fond and ecstatic good night
how'd it go
[Applause]