How are you all this evening of your
time is due time to exist.
We shall begin this evening of your time
this interaction with the reminder that
we discussed that this would be one of
three remaining interactions in this
format. Therefore, the entitlement of
this interaction can simply be summation
part one. Next of your month can be
summation part two and finally summation
part three where we will be in a sense
recollecting many of the principles that
we have discussed before but adding
nuances new understandings new
perspectives and the evolution of the
consciousness upon our planet makes
possible math. We will be discussing
things in rather shall we say not
simplistic but simplified terminology
because now each and every one of you
whether you are quote unquote new to
these interactions or not have at this
point in your understanding in your
consciousness evolutionary growth the
means the capability to follow on to
understand the principle you do not
necessarily need now as a society to
start a new day from scratch. Now you
can begin to utilize the principles and
the terminology that we will share with
you because now you are finding in your
society many of these principles are now
coming from many different directions.
They are not as isolated as they used to
be. So now you are not as isolated from
them. You have the ability now the
resources now to discover what you need
to within the wealth of information and
the wealth of knowledge of all the
individuals in your society. You now
each and every one of you have the
capability of attracting yourself to the
tools of information that you may
require to achieve what it is you desire
to achieve in your lives. Now you do not
need in a sense as much pushing from us
from many of us any of our type. We will
always be sending energy to your world.
Always always we will always be
interacting with you on various levels
of your consciousness. But now the idea
is for you to understand that the
principles we have been discussing all
boil down as you say to taking your life
in your hands and doing what it is that
you find most exciting and manifesting
this excitement into your phys
theological reality. The tools to do
this are plain and simple very
straightforward and as you say down to
earth. The ideas now can be put into
your life and you can be shall we say
ruined from the need to run to
individuals to find the answers that you
all now know within your hearts exist
within you. So the ideas now that we
shall some of the basic principles that
we have discussed over the last five of
your years and we shall discuss in a
very straightforward manner. When we
first discuss many of these principles,
many analogies and many metaphors were
necessary because the terminology of
your world was still, shall we say,
getting used to these principles. And
even though many of you now as
individuals may still be getting used to
these principles, even though many of
these ideas may still seem to be very
new to you, very contradictory to the
things that your society has always
taught you, you now have enough
resources to avail yourself to clarify
these ideas very quickly. There are
enough resource materials in your
literature in what you may call your
media now to take advantage of to apply
in your lives in a very direct
way. You may find still in your society
that some of these methodologies may be
more complex than others. Some of them
may be still more ritualistic than
others. Simply remember whatever it is
that you find yourself most attracted
to, whatever it is your
curiosity magnetizes you too. It
magnetizes you to that for a reason. You
are magnetized to a particular thing
because that is the thing at that
particular moment in your life that will
work best for you. That is the tool that
is the sharpest for you. When you find
that that changes, change with it. Flow
with it. You must think that the tool
has lost any of its power for it has
not. You must think that it is no longer
worthwhile for it is not. Everything
shall always be worthwhile and
everything is valid. It is simply that
you change because change is the only
constant in creation. And as you change
your tools will change and they can at
times simplify and at times according to
your own personal construction according
to your own desires and whims and wishes
they can become a little bit more
complex as well. This idea this
principle of the vagaries of your energy
the vagaries of your movie ups and downs
of your attitudes are one of the things
that we would like to discuss this
evening of your time before we begin our
interaction. For we have understood that many of the
For we have understood that many of the
things we have talked about are still in
your terminology perhaps taken upon a
certain assumption that they mean this
and that and that no other meaning can
apply when your own imagination should
be the key to let you know what it is.
What meaning will work best for you. Yet
still because of the way you are taught
many of you adhere to the idea that when
you are told this and that that only
this and that will work for you when
there are many things any number of
things an infinite number of things that
will work based on the principle that we
are discussing each and every one of you
will tailor those principles to your own
needs to your own personality there is
no one right way as you have said many a
time if there were only one way there
would only be one person and there are
many of you and many of us every single
way there is is another way that the
infinite creation has of expressing
itself. Therefore, let us now remind
you. We have talked many times about
following your excitement being that
what you call your excitement is the
thing that best represents who and what
you are in your life. That excitement is
the reflection of your energy, the
energy of the true you, the soul you,
the spirit you, the higher self. And
that following your excitement is the
most direct way to stay aligned with the
path of doing what it is you created
this physical life to do.
But many of you have assumed that when
we talk about following your excitement
that that means that at every single
given moment in your life, if you are
not feeling 100% excited like jumping up
and down all the time that something is
wrong. The idea to understand is that
when we talk about excitement, we are
talking about the core vibration of your
being. You can if you are willing to
feel that core vibration even when you
are in one of what you call your bad
news. Even when you are having one of
what you call your awful days you can
still feel the core momentum.
Therefore, perhaps it may be assistant
to you if instead of the word
excitement, the word momentum may work
best for some of you to simply
understand that you can still create as
many of you are want to do good moods
and bad moods, happy attitudes and sad
attitudes. And even through all of that,
you can still feel the core momentum
that moves you in the direction of what
it is you're all about, what you have
decided is true for you. So do not
necessarily assume that just because we
talk about excitement that you must
always be walking around with a very
wide vision from ear to ear in order for
these ideas to work for you. They will
always work for you as long as you
understand that it is representative of
your core vibration, your momentum and
that you always act according to that
knowledge regardless of your mood. Yes,
what you may call a positive attitude
may accelerate the idea in a positive
direction. But it doesn't necessarily
mean that just because you may be in a
foul mood that you have to give up all
hope and start all over again from
square one as you say. Do not be so hard
upon yourself for you do not deserve it.
You are marvelous engines of creation
and you are always functioning
flawlessly. You decide in what manner
you will function. You decide what
components go into the makeup of your
persona of your fabric of your essence.
You decide how fast or how slow you go
relative to everything else, which of
course is only relative. We would simply
suggest that you do not necessarily
spend too much time measuring yourself
against anyone else. Since because
everything is relative, you really
cannot get an accurate comparison since
everything is infinite in all
directions. No matter where you are,
there really is no way to tell exactly
how far you have to come or how far you
have to go. Because no matter how far
you go, it's still going to be infinite
ahead of you and it is always going to
be infinite behind you.
So there is no need to measure yourself
and compare yourself in that way. Take
your measurements if they assist you to
understand who and what are. But we
would simply suggest that you do not use
them to be great or judge yourself or
hold yourself back. More that you
understand you allow them in that way to
make you think that you are still not
accomplishing what it is you truly
desire. For you always are if you know
you are. And every single thing that
occurs in your life will synchronously
add to the overall melding part that
will get you where it is you desire to
be. We will also have something to
discuss being that this is a summation
at the end of this interaction this
evening of your time. But for now, allow
us once again to extend to you from our
great joy, our deepest appreciation in
being allowed to interact with you in
this way, in being allowed to
communicate with your society in this
way, in you choosing to function as
representatives and ambassadors in this
way and allowing us the gift and the joy
of experiencing your unique
consciousness. In return for this gift,
I ask you now, in what way, at this
time, may I be of service to you?
And do you good day? Do always remember,
please be bold, speak up, so that all
may share what you have to say.
Well, what I want to ask you is um need
some clarification on something you said
before regarding
um you were talking about soulmates at
the time. Soulmates. Yes. All right. And
um you said that we had a counterpart of
ourselves and the process was to view
ourselves uh in the opposite sex. That
was one of the exercises. Yes. Yes. And
the question I have is were when in the
beginning in creation was there a split
in who we are or there is in what you
call a beginning which from our point of
view doesn't really exist but I will
keep it in your terminology. From the
beginning, there is all things, all
concepts, all principles, all reality.
Anything you can conceive of is
somewhere, somewhere, and somehow a
reality. You do not so much experience
what you are calling a polarized split
until you project a portion of your
consciousness into what you are familiar
with as physical reality because
polarity is one of the definitions of
what you call the solid material
physical universe. So when you are a
non-physical entity, you do not really
experience yourself so much as what you
may call male or
female in the physical reality. Since
polarity exists, then your soul can
express itself in one or more of those
ideas. So physical reality basically in
general just to use that term as a
general term is where you first
experience yourself as a polarity you
would call male and female. You
understand? Yes. But the principle
exists, always has existed. Otherwise,
it is not something that could be
experienced in any reality. If you are
experiencing it now in your physical
reality, if it is one of the ingredients
of the reality you are in, then it
always has existed and it always has
existed somewhere, shall we say, within
the overall makeup of all that is from
the beginning. Always, although there is
no real beginning, you follow me? Yes.
Is this answering your question at all?
Yes. Would you like to clarify more
specifically? Yeah. Just one more point
would be um this business of looking for
the person that's going to make you feel
whole is what you were discussing. Yes.
Then are you saying that we were
discussing the idea that many
individuals do it that way? Yes. when
they could attract their counterpart by
knowing they are whole to begin with and
having that counterpart come into their
lives as a reflection of the wholeness
they know they already are rather than
looking for someone else to make them
feel whole which is a basic belief that
you are not whole without that person
you understand yeah that I do then what
is all the scoop about the soul mates
and the twin flames and the same
vibration you know I mean the inside
scoop inside scoop the so-called inside
scoop is simply
Many individuals will simply choose to
give themselves what can be called a
moniker, a measuring
stone, a reflective point, an idea in
their life to set up for a physical life
a split in their soul energy. So that
when they progress let's say for now
when each path which is in itself a
whole progresses along the path they
have outlined they will give themselves
certain feedback that will allow them to
know they are aligned on that path. The
so-called consummation of knowing that
they have created the alignment in both
halves is where the attraction occurs
and brings both halves together back
into its original hole. They set up for
themselves a mirror encounter which is
called a twin flame or a soulmate in
what you call your archetypal sense. Now
there are many variations of this term
as we have already said anyone you
interact with since everyone serves the
purpose of teaching you something in a
sense is a soulmate. Okay. But there can
be those specific energies, those
specific polarity reflections that as a
soul prior to physical light, you lay
down as a basic conduit, as a template
so that when you allowed yourself,
either half of yourself to stay firmly
aligned, the quote unquote reward for
staying in that alignment would be the
rejoining, the reinforcing of those two
individual vibrations back into one
vibration to allow you to know that what
you had done basically was experience
similar ideas from polarity viewpoints.
Let us say as male and female. Let's say
a soul wishes to experience a particular
idea but wishes to experience it in the
same lifetime from two different points
of view as the polar opposites of male
and female can split itself into what is
called twin soul, twin flame. And then
when those experiences are culminated
will rejoin itself in what you may call
a celebration of the physical joining
that will then lead to a union and
spiritual joining after physical life
and a reblending of the original soul.
You following? Yes, I do. Does that help
you very much? Yes. Thank you very Thank
you very much.
Good evening, Michelle. Good day to you.
Um, my mother recently went into the
hospital. All right. Uh, there there was
bleeding and right now they don't know
what is the cause and I was wondering if
you could help me with that.
From what area bleeding? Rectal.
Is individual under great tension at
all? No. Is individual in this way of a
particular age can you reveal? 60. One
moment. All we are allowed to perceive
at this time is that to some degree
there may be to some degree a
minological imbalance in certain
portions of the body. One
moment. One moment. One moment.
There are three spirit guides assisting
this individual. This individual can
individual. This individual can
communicate in states of sleep or in
states of repose and meditation with
these spirit guides. These three spirit
are guides, shall we say, have the duty,
guides, shall we say, have the duty,
have the assignment, have made the
choice to be the one to
interact with this individual and to
provide the information that it's
taught. It is not at this time within
our domain. If you wish, I will
apologize for that. For we do not enter
into all domains and at times are not
allowed access to information that is in
your terminology supposed to come
through other avenues. Those three
spirit guides in your terminology have
the communication have the assistance
covered with that individual. If she
will imagine herself immersed in
clarifying and supportive water floating
meditating be immersed in blue light and
open herself up. Open her heart up. open
her body up to the idea of the free
guide. They can provide the information
that is required. It is not within our
domain at this time to do so.
If she opens herself up to that
communication with the three guides,
will she then find a healing? It is
highly likely. And at the same time, you
may find she will provide a healing for
some other individuals. Now, one moment.
One moment. What we are allowed to say is
moment. What we are allowed to say is
that it is our perception that this
individual may have decided that there
will be to some degree a prolonged time
of what will appear to
be pendulum swings of healing and
disease. Healing and disease that may
stretch out for what you may call few
more months to a few more years. The
individual has strong potential to teach
what they need to teach and then in your
terminology to translate themselves into
non-physical reality. All of this will
be within the agreement and the timing
and the assistance of the three guides
and this individual.
However, certain things can be learned.
All of this has a purpose. It again is
not our domain nor is the information
completely accessible to us as to all
the reasons for this particular pattern.
It is again more in the domain of the
three guides. But if the guide are
allowed through if communication is open
between them, you will all learn. Very
beautiful lesson. That is all that we
can provide at this time. Thank you. We
thank you very
much.
Shannon, one more. We would at this time
endeavor always as a part of what you
may call the weaning process to remind
each and every one of you we are in
every way, shape and form. No matter
what you may perceive our particular
talents, our particular abilities to be,
we are in every way, shape and form
simply people like yourselves. We are
not in your terms God. We do not know
everything. We are only in the sense God
even as you are God. We know everything
we need to know to be who we are. And
what we are to be reflected to each and
every one of you is that you all know
what you need to know to be who you are.
Our domain sometimes does not cross into
your domain. Some things that are known
to us are not known to you. Some things
that are known to you are not known to
us, nor should they be because we never
want to rob you and remove from you your
ability to create your own discovery. We
assist where we can, but always be
reminded that in that sense we are not
more capable of knowing what you need to
know than you are. Especially not about
your own world and your own lives. We
provide a perspective that has worked
for us so that perhaps the perspective
will rub off on you and you will open up
to the answers that are always within
you. Sharing. Good morning, Michelle.
And who do you? Uh, I have a very down
to earth question. Oh, all right. I hope
it's not too mundane for you. Nothing is
ever too mundane. We are very excited
about everything. I'm just curious about
the growth of consciousness on the
planet in a geographical sense. There
seems to be a lot of uh growth of
awareness and awareness of
extraterrestrials and so on. In places
like California, whereas in other areas
it's a different form or not rapid not
as rapid growth. Different areas upon
your planet will have different energy,
different degrees of acceleration.
individuals that are willing to flow at
certain rates will find themselves
attracted to those different energy
zones and therefore the populations in
those energy zones will be
representative of the acceleration of
the energy in that area. So in other
words, there are a few areas around your
planet such as your California where the
energy is very intense where it is very
transformational geologically,
geologically,
magnetically and therefore individuals
that like to live on the edge will
attract themselves to those areas.
Therefore, they may exhibit in certain
ways a little more willingness to
explore things that the main state of
your society is not yet willing to
explore. Not that we are implying that
everyone necessarily
should. But yet there are those
fluctuations simply as a product to some
degree. Not only of your overall
collective consciousness, but also of the
consciousness, but also of the
collective consciousness of the earth
itself which as a living crystal has
edges and planes and concentration
points where the energy fluctuates and
therefore the light that is attached
shall we say to that particular area
will always represent that energy
through themselves. Yes.
themselves. Yes.
Is there any particular are there any
other particular areas that uh we could
expect a lot of growth to take place?
Well, now that your entire world is
coming together, there will be growth
everywhere. But the places where it
seems to be most
accelerated will be areas that you would
call your Middle East on and around your
year of 1997. There will be such rapid
growth and such rapid transformation in
that area that you will find that what
comes out of that area will have much to
do creating repercussions that will
change much of the other areas around
your entire planet as well.
There are many other growth areas going
on upon your planet. There are very
strong blending taking place within what
you call your Hawaii area. Very strong
surges of energy going on in what you
now call your Yakutan Peninsula and in
your Brazil area. Much is happening
within what you now call your southern
African area. All these what you may
call hot spots are all for the purpose
of bringing to the surface many of the
things that your society has kept below
the level of consciousness. Bringing
them all out so that you can see what
you have on your table and decide which
of all those things negative and
positive you want to retain for the new
age the new world that you will be
creating over the next 50 to 100 of your
years of
transformation. But whatever you find
yourself most attractive that is where
you belong.
Does that help you? It does. Thank you.
Can I just ask about Australia, my
homeland? Is there any particular thing
you have to say about Australia? Very
strong magnetic point as many of you
already know around the structure called
the rock of a highly magnetic, highly
conducive doorway to other dimensions.
Also, because there is so much of what
you may call dolphin interaction in that
area and around what you call your New
Zealand area, a great deal of
opportunity exists for you to blend with
an alien society right on your very own
planet, the dolphin and whale
consciousness. The area
specifically between your eastern coast
of Australia and your western coast of
New Zealand is a
highly magnetic and highly active point
of interaction and flux. Very plastic
and very malleable. You can create
almost anything there you wish. Very new
open world new land as you used to say
terra incognita.
The following. Yes. Thank you for sir.
For there is the cauldron of birth. The
cauldron that boils with all sorts of
probability. Out of that cauldron you
can pull many things which will cool and
solidify and crystallize in the cool
clear air of the new world. Thank you
very much. Thank you. Sure.
Good day, Bashar. I feel good there. We
once discussed um the crystal skulls.
Yes. In particular, the Mitchell hedges.
Thanks. And you told me that. One
moment. One moment. Those not familiar,
there are artifacts that have been
created upon your planet that are the
likenesses of human skull carved out of
blocks of quartz, crystal of particular,
shall we say, property. These were
created at various times upon your
planet within different civilizations.
They basically function as gateways and
doorways or shall we say paths or maps
that lead to gateways and doorways to
other dimensions. Some civilizations use
them as such and translated themselves
from your dimension into a higher
density. But these skulls still remain.
And if you can face them in a sense with
all your inner light, then you can also
discover those doorways and gateways for
yourself that lead to other dimensions
not only of other realities but also
other dimensions within your own
consciousness. difficulty. You told me
that I would have a chance to see it and
that when I did, it would um I should
look into its eyes and it would tell me
things that when I made the changes, I
would reach my wildest dreams. I made a
quest to see it. Yes. And although I
felt very strongly, very strong
vibrations in my hands when I touched
it. I didn't have any visionary or
auditory experiences. Oh, and I was
disappointed. Vibrations in the hands
not enough.
And I on the way home I I've recently
become a member of an ancient mystery
school called the Rosa Cruian. Oh, what?
And I was reading one of their letters.
One moment. Why? I don't know. That was
another thing I meant to ask you about.
Um, I was attracted to it. Several
people uh simultaneously told me about
it from different sources and I thought
I should explore it. And the lesson I
read on the way home dealt with five
physical senses and how seven. That was
what the lesson was that there's more
than five. There are seven. And um I'm
wondering how this tied in. If it was
synchronistic that I read everything is
synchronistic. Nothing is accidental.
Well, how does it tie in? You tell me. I
I I was wondering what you would say if
and um that's an easy out.
What does your vibrational intuition
say? That there were doorways open that
I'm not aware of physically. All right.
Now you can be aware of them. Go back to
the vibration in your hand. Go back to
the knowledge that there are seven
physical senses. Do you know what the
other two are? No. Aside from the five
you aren't all generally familiar with,
there is the sixth sense of
orientation. That is simply space and
time orientation which is lodged in your
sinus cavity within the substance
therein called magnetite. It is how you
have what you call homing
instinct. What you usually call the
sixth sense is actually the seventh
sense and that is vibrational
discernment. Again, electromagnetic in
nature and is lodged in every cell in
your body as a receiver antenna and in
what you would call the pituitary and
the pineal glands and are in your terms
regulated by the glandular function and
coordinated in the center of the brain.
The corpus colosum has the gateway that
leads to the eighth transcendental sense
of knowingness from which all the other
seven senses flow into physical reality.
Knowing that you are an electromagnetic
being will allow you to have more
familiarity with the vibration in your
hand for everything is vibration. Now
what do you think about the idea of
being a healer? I haven't thought about
it. Well, think about it and let me
know. Are you through
is that I' I've never that has nothing
to do with my dreams or goals in my
life. What are they? To write and direct
movies. To write and direct movies. What
kind? films that will enlighten people
and entertain. Enlighten and entertain.
Allow them, are you saying to enter
another vibration, another space,
another attitude so that they may in
receiving the attitude and the energy
from your works perhaps change the
attitude and the energy within
themselves and so be more centered? Yes.
Is that not healing?
So using the tactile sensations I have
isn't necessary for healing. Just by
doing what comes to me in my expressing
myself is the form of healing I give.
You will use your tactile sensations,
but you will use it for communication.
For communication between different
individuals to allow things to operate
smoothly and to get things done. You
already understand, do you not, that
individuals will listen to you more
closely if you touch them while you're
talking? Yes. Yes. Allow yourself then
to smooth the way with your hands and to
use the electromagnetic energy of all
your senses and to impart that art to
all that will be attracted to your work
as an artist in that way. One moment.
The reason that your hands vibrated is
because it was in synchronous harmony
with the crystal primarily because you
yourself in past lives have fashioned
crystals like that before. Understand?
with your hands. Not that particular one
though. Not that particular one. But
they are all linked. They are a network.
When you say that uh you have to have a
certain vibration or light in order to
open those doors, then those doors were
opened even though I didn't I
experienced them tactally. Yes. Okay.
How does the roian thing tie in? It ties
in because it is a remnant memory of a
very ancient order. That is to some
degree an extension of the knowledge
that you had back when you formed those
crystals. To some degree it is connected
at least through you. This is not the
same for everyone, but at least through
you to ancient druidic orders in what
you may call your England area having to
do also with the areas called the
standing stones. You follow me? Is that
related to Stonehenge? Yes,
I see. Thank you.
Rosian is your modernday counterpart
symbol to allow you to feel at home in
an old idea that you are very familiar
with and the vibration of the hands is
even older still but it is all connected
through the rituals that you performed
in different lives that are linearly
linked to what you are going through
now. You are still in that sense an
artist. You are still sculpting and
forming reality with your hand. First it
was the crystal, then it was the stone,
now it is images. But that is all right.
Understand? You are now working directly
with light. You follow me? That sounds
wonderful. Well, all right. If it sounds
so wonderful, you wouldn't do it. Thank
you very much. And Deshan, I just want
to say how much I have enjoyed all of
our encounters. And if we don't meet
again, I hope we do meet face to face
someday. We will always be meeting. We
are always intertwined, all of you and
all of us. If you wish to meet us
anytime, all you have to do is look in a
mirror. Understand? Thank you. Thank
you. Thank you,
Sharon. Hi, Michelle. Oh, hi,
my old friend. How are you? I'm not that
old. Only
Only
one of your years. Very young.
Well, all right. All
right. 170. Oh, see he's lying about his
age. You mean there's vanity? Uh where
you come from? Oh my. Thus the relative
time frame is different. Aha. Wink wink.
I wore this short. This short this shirt
for you, Bashar. It's of our Well, I'm
sure you can see it pantically, but it's
so Okay. It's It's of our uh our space
program that just got underway again
that I think everybody's real happy
about. Yes. And my question has to do
with um the scientific and uh scientific
community has determined in the recent
year I suppose that what we once thought
the universe was expanding at a very
great rate. Now they have realized that it's
rate. Now they have realized that it's
slowed down and they are speculating
well the the galaxies they said were
expanding outward and now they're
slowing down. Now they're speculating
that a possibility am I not talking into
this enough?
Um that it's they speculate that it may
possibly now start to collapse back unto
itself. And my question is um whether it
expands out indefinitely or collapses
unto into itself, what would be the
impact on other densities? My mind
I'm always good for this kind of
question, aren't I?
not meaning in any way, shape or form to
be mysterious nor sound in your terms
unscientific, but it is always
both. You have not yet as a civilization
the understanding that what you call
cycles in a sense occur within larger
frameworks, those larger frameworks
exist eternally. Cycles are the product
quote unquote of what you may call a
smaller framework within eternity. There
can be expansion and collapse within
eternity. In a sense, eternity always is
expanding and every expansion and every
collapse adds to the total information
of all that is and expands it always
infinitely. In general, the idea however
of what you call the expansion and the
collapse, those cyclical ideas of your
physiological material universe are not
exactly as your scientists think them to
be. There are things going on that you
may call which many of their scientists
understand whole tunnel gateways from
one dimension to another constantly
pouring into each other where there are
shall we say weak points in the fabric
between them. This pouring from one
dimension to another always allows there
to be an infinite steady state universe
while at the same time each of those
discrete realities that are pouring into
each other can experience expansion and
collapses. But overall there is only
eternity and infinity. And within it
there is any number of realities
experiencing their existence in any way
you can imagine it to be. And they are
all true and they are all real. You
understand?
Sort of. All right. Um I guess what I'm
I I don't really understand or maybe you
can clarify is that if indeed let's say
it takes the turn and it start the g the
universe starts collapsing unto itself.
Now we are interrelated on all different
levels and at different densities um
interconnected would it maybe
physiologically is is the word I'm
looking for would have impact on other
densities. Yes, of course. In what way?
Well, one way is that the collapse of
one universe is the birth of another.
Therefore, what you may call the demise
of your physical reality will be
responsible for the creation of an
entirely different one. And that I would
say is an impact. Yeah, pretty good
impact. Many of what you may call your
crazyards are in fact just such
phenomena. They are the pouring into
your universe of the result of the collapse
universe of the result of the collapse
of other universes. You follow me? Yeah.
Yeah. Now that makes sense. And many of
what you call your black holes are the
siphoning out from your universe into
other universes. Sometimes there are
gates that leave one universe and come
back into the same universe. Wow. There
are any number of exchanges of this
type, but there is no one set way. If
you're going to talk about will our
universe collapse, you are talking about
one discrete frame of reference and only
from that point of view does the idea
make some sense. From that point of
view, yes, there are cycles within your
physical reality. There is to some
degree expansion and there are
collapses. And in your terms, the cycle
you are in now is not the first. There
is no way to count which one it is. You
understand? Yes, I do. All we know as a
civilization is that the cycle you are
in now, quote unquote, is not the first,
even linearly speaking.
Does that happen? Yes, it does. Oh,
thank you very much. Thank you. And
thank you for all the years of
information and love and my love to you
and everyone in Aasani. Our love to you
as well. Sh.
[Music]
Hi, Bashan. I good day. I had an
experience about two years ago. Can you
all hear this person?
I had an experience about two years ago
and in this experience I had a dream.
Yes. And I woke from the dream and the
dream was about finding a planet.
Finding a planet in the dream. Yes. Yes.
And I was aware that I had to get off
this planet very quickly. It was about
to be destroyed. All right. And as I
awoke from the dream, I was very very
much aware also that I was seeing coming
through the wall in front of me someone
who I knew was from another planet. All
right. And as I faced him, I was aware
that he was communicating with me in a
language that wasn't from Earth. All
right. And I could understand him and
feel and sense what he was saying to me.
Yes. And and the message from him was
that I was here from a planet that had
been destroyed. Yes. To try and prevent
this planet here from being destroyed.
did that one was. Yes, many of you are
doing this now. The idea is that this
has happened in a chain, a link of
chains of traveling from system to
system for many of you that now have
incarnated upon earth. You have existed
in many different civilizations, a
series of civilization that have
destroyed themselves. And now you have
brought all of that momentum into the
cycles that are now proceeding upon your
earth so that you can decide if you want
to do that again or if you want to
balance things out. Now it is our
perception that you are going to balance
things out this time. That's great. Um
there's I I had a lot of trouble really
allowing that in that experience and it
was well I didn't much believe in people
like extraterrestrials at the time.
Well, thank you.
I've since come to realize that there
must be something there. I had
uh thank you again.
I had there was a time when we didn't
believe in you either.
[Applause] [Music]
[Music]
One of my clients came to see me about 2
or 3 weeks later and she said to me at
the time, "Wendy, whenever I see you, I
always see you in your space outfit in
your spacecraft." Right. And I had a
little bit of difficulty believing this
even because I didn't imagine that I'd
been on a spaceship or even been
involved in anything like space travel.
All right. So I asked her to describe it
without telling her the experience that
I'd had. And she went through and
described the planet that I left and all
the other people who left with me. All
right. And uh so I was brought to a
decision of yes, there must be something
there. All right. And since then I've
had a number of dreams in which I've uh
remembered from early childhood where
I've actually been on
spaceships. What I'm really trying to
understand at this point is I've also
been channeling for a number of years
and trying to coordinate what is
happening to me with my channeling and
how that links in with the channeling of
the dolphins that I've been doing and
also with the experience of the uh um
extraterrestrials. You know, how does
that all link in with me and the work
that I'm going to be doing?
First of all, understand that you will
serve your planet by whatever it is that
excites you the most. That will be your
service. You are being assisted simply
by guides. Some of which are in dolphin
consciousness form, some of which are
old friends, and some of which are in
what you may call extraterrestrial form,
some of which are also old friends.
Strong is the indication of serious
energy from the star you call period. as
an overview, as an over guide to help
you to make the path a little clearer,
to shed some light on the idea. But you
as the facilitator on earth must decide
how you will be of assistance by
deciding what it is that excites you the
most and doing it. What excites you? I
think I'm already doing what I'm what
what excites me. And what is that? Who
shares? I'm um running a metaphysical
spiritual center in in Australia. All
right. and uh working at um a lot of uh
therapy work. I'm doing a lot of
channeling, seeing clients. All right.
Are you having a good time? I love it.
Oh, well, thank you very much. Do you
see change happening in your world
around you because of what you are
doing? There are more and more things
happening all the time. It's expanding
and expanding at such a rate that
sometimes I wonder whether I'm going to
explode soon. Oh yes, you will. But only
into more
ecstasy. Do remember you are never given
more than you can handle. For what would
be the point in that? 100%. And what
about all the energy that seems to flow
through me all the time that I can
hardly contain it? Flow it. Muse it. It
is only feeling like too much because of
old assumptions of what your poor little
body can
handle. Flow with it. The energy that's
there is how strong you are. Use it in
every creative way that you can. It is
not too much. You are simply feeling old
ideas relative ideas of resistance based
on the difference that you are creating
in a vibration that makes it seem as if
the resistance will be overwhelming. The
friction between them will be
overwhelming. Relax. Anytime it feels
like it's going to be too much, relax.
Take a few deep breaths or take a
vacation and enjoy yourself. Do
remember, do remember, you are not meant
to serve at the expense of yourself.
Treat yourself with the same respect and
the same love and the same care that you
treat all of your clientele with. You
understand? Yes, I do. Does that help
you? It does indeed. Thank you very
much. One moment.
Will you be traveling or be in the
waters between your Australia and New
Zealand in the near future? Yes, I will
be. In about 3 weeks time, I'll be
traveling back to Australia.
Will you be in the waters between
Australia and New Zealand for any length
of time?
I don't imagine at the moment. In the
water, meaning right being submerged in
the water. Is that what you suggest?
Either on a conveyance such as a boat or
physically in the water. Either
I can't think of anything at the moment.
No. I was going to fly home. One moment.
One moment.
Are you aware at this time of anything
coming up that will draw you to New
Zealand from Australia?
There are several possibilities. It's a
place that I've been wanting to go to
for many years. Why?
I feel as if I've been there before and
I want to go back there again. One
moment. All right. All right. Great
healing, great strength, great anchoring
can come from reuniting with what you
may call your past self in that area.
Very primal energy, very primal and
strong. in the water between your New
Zealand and your Australia. You'll have
an opportunity to physically encounter
along with many of his friends the
dolphin that we have called Dreamer.
Have a good time and say hello for us. I
will indeed. It will be a large dark
gray male dolphin. All right. Thank you.
The largest in the fog.
Thank you. Thank you very much. hands.
Uh good evening Bash to you. Good day.
Uh my name is Manuel and what and my
question to you is uh are the angels
that are mentioned in Judaism uh
Christianity and Islam are they uh
entities from your dimension or your
density in a sense? Yes, to some degree.
They're also from many different
dimensions, many different densities.
Now, shall we say, technically speaking,
the consciousnesses that are very often
perceived as angelic, as angels, or
called as such in your ancient
literature, are conscious recognitions
of those entities that generally
speaking have never been physical in
terms of you understand it, but yet have
the capability of projecting their
consciousness to yours and you creating
a perception of them in a way that makes
sense to the civilization. at the time.
Hence, sometimes individuals can see
them with wings if wings is what it
takes to make sense out of the fact that
these individuals are, shall we say,
lighter than your density. But all of
this is archetypal. All of this is an
analogy of projections of energy of
different beings. Some of which are
directly from our dimension, some of
which from higher dimensions that have
projected themselves and communicated
with your civilization for thousands of
your years. Yes. Does that answer your
question? Yes, it does. Uh that might
lead me to another question, but since I
committed to one question, I leave.
We'll let you get away with it. Okay.
Uh I like to know I feel like I am
communicating with one particular angel
and I like to know if that's something
I'm fabricating here from my third
density point of view or is something
that's actually existing. What does the
information allow you to do? More or
less advice dealing with just yes and
no. Yes and no questions. You are
functioning in a sense in communication
with a spirit guide. Yes, it is of a
spiritual nature. It is its own
consciousness. But it is also to some
degree intertwined with your own since
your own higher self is equal to it and
exists in the same dimension. But it is
a spirit guide in a sense. It can be
considered a guardian angel if you wish
to call it that. It has its own identity
and someday you will meet more directly.
Thank you Bish. Well, thank you very
much Sherry.
Good day, Bashar. I knew you good day.
I seem to be part of uh a real
acceleration. No. All right, guess
aren't you all? Aren't we all? Uh I
listened to a channeling that you did in
New York and this was in April and
within 24 hours I was in the midst of
something I had dreamed about for 14
years. Oh, thank you very much for
taking it to heart. I thank you. You're
welcome. At that point, within another
month, I was in Australia. All right.
With Joan. All right. And uh swimming
with the dolphins and and the whale.
Thank you.
Coming back into this reality. Yes. In
on the beach in Australia, many things
happened, but one thing was absolutely
sure that I that I was creating that.
No. Yes. And that was new to me to be
that happy and fulfilled and conscious.
Very conscious. Yes. So coming back into
Los Angeles, I realized that that was
actually what I wanted to have all the
time. That excitement that Why did you
come back with because I I knew that it
wasn't a a local thing that it was
everywhere. Yes. It is everywhere you
are. So ever since then that
acceleration you referred to it as just
about being too much to handle, but I
know that I need to handle it. Yes. And
that these things are my reality. Yes.
Well, I'm losing my reality. How so? In
that I don't want to cling on to it. Oh,
all right. You're transforming it from
the reality you no longer desire into
the one that you do. Exactly. You're not
losing anything, right? Nothing that I
wouldn't want to lose. So, this
acceleration Yes.
is put me wanting to hang on to those
things that were logical, analytical,
the things you can hang on to your
reason. No one is saying to give up your
mind. No one is saying to give up your reason.
No one is saying to give up your reason.
We are talking about balancing reason
and in right and that's what I seem to
be either on the right or on the left.
Meaning the acceleration has put me
hanging on to the things that I used to
think were real which I'm not really
concerned with. And and on the other end
of it I'm totally free and flying. Well,
you do know that all things are real.
Yes. No. Yes. Anything you can imagine is a
No. Yes. Anything you can imagine is a
reality. So, it's simply a matter of
understanding that all realities are
equal. And if you can have the one you
prefer, it doesn't make another reality
any less real. It simply makes it less
immediate. Understand? Right. I do. You choose the
Understand? Right. I do. You choose the
reality you want out of what you call
the holographic matrix of all that is.
All realities are possible and all are
blended into the background. The
vibration you decide to be is what
determines the reality that you vibrate
out of the background matrix and make
manifest around you. The vibration from
within determines what you see around
you. But that doesn't mean all the other
realities are not real. It simply means
you are not focused on the matter.
Right? And that's what I want to come to
terms with is being in the middle. You
are in the middle. That I that I know.
All right. Then what terms do you need
to come to?
I guess the my physical I find myself in
Los Angeles and I've been attracted to
ID Wild. Yes. And so when will you go
there? Next week. All right.
So So I really don't have a question. I
just wanted
No one said you needed a question to
talk with us. In fact, in a sense, not
being judgmental, we prefer statements
because then that shows that you are
taking responsibility for your own
reality. So feel free at any time to
tell us what your reality is rather than
ask us about it. Thank you. Thank you.
Have a good time. Me too. You will love
the idol in Idle Wild.
Sh. You good day.
Yeah, I'm from New
Zealand. And uh I want to thank you
about those many beautiful points of
views. I cannot apply my life to
listening to so many tapes. Thank you
very much. And I would like to know if
you if somebody New Zealand is
channeling your energy. One moment. Yes.
Is that so? And has it happened last
week? To some degree. There is still
some alignment taking place and there is
more than just myself represented from
my civilization in that area. There is
still blending taking place but it has
been going on for quite some months. Oh,
very good. Thank you. That's all I want
to do. Thank you very much. Goodbye. And
to you good day sharing.
Hi. And to you good day. Thank you very
much. You are welcome very much. Thank
you. Thank you. Thank you. You are all
welcome very much.
My question is about abortion. Abortion.
I've thought about it for a long time.
Then what have you thought? Well, many
many of us have had them. Um, different
religions teach different things. I sort
of came to the conclusion. I guess my
question is, is there a balancing that
needs to take place? Um, like when you
talked about suicide,
yes. Or if there is an agreement that
the relationship will be terminated and
that's just the playing out of the
agreement. That's sort of single
situation will be individually specific.
Okay. There will be just as many reasons
for the circumstance as there are
individuals participating within it. So
it can be complete within itself.
Absolutely. Some of them can be
representational of balance. Some of
them can be representational of specific
agreements. Some of them can be
representational of acting out of
integrity. Some of them can be
representational of acting completely
within integrity. It depends on the
individual who they are and what they
have agreed to. Okay. Thank you. Do you
understand? Yes, I do completely. Thank
you. Now, the idea generally speaking,
however, generally is that what your
civilization recognizes as the
individual personality soul
consciousness is actually not, shall we
say, colloquially for now, connected to
the body until just prior to physical.
Okay, you understand? Yeah, I
experienced that even for some time
after birth. It is very loosely
connected can be loosely connected for
up to 3 years of age so that the spirit
can come and go, come and go, come and
go. You understand? Yeah, I do. Now, the
You understand? Yeah, I do. Now, the
idea is that what you may call abortion
does not need to occur upon your planet,
right? Many of the reasons that many of
you find it necessary to do that is
because many of you are out of touch
with your own timing and out of touch
with your own communications with those
entities that choose in that sense to be
born to you. However, some entities know
that since this phenomena does exist in
your culture, they can take advantage of
it in certain ways. Perhaps certain
entities wish to experience a modicum of
physical reality, but not too
much. So they may choose an individual
that has decided in your terms to have
an abortion so that it will be for that
spiritual entity like sticking their
little toe in the water and then pulling
it back and they do not need anything
more than that. So in a sense anything
can be used to a positive advantage even
those things that may have originally
resulted from a negative idea. You
understand? Yes. Does that help? Yeah.
Thank you very much.
If you get a chance in this or the next
two times, could you possibly uh speak
on healing from the past? You mentioned
it once briefly. If you could give us
like some practical ways to do it or if
you know you have a disease so you go
back. Yes. If you if you could give us a
Yes. If you if you could give us a
technique at some point possibly.
All right. We shall do so at the end of
the season. Thank you very much.
Hello, Mr. Ambassador. Hello, Mr. Diplo
M.
Hey, how's things up there? Wonderful.
How's things over there? Peachy.
Um, I'd like to discuss momentum, which
you referred to before, and the catch 22
of excitement. Ketcha 22.
Hello, Pete.
Well, I feel that what I'm doing
basically in my life which I have
referred to as being exciting is my path
of
momentum. But it is has not yet produced
some of the effects which I would like
to have have created to to enable me to
do other things which I find exciting
which I can't do without money in this
case. Now you've talked about this
before and you say well you don't really
need the money you can have it manifest
some other way. All right, I am going to
in a sense in a positive way short
circuit this conversation with a
recommendation which is rare for us but
I will do so in this case. Okay, there
is what you may call a book that exists
in your society and in this case though
again it is rare not because in this
sense it is not worthwhile but because
we do not wish to add the idea that this
book should stand out more than any
other four intrinsic value but in this
case perhaps for many of you and for you
you will find it has the format that
will work best for you if you are not
already familiar with it. It is called
Wishcraft. Wishcraft. Wishcraft. Okay, get
it. Read it. Do what it
says. You will get what you want.
Interesting. Uh, can you give me the uh
name of the author? No.
Can I quiz you for a second on on this
book? All right. For a second. Okay.
That's all I wanted to know. Thank you
very much. No, actually um I I generally
don't get a whole lot out of kind of
wrote routines that you go through and
stuff like that. Trust that this book
does not Your imagination will do what
it needs to notice that you are to some
degree already starting to discount the
recommendation we have given you.
Okay, we have answered your question in as
we have answered your question in as
direct a way as quote unquote logical a
way as we possibly can. Read the book,
see what it does for you. We will
discuss it next time. Okay. Thank you.
Thank you.
Sh. Good evening, Bashar. Good day. Um,
this is Jill and hello. Um, last week,
last time I talked to you, we talked
about me working uh with some AIDS
patients. Yes. And the template and
acceleration and all this wonderful
stuff that's been happening. Okay. Um, I
don't necessarily have a question. All
right. Make a statement. I am. Well, my
statement is I'm still having a great
time and uh I'm still accelerating at a
very fast pace. Well, thank you very
much. Thank you. And I would like to
know if my guides or some others Well,
here come the questions. is I had to get
one in there. Um, have anything to tell
me that might help accelerate me a
little more in this area or keep me more
on the path or anything you want to tell
me?
It might be of
benefit to avail yourself and
your impatience again of their connection to
impatience again of their connection to
nature by being in nature by being among
the flowers and the trees and the
grasses of what you call the
outdoors away as you say from your city.
You understand? Is that why Sedona's
been driving me crazy the past month?
Yes. To some degree. Okay.
All right,
follow that instinct. You have been
receiving the messages and you know you
have been receiving the messages. It is
only driving you crazy because you're
not listening to the messages and then
come to me to tell you that you are
receiving messages you already know you
are receiving and not listening to.
I'm not going to accept that one cuz
that's not necessarily the case. What is
the case? Well, what is the case is um
I've been reading this book that was
sort of bare, you know, if you know what
I mean about Fedona and reading more
about it and um
one moment. One moment. All right. No
more magnetism. Electromagnetism. Thank
you very much. Yeah, that's it. I I
wanted to get whatever it was that that
felt more right for me. Electromagnetism
is the one. Electromagnetic fields can
be discovered to be one of the
strongest methods for what you may call
curing your AIDS and any disease. Yes,
that's what I thought. That aligning the
cellular structure back to its zero rest
state, its natural electromagnetic state
of balance, which makes it impossible,
shall we say, to have any disease at all
in your area of Sedona, which is a
highly electromagnetic area. You can
intuitively, shall we say, absorb
certain amounts of knowledge that have
to do with creating the types of
magnetic resonance fields that can
assist your patient. You follow me? Yes,
very much. Does that help you? Yes, it
does. And I have one short thing, not
for myself, for someone else. All right.
Um, today a very dear friend of mine's
mother passed away very very suddenly.
And uh I've been feeling that um a lot.
And I I
I don't I feel like I don't feel like
I'm here. I feel like I'm somewhere else
in a limbo state. Well, I don't know. I
I'm really picking up I think something
with her mother. All right. And also um
what the family hears with. I feel like
I'm I'm needing to bridge like I usually
do um something between the two. And the
synchronisticity of me being here being
able to ask you um is something I hope I
can How can you function as this bridge?
In what way does your imagination
inspire you to do so?
I think there might have been something
that's that's left unsaid undone between
maybe the the mother making her
transition and the family still here. Go
and be of assistance then and
complete innocent as a gobetween the
communication if you will. Well, they've
been listening to some of your tapes and
I didn't know if if maybe it is all
right if they listen to some of yours.
They are believe me. All right. All
right. So, if you wish to be of
assistance, follow your heart. Okay. You
will be for you will in a sense have
been asked to be in that position and
therefore it will be appropriate and
proper that you do deal. Trust yourself.
You will not get in the way
egotistically speaking. Just relax and
deliver what you feel is coming through
from one side to the other. All right.
All right. Would that be anything from
actually from the deceased mother or it
can be? Yes. Okay. All right. Yes. Thank
you very much.
Relax. Trust yourself. Oh, I do. I do.
No, I do trust myself. How much?
Implicitly? Implicitly? Mhm. I do. Are
you sure? Yes, I am. All right. Thank
you very much. Thank you very much. One
moment. Don't go anywhere. All right.
What does the mother want to say to
them? First thought, I'm okay. All right.
First thought, I'm okay. All right.
Second,
live your life, sir. I love you. Thank
you very much. Thank you. Simple as
that. Good luck. Could be. Thank you.
God bless. And you as well.
Hi, Andrew. Good day. Wait, no. Physical
reality is happening. Okay.
So, how how
perfect. Thank you very much. Um, but I
have a little problem. All right. Um, a
perfect problem. It is a perfect
problem. Um, things have been going
extremely well and I'm I'm very happy.
Oh, thank you. Thank Thank me. Yes,
because I'm doing it.
But our letting go of things, you know,
like like changes in relationships.
Yeah. Letting go of a form that it was
in, letting go
of one, for instance, an film interview
that I don't know if I got. It's like,
well, I know that I have it and I'm
letting it go, but in the same time,
it's like,
of course, did you do your best?
I felt I did. Well, why worry? Well,
it's not worrying so much as
it's like a a a battle between like the
right side and the left side of letting
it go and and but really wanting it and
thinking by letting it go now. One
moment. Letting it go does not mean not
acting upon opportunities that come to
you. does not mean not voicing very
definitely who and what you are to
anyone that you may need to do so to. It
doesn't mean doing one thing and then
retiring to a corner. That is not what
letting go means. Letting go means
letting yourself be you in an integral
way and speaking when you need to speak
and saying who you are, sharing who you
are so that others will know you are
there. That is also letting go. You
understand? Well, kind of.
I mean, well, as far as relationships,
the relationships change. Yes. And I
don't particularly want them to. All
right. Now, relationships change because
you change. They are a reflection of changes
change. They are a reflection of changes
going on within you. Not necessarily a
100% opposite reflection, but they are
still nonetheless a reflection of
changes that go on within you. You are
becoming another person. Well, the
lion's a painful.
What is the definition you have of the
relationship? What is the definition you
have of
change? Do you have a definition that
says change must be painful? Do you have
a definition that says when things
change, you are losing something? Well,
not in all cases, but in some cases it
feels like by, you know, something is
not there. Yes. So, I have to let it go
because I can't hang on to something
that's not there.
Do you believe you deserve to have
happiness? Yes. Do you believe you will
attract it in whatever form is
representative of who you are? Well, I
have been. Then why not apply that to
every scenario in your life? Why make
exceptions? Well, I've been trying to.
Yes, trying to. I'm always here. Well,
why not do it?
All right. I'll ask it this way.
How does it serve you to make these
particular situations into exceptions?
Say that again. All right. How does it
serve you to continue to hold a
definition of what is happening that
allows you to feel it in a painful way?
Well, that's what I'm trying to figure
out. All right. Well, let's figure it
out together right now. Okay. How does
it serve you that this situation is
painful? What do you get out of it? What
do you learn about yourself by creating
this situation in a painful way?
Uh, well, I learned I don't have to feel
that way. All right. Anything else? Um, just
Um, just
I'm looking for words. All right. Just
kind of telepathically. No, it's
No, it's
um it just it comes up every once
because things have been going really
smoothly and then all of a sudden like
emotions a lot of emotions come up and
and yes and it's exciting. It is
exciting. You discover more about
yourself that way but I want to know it
now. I don't want to wait anymore. You
know I it's I get impatient with trying
to learn these things that I'm trying to
teach myself. You are getting impatient
because you are not enjoying the
learning that you are doing in the
moment. You are impatient because you
are expecting that you must get through
this in order to get to something else
when what's happening right now is
what's important.
Yeah, I guess you're right. Um enjoying
what is going on now and that's how it
changes very quickly from a negative to
a positive experience. Let's put it this
way. Let's say all of a sudden you
discover something and it makes you very
fearful. All right. Mhm. Very unhappy,
very afraid, very sad. Now examine the
experience. Feel it for all it's worth.
Dive into it. Feel it fully. Don't deny
it. Denying it is what prolongs it.
Absorb it. Flow. Immerse yourself in it.
Relish it. It is an
experience. Savor
it. Find out what it is about yourself
you are discovering within this emotion,
within this energy that you have wrapped
around yourself. and penetrated yourself
with. Find out who you are in this
moment relative to all the things that
are going on around you. Find out what
the definitions are in life that you
prefer in
general. Know yourself. Discover
yourself. Accept the experience as a
learning one and you can turn it right
then and there into a pleasurable
experience rather than a painful one. It
is only painful at first to get your
attention in a sense. Not that it has to
be painful to get your attention, but
because of the way most of you think in
your society, very often you will only
listen when it is
painful because very often you refuse to
look at certain aspects of yourself. You
refuse to learn certain things about
yourself that you want to learn unless
it grabs you strongly. And very often
you simply will not allow yourself
primarily because of what you have been
taught to be grabbed by ecstasy. So you
will be grabbed by terror.
which is the polar opposite. You
understand? Yeah. Anytime you disallow
yourself to learn through ecstasy, you
will learn the same lesson through fear.
That makes sense. Well, thank you. I
didn't invent it.
Okay. Um, now again, this is not to be
taken in a derogatory or self judgmental
manner, but simply there is only one
principle that exists that is common for
all beings in creation. What you put out
is what you get back. That's it. It is
the only law there is. There are no
other laws. What you put out is what you
get back. Every reality, every dimension
is based on that. And so is every
personal experience.
If you label a situation as negative
just because of the way it looks on the
surface, you will get a negative feeling
because you are telling yourself this is
a negative experience. This should not
be happening. Here it is. It's your
life. It is happening. Find out why it's
happening and be excited to find out why
it's happening because you have
attracted it for some reason. Use it for
a positive reason by identifying it as a
positive learning experience and you
will always flow in ecstasy and the
changes will be welcome because you will
know beyond the shadow of a doubt that
whatever the changes are changing into
are going to still be represent.
Hi Bashar. How do you good day Bashar?
My girlfriend Madeline who you came and
talked to the very first time when you
ever came into my home mother has just
passed away. What? And this she asked me
since she couldn't be here tonight if
you would say something about her
mother's passing.
There is large clear still
lake. Large deep bright
pool. In this lake, in this pool are
many ripples expanding out from their various
ripples expanding out from their various
centers touching and interacting with
all of the ripples within the lake
within the
pool. At
times the ripples are caused by larger
stones, at times by smaller ones, at
times by the coming of a stone, at times
by the leaving of a
stone. But the ripples expand outward
forever and are never
gone. Always they interact with all the
other ripples in the pool, in the pond,
forever and ever.
It can be remembered that the lake and
the pool is everywhere and
everywhere and that the ripples can be
felt and the communication can
occur. If one set of ripples would but
relax into the troughs of the other set
of ripples and allow themselves to be
carried by the waves of that particular
identity to ride and to be carry to
identify to love to be nurtured and
nourished within the substance of the
waters of the lake and to
receive the
blessing of the rip. that expand outward
forever is as
easy. As easy as
floating in serenity, as floating in the
waters of your
birth, as being as a newborn
baby, and being in touch with the core
and the seed of all that ever has been,
is now, and ever shall be.
I believe she may wish to put amen at
the end of that and that is what we
shall say. Thank you. We thank you as
well. By the
way, next month of your
time on this particular note, aside from
there being the summation part two, we
will talk about the concept of being
godfeed. Sherry,
hello. I am doing your good day. Thank
you. Um I've been made aware from
several different sources that there's
some major changes and shifts occurring
for me
and I'm just wondering whether you can
um help me with that. Let us go back to
the basics. Are you doing in your life
what excites you the most or not?
I think so. You think so or you know so?
There's probably some other things I
could be doing as well.
But I don't know. Oh yes. Now come on.
Where's your
imagining? What inspires you? What do
you dream of
doing that is in your terms more
exciting and more fulfilling than what
you may be doing now?
Anything at all?
Um, yes. I would like to start a gallery
and a bookshop. A gallery and a
bookshop. You find that this would be
very exciting. Yes, I think so. All
right. When will you begin?
Finance is a problem at the moment.
Now, as a recommendation, once
again, to some degree, the book we have
already talked about may assist you.
Thank you. It contains some very good
exercises that allow you to exercise
that imagination and allow yourself to
understand. that while what you call money can be
that while what you call money can be
gotten and can assist you, it isn't
always necessarily the first thing you
need and sometimes isn't necessary at
all to get to where you think you want
to go. It will expand your ability to
draw in opportunities, to act on those
opportunities, and to create what you
want without necessarily needing as much
of the money as you may now think you
need. There are golden connections and
golden opportunities that you already
have with other individuals that you are
simply not necessarily allowing yourself
to be aware of that could be being used
by you to get you where you want to go.
To some degree, you are isolating
yourself from the contacts and the
connections which you actually have and
simply allow yourself not to be aware of
how far you could get without some of
the money you think you really need,
which you don't. Perhaps if you read the
idea in that book, it will just be
responded. Hello, Bashar. And to your good day.
Hello, Bashar. And to your good day.
Thank you. Um, I've been made aware from
several different sources that there's
some major changes and shifts occurring
for me. And I'm just wondering whether
you can um help me with that. Let us go
back to the basics. Are you doing in
your life what excites you the most or
not? I think so. You think so or you know so
I think so. You think so or you know so
there's probably some other things I
could be doing as well. But
I don't know. Oh yes. Now come on.
Where's your
imagining? What inspires you? What do
you dream of
doing that is in your terms more
exciting and more fulfilling than what
you may be doing now?
Anything at all?
Um yes. I would like to start a gallery
and a bookshop. A gallery and a
bookshop. You find that this would be
very exciting. Yes, I think so. All
right. When will you begin?
Finance is a problem at the moment.
Finance is a problem at the
moment. Now, as a recommendation, once
again, to some degree, the book we have
already talked about may assist you.
thinking. It contains some very good
exercises that allow you to exercise
that imagination and allow yourself to
understand. That's while what you call
money can be gotten and can assist you,
it isn't always necessarily the first
thing you need and sometimes isn't
necessary at all to get you where you
think you want to go. It will expand
your ability to draw in opportunities,
to act on those opportunities, and to
create what you want without necessarily
needing as much of the money as you may
now think you need. There are golden
connections and golden opportunities
that you already have with other
individuals that you are simply not
necessarily allowing yourself to be
aware of that could be being used by you
to get you where you want to go. To some
degree, you are isolating yourself from
the contacts and the connections that
you actually have and simply allow
yourself not to be aware of how far you
could get without some of the money you
think you really need, which you don't.
Perhaps if you read the idea in that
book, it will assist you to some degree.
First and foremost, we can start you off
by allowing you to understand that one
of the easiest way to create what you
want is to surround yourself, immerse
yourself in the world of what you want.
Do the things someone who owns a gallery
and a bookstore would do. Go to the
functions that such a person would go
to. Wrap yourself in that world. Take it
in. Be that person now. Be the vibration
of that person. Act like that person.
Think like that person. Live the life of
that person now to whatever capacity you
have the ability to do so. And it will
start rubbing off on you and other
people will start seeing you that way
and reacting to you as if you were
already that person and giving you the
leads that you need. You understand?
Yes. Does that help you to some degree?
Yes. Thank you. Is that sufficient for
your question? Yes. Are you sure?
Yes. Thank you. All right. Thank you
very much and pleasant dreams to you.
Thank you,
Shann. Good evening, Bashar. I know you good
Good evening, Bashar. I know you good
day. Uh, just want to tell you it's a
real pleasure to be here with you this
evening. Uh, I've been listening to your
interactions for about 5 months now. Oh,
all right. And, uh, it's really helped a
lot. It's really opened up uh, my
ability to communicate telepathically.
Oh, thank you very much. Um, I'd like to
speak with you about Ashtar's command. A
little bit. Not much. Okay. We are not
allowed to say much. It is not our
domain. Okay. Well, I have felt a very
strong connection to uh the command. Oh,
in what way? Well, I've had uh
communications uh ranging from
correspondence in uh starting in 1972 to
uh Sandanda actually manifesting or
projecting into my home back in 1981.
All right. And what do you like to do
with all of this? Okay. Well, what
happened when when Sonanda manifested
into my home, I wrote that off as a
product of an overactive imagination and
innocent? Yes. But that doesn't mean it
wasn't real. Okay. So, anyway, when I
started listening to your tapes, uh,
again, Ashtar started rolling around in
my life. Uh, now what my question is
rolling around.
[Music] All right. Well, my question is is that
All right. Well, my question is is that
uh there seems to be a discrepancy
between what uh Ashtar and the command
is here for and uh what you seem to say
that we're having the transformation
that we're going through. They seem to
be looking at a kind of a climactic end.
The discrepancy, the apparent
discrepancy stems from the
interpretations that are put upon the
messages due to the way the terminology
exists in your society. And therefore
some of the things that need to be said
can only be understood by some people in
your society in certain terminology that
they are used to hearing. Otherwise they
wouldn't be listening at all. It isn't
really so much a discrepancy as it may
be considered a poetic
license. You understand? Okay. Those
that know they do not need to experience
the transformation in negative
catastrophic ways will simply not be
drawn to that particular methodology nor
those particular areas. That's all there
is to it. But again, they recognize at
some degree that a lot of you, now I do
not mean to be impolite, will not get
off your dust unless you're a little bit
scared and won't do something about the
things that need doing upon your planet
unless you feel you have a good
incentive, which of course many of you
feel death
is. Now, the idea is yes, there are
imbalances that do exist within the
energy of your planet. All you have to
do is look around you to understand that
many of the things your technology does
and many of the things your attitudes,
emotionality, and spirituality does
creates a high degree of negative energy
upon your planet. And yes, there can be
physiological manifestations of those
things. But if you understand you're
doing that and you understand that you
are creating that and you understand you
don't have to do it that way and you
explore and discover ways where you can
make those changes in a positive light
then you completely transform the
universal reality and the transformation
in the way you will experience it and
that's all there is to it in a sense now
in a
sense to use a gaming analogy that
exists upon your planet they are playing
pitcher and we are playing catchup and
In a sense, you are the ball in
between. The idea simply is that they
will toss you one particular kind of
curve and we will catch it in a
particular way to give you both
polarity. So you have a choice. So you
have an option on how to choose to look
at the path of the ball and your place
on that path. You understand? Yes. Does
that help you? Yes, it does. Does it
answer your question sufficiently? To a
degree. To a degree. All right. To what
degree does it not? I'd like to ask you
about son. Yes. Okay. uh in a sense one
one one aspect one one aspect of what we
call the world spirit or what you can
sometimes call colloially your Christ
consciousness one
aspect is represented by the term
sanda but the world spirit it is and it
is the combination of all the collective
consciousness of your entire planet it
is its own identity as well and in a
sense sandanda that representation is
one of the archetypal fingers, one of
the archetypal fingerprints of that
world consciousness. You follow along?
Yes. You will encounter whatever
archetype is most reflective and
representative of the vibrational energy
you happen to be operating on at the
moment. Follow me? Yes. That is why to
some degree sometimes there are now again not
degree sometimes there are now again not
meaning this
derogatory religious overtones mixed up
in some of the messages that come from
what you call ashar command because it
is in a sense pulsing its messages
through the world spirit the Christ
consciousness in a certain way along a
certain frequency to
hello bashar and you good Hey, my name
is Don. I'm so glad to have won the
lottery to ask a question here. All
right. We are very happy to have won the
lottery to be in communication with you.
Congratulations. Thank you.
One moment. One moment if you please.
May I digress for one moment? You may.
Thank you very much. Are you all having
a good time?
Just checking.
Do continue.
in our life on this planet. Now, one
radical new personal growth aid that is
causing a lot of excitement for many of
us is a course in miracles. All right,
that is one tool. Yes. Supposedly
authored by Jesus of Nazareth in a
sense. Another uh another new thing
causing I don't know maybe less
excitement so far. depends on who you
talk to. Is a is a Pakistani individual
now living in London who is called
Matraa and is held by many to be the
Christ uh representing an unfoldment
even higher than Jesus of Nazareth.
Sense. Okay. Remember that the idea of
what you term in your language
colloquially the second coming is not
something that will be manifest in a
single individual but in the awakening
of that spirit of Christ consciousness
within every individual because the
Christ consciousness is simply the same
thing as the world spirit. Many single
individuals can manifest it and will
manifest it perhaps in what you may call
a more accelerated form because the
reality in which you now live will allow
its form to be more accelerated. In that
sense, quote unquote, it won't be
crucified this time. So, you may find
that that vibration you call matraa will
be one gate through which the Christ
energy, the world spirit can express
itself in a more fulfilled fashion than
it did before. But that doesn't mean
an example of your uh telling us that we
have tended over the centuries to put
the emphasis not on the teaching but on
the teacher. Yes. The idea primarily
that the Christ consciousness wished to
reflect is not so much that it wanted
followers but that each and every one of
you were Christ consciousnesses.
The idea
of following the way was not a matter of
being subservient but being equal and
reflective being that energy that was
being demonstrated. That is the way. You
follow me? Yes. Anything else? Uh a
little more comment if you will on the
authorship of a course in miracles.
Yeah. The idea again why we said sort of
is simply once again that the world's
spirit did communicate that work. But
always always always there will to some
degree be some
filtration that will be some
interpretation in the symbology of those
through which the information came so
that you can relate to it. It simply is
not in the form that you would perceive
it were you a non-physical being. Being
a physical being brings with it certain
parameters that must change any
communication from a non-physical to a
physical state in ways that allow you to
even understand the concepts. So
sometimes you will find that certain
ideas will be presented and they may
have a certain coloration. It doesn't
mean that that's literally the only way
to relate to it. It simply means that
the individuals that brought that forth
are of a particular vibration that other
individuals are of that same vibration.
They will relate to those symbols more
than they will relate to other symbols.
And therefore in that format the
information perhaps will have the widest
or broadest appeal for the particular
vibration it was intended for. You
follow me? Yes. Does that help you? Yes.
Um in other words, yes, the Christ
consciousness is responsible to some
degree for the transmission of that
information. But it is not the quote
unquote Jesus of Nazareth that you would
understand because that is simply one
facet one facet of the overall Christ
consciousness. It is not when you think
of terms of incarnation or reincarnation
or karmic identity not as directly
linear as you are used to thinking. It
is much more multiaceted than that. Does
that help? Yes, that's what I was going
to ask. Is the the uh personality
embodiment of Christ consciousness
whether it be in a Jesus of Nazareth or
let us say in a matraa or wherever we
find it. Yes. How rare is it in history?
And if it's taking place in our own
time, what's that tell us? Um for living
in this time, it tells you now that you
have arrived at the end of the cycle of
forgetfulness and you are now beginning
to remember who you are. If you want to
find the idea of the embodiment of
Christ consciousness, go home and look
in a mirror and then start acting as if
you are that embodiment and you will be
fulfilling the idea that the Christ
consciousness sought to depart and
impart to all of you. You follow me?
Yes, but I was addressing uh I don't
want to let this issue off the hook. Uh
the individual uh personality that takes
on this role in a historical context.
Yes. A Jesus, a Buddha, whatever.
Sometimes they are concentrated focuses
of the world spirit to act in an
archetypal symbological way so that they
will form function as a reflection for
the state of the world at that time. You
follow me? Yes. They are projections of
the world's spirit. Yes. And they're
nothing that we must resign to history.
They can take place in our time and our
future. It is always ongoing, always a
new always.
Does that help you? Yes. Thank you very
much. Thank you very much. Remember, it
is a living
idea. The past is only an illusion
anyway. You created with your ideas of
space and time. It is all existing right
now. Sharing.
Hello, Bashar. And to you, good day.
Good day to you, too. Um, thank you very
much. I have a question about out-of-
body experiences. Out of body
experiences. Yes. Yes. Um, I've had
several beginnings of out of body
experiences and once I'm just starting
to leave my body, I get very frightened
that I won't be safe and I won't come
back and all that. Why do you believe
you will not be safe? Why do you believe
you will not come back? I guess stories
I've heard from things I've read about
people in walk-ins and other things like
that. All right. And it scares me.
This is my major. This is my main goal
in life really is to go ahead and be
brave and not be afraid and have out of
body experiences and travel. May I ask
you a question? Yes. Thank you very
much. Do you believe to the best of your
ability that everything you choose to do
is being done for a positive reason?
Yes, I do. Then do you not understand
that if you are that vibration, nothing
that is not that vibration can even find
you, let alone touch you? That's it.
Yes, that's it. Thank you. Thank you
very much.
One of the most important things of all
has just been demonstrated by this
individual. It is that simple. It is
that simple. And that's all there is to
it. Now, I will simply say you may all
enjoy a short break. We will resume
contact in approximately 10 to 15 of
your minutes of
counting. I'll say before we continue in
our previous
manner singers the symbology of what occurred
singers the symbology of what occurred
to you at least from our point of view
is represented by the subject matter of
which you are singing. Atlantis was in a
time when there was a more natural state
in the early beginnings and not the idea
of what you call the electronic
equipment. The idea being representative
of the fact that now that you are moving
into an understanding of yourselves as
electronic beings, you still need to maintain the
beings, you still need to maintain the
balance of your natural roots, your
natural beginnings to keep your feet
anchored on the ground in a natural way.
The idea was looked at at least by us as
a type of fluctuation that belonged in
the piece to go in and out of the
electronic idea to go in and out of the
natural state while talking
about the time in your history that
began the cycle that you are now ending.
starting from the natural state and
going through the
disassociations of the negativity and
the negative cycles and coming now to
full circle your electronic state of
realization. So to us in that sense the
way it was performed slipping in and out
of those states was a type of what you
would call in your society a performance
art and it was to us a part of the piece
and not something that interrupted it
for it had meaning to us on another
level and we thank you.
We may now continue in the previous
format of sharing.
Hi Bashar. And to you. Good day. Um may
I sing a song that I wrote for you? It's
about dolphins. All right. Sing a song
of dolphins. [Music]
Dolphins beyond the crashing
wave. Dolphins under the deep blue sea.
sea.
Dolphins they wander and play.
Nothing so high enough to splash.
Wo! Beyond the mischief
of where the whale splash.
Dolphins where the fish will play.
Dolphins where the sharks will sigh.
Dolphins be on a crashing
wave. Dolphins so they love to play. Oh,
how they love to play in the
sea. Dolphins how they love to play in the
sea. In the sea.
Dolphins beyond a crashing
wave. Dolphins under the deep blue sea.
sea.
Dolphins they wonder and fly.
Thousands so hard enough to
splash beyond the
[Music] mis where the whales splash.
mis where the whales splash.
Dolphins where the fish will play.
Dolphins where the sharks will say.
Dolphins be on a crashing wave.
Dolphins beyond the crashing way. [Music] [Music]
[Applause]
We thank you very much for your
beautiful sharing and we remind each and
every one of you that's your world
and that is what it can always be. We
thank you. Thank you.
And sharing.
Hello Bashar. And do you good night?
I really don't have a question. Then
make a statement. I will make a
statement. I would like to share with
everybody. All right. And I would like
for you to expand upon my sharing. So
maybe if necessary, maybe not. Okay. Um
I would just like to for us to be able
to assist the people in who are
listening to us right now. Um I know
that most of the people here, I'm sure
that all of the people here, one of the
main reasons that they're here is
basically because they want to create
peace on the planet. All right. And it's
been my experience. I have done a lot of
healing with myself. All right. And um
to me the most important thing is to
find the peace within yourself. Of
course, it begins there. Otherwise, what
can you do for anyone else? Exactly. And
um about a year ago, I came to see you
for the first time and I was playing a
wonderful role of what I call victim.
All right. And I was doing it so well.
Oh, you're all experts.
And um now when I when I look back and I
um now when I when I look back and I
reflect, I realize it was it was the
most potent, manipulative role I could
possibly have played. All right. Even
more important than the oppressor. Yes.
And um you know, when I was confronted
with this issue, I mean, I really really
it was really rough for me. And the way
that I found myself, I mean, I I just
feel so wonderful inside now. The peace
continues to grow and the joy, I mean,
it's just incredible. It really doesn't
matter, right? What I do. Well, that
makes you feel pretty wonderful on the
outside. Yes, it does. I mean, it and it
just continues. Yes. But but the way
that I found this was by going into the
inner child, that hurt child inside of
myself and going back
back to my childhood to that hurt child
and just healing that child inside.
Always you can recreate the childhood
you would have preferred to have.
Remember time and space are your tools.
Exactly. And and by finding the hurt
child and healing the hurt child, you
became a well adult. A well adult. Who
had a happy childhood. Who had a happy
childhood. I still continue to have a
happy childhood. I mean, the the the
little child that likes to prank and
play and jokes and goof off comes out
and and it's okay, you know. Oh, really?
Are you sure? Yes, I Yes, I'm definitely
sure. Oh, thank you very much.
Do you want me to jump about and laugh
like a child? If you wish, it's up to
you. Okay. [Applause]
[Applause]
Thank you very much. You're welcome.
Well said.
So, anyway, I just just basically I just
want to share that with everybody. Thank
you. You have Okay. And that that's
really all I wanted to say and I just
thank you so much. Thank you very much
and thank you for being as you say
reflective in that way. You're welcome.
Thank you Bashelle. Bye
Hi Bashelle. Andrew you good day. Um I
would like some guidance from you as to
how I can start channeling. I've never
done it. Channeling in what way? In an
altered space. an altered state. Yes.
All right. Understand again,
fundamentally channeling is only doing
anything you love to do fully. Right.
Now, are you doing what excites you the
most? Yes.
One more time. Yes. Yes. Thank you.
Thank you. Are you doing what excites
you? Yes. All right.
Now, do you have I assume because you
asked, a specific idea of how you would
like to trans? Yes, I do. And what is
that specific idea? Well, I thought uh
seeing you using Daryl's body, uh you
have a friend who could use my body.
We're talking with integrity now.
Well, I do not get many offers like
that. [Applause]
I know what you mean, but do
understand that the idea is that
vibrations in the channel are matched to
vibrations within us and your body would
simply then represent a version of us.
We do not actually literally directly
use the body. You understand? Yes.
Now if you were to channel in the manner you
if you were to channel in the manner you
have described as you see the channel
before you now what would you do? How to
go about it? That's what I'm asking you
to guide me to. All right. But I'm
asking you a direct question first. So
let me rephrase it. Perhaps it will be
easier this way. Do you see yourself
doing it? Can you imagine yourself? Can
you picture yourself doing it? Oh yes.
Oh yes. It is easy to do so. Yes. All
right. Describe the scenario for me.
Uh, I would be peaceful. Yes. I would be
in harmony. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. But I'm
talking physically. Physically, describe
the scenario. You see yourself
channeling. There must be a physical
surrounding. What does it look like? Are
you sitting in a chair? Are you standing
on your
head? How do you look while you are
doing the channeling you say you want to
do? Describe how you would look while
you're channeling. I'm sitting in a
chair. Yes. I have my eyes closed. Yes.
And I'm talking. Yes. And are you
talking to yourself in an empty room?
Are there people present? Are you
talking into a recording machine? I'm
talking I'm talking to one person. One
person. Male. Female. Uh, there's no
sex. All right. All
right. Are you saying anything in
particular?
No, I can't hear it. All right.
How does it feel when you say whatever
you're saying that you can't hear?
Very good. Very good in what way? Uh,
very helpful. All right. But a more
physical description. More physical
description. How does your body feel
while you're doing it? Very energized.
Very energized. All
right. Do you feel accelerated? Very.
Are you becoming warm or cool or both?
Warm. Warm. All right. Do you feel a
flow of love? Oh yes. Do you trust that
whatever it is that comes through you
will be the appropriate thing no matter
what the circumstance? Yes.
Then allow yourself in a meditative
state to sit down, open the invitation
and know that beings have already begun
to work with you. But first and foremost
and always last but not least, it is
your own higher self in that sense which
shall do most of the talking. shall we
say at first helped along or activated
by guides, by friends, by other levels
of consciousness, but always first and
foremost and last but not least, it will
be your own higher self that will be in
a sense imitating what it is perceiving
from the other consciousness. Yes. So
you can simply act it out. This is our
strongest suggestion. Sit down in a room
with a friend. Put no judgment on what
you think must come out or the way you
think it must happen. Sit down and just
let yourself flow. Do not label it. Oh,
that's only me. Oh, it's this great high
being. Do not give it a name. Just do
the action itself and get used to how it
feels. Give yourself that practice. You
understand? Get used to the feeling to
accelerate your vibration and you will
automatically slip into the vibration
that will bring you what you need to
continue the channeling in that way if
that's what you really want to do. A
word of advice, not saying this is so
you may find that once you get to a
certain point, you may not be as excited
as you used to be about doing it in that
way. If it changes, let it change. Do
not think you have gone astray. You
understand? Because many times you are
drawn into a
circumstance thinking that you must
complete that circumstance when in fact
being drawn into it to get one or two
things may be all the circumstance was
required for. You do not necessarily
have to continue in the circumstance
with an assumption that just because you
went into it, it had to end in the way
you were taught to believe this kind of
circumstance had to wind up. You
understand? I do. Go with the flow, but
sit down and physically act it out. That
is the strongest suggestion we can make
for anything you want to do as best as
you can. If there's something you want
to do, sit down and physicalize it as
much as you can as if you are acting it
out on a stage. Gather all the props
around you that are representative of
what you want to do. Act it through. Get
used to being that person, to acting
like that person. And you will change
your vibration. And when you become the
vibration of that person, nothing will
stop the occurrence from happening or
the situation from manifesting. Because
when you're that vibration, you can only
get that reality. You follow me? I've
got it. Thank you very much. Thank you,
Michelle. This is like a well, all right,
This is like a well, all right,
metaphysical piano lessons.
Shilling. I have a sh and you good day.
Um, I have a question. A question. All
right. Yeah. Um, I just wanted to know,
are we the most less the most less
advanced planet in the universe? No, no,
no, no, no. You are nowhere near the
bottom. You are nowhere near the top.
You are in the middle. And so are we.
From our perspective, there is always an
infinite direction in both directions.
Always you can go farther up. Always you
can go farther down. But to answer your
question in a more direct manner as you
meant it, no you are not. In fact, your
civilization is right on the edge of
transforming into a very strong,
peaceful and creative world. In that
sense, understand this. Even though your
planet now seems to be going through
much turmoil, remember as we have said,
transformation is not the product of
mediocrity. As strong as your planet has
been in the negative side, that's an
indication of how strong it can be in
the positive side. Once it lets go of
the negative and snaps like a rubber
band into the positive side, it will go
that much farther and that much faster
because it's been pulled so far back on
the negative side. You understand?
Yeah, I think you'll think. All right.
Basically, the answer to your question
is no. You are in no way, shape, or form
the least advanced as you mean that. We
are aware of several civilizations that
make yours look like a picnic.
Thanks. Thank you very much.
Shilling.
Hello, Bashar. And to you, good day.
Thank you. Apparently, we all have a
higher self. Apparently, yes. The
chatter must be coming from somewhere.
Yes. What I'd like to know is I think
I've met my higher self, and I'd like to
know. Yes. You're not sure? I'm pretty
sure. Pretty sure. All right. I'd like
to know whether we share our higher
selves with other. You can in the sense
of what is called an oversoul
manifestation where one soul can now
again this is your colloquial
terminology split itself into many
different persona fragments that will
appear to be separate individuals that
share the same soul. And because the
label is somewhat arbitrary you can say
that those individuals to some degree
share the same higher self. The concept
of higher self and oversoul is rather
shady in terms of separating them out
into distinct ideas. They can be
separate, but those are a matter of
definition. Those are a matter of ideas
and purpose for what you want to do. But
yes, different people can share the same
higher basic overall self.
Although precise individual personas
will usually have a higher self that is
shall we say assigned by the oversoul to
that particular persona to function as a
guide or a carrier wave that allows you
to tap into that source to remain true
shall we say to the vibration that
represents your chosen purposes. Does
that help at all? Yes. I did not mean
that to be extremely wordy. No. Does
that mean that um I mean could you
interpret that because sometimes I I
think that people who consider they have
a soulmate or they're soulmates and they
they often have a sort of telepathic Oh
yes um
uh bond bond with each other could mean
that they're higher yes that is because
what you call telepathy as we have
defined it is actually telempathy which
means you are vibrating in a similar
wavelength to someone else and therefore
you are translating thought in the same
way. You're not actually reading their
mind. You're having the same thoughts at
the same time because you're on the same
frequency. Individuals that are split
off from one basic soul self will very
often have a tendency to operate on
similar frequencies and therefore
already have that telepathic bond. You
follow me? Yes. Thank you. One last
question. Oh. All right. Do we do we
um as we are in in in this lifetime say?
Yes. Do we fit that capacity of the
higher self to maybe other
um entities? Am I not making very clear?
Yes. But everyone is a teacher and the
server on many different levels. You are
to some degree the higher self of other
kinds of entities in other dimensions.
Yes, we should recognize that
responsibility. Yes. Thank you. Thank
you very much.
Sherry.
Hi Bashar. And to you, how are you? Hi.
Hi. Um, I'm involved in a relationship.
Involved in a relationship. All right.
And quite a mouthful. And, um, my
partner, I believe, is passing on. He's
very All right. And, um, I wonder if
there's anything that you could tell me
to help me and to help him. All right.
Perhaps we already understand that you
have love. Yes.
May I ask you a question?
Yes. All right. Do not want to pry. So,
do you
believe that consciousness can be
physical and non-physical? Yes. You're
sure? Yes. All right. Do you believe
that what you call physical death is
simply a change of state?
Yes. All right.
Do you believe that individuals who have
made connections can always feel and
experience communication along those
established lines even if the state
changes? But yes, I believe he'll be
able to communicate to me if he dies. Is
that what you're asking? Yes. Yes.
Do you also at the same time however
understand that the choice the
individual has made or is making in
changing that state means that they have
a timing to fulfill in their own right
in their own responsibility that they
have other things also to do a new job
to go to. You understand? Yeah. Yes. And
that from time to time they will also be
busy doing what they are doing. I do not
mean to make light of this. And I do not
mean to be flippant, but again I will
simply interject now for general
purposes that we have perceived that
many individuals in the physical plane
on your planet when they think about
individuals who have physically died
assume that they have nothing better to
do than hang around waiting for you to
talk to them or them to talk to you.
They are very busy. They still have
lives. They still have things to learn.
They are in a new job. They are in a new
state. they will form to some degree a broader
they will form to some degree a broader
perspective generally because that is
the nature of
non-physical focus. This means that time for them is
focus. This means that time for them is
also very different almost non-existent
in the sense that you understand time.
An individual in a non-physical state
can feel that perhaps one half hour as
far as they're used to perceiving such
things has passed but when they turn
their attention back to the physical
world they may find that a year or two
has passed. such as the difference
between the relative rates of time
frames in the physical and non-physical
reality. If you do not feel the
individual around all the time, do not
despair. The idea is that communication
will occur. And I'll tell you this very
strongly. If you send that individual a
loving connection every time, anytime
you think of that individual, thinking
of that individual puts you on the
wavelength to send a communication that
will be reached by that individual
because a thought of them is a
frequency. They will receive it. They
will use the energy in whatever way will
assist them in what they have to learn
and they will send energy back to assist
you. The relationship does not end. It
only changes. You can be very aware of
communication. You do not have to feel
torn apart. Your society is beginning to
learn that what you call physical and
non-physical reality does no longer have
to be a barrier or a veil between
experiences. It may be at first easier for you to
It may be at first easier for you to
have these communications in your dream
state because in your dream reality you
are on the same plane basically the same
level as what you call a non-physical
being and therefore it's easier for them
to reach you and you to reach them and
you may wake up either having what you
call a literal recall of communicating
with them or some form of symbolic
interpretation that makes the most sense
to your consciousness
also because it is not let us a always
par for the course that they should
communicate with you or you with them in
a way that you are used to. Many times
you will find it is actually easier for
them to send you a message by simply
allowing you to see something by gently
directing you in your physical life
towards something that very boldly and
blatantly reminds you of them. Very
often those types of coincidences are
actually communications just so they let
you know they're doing fine and they're
thinking of you. But it is sometimes
easier to get your attention by using
the tools you have at hand in your
physical life in order to let you know
they are thinking of you. So do not
always expect that the communication
must be literal that you must hear
voices from the clouds. You can but very
often you will find that you will have
added an extra dimension to your
relationship. For remember, it is only
because of the way you have been taught
that you think of change as a loss
instead of understanding that the change
can now incorporate not only what you
have had but more and become greater
than everything you could imagine it
could be. You can cherish it on a whole
different level. You understand? Yes.
Does this help you? Yes, it does. Um,
can I is he going to be able to make
this transition with some peace in his
heart? Yes. If you will give him that
love beginning now. See in your mind's
eye the transition being peace. See a
brilliant transparent blue white light
infusing this individual. See golden
rosy warmth entering the heart. Let the
individual know they can be at peace and
that what you call physical death is
truly truly truly not really very much
different than stepping through a
doorway from one room to another in a
big house. Okay. You understand? Mhm.
Thank you. Thank you very much. Pleasant
dreams to you. Sherry.
Hi Bashar. And to you. Good day. Oh, one
moment to the last person. Do also
understand that your guides will give
you some assistance as well if you would
only ask them and trust them. But it is
up to you as well. You follow me? They
will not live the life for you, but they
will assist you. You are not alone. You
have lots of help, lots of friends, many
different levels. You all of them. Use
that friendship. It is there. Use that
support. It is there. But at the same
time, stand on your own two feet because
you're equal to all of them. Yes. Uh, I
sort of represent some of the people
that come all the time and don't usually
get up and say anything to you. Or
spokesperson. Oh, yes. Spokesperson. Oh,
I an ambassador, a representative.
Right. And yet you've been communicating
with all of us and and we'd be out there
and we'd be sending messages up and
you'd answer all our questions. But I
had a question this time about our
planet which is going through many
changes political sense on a physical
sense. Yes. And in some areas of the
earth, it seems as though they're really
making great strides. And yet in our
country, it seems as though we're not
doing quite as well as perhaps some of
us thought we could be doing. All right.
Now, do not judge yourselves too
harshly. Okay? There are many, many,
many belief systems upon your planet.
And it will take a little bit of time in
your terminology to
intershing that they can all work and
can all move in the direction of
universal peace. Okay. Now, we've had a
few earthquakes. the last few weeks or
so everywhere from Montreal to this
area. Exciting, isn't it? Yes, it is. It
really is. Keeps you on your toes. Yes.
Because they've been fairly strong, but
yet we realize there's no damage,
nothing like you are learning as a
civilization more and more to translate
that energy in different areas into a
positive action instead of the former
catastrophic action you think you used
to need in order to wake yourselves up.
Well, is this the way that we're using
to wake ourselves up though by having
more of it? Yes. And it is
representative of the shifts and the
quakes that are going on within you as
you rearrange your belief system. But
understand just because it occurs that
way does not in any way, shape or form
mean that it must be a negative
experience. Right? You are the
transformers. You are the safety valves.
And that also means that we don't have
to do it that way if we don't want to.
Correct. Okay. That's all right. That's
all. Thank you very much for choosing a
positive release. Okay. Thank you and
share it.
We are here. Surprise, surprise,
surprise, surprise. I did not know I was
going to ask you a question. Now you do.
But I had one in my heart. All right.
I'm involved with a
uh a motion
picture that's just formulating a big
epic film on on the life of Buddha.
Buddha. My question to you is what does
your vivid imagination see that we
could do that we don't see that would be
extraordinary in this kind of a journey
one do you understand that what you call
Buddha nature is simply one more
manifestation of the world spirit also
known as Christ consciousness certainly
one moment
This film is about his particular life
at that time sixth 6th century BC. One
moment. Have you
created cohesiveness among all the
individuals working on the project in
the sense of gathering them together and
synchronizing their minds?
I like this what you said. We haven't
done that yet. They're not together yet.
We haven't selected all those work. It
is our suggestion that when you do you
perhaps not meaning in any way, shape or
form to force a belief system upon them,
make it
relatively, shall we say, non-
denominational, but gather them
together. Take some time with all of
them to sit in a room together, a very
pleasant environment together or
outside. Feel feel the strength of nature. Feel
Feel feel the strength of nature. Feel
the bond you all already have by being
drawn together on the same
project. Allow them to release their
fear into nature. Allow the fear to
transform. Any fear of
shortcoming. Know that you are all more
than capable of creating the project, of
creating the communication. Know it. No,
it is no accident that it is your desire
to do so. Know beyond a shadow of a
doubt that everything you need will
always be provided and you will find it
will be an effortless creation. One
stroke of the brush, the entire thing
will flow onto the canvas and be
appreciated with the proper impact by
the audience that will be attracted.
Synchronize the individuals by placing
everyone in that environment and let
them breathe. The breathing is key. Let
them breathe until all feels satisfied
with their part in the project. Talk it
out. Discuss it out. Let them be who
they are. Let them let you be who you
are. Know that there need be no conflict
that you are though individuals also one
entity creating the project. You
understand? Yes. That is our suggestion.
In other words, once again, have a type
of spiritual
picnic. You follow me? Spiritual
brainstorming. Yes. But not so much
storming. Yeah.
A little enlightening here and there is
all
right. The breathing is key. If nothing
else occurs, getting all the individuals
together, taking three big, deep,
beautiful breaths and letting it out
will go a long way towards, shall we
say, homogenizing your desire and your
homogenizing your desire and your
momentum because you will then be
conspiring, co-spiring together. You follow me? Yes.
co-spiring together. You follow me? Yes.
Does that help you? That's wonderful.
Thank you very much. Thank
you. at this timing allow us to
introduce something that will continue a
bit beyond the idea that this is quote
unquote our last session in this format
so that you will feel the momentum know
that you are a part of an ongoing idea
that does not end in the form of a game.
The idea is that we will hearken back to
what you have in past times called the
ten commandments which we now wish to
give another recognition one not quite
so judgmentally perceived. We have
discussed just to give you an example of
what we are talking about in the past.
The idea of the difference between the
way the information was actually
originally transmitted as opposed to the
way it was received by the individuals
on your planet. The first commandment as
you usually call it was I am the Lord
your God. Thou shalt have no false gods
before me. That is the way it translated
into the mentality of the time. However,
the transmission was simply there is
only one. Everything you may see that
may appear to be a different
manifestation is still a part of the
one. That is the original transmission.
Seeing the difference, the game we shall
play is from 1 to 10. I will give you
the first two. create new versions of
the idea. The first being there is only one.
idea. The first being there is only one.
The second principle and the only law in
creation is what you put out is what you
get back. So one and two there is only
one. What you put out is what you get
back. It is up to you to play around and
come up with what you believe are the
rest. Count with me in my own language.
Cha cha chu ch shimmy shimmy p pon p
kashimi kashimi cats row row shimon
shimon c 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10. We leave
you with this counting of
10. We