[Music]
El say how are you all this evening of
your time is you create time to
exist allow us to begin this the first
interaction of your new year of your
time of counting with the
idea called selfawareness that may be
your entitlement if you wish now I have
discussed from time to time with many of
you the idea of what you call the
patterns and the habitual rituals that
many of you find yourselves in in your
physiological reality this analogy can assist in our
reality this analogy can assist in our
understanding of the very ability for
self-awareness itself we have discussed along with the
itself we have discussed along with the
idea the notion of
habits that once you recognize you have
a habit you no longer have it that you
have to be outside of it Beyond it in a
sense in order to know you you had
it when you are in the framework you do
not know you are in the framework you do
not see the framework for what it is
when you arrive at a point in your life
when you recognize that you were in a
particular framework then it must by
definition be past tense you have to
already be Beyond it outside of it so to
speak in order to know that the
framework existed because only from that
point of view can you see the idea of
what the framework is and how it relates
to everything else you have been doing
in your
life the analogy that will have used
once again is the idea of being on a
Mountaintop and from The Mountaintop
then you understand that before you
climbed the mountain you used to live in
a valley but it is not something that
you may recognize until you reach the
Mountaintop for there your perspective
allows you truly see in a much broader
sense the terrain of the inhabitation
you experienced
before the
idea of selfawareness
the recognition of selfawareness to some
degree functions alongside parallel to
this analogy and the Very ability to be
analogy and the Very ability to be
self-aware in a sense
for lack of a better term can be called
a proof that your mind your
Consciousness must by definition be in a
sense of a nonphysical nature to begin
with let us illuminate the idea
further we recognize on your planet
there have been for quite some time
ideas belief
systems where individuals might think
that your physical reality
is all there is and that there is no
physical no physical extension beyond
your lifespan and that in there being no
lifespan and that in there being no
physical extension beyond your
lifespan then the idea that you are the
mind that you are the Consciousness that
you are ceases to exist we recognize
that this has been a belief on your
planet held by some individuals for
quite some
time the idea however
can be seen to be self-contradictory
for you can recognize that your ability
to be
self-aware self-reflective to see yourself requires
self-reflective to see yourself requires
that you have the capacity in a sense to
stand outside the Paradigm that you are
to stand outside the framework that you
are the ability for
self-reflection cannot come from within
the framework in which you
exist on the physiological
level the idea that mind is simply the
product of physiological chemical
interactions and nothing
more would be
contradictory in the sense that a
physical object if that is all there is
is a physical reality if that is the
only framework and there is no other
framework from which you can view physical reality
from which you can view physical reality
then self-awareness would not be
possible you would not be able to have
that remote self-reflective ability for
there would be nothing Beyond
it those
measurements the recognition of self is
a measurement that can only be made
outside of the thing that you are
measuring the framework you are
measuring in in
if physical
materiality was all that there
is in that sense you would simply be
programmed as you say
hardwired there would be no flexibility
no
reprogramming no ability to extend a
reflection back to
yourself for the idea of physical
reality would be self-contained
non- physicality to some
degree is simply an extension of the
physicality you are used
to it is a more rarified
version a vibrational a frequency
shift but one with
profound sensorial effects one that is
expansive in its point of view relative
to the physical reality you are used to
inhabiting shall we say now this does
not mean that it is the end all be all
this non-physical reality in terms of
having a point of view in terms of
expansiveness in terms of
knowing there are still yet many levels
shall we say many degrees and they are
quite infinite of knowingness of
infinite of knowingness of
self-reflectivity it is open-ended and
must be open-ended once again in order
to have the ability for
self-reflection that
open-endedness the ability to be
infinite is what creates the ability to
see yourself to be aware of yourself and
to recognize yourself at any place at
any stage within the whole idea of
existence if it were not infinite once
again it would be a closed framework and
in a closed framework there cannot be
self-reflection
so Infinity non-physical
reality these things in a sense are
necessary ingredients for you to be even
able to possess the capability of
self-awareness for self-awareness is the
first shall we say
separation you are you you are one idea
to be able to see
yourself implies that there is more than
the one idea you have thought yourself
to be for so long it is an extended or
how you say existential point of view a
transcendental point of view it is a
loop like a
mirror it
implies that there is another point of
view beyond that which you express
yourself to be at any given local in
space time to be able to extend your senses to
time to be able to extend your senses to
the place where you can think about
yourself where you can be
self-aware implies by definition that there is
implies by definition that there is
something
beyond the reality at any given moment
that you immediately
inhabit and always will be
forever we will be
delineating more of the ideas of aspects
of
consciousness clarify these abilities within many of
clarify these abilities within many of
you within this your new year what we
have termed year of
conviction but by whatever
name this time in your lives goes
by it is the time of explosions and
Explorations and true
allowance true redefining of the person
the personality that you
are many of the ideas that have been
termed workshops that we will be
discussing in this your new year we'll
deal directly with specific ways to redesign
directly with specific ways to redesign
the Persona that you are into what you
wish it to
be all the tools are now available the
level of awareness on your planet makes
it so that you can begin to
truly Define and
redesign the Persona that you
are and have the different lifestyle
that is representative of the new
persona the new personality the new
construct you express yourself to
be we will also be
discussing Altered States Of
Consciousness and as they apply both to
your physiological
reality and several other
realities that you are connected to but
have not in your reality had conscious
remembrance of for quite some
time but it will form links for you that
can be translated in ways that you can
apply in your physiological reality to
Aid in the assistance and acceleration
of your own self-awareness because you
will be able to use those other places
you also exist as mirrors larger mirrors
to see what you may call the bigger
picture of your physical
reality to see more clearly and cleanly
how you
fit because you do not to see whether
you fit but how you fit for if you did
not fit you would not be where you
are but can begin to use what you may
call those higher selves
those future selves those
mirrors to reflect back to you that
point of view that self-aware
reflection that will allow you to truly
see how you are intermingled with all
other individual personas in your
physiological
reality we will be
discussing ideas of your sensitivity of
awareness within your physical reality
and how to increase that
and all the ideas of keying into
vibration and energy the energy that you
are for you are made of energy and the
frequency the pitch at which you vibrate
determines everything you experience
everything and we will be discussing
that and how to apply that in your lives
in a very conscious direct methodology
that will give you immediate
feedback so that you understand you are
responsible for the creation of your
physiological realities this in having
termed it your year of
conviction is where we work together in
more parallel ways hand in hand as you
say with tools and
methodologies that will allow you an
immediate reflection of all the concepts
and ideas and belief systems we have
discussed for the previous four years of
your time
so that you will have what you call your
practical experience with these ideas
know they are tools that will feel solid
to you that you can apply in your life
and get a result from
immediately less time is necessary
now more conviction means less time is
necessary to get the results you
desire it will take you through many
roots of yourself will put you in touch
with many beliefs that you may have
and not know that you have but that will
be part of the
fun for that self-discovery will always
once again lead you to the recognition
of the greater self that functions as a
mirror to become more self-aware of the
you you are in all the expanded ways you
can these are some of the things we will
be discussing this year of your
time and all of it all of it will be for
the purpose of
expanding your
self-awareness and your activity your
conviction and increasing the
potential of allowing you to be one mind
individuals always but one mind in Step
harmoniously smoothly effortlessly
smoothly effortlessly
joyfully for these things are are your
birth rights nothing in the universe denies
rights nothing in the universe denies
happiness to you but
yourselves you all are that
powerful every single one of
you every single one is a universe unto
him or
herself or itself depending upon the
reality you come from
this year will put you more in touch
with all the ideas that you
are we thank you for your willingness to
have created the world you have
created the world you have
created to have it be such a bold
expression to be so very
exciting in return
for the sharing you have done with
us I ask you now how may I serve
you hello Bashar and to you good day and
good New Year oh happy New Year to you
too and everybody
else um I've been doing some research
into neuroimmunology and what I'm discovering
neuroimmunology and what I'm discovering
is that a lot of
um universities are also doing
experimentations with this and they're
calling it like Mind Over the immune
system yes and what I've discovered
through this research is that they have
found that there is the AIDS virus in
cats fleas fruit flies and
mosquitoes and what I want to ask you is
is that true and if it is to some degree
yes is is it can we get bit by a
mosquito and get the AIDS virus
not really not
directly there can be certain cases
where there may be
susceptibility where complications as
you say may set in from the bite the
transmittal of one disease as you say
may pave the way for the breaking down
of the immune system to receive the
other disease it will be an indirect route in
disease it will be an indirect route in
that sense however the
existence of that particular disease in
some of those animal forms can give you
if you know where to look Clues as to
how the disease works by understanding
the nervous systems of those animals why
specifically cats and not dogs or
rabbits or
rats because the idea once again now
there is many reasons but foundationally
basically generally once again remember
that the cat animal in your Society
represents the bridge between physical
and non-physical reality and that is
what you are learning to assimilate to
create the dream and the physical world
to be one because only in your
dreams will you alleviate all suffering
it pushes you in that
direction to seek in your dreams to
create the world that you desire to
manifest your dreams into physical
Reality by understanding that they are
one and the same thing your cat animal
represents this symbolically it also
represents to some degree the
Notions of the subconscious and
unconscious Realms being what you would call a being
Realms being what you would call a being
considered to be a being of the night
the darkness the idea of getting in
touch with those subconscious Realms
bringing them to light seeing the things
that are there to see that you have not
allowed yourself to see before even in
the same way you know your cat animal
sees things you do not to see into other
areas to see into what you formerly have
called dream realities that is what is
symbolized by the
cat you understand yes I do so is it
going to help our research for these
animals to it will completely depend
upon who will take the information and how
who will take the information and how
they will use it it is completely up to
you in your hands now we do perceive
that generally
speaking breakthroughs as you call them
will be made
before your century is
out and they will be arrived at from
many different points of view but each
and every one of these points of view
will involve at least as a seed at least
as a
kernel around which all the ritual is
wrapped the notion that your
Consciousness itself is responsible for
everything your scientists your medical
practitioners in a sense along with all
of you are creating
situations that force you into a corner
so you have nowhere else to look but
within everything in that sense is
closing in on you you are seeing
manifestations in nature all around you
of the idea of disease and
destruction it forces you to understand
that it began with you and can only be
changed through
you understand yes thank you it is
always up to each and every one of you
thank you well thank you can you clarify
something you said earlier is all that
is
self-conscious it it is self-conscious because it is
it it is self-conscious because it is
infinite as long as it is open-ended all
that is because it is infinite can be
self-aware if it were not infinite it
could not be but it is it seems
contradictory to say all that is and yet
say it is infinite for it seems as if
you can never know exactly what all that
is is because it never
ends but because it is open-ended that
ability allows all that is to be
self-aware does this make sense yeah in
a way all right thank you perhaps if you
wish you can let all that is worry about
that the IDE
to some degree can be expressed more
simply by recognizing that if you are
self-aware all that is must
be understand thank you
sharing hi Bashar and to you good day
and good new year thank you I wanted to
wish you and all your people a very
loving New Year well thank you um coming
up here tonight is a total choice for me
because my name was actually drawn at
the last session and I somehow developed
this idea that whether or not I came up
here was symbolic of this door that I
need to go through but have been
resistant to go through right coming
tonight was my attempt to go through
that door well thank you what did you
find on the other side well I don't know
oh all right are you still standing on
the threshold I maybe all right um the
only thing I know about that door is
that it's somehow manifests in me
through this an idea of choking I choke
a lot right and in the past couple of
weeks it's been really bizarre because I
mean I just started choking violently
while I was crossing the street the
other day and then I had a dream about a
dog whose Jaws were around my throat in
a non-belligerent
way and I don't know what's through the door
and I don't know what's through the door
but I just knew I had to go through it
and all I really want to say was to
thank you to giving me the opportunity
to step through my door well thank you
do remember the dog symbolizes service
in your Society show shows you
things that serve you serves you by
allowing you to see more of yourself
more what you need to see to grow in the
directions you have chosen to grow is
that constant companion that constant
reminder to look in directions that will
increase your awareness of
yourself now do remember and this
perhaps can alleviate some of the idea
of choking of choking up on making em
motion it is symbolic to some degree of
freedom of expression of expressing of
the fullness of the self of holding that
back or feeling like your society would
somehow prevent you from expressing
yourself fully sometimes these things these
fully sometimes these things these
physiological choking Sensations
sometimes are connected to the idea of
what you call past life scenarios or
experiences where individuals in that
sense were choked to death shall we say
suffocated in many ways for the
expression of what they believe
sometimes when you arrive at a similar
point in the present life you may replay
some of those ideas that you lived out
before that concluded with the idea of
having the life choked out of you
because of your expressive of self now
you come to the threshold of learning to
express yourself fully again so perhaps
you pass through those scenarios again
but do remember always you can never
never never attract to yourself an
opportunity that is bigger than you are
are capable of handling at any given
moment it is not possible and in that
sense it is not logical it would be
completely imbalanced if that were so
whatever vibration you are that is what
you attract and what you attract cannot
be more than the vibration you are is
capable of
handling understand yes I do does that
assist you yes thank you then know you
have the key swing the door open freely
because anything you find will only be
what you wanted to find to grow in the
way you decided to grow use it in a
positive way and you will always find
you will have the freedom of expressing
who and what you discover yourself to be
for once again every full conviction
expression of self will always lead
itself into the appropriate
circumstances where there is an audience
to listen always for every being that
expresses thems there is a stage for
that expression it cannot be otherwise
otherwise creation as you say would be
lopsided for every creation that exists
there must be a way for that creation to
create to express itself to the fullness
of its
capacity do not have to hold back
because you believe you do not
fit understand yes I do does this assist
you yes thank you very much thank you
very much and you said that very
well sharing
hello buar and good day good New Year to
you how you doing today perfect than you
all right all
right I wanted to ask you in your
Society does music play a role is that a
joke no yes it does very much so but it
is mostly a spontaneous creation that is
the role it plays it is one of the ways
we have of expressing ourselves much in
the same way you do now our
instrumentation physiologically speaking
shall we say is not as complex as yours
we do not have as many instruments Upon
Our Planet at this time as do you for it
takes very little tonality very little
vibration shall we say to set us off to
set up the atmosphere necessary for us
to go through whatever Transformations
are representative by the spontaneous
creation of that tonal
vibration so we have instruments that
are similar in certain ways to what you
might call some of your bell-like
structures some of your string like
structures some of your percussion like
structures it is more
similar to what you might call the music
of your Asiatic culture upon your
planet but many of them are pattern on
trinary Beats as you would call it and
this sets up the prime foundational
vibration our entire Society
cues off of an individual who simply
feels so moved to play will play and if
there is need of an audience they will
automatically find themselves in a
location where there is an appreciative
audience exactly the audience that needs
to hear exactly what the person who is
playing is
playing so yes there is musical
expression there is artistic expression
in many ways again similar to your own
world although different in many ways
way I myself am very as you say fond of
physiological sculpture and that is one of the
sculpture and that is one of the
Expressions I undertake as you say when
the spirit moves
me don't this answer your question yes
it does well thank you very much thank
you for creating music with us sharing
hello Bashar and good day good New Year
to you same to you I I thought you in
the audience might be interested that
they have belief system psychology at
The Learning Tree University in
Chatsworth now information is really
getting out there all right what I want
to it is as you say leaking more and
more and more into your educational
foundations the understanding that the
mind is where it all begins the
Consciousness is where it all stems from
and that's where it all ends
up okay proceed I've been reading lately
about the aura of the planet the the
energy patterns the vibrations of the
different rays and the way they go
around and how they affect the different
areas yes and how they are also
representative of how different areas
have been affected mhm well one thing
kind of surprised me is reading about
they like synchronistically kept
referring to Aries as a point of
reference which I happen to be an Aries
but it sounds like that being born in
Aries the red ray when they started
describing the red ray it just described
almost what I am in this life no right
so when I come into physicality you come
into that birthday that R kind of
like the design when you come in for
what you're going to do in physicality
is in a sense yes although it is not
absolutely structured as much as many
individuals might think there is always
some leeway for creation there must be
the idea however is to think of it
perhaps in the following manner if this
will be of assistance you are made of
energy so to speak when you physicalize
it is like
crystallizing that energy in much the
same way that you would allow ice to
crystallize out of a sea of water when
you crystallize
when you become physical obviously
whatever patterns or currents are
existent within the free floating energy
at the time of the crystalization will
in a sense be frozen within your
structure and therefore to some degree
representative of the style of energy
Arrangement the pattern of energy
Arrangement that you have created
yourself to be you will simply take the
pattern and the style of energy
arrangement of physiological
crystallized energy Arrangement that is
most reflective and represent
reprentative of the ideas that you know
you wish to play out before that
physical life so you will quote unquote
time the event of your birth to
coincide floating energy that is most
conducive to setting up patterns in your
physical life that will really take you
in the quickest possible way in the
directions you really need to explore
and so you will be born physicalized at
that time to freeze those patterns into
position so they will be the most likely
patterns that will affect your
physiological reality and not the free
floating ones you understand I
understand would there be any
significance to the fact that I was born
on Easter Sunday on a specific day well
of course there's significance to
everything what is the significance to
you well part of it I understand Easter
Sunday is a new beginning no all
right others I was pretty aberrated on
the subject of Christianity I don't know
why I would be doing the reverse
Christmas oh many times you will explore
the idea of polarities to get exactly
where you need to go but what you call
the red ray in that sense in a sense is
the beginning of what you would call the
spectrum of vibrational realities that
you know as physical realities and now
you are to some degree beginning a new
Spectrum again but this time it is not
simply one isolated Ray at a time one
isolated epic or era at a time now it is
the red ray with the blending of all the
others now it is the orange with the
blending of all the others now it is the
yellow with the blending of all the
others and so on up the scale as you say
now each and every one of you may have a
slightly shall we say biased energy to a
particular frequency a particular Ray
but you will now because this is the
transformational life be exploring all
the other ideas and how they apply to
the ray you are strongest
in most deeply embedded in because then
your learning and your teaching will
assist all others to understand how each
Ray in a sense is an extension of all
the others and each Ray is a
manifestation of the one Primal white
light of all that is so you have much
leeway now in how you explore how your
red ray vibration fits or applies into
your physiological reality now much
differently than that would have been
experience shall we say 10 of your
thousand years ago where it was a far
more isolated idea where the idea of red
Ray would be almost all that would be
experienced upon your planet in certain
areas now there is a blending and a
sharing of all the things you have
learned by being in that Ray and how you
can apply a knowledge and an exploration
and understanding of all the other
frequencies to that so there is a
blending from every level so that the
red blends with all the orange orange
blends with all and so on up the scale
and becomes more
self-reflective so that it all
accelerates together and when you have
all colors accelera together they
homogenize back into the white light of
all that
is perhaps if you
wish as an assistive tool if none of you
have done this some of you may have done
this this exists upon your world if you
take what you call a color wheed
and you delineate the seven of your
colors in your spectrum
along the edge of that wheel in
pie-shaped sections and then you spin
the wheel very fast they will look like
a white wheel when all colors are
Blended at a particular
frequency this can Aid you perhaps as a
meditational tool to understand how a
preponderance of any one Ray can blend
and assist all the others understand yes
does this assist you yes it does thank
you thank you very much for recognizing
your own Beginnings your own cycles and
the willingness to put them into action
in a particular way to be of assistance
to all other rays and Cycles on your
planet at this time whatever
significance you discover understand you
are creating that with your
Consciousness and whatever significance
you do discover is representative of who
you are so apply it that way there is no
right and wrong way to understand the
significance of such person Al important
things whatever is most personally
important to you in that way whatever
the meaning really is whatever meaning
you give it will determine the type of
reality that stems from it that grows
from it that you experience from the
giving of that meaning you understand
yes thank you well thank you very much
and do understand
also that symbolically in that sense of
course generally for all of you it
represents that Easter time the whole
idea of a resurrection from old ideas to new
of a resurrection from old ideas to new
ideas and then very shortly thereafter
of an Ascension a Transcendence into
another level of reality altogether an
acceleration of your vibratory energy
and that is in a sense truly a new
beginning we thank you thank you
sharing hello bishop and to you good day
and happy New Year and happy New Year to
you um right now I'm in a Crossroads uh
oh very exciting yes it is um as far as
my career goes but also I think the
direction of my whole life right now oh
whole life all yes
and um I know where I want to go but I'm
not really sure how to get there now
have you heard about the idea before of doing
you heard about the idea before of doing
what excites you yes have you applied
that idea at every given moment in your
life probably not every no but I'm
trying to more and more all right I'll
let you say trying for now
now
remember that you do not necessarily
need a particular idea that functions as
a
career that you will do for the rest of
your life to be able to do at any given
moment what excites you the most at that
moment with
Integrity again it may be simply an
issue of learning to place your trust in
a positive frame of reference as opposed
to placing trust in a negative frame of
reference do remember do remember and we
do not mean that this indicates it must
take a long time but do remember that
your Society has shall we say
impregnated all of you with so many
beliefs so many different definitions
that it may simply take a little while
before you play all of them out bring
them all back up to the surface to
determine and decide for yourself which
of those definitions really represents
the life you really prefer and therefore
which of those definitions you want to
keep and which of those definitions you
want to change it may simply take a
little while to do that because you have
so many
definitions have things in your
estimation using your language been
generally improving oh yes all right
does that allow you to feel happy very
much so does feeling happy allow things
in your life to generally improve faster
yes all right so the happier you are the
faster they will improve according to
your preference yes mhm so be as happy
as you
can that is one of the things each and
every one of you can do and it isn't a
matter it isn't a matter of the idea
saying oh well yes all well and good to
have a nice attitude but that doesn't
really affect the nature of things in my
life oh yes it does attitude is
everything it is the main lever the main
dial the main pointer that takes you
down the hallway of
events because there are many probable
hallways of styles of events of how
things in your life might manifest when
your pointer is always happy then you
always go down the hallways that
represent the happiest and most
synchronous events so the idea of what can you do is
events so the idea of what can you do is
first to be in that place in the present
to be in that energy state in the
present where you are happy with who and
what you are to begin with full self
validation full self
validation no doubt no regret
no guilt in the negative sense full
Integrity full trust in a positive
notion the positive direction you know
you are the positive idea you know you
are and also remembering that you don't
need me to remind you of these things
that the interaction we are having now
you are perceiving not because of me but
because of you because you are creating
this interaction in your reality so
anytime you feel you need a pep talk
understand you have the capability of
allowing any portion of yourself to give
it to
you you do not have to rely on a
seemingly exteriorized
reflection because all you're hearing
right now are your own words anyway not
really directly mine my vibrational
intention is aligned in that sense with
what you really desire to hear but
remember your capability of hearing what
I am saying comes from the fact that you
are actually telling yourself these
things because that's what is the
reality you prefer so if you understand
that you are capable of hearing these
ideas because that's the reality you
prefer then you are capable of
manifesting that reality because it's
self-contained to begin with understand
yes does this help you yes it does well
thank you very much thank
you
sharing and to you happy day good New
Year thank you I had a telephone call
recently from um a girl I met briefly
about 12 14 13 years ago all right and
uh she went to a great deal of trouble
to get my
number and
um to uh to
locate and telephone yes and I am not
sure what
the um purpose is so and um I felt she
it was acquired for help all right and
so so can you be of
assistance that's what I'm I'm wondering
wondering yes I thought uh I I don't
quite understand what it is she wants
well have you discussed it yes uh
nothing comes out that you can term a
specific idea things came out that I
would have thought would have been a a
great problem to her she's been um not
out of the house for five years and um
she expresses a great deal of fear all
right perhaps some of the greatest
assistance you can perhaps give to this
individual is a lack of
ambiguity be firm about the things that
represent to you your point of view
about the lifestyle you prefer what
makes you happy the things that you
prefer to do simply act as a mirror as a
reflection for ideas is that the other
individual could incorporate into her
life if she chooses to doesn't mean she
has to but if someone reaches out to you
then they are reaching out to who you
are so be fully who you are it doesn't
even mean that you have to quote
unquote specifically help them in any
particular way there does not have to be
a particular methodology that you should
be good at just because they found you
being yourself is the methodology that
is required to help them best so when
someone is looking for an answer from
you the only real answer you can give
them is simply who you
are you can suggest well if what you say
is happening to you what happening to me
this is what I think it would represent
this is what I would choose to do about
it this is how I would choose to
transform it but that's
me now you are you you can tell this
person and if I have been of some
assistance in Illuminating Who You Are
by telling you who I am and what I would
do then I am very happy to have been of
help but I can only be of help by being
who I am I cannot be you so I will
assume that whether it appears apparent
on the surface yet or
not who I am because you found found me
and we found each other somehow does
make a difference in who you will now
consider yourself to be from this moment
forward and that will have given you
whatever it is you need it even if I
don't know what it is you need
it I see understand you don't have to
have conscious analytical awareness of
exactly what a person needs in order to
help them in the way they need to be
helped just by being who you are in
interaction with them will be what they
need just let it flow however it flows
yes as long as you know you are being
loving using your
integrity and simply suggesting to them
options and points of view not saying
you ought to do this and you better do
that but simply that this is who you are
this is what you would do this is what
would allow you to feel complete within
yourself integral within yourself if you
were in their as you say shoes and then
allow them to extract from
what you have shared with them what they
need out of for you cannot tell them
what they need only they can tell
themselves what they need out of what
they got from you I see she might not
even know herself why she she may not
know herself at this point I I couldn't
seem to extract or find out exactly what
it was you do not necessarily need to
just be the fullest you you can be and
that individual will get what they need
out of having contacted you thank you
very much thank you very much for being
so
helpful
sharing good evening B and good day and
good New Year to you same to you and
yours and everyone here uh I'm here
visiting California with a very dear
friend and my husband and I are here uh
and also thinking of
relocating right to physical conditions
that he has however I'm very nervous
about it because I hear about all the
earthquakes in
California shaky situation very and it
concerns me a great deal because he
likes it here and I love it may I ask
you a personal question yes well thank
you very
much when you feel within yourself the
idea that you really really fit that you
really belong that you really like it
where you are that you're really drawn
and really attracted to a particular
location don't you assume that there's
probably a good reason for that oh yes
then why not simply trust that whatever
that reason is fits into the
understanding of your positive growth
potential rather than the idea of
forming an interruption or destructive
idea in your life that makes sense it's
again a matter of where you place your
trust but what about all the predictions
that between February and April yes
California's going to go in this spe
going to go into the ocean will you
answer another question for
me yes how many of those predictions
have there
been many and how many have happened
none thank you now this does not mean
that An Occurrence cannot come to pass
but recognize once again the idea the
issue of
vibration first of all we do not
perceive that what you call your
California area is going to wind up in
the ocean there may be some release of
energy in what you might call Tremor
fashion but it does not even have to be
as large as many of you think it can be
released in many ways remember that your
energy your Consciousness is reflected
in the physical reality in which you
exist and if individuals need to be
shaken awake they will be but if they
wake up first they don't have to be
the idea is that the energy can be
translated or transformed in other ways
but also even if an area does have the
collective energy that says it is going
to experience that type of physiological
manifestation if you are not of that
vibration then you will not experience
it in a negative way because it simply
doesn't fit in your life in a negative
way so if you are attracted and are
drawn to a particular area and and you
hear all these things that seem to be
negative ideas about the area
assume that it is an opportunity for you
to weigh and balance the definitions you
have within yourself and decide which
you are going to trust more the voice
within yourself or the voices outside
you which is more truly representative
of the reality you will personally
experience regardless of what anyone
else around you experiences for remember
anyone who is not of a vibration of a
who is not of a vibration of a
particular idea cannot experience that
reality even if they are standing in the
midst of it it may happen all around
them but nothing will touch them in a
negative way if it is going to happen in a
way if it is going to happen in a
negative way for an area and an
individual does not belong there then
circumstances in your life will
automatically effortlessly arrange
themselves to take you out of the area
whether you plan to be out or not
so once again you don't have to worry
about it in fact paradoxically it is the
worry and the fear and the concern that
would be more likely to attract you into
the negative manifestation because
that's the negative vibration fear and
worry and that adheres you to negative
manifestations of Consciousness if you
simply take all this information as you
say with a grain of salt and you simply
say well all right obviously I'm being
given an opportunity to examine to
explore something
here what do I really believe when it
comes down to assessing all the
information as you say all the data that
I am getting what do I really believe
well there must be a reason for the
attraction I trust I know I am moving in
positive directions that are always
expanding in exactly the way I need to
expand and that I would not have an
attraction to a particular area if it
did not serve me in a positive way
you can trust that you can go off of
that and then everything else will
arrange itself all the details will fall
into place automatically and if you
simply know you do not need to
experience the negative side of such a
manifestation it won't be there even if
you experience it quote unquote you will
experience it from the level from the
frequency from the point of view that is
of who you are and therefore it will not
be a negative experience for
you understand yes does this assist you
it does very much well thank you very
much thank you
sharing Bashar hello happy New Year good
day good New Year to you about um about
a year ago I came to you and asked you
if there was anything you could suggest
to uh help me um cover the hills with
wild flowers because last year there
were hardly any and the year before they
were so beautiful that I missed them all
right and what did you do well I did
what you suggested I went up on the hill
and uh did some meditation and saw the
wild flowers in my mind and it seems
like we've had one of the most ideal
years that I've ever seen for making
wild flowers lots of thank you for
creating that thank you for giving me
the suggestion so um that's a bright spot in
suggestion so um that's a bright spot in
my life and uh a little dark spot in my
life is bright spot dark
spot is all the rest sort of
gray no no it's
pry um is anger and yes there's there's
been quite a bit of anger sort of uh
popping off in my life lately all right
how does it serve
you well can you use it in a positive
way you do remember what the positive
definition of anger is yes at this
particular point in time I'm not I don't
remember now it is alignment alignment
with what you know to be true as
compared to something you're seeing in
another reality just alignment uhhuh comparative
reality just alignment uhhuh comparative
alignment understand it is a rush of
knowingness I am not that I am this and
what about anger from the other side
that is judgment and invalidation that's
when you start
projecting around you to other
individuals what you think they ought to
be rather than allowing yourself to
understand that you are the creator of
your reality and whatever it is you
really desire to experience will be all
that you experience when you are
centered within yourself then you will
also understand that no matter what
anyone else around you does it cannot
touch you in a negative way if you don't
buy into it the idea of negative anger
is the belief that someone else can
affect your life against your will and
it can't happen that
way that's what I'm experiencing that I
I I sense myself just it's just uh evens
out as it and the more it seems like the
more it's projected at me the more it
just sort of evens out it's really so
you ought to learning and you are
assimilating what you need to in that
sense you are learning to blend the
definitions and balance them in a
positive way that's correct now the sooner you
way that's correct now the sooner you
allow yourself to understand that it
basically comes from you in terms of
your ability to
experience the energy that way in a
seemingly negative way then the sooner
you can allow yourself to create only a
positive experience of any interaction
which generates that
energy remember no situation has
built-in meaning all situations are
fundamentally empty of meaning blank
neutral they are
props you give them meaning the meaning
you give them determines the effect you
get out of it so if you give a situation
a negative meaning you will embroil
yourself within the negative energy
energy of that event and become as that
energy if you give it a positive meaning
you will be intertwined with the energy
of that event and get that meaning and
that effect out of it a positive one so
the positive energy that I'm looking for
when I get into the obsessive thinking
about the anger is the alignment is that
yes any sense but first perhaps it would
be of assistance to Simply start in what
you call the neutral fashion it may be
assistant to Simply look at a situation
as simply a situation and that's it
uhhuh just a situation that's all it is
it doesn't mean
anything it's just a situation this
person is there this person is there now
they may have their own meanings and you
may sense those meanings you may pick up
on those meanings and think they're your
own oh understand I do have a tendency
to do that just look at it as a neutral
situation first this does not mean you
have to be become cold and detached in
that sense but the idea is that you can
sense but the idea is that you can
simply regard the circumstance as
neutral to begin with as if the curtain
has gone up on act one of a
play you see the characters standing on
the stage but you don't know who they
are yet you don't know what they're all
about yet they haven't said anything
yet every event can be seen
from just such a point of view as if it
is the beginning of something no matter
what you think they are saying no matter
how far along they seem to be look at it
as if it is the moment of the curtain
going up everything is neutral you don't
really know why that person is saying
what they're saying you don't really
know why that person is reacting the way
they're reacting you don't really know
the story yet now you may have a
built-in sense of whether one individual
is using integrity and another is not
you may be able to pick that up as you
say Tel empathically MH but just because
you pick that up you do not have to
allow that to
color your assessment of what it is they
are learning understand what it is they are
learning understand what it is they are
learning yes and what it is you are
learning you don't have to invalidate
the idea you do not necessarily have to
label everything so strongly right away
mhm allow yourself to truly perceive all
sides of what is going on see it in that
neutral light well all right this person
said this this person reacted that way
now on the surface that seems to be a
very negative thing but what if the
person was coming from this point of
view then would what they have said be
so negative maybe maybe not MH allow
yourself the opportunity to recognize
that even though you may empathically
feel what is going on that does not
necessarily mean you have to structure I
it or
rigidized because it can change even if
what you perceive is accurate it can
change labeling it so
strongly keeps it from changing you
freeze frame it as you say by applying
labels to everything yes I know I sense
that and I I get when I when I get into
the obsessive thinking I'm back off so
allow yourself to not be so
prone shall we say to labeling that this
person by doing this means exactly that
right that this person by reacting this
way means they are exactly this let it
become a little more diffused for a
moment uhhuh start playing with
different definitions a situation could
be sometimes even some of the most
interesting shall we say and exciting
recognitions can come from
absolutely taking what you have labeled
them with and reversing those labels and
see if it still makes sense because
sometimes it
will okay I'll do that yes I will play
around with it and simply remember no
situation has built in meaning the
meaning you give it determines the
effect you get out of it in your
participation okay thank you thank you
bishar
shining hello bisher and good day and
good New Year to you good new Good Year
to you thank you
well uh
uh
Ace I'm trying to not trying you don't
like that doesn't matter what I
like and it isn't that I do not like it
I simply usually remind individuals that
trying is not the doing of the thing
they want to do it is the doing of
trying yes but because I do that does
not mean that you have to watch every
word I do not mean to make you hesitate
to speak freely whatever you have to say
will come out just fine simply say it
thank you
um it has to do with me moving to Sedona
I guess is one of my biggest questions
I've been told I should or it would be
nice for me to go to Sedona so I all
right I went to Sedona a few days ago
and um I feel very good there oh all right
um I feel very good there oh all right
and and I had an unusual experience uh
in a church yeah it's all I don't
usually like churches and things like
that so I was in this church and I
started crying oh all right what a
beautiful prayer yeah was it a prayer I
didn't it was a centering and an
alignment with the idea of the energy of
the area with all that is it was a
release of much old information
oh that that's that's interesting
because I was trying I thought um
intellectually all that old information
was gone but I guess experientially it
wasn't now also understand to some
degree it was also a recognitional
release the idea of as you more more
often than notd in your Society of
coming home understand yes it was a release in
home understand yes it was a release in
that sense too we don't mean to imply
that you necessarily had shall we say
tons and tons and tons of things to Ste
process yes but simply that you did the
balancing and the releasing through the
idea of the
tears and that simply implies that your
balancing was done from a point of
view that looks back to the past in the
sense of measuring how far you have come
so since the focus is simply backwards
in that sense to some degree then it is
simply the idea of old information old
issues and now can be seen also to be
right in the middle right on the
threshold of looking forward as you say
to the recognition of the energies that
you now know exist that you always knew
existed but now you have given yourself
the opportunity to really begin to feel
experientially in your life so it was in
that sense a
celebration it was a releasing it was a
recognition it was a homecoming and it
was also a statement of conviction to
truly get on with some of the things now
that you can get on with that you have
been waiting to
do yes uh that that's what it was for
me I didn't realize it until you
Amplified it well to have a good time
did you have a good time yes yes I did
and uh I was feeling so very happy the
next morning and I thought I don't even
mind going home oh all right very good
the neutrality of things yes and also
recognizing that in a sense everywhere
is home yes yes so um then I I really
realized didn't have to consider whether
I should move there or not move there
because there's some problems with me
moving there allow whatever represents
the path of least resistance to make
itself obvious in terms of how it is you
manifest what you need the least
resistance what's easiest for me to do
as long as it is in line with your
integrity yes
mm recognize that whatever you really
need to do that is really representative
of your excitement and your Integrity
will come to you as an obvious
opportunity and if it doesn't come in an
obvious way then in that sense you can
take that as a sign that it doesn't
necessarily represent the path of least
resistance understand so in other words
to use your own analogy if it seems as
if your visit there has accomplished
what needed to be accomplished and that
the idea of actually moving there
contains obstacles that you do not
necessarily prefer in your life or need
in your life then the idea may have
already been accomplished you may have
already moved there for a sufficient
amount of
time remember that a lot of you simply
make the assumption that when you're
told to go to a certain place to move
there to live there you think that that
has to be for a certain duration in
order to accomplish the Fulfillment of
that phrase you can do it in a
second Oh I thought of about that oh all
right and uh I guess it is true uh and I
thank you thank you for being there and
for me I thank myself for creating you
and I guess I really don't have to ask
people questions not really I guess you
can discuss many things or you can ask
questions you can always allow your
curiosity to be expanded in that sense
and you can always accept the advice of
others that you cherish in that way but
simply remember that as you say on your
planet the bottom line is that it always
comes down to you whatever you decide to
accept that's the reality you
experience thank you oh thank you very
much sharing happy New Year Bashar and
good day happy New Year and good new
season to you thank you um I wanted I
want want to explore a little bit more
what you talked about at on Christmas
Eve oh all right what you said was a
loose translation something called the
Christmas story about when Christmas
bells when the when the world Spirit of
esia is aani yes incarnated for 3 days
and you slept for three days as a world
Planet well not me I was not there in
this incarnational sense okay but the
but as as aani did yes and everyone um
in a sense it wasn't exactly it was like
a resurrection too because when everyone
awoke they lived a dream forever yes
they were aware of each other right they
knew each other telepathically in
unconditional love and we have never
slept since and so everyone who has
reincarnated into that world yes shares
in that oh absolutely because that's the
vibration of that world now okay so I
was kind of wondering about when that's
when that kind of thing can happen for
us that's up to you isn't isn't it now
we do perceive that the way your energy
is going is that within what you call
the next 30 of your years you will have
already laid all the foundations
necessary for just such a reality and
that by the time comes along that you
call 50 of your years you will be fully
living that idea oh good because when I
was listening to it I thought oh that's
going to take us eons and eons and you
know and I thought I have to ask and but
you are accelerating and remember what
acceleration means
as of shall we say perhaps a thousand of
your years ago it may have taken eons
but as of now it doesn't need to okay
that's great thank you well thank you
it's your pleas what what could we do to
accelerate a little more even by doing
the thing it excites you the most to do
right now okay great thank you remember
when you talk about making things happen
faster the way things happen faster is
if you give them less time to happen in
so when you live in the present you
don't create as much time and therefore
there isn't as much time for everything
to happen in so it has to happen more
quickly great thank you thank you very
much remember that this is more than
just philosophy this is actually physics
living in the moment means you do not
create the same amount of experiential
time that you do when you live in a
segregated focused manner of the idea of
of worrying about the future regretting
the past you extend your timeline out
when you bring into play all the
different detailed segregational focuses
that you are used to looking at your
reality in when you live in the present
when now is the only experiential time
there is then you don't create as much
time so everything happens
faster shenny hi I'm sunny all right I'm
astrologer and
I was very happy to hear you talk to the
other man about sign Aries and you know
that's the crystallization of energy
beginnings and red and fire fire energy
now I would like to know why so many
people have closed minds to astrology
and only few have open oh all right do
understand of course that in a sense
this is quite obvious if you simply take
time to examine the history of your
Society the focus of your Society
has because it has forgotten its
connection to all that is focused only
on the physically material issues of
life this is one of the things we were
addressing with our opening remarks
about self-awareness that most people do
not understand that self-awareness
cannot exist if all you are is simply a
physically focused or created
being when a society such as yours
creates such a strong focus on
physicality then it assumes that everything must
then it assumes that everything must
must exist only within that physicality
and that anything that is not as you say
solid tangible that can be directly
tasted smelt touched felt heard seen
with your physical senses therefore does
not exist this attitude therefore is
exist this attitude therefore is
obviously responsible for the denial of
the existence of anything that is not
immediately apparent to the physical
senses understand yes so now that your
Society is beginning to realize that it
is more than just a physical expression
now you are becoming more sensitized as
a whole society to the fact that
Consciousness itself creates reality and
that what you call the physiological
Universe the Stars the planets the space
the time that all of these things are
actually the product of your
Consciousness and that what you see in
the exteriorized reality is actually a
reflection simply of your own
Consciousness back to you a reflection
of your selfawareness of the style of
your self-awareness in this particular
physiological format other
beings other
consciousnesses in other
universes Express the reflection back to
themselves in different ways so they
experience different universes through
their fa version of physical senses but
the one you experience has a degree of
commonality to many beings because we
share in a consensus reality a
telepathically reinforced agreement that
we shall all experience the basic
universe as a particular format at least
this particular Universal reality but
now that you are Awakening up to the
fact that physical reality is actually
created through your imagination you are
becoming more sensitized as a society to
the idea that non- physicality is just
as valid that energy itself is just as
solid as physical
matter takes a little while for people
that have been trained to only look at
the physical to break away from that and
include the nonphysical energy as well
because a high degree of focus on the
physical reality creates an ego
structure that if it is removed from the
physical reality panics because it
thinks the physical reality is the only
place that exists and if all of a sudden
you start forcing the ego structure that
has been physically focused to look at
non-physical reality it thinks it's
dying because it doesn't understand that
non-physical reality is just as real as
physical reality that is the reluctance
that you are experiencing in your
Society understand yes does that assist
you yes it does well thank you very much
thank you very much too thank
you shedding hi bash oh good hi to you good
shedding hi bash oh good hi to you good
new year happy and exciting New Year to
you too yes yes yes yes um okay
something came up for me yes which was
an old thought pattern oh wow right and
um what's been happening I One Moment
One Moment yeah but since you are now a
new you it isn't
really the
same not really the
identical old thought pattern because
now you are a new you looking at it from
a perspective you have never looked at
it from
before understand yes I understand so
recognize that there really is even if
it may seem subtle there really is a
difference between the thought pattern
you are looking at now and the thought
pattern as it actually existed back then
mhm but do continue okay um about three
and a half years ago yes um I had a
really Vivid dream and um what happened
was the spaceship came down and um
picked me up and they took me they
pulled me away from my friends who I was
with yes pulled me into the spaceship
and they pinned me up to um all these
like computer like machines that I had
never seen before and they pinned
electrodes over my whole body and they
apologized to me as they were doing it
and um they started giving me electric
shark treatment yes and as they were
doing this they said to me we apologize
for doing this but you're not moving as
fast as you have agreed to move yes so
we have to do this to speed up your
growth and movement okay so um the next
morning my two of my roommates told me
that they had had a dream that a
spaceship had come and picked me up yes
and and um then a week and a half later
yes um I was shooting a film and um did
it
die no but my physical body nearly did
all right um I I was skydiving and um I
wasn't a St person and I landed in rocks
and I I I almost died I was like well I
bet that accelerated you
yeah so what happened um like everything
in both of my legs yes was especially
the right side both I was had two casts
on and my right foot was hanging off and
this leg was shattered oh all right and
um that's breaking up those old belief
systems yeah those old foundations yes
it I mean you didn't have to do it that
way I know but you are very
bold and
yeah I know I see then in the hospital
yes I had another dream that space
people came down and like lifted me up I
was in a lot of pain and the even the
morphine didn't take the pain away and
so they lifted me up and I felt this
like white healing light yes through
this glass cabinet like just surrounding
me and I was terrified cuz the doctors
were telling me that I was going to be
crippled and I'm a dancer and and they
told me that I might never walk again I
see and stuff like this and um
then I I was in a depression and I
wouldn't talk to anyone I wouldn't talk
to the doctors and then yes you were
re-evaluating who and what you really
were I made up my mind that I I wasn't
going to listen to the doctors and I
would change everything all right and
that and and it continued for a long long
and and it continued for a long long
time and I just um kept on going you
know I I got out the cast and I just I
got through the whole thing conviction
and before I could even walk properly I
went into dance class yes and I started
dancing even when I couldn't walk and um
through the dancing I was able to heal
myself and the doctors would still tell
me
that I was going to be crippled and that
I was crippled and that I couldn't dance
well they had made a big investment in
that reality you
know but one of the things that's coming
up now is because I'm involved in I'm
still involved in litigation three and a
half years later and the pain is still
there and right it's like the pain
actually has got worse but I mean I run
and I I don't I can't run like a runner
like all right all right but it's like
it's coming up for me again yes yes yes
yes yes stop
uh-huh now it is not coming up again it is
now it is not coming up again it is
completely newly created mhm in a sense
because you are placing yourself in
circumstances which by definition
involve conflict you you know who you are and
conflict you you know who you are and
who you desire to be
mhm they believe they know who they are
and who they desire to be all the
circumstances that you have experienced
you have created to get you to the
understandings you have now to the
recognitions you have now to the clarity
of the issues and the definitions within
you that you are now beginning to
discover a suggest sugestion mhm just on
a lifestyle level
uhhuh would
be to ask you first of all can you let
the past circumstance
go can you let the circumstance that
brought you to where you are be a part
of the life that was necessary that you
at that time obviously believed was
necessary to get you to where you are
now can you in that sense not
blame those circumstances on anyone I
don't blame anybody for anything I may I
ask you why you are in your terms in
litigation because um
yes because yes I guess because I yeah
because yes I was in a lot of physical
pain and that's how this work World
works and whose
and whose
World whose
world what kind of a world do you prefer
it to
be I understand before you go
on let me explain I understand this may
seem hard for you the money could never
fix the physical pain well
then do you need it
oh I see you're helping me to let go yes
I see you see many
times holding on to the circumstances
that brought you to where you
are now there can be differences it
doesn't have to happen this way across
the board as you say not all situations
are going to be the same but what we are
perceiving now within you is that
holding on to those circumstances is
what creates you to remember
the place you're at because in a sense
you have a vested interest in
maintaining the pain because if you
don't maintain the pain who can you
blame in the
litigation well your honor I'm just
fine well then what's this all
about understand yeah I understand
however I I did this because this was a
this there was a workman's compensation
part to this it does not matter what
kind of definitions you put on these
ideas is again the idea can be shown and we do
is again the idea can be shown and we do
not mean to refute that some of the
Avenues your world has set up do not
work for some individuals but for what
you are going for for what you are
shooting forh the idea of
forh the idea of
compensation is not the full expression
of who you want to be you are in that
sense compensating you are wanting to be
compensated externally rather than
externally rather than
internally the idea is to understand if
you no longer need to hold on to the
idea of pain to convince someone that
you should be
compensated then the pain will serve no
purpose for and it will go
away it will transform more into the
energy of your acceleration forward it
will move you forward faster and give
you the ability to move forward faster
which will translate in more Mobility
physically more physical
expression but if you need to hold on to
the pain because that is your best
defense then that will stay there for
you so our suggestion we cannot tell you
what to do but in terms of describing
what we perceive to be the mechanics of
your circumstance our suggestion would be to
circumstance our suggestion would be to
let go of the
litigation because you have a vested
interest in
maintaining disability in order to be compensated by
disability in order to be compensated by
someone else once you understand that
the full expression of yourself will
supply you with whatever abundance you
need then you can move forward you will
be supplied with whatever abundance you
need and you will not have to hang on to
the issue of being compensated by
someone else for circumstances that you
attracted in your life to get you where
you are now to realize the very thing we
are talking about
mhm I I I just want to share go ahead
and then we will talk about something
else okay I want to share with everyone
that there there has been there was
almost immediately an internal
compensation um the feeling of the
clarity and the light that has come from
this oh yes walking through what you
call the door of death the door of
transformation is a very accelerating
and clarifying process and one that
really allows you to live in the moment
because if you won't live in the moment
any other way sometimes you will force
yourself into circumstances like that
because then you absolutely guarantee
beyond the shadow of a doubt that you'll
be living in the
moment yeah and that's why that is why
the entire perception and the entire
phrase of your life life flashing before
your eyes came up because you are so at
that moment fully living in the present
that your entire life is actually
existent in that one
moment because there is no other time
for your life to exist in but right here
right now that's why that phenomena
happens you become absolutely
holographic at that moment so of course
you're going to be left with a residual
Clarity when you reconnect into to the
time frame you will not reconnect in the
same manner unless you choose to hold on
to some of the old patterns as you are
suggesting you are doing now what well
the main purpose for this conversation
is that what I'm coming up against right
now against more
against more
conflict yes all right um it seems like
I have a lot of I've always had a lot of
trouble being grounded and being earthed
I I tend to prefer to be in the
spiritual Realms oh I understand exactly
what you are saying um my my boyfriend
is very grounded and he has been a
teacher and he back to me sometimes why
I'm not getting to do what I then you
are serving each other in that way and
he mentioned the weekend that I'm
missing some of the stepping stones of
the of the earth you're not really
missing the stepping stones but you are
not allowing yourself to see what is
there you have them but you don't see
them the first and most obvious one is
that obviously you chose to be born on
earthh therefore since you now know that
that was an actual conscious choice you
can also see that your preference to the
idea of spirituality is to some degree
balanced by your preference to be born
physically on Earth so that in that
sense you did did choose to be grounded
in that
way and see the idea of spirituality
through those eyes through that
perspective so you can start to look at
it from that direction to begin with mhm
you don't have to think of yourself as
groundless was that the reason why I
landed in the rocks to some degree to
some degree the idea
degree the idea
also can be
to recognize and remember that you are
still making perhaps because of a belief
system that you were taught you're still
making a differentiation between
physical and spiritual reality as if
they really are two completely different
things that have nothing to do with each
other physical reality is just as
spiritual as any level of reality
because it is made of spirit remember
that your spirit does not actually in
habit mechanically speaking your
physical body your physical body is your
spirit in physical
terminology so being physical doesn't
mean you're not
spiritual all right I I understand I've
been all right then allow yourself to
begin with to soften the definition that
there is a major difference between
being physical and exploring
spirituality because there really isn't
as much of a difference as you think or
have been taught to think therefore you
may find that when you remove that
definitional difference more things in
physiological nature will seem more
spiritual to you and will entice you in
a spiritual way to become involved with
nature more closely and that will
automatically balance and ground
you because you will start to see
physical reality as just as spiritual as
anything and paradoxically when you
accelerate through your point of view
physical reality to be more spiritual
then you exist in a reality that is
vibrationally closer to the type of
levels of spirituality you say you
actually prefer and it makes it easier
to experience both types because the
whole idea is to meet it halfway not to
leave where you obviously chose to be
and vacate the premises because you
chose to be where you are for a reason
and one of the main reasons that all of
you have chosen especially now in this
transformation life is to accelerate and
uplift the vibration of physical reality
so that you understand physical reality
is one of the spiritual levels allow
that reality to be more like the
non-physical spiritual levels and then
blend the two so that there really isn't
as much of of a difference that's the
whole purpose it's not the idea of
running away from Earth to seek Heaven
it's the idea of creating Heaven on
Earth that's why you're all choosing to
be born physically on Earth but you
always as you have already suggested
attract whatever balancing ideas you
need such as your
boyfriend um trust that you do know what
you're doing don't focus on the negative
ideas of what you think you're looking
for where you are is what you need to
learn about yourself and what can
represent a place of Peace even if you
don't prefer it where you are exploring
where you are will give you the
information you need
now aside from the whole issue of just
letting go of past ideas that would
allow you to hold on to the pain you can
also assist yourself through what you
may call meditation the one that we have
shared that is called the blue white
light technique mhm are you familiar
with it yes Infuse yourself with a blue
jellylike substance in the areas of
greatest pain feel that that blue
jellylike substance actually acts as a
lubricant for all of your hard bones and
connective areas and as a sheath for all
of your nerve areas so that the entire
interaction is synergistic is one
environment enveloped in the blue gel
feel it Infuse itself into every cell
where you have
pain and allow it to
dissolve and stop thinking in terms of
structures of separate parts
think as a whole a fluid
hole and
relax does this assist you yes it does
um can I ask
one no
yes yes yes um my boyfriend um I was
supposed to ask he has problems when
he's driving he gets dizzy and um
like blacks out and I wanted to ask if
you could assist me in the reason why
this was
happening what we can suggest is that
you use the technique if you wish Center
and balance yourself when you are in
that state before you go into what you
call Dream time sleep time focus on the
idea of the strong magnetic energy of
your boyfriend
see the idea of the black hole the
central Vortex of
magnetism and allow yourself
telepathically to remind
him that a black
hole a black Ness a void or what appears
to be a void is not empty and actually
contains 99% of all
reality that there is light within the
blackness mhm send that as you are in a balanced
mhm send that as you are in a balanced
state three nights in a
row see if that begins to allow him to
relax enough to receive assistance from
his guides for they can be of best more
than we can okay and so can you okay we
thank you and we send you and remind you
our unconditional love and unconditional
love is all the it takes to be anywhere
and anyone you wish to
be all right thank you very much well
thank you very much for the sharing of
your heart and you may all take a short
break how's it
going please have a break and if you
want a copy of tonight's tape see Pamela
she'll be back around the corner making
the I'll say continue
happy New Year Bashar good day and good
New Year to you um Bashar I've been
thinking a lot lately about what you
talked about earlier about the body
being a vibrational frequency as and how
everything around us is also a
vibrational frequency like as the food
we eat would have a certain vibration
each individual food colors clothing s
everything is different or seen as
different because it is a different
vibrational frequency of the same Primal
energy right and but the the Primal part
is homogenous when you yeah when you
meet frequencies everything that is
unlike that Primal will then meet face
to face right and that way you identify
differences in a sense yes and maybe
clear them away so that one day they'll
all be the same basics in a sense that
does not devalue
individuality and in a sense anything
that has ever existed will always exist
but creation within itself can be shall
we say
harmoniously aligned right um for about the last year
aligned right um for about the last year
and a half I've had a real interesting
physiological symptomology yes and I
thought at first that it was like
chemical I have had a like my lower
intestine swells and my left leg the
Foot and Ankle swell up
and so I got very interested in herbs
and all kinds of things because I didn't
want to go the traditional route with it
all right and recently I've beginning to
think it might be a vibrational thing or
an energetic of some kind well do
understand of course that all
physiological reality is representative
of a vibration and sometimes when you're
in a particular vibrational State you
will of course generate a physical and
or chemical reason for a particular
manifestation right
because everything must have a
counterpart in that particular reality
in order to be experienced in that
reality a psychic told me that she
thought I was working out something that
I hadn't been strong enough to work out
before now I wondered if you would
reflect on that with me because I know
one one night when my foot was
particularly swollen a friend did some
reiche on it and it like went right down
in 15 minutes and I thought well that's
interesting because it seems more like
an energetic to do that that does not
mean that that particular methodology of
assimilation isn't connected to a
particular origin for that energy
whatever the methodology is that
assimilates it does not necessarily have
to be representative of how that
particular situation got started it can
simply be representative of the ability
to accept balance and blending
regardless of what the reasons are you
may have created for initiating that
particular circumstance to begin with so
in your perspective it has to do with
balance well everything does ultimately
in other words a being that is imperfect
balance cannot experience what you call
disease of any Nature by definition
right now ask a question please do thank
you how do you think of yourself or have
you ever thought of yourself as what you
may call A
Healer yes I went through some changes
about that one all right would you care
to illuminate some of those
changes um about seven years ago when I
started studying the course and miracles
um my hands started having this life of
their own and
U and I was also studying um with a d
priest at around the same time and I
remember I would be drawn to people who
had any kind of imbalance and I move my
hands around over them and I got very
insecure about what I was doing and
because I didn't know I thought well I
don't know what I'm doing what am I
doing and they would they would seem to
get better you know and do you now know
that you knew what you were doing I do
know that now oh all right yeah I've
gone through some changes on what I did
is I brought up past life stuff where I
was a real afraid of what would happen
to me if I did these kinds of things Oh
you mean like the psychic told
you which psychic you mean the one that
which one was it the one that said you
were still working some stuff out oh
from a past life Association is that all
related to of course I'm blocking that
energy because you have arrived at a
similar point in this life analogous to
the point you are at in the other life
so the same ideas are coming up again
how you handle it now how you assimilate
it now will depend upon the Persona the
person you have created yourself to be
now the only hangup shall we say is if
you still identify with the Persona you
used to be then right I saw that and so
I've been letting go of all that that's
another time that's not me now yes and
um I thought the healing energy was
going to be mainly coming out in my
artwork my paintings tell me that but
you have been very active with the using
of your hands in many
civilizations you were very strong this
way in Atlantean times as well I'm very
drawn to uh study some techniques now to
use the hands just so that I'll feel
like I have all right a suggest pattern
to use suggestion about the idea of the
swelling in your own form would be to
think in terms of fluidics and the idea
of fluid seeking its own level and
balancing out rather than building up
piling up in any one particular area
that may represent an imbalance of flow
think of energy flow balance of
flow and then there will not need to be
a physiological manifestation of the
swelling up of any particular area
because the flow is
imbalanced understand I do understand is
and and if
I stop blocking all this other energy
try and let that all flow flow through
you and go ahead and let it manifest
however it manifest with Integrity yes
with Integrity always yeah um that's
interesting so um it's a balance of
fluids or it's just manifesting that way
you mean yes to some degree manifesting
as an imbalance of fluids because of the
imbalance of the energy fluid within you
oh the fluidity of the energy I get it
oh great well thank you very much and I
wanted to tell you that um life is
becoming very exciting oh thank you
every day is a wonderful adventure oh
thank you very much do remember life has
always been that exciting you're just
remembering that yes I'm really glad
too thank you thank you
Bashar
sharing hello Bish good day and good New
Year to you good New Year same to you
um a lot of things has been happening to
us as a family group and everything very
exciting and and um speak up so that all
may share okay that um uh I'd like to
thank you for your encouragement all the
time that easy to play those games uh
and uh something else have been
occurring that um I don't quite
understand what's happening and that's
why I decid to ask you it is about uh
our little daughter she's almost four
years old all right and uh she's been
she was sleeping pretty good every night
until suddenly she start waking up and
you know it was some panic and
uh uh for that's happening for like two
and a half months something like that
every night around 11 or 12:00 and then
I started receiving myself some uh some
kind of uh the panic I that she was
feeling I started feeling it myself so
that helped me to use some techniques on
her and so has been useful for me too
but uh all right very good and uh I I
found like uh a help her too to run some
uh I mean to get like to confront some
negativity of fears in herself but right
after that
uh she suddenly wasn't afraid and so but
she was still waking up so I asked her
what happened and she said guys came you
know she said that it's a little guy
comes to wake it up at night and she
said he he said Scarlet Scarlet uh let's
play with the toys and he said he start
playing he starts playing with the toys
yes so uh I said you know I see nothing
unusual in this so far but
but
then then she says that uh and I but I
ask most more questions about how does
he look he said about my size and all
this and so she says that he came uh
flying through the window you know so I
you know I relax and I start
understanding was you know I think it
was happening with it or whatever yes
but the only thing is no worries me but
uh uh I can say it bothers me a little
bit she keeps waking up still sometimes
they like two or 3 hours at night and
she comes to our bed constantly so I I
stay kind of awake several times too so
all right I just like to ask you uh
what's happening right now after that
she's a little bit you know sick you
know some congestion her chest and I've
been help but still she has a little bit
like cold and congestion things like
that so I just want to ask you what's
happening all right please one moment
until what you call of of seven certain
ideas from other lives and agreements
that you have all made are going to
continue to be worked out you are going
to continue to receive some assistance
in working those out and processing the
energy through each and every one of you
the members of the family up until that
time in various ways approximately at
the age of seven of your daughter's age
in that sense there will be a change and
a transformation in the way the energy
and the agreements and the assistance is
worked out or experienced by all of you
the child is simply still in what you
may call a susceptible state to changes
in energy has picked up certain belief
structures from the Society of course
and has learned now is learning now
through you to assimilate those beliefs
in a positive way there are still
certain ideas that may manifest here and
there as small diseases in that way a
processing a purifying clearing out our
suggestion would be not that you will
not necessarily stop the occurrence of
waking up for at those times of your
night is's a very high receptive psychic
activity time when some of the strongest
communication can go on between
yourselves and those you have chosen to
function as your guides which is what
the being represents yes on many
different levels in many different ways
a suggestion is that perhaps together if
you can while you are in your own rooms
if that is the arrangement of your house
you learn to breathe together you set
aside some time with your daughter in
that sense and with anyone in the
household to be in your own rooms and
learn to breathe together to know beyond
the shadow of a doubt that the pacing of
your breathing is being mirrored by all
other individuals in the house and that
you are breathing as one so you do not
have to feel disconnected or
compartmentalized in separate rooms so
that you all know you are in the event
together as one and so that you can
become more telepathically psychically
sensitive to what each is experiencing
and the reasons for why you are
experiencing these things now I cannot I
am not allowed to go into great detail
with the specific ideas that are
involved in the communications for those
things will play themselves out in the
lives the physical lives that all of you
are living in very blatant and obvious
ways your daughter has the ability and
has chosen as we are allowed to perceive
the agreement to be extremely
psychically sensitive in that way and
this will come into play major activity
in roles after the age of seven between
what you call the age of 7 to 10 will be
a very concentrated very highly focused
time of assimilation for your daughter
as we perceive her energy in all the
things that the guide has taught and all
the things that the friend has taught
from the age of 7 to 10 she will have to
learn how to assimilate all that
knowledge in a way that can be applied
in your physiological Society it may be
a time of high concentration that there
may seem to be some idea of conflict or
polarities involved with her particular
exploration at that time but from the
idea also of 10 forward to approximately
13 there will be a complete uprooting a
complete rearrangement of the
foundations in her life in that way so
that she will then from that point
forward through her period of
adolescence have the opportunity to
discover what it is she will Define her
reality to be now if you allow yourself
the opportunity now to learn to breathe
together as one you also will be
sensitized to the changes that she will
go through in such a way that will
alleviate your fear that what she is
going through is inherently negative and
will strengthen with your co- breathing
her ability to be able to assimilate all
that knowledge all that raw open exposed
energy and information that she will be
drawing in in a way that will be able to
be applied physically materially in
beneficial terminology so our suggestion
for now is to learn to breathe together
breathe together set aside some times to
learn to breathe together first you can
begin by doing it in one room and allow
everyone to understand the pace of the
easy deep and relaxed breathing and see
bright blue white light filling you and
surrounding you and immersing you and
you are breathing it in and then when
you are in your separate rooms remind
all right breathe together now as you
drift off into sleep breathe together we
are one we are breathing as one everyone
is together no one is apart these are
the things we have agreed to do we are
wrapped in love we are warm in the
blanket of light and life everyone will
then be able to participate in a union
with the idea of the guide energy and
will not feel as if anyone is being
singled out or picked out or isolated in
that way so those fears those ideas of
isolation the uncertainties and the
doubts will not have to manifest as
strongly you can lay a foundation a very
loving and warm Foundation by filling
your lives and your house with the
Breath of Life the breath of certainty
the breath in that sense of absolute
trust that you are really one being
breathing together you understand yes B
now thank you there has been much more
that we have imparted other than what
you heard verbally and some of this will
come out in your dream realities and
assist you in learning how to soften and
balance the ideas we have discussed in
terms of energy and there has also been
transmission to your child as well but
mostly for now to the child within you
okay we thank you thank you very much
and pleasant
dreams shedding good evening Bashar and
do you good day and a good New Year and
an ecstatic New Year to you oh thank you
double infinity for us 88 double
infinity yes all
right I don't know an Infinity of
Infinities all right
exactly well the timing has arrived for
us to speak of orcas and Japan orcas and
Japan yes um first of all I want to
thank you for your opening
remarks and for what you had to say
about full self validation that really
struck a chord within me all right and
self-awareness um I've been exploring my
own Orca energy as power and and
integrity one moment yes by the way for
those not familiarized with what we have
discussed what you call the Ora
represents the polarity energy of the
consciousness of the whale and dolphin
life forms upon your planet which is the
other alien species upon your world you
have two human satation the Orca
represents Loosely put the samurai or
the Sorcerer of the sea the path of
absolute conviction no turning back you
have to be shall we say very clear very
clean very pure when dealing with the
Orca energy or it will collapse very
strongly upon
continue yes I have attracted uh
situations to myself recently so that I
could really explore that and I've been
um understanding more and more about
what that is oh thank you and I want to
thank you for all your loving
Reflections that have enabled me to
reflect to myself what I need to know oh
well you know what what you're
welcome I know that I love you B we love
you as well all of you un conditionally
no matter what you choose to think of
yourselves we will love you
anyway that's nice to know um we went to
SeaWorld on New Year's Day all right and
visited the Dolphins petting pool and
also the orcas and as you may know that
since there have been the last couple of
quote unquote accidents yes as we said
come crashing down yes exactly I I got
that between the orcas and the trainers
not allowed now to swim with them or to
interact with them in water and when we
saw the first show we were feeling very
sad about the separation and the lack of
trust because it was such a beautiful um
expression of trust and integrity and
power and gentleness all at once oh yes
yes yes but there is no real reason to
have to be sad for those individuals are
now going to be forced to face certain
things within themselves that they would
not have faced before and in that sense
the orcas have done that for them yes I
have uh come to realize quite a bit
about that you can rejoice in the
strength and the boldness of the
discovery I was thinking of that earlier
when you were sharing with somebody else
those ideas well to continue we stayed
for the last show and we went back to
see the last Orca show and afterwards as
the stadium emptied out there were six
of us there and we stood there and sent
love and appreciation and as much
communication and emotion as we could to
the Orchid and we're receiving it back
from them as well as vocal sounds yes
and there were three of them in the tank
and six of us and we decided we would
ask them telepathically if they would
come and slide out on the platform in
front of us which they did nice and two
of them came up first and they turned
sideways and they pointed their noses in
opposite directions and arched their
backs were they making this perfect
formation with their tails yes that we
found extremely exciting yes and then
when they slid down into the water again
the third one came up on the tank so
they all were in very close
communication with us and we were them
yes and then as we left we walked down
past the tank and they were very close
to the glass inside or to the
plexiglass and they were pressing
themselves against it and looking at us
and and opening the mouths right at eye
level so we could see them and we all
just pressed ourselves up against the
glass and we kissing the glass and
crying with emotion it was so intense
well than and during the interaction uh
as I was feeling this sadness of the
separation washing over
me I got a
realization that enabled me to see that there is so
that enabled me to see that there is so
much more going on there's like new
levels of awareness were opening up and
what from them is the idea that there is
Harmony and unity and that we are
connected spiritually yes and what you
are actually feeling as what you are
terming that overwhelming emotion is
that you are identifying and feeling the
true size of their
hearts yes and it expanded you
it certainly did we reached many many
levels we've been integrating ever since
it so you may simply ask yourselves and
I do not bring this up to give you more
opportunity at self-
invalidation but you may simply ask
yourselves how many of you in your lives
Express the level of Integrity expressed
by those beings exactly that can give
you something to think about
because now there are seven of them in a
very small area and I know on some level
they long for the Freedom of the Seas
which is their Birthright yes and on
another level I know they've chosen to
be there as ambassadors yes to interact
with us nice things are
changing I'm very interested in orcas
having to do of course the samurai
connection and Japan now that Daryl's
going to Japan is there going to be some
um communication some
interaction energetically consciously
yes yes um can you say a bit about that I
yes um can you say a bit about that I
don't really know what to ask there is
nothing for me to say at this time
whatever is the mass Consciousness shall
we say the miniature Mass consciousness
of that area will determine what will
come through and what will be said at
the moment of that
interaction remember we don't plan ahead
yeah and right now the things that could
be said the things that are in motion
are many and we do not have a perception
of the determination of any particular
one that needs to crystallize except
that there will be communication from
the satation half of your world to the
human half of your world in that
area I'm very excited about that because
I've I'm well aware of some of the
interactions that have gone on uh with
the Japanese fishermen and the Dolphins
yes and
I've learned a lot about that and I
think well I know that that's had an
enormous effect on the mass reality of
the Japanese as well as the world all of
you all of you are truly becoming one
world thank you thank you very much
forar next time thank you
Shing hello Bash and good day and good
New Year to you and a joyous New Year to
you thank you um I read Intruders last
week yes and I know I'm pretty sure it
was Margo who had asked you about it and
I read it with the idea of your response
namely that these uh quote unquote
abductions detainments detainments yes
were for the purpose of
integrating and Fa in our fears and integrating
and Fa in our fears and integrating
those fears that's
one okay what was the other
one keep going okay so I read the book
with that in mind yes now when I read
communion uh stribus or stus book I had
read that before and I could see it that
it was happening in those experiences
yes but reading
Intruders I didn't see that at all in
there I think it it's a very um
carefully written book uh nothing you
know oh they abducting us and all kinds
of things it's careful research and the
reports from the people who were
detained um most of the emotions that have come
um most of the emotions that have come
up and are still there include anger
anger anxiety and they have not really
integrated it not yet okay now to me and
in fact one person in this book is
reported to have said and that was my
reaction if they really want to detain us and
if they really want to detain us and
that's another question for the purpose
that they're doing it uh why can't it be
made conscious that there is an
agreement I mean for example darl's
agreement with you was was conscious and
I can't see not before a certain point
no but but before he before he started
actually channeling there are many
things the channel has not yet
discovered that we have talked about
okay but still this agreement is did
come into Consciousness and it is coming
into Consciousness more and more yes but
from from none of the reports in this
book does it seem that it came into
Consciousness and ah one
moment though there may be to some
degree some confusion on the part of
some individuals if you will carefully review
individuals if you will carefully review
the idea of the book again you'll
realize that there are references made
to circumstances and situations out of
which the individuals emerged as you say
in fear in anger and there are
references made to situations and
circumstances of identical nature in
which the individuals were at ease yes I
know that's true that's true that's
that's another aspect of it my feeling
in
Reading what happened to these
individuals what they remembered
happening especially in terms of the um
the seeming genetic experiments um was
that we were more of used to them than
they're of used to us and it is two ways
always two ways I understand what you
mean you have made an agreement with
them for this particular manifestation
and yes you are very important to them
but what what is their real P purpose
one of the hypothesis is that that their
civilization is sort of dying out and
they need I will say to some degree this
is
so but not in the way you understand it
are they part of the association yes
because it really doesn't seem all that
ethical the way that they treat they
don't seem to be treating us as equals
for one I understand but also understand
what they have to deal
with they have to deal with many belief
systems that will not allow a lot of
conscious understanding to take
place also you are perhaps making a
small assumption that every civilization
assumption that every civilization
thinks as yours does oh no no that that
came out very clearly I think in the
book that their thinking is very
different all right and what about their
their seeming lack of understanding one
moment you are contradicting yourself
listen to the words no no no what I'm
saying is it was very clear that they
think differently than we do yes uh one
of the things that really struck me is
that they seem and I'm saying see you
know that they don't understand maternal
emotions to some degree this is so and
and so I thought oh since they do not
reproduce that
way they well they seem to reproduced
with humans the same way humans do of
late uhhuh but that is also a part of
what you have called The Experiment it
was not always so oh I see I am
speaking haltingly for a
reason you are as you say pushing
the edge of what we are allowed to
reveal okay some of the
information will be coming out in this
your new
year but not yet well there's a lot of
information in here oh yes and but not
what is not there and
okay are they forth density
that cannot at this time be answered
specifically uhhuh yeah because it seem
to be a little bit of both yes third and
and fourth
yes okay thank you very much all that we
more more important ideas some of the
more important reasons as to why that is
occurring well that's good now for my
point of view I mean I would be very
willing to to uh be of service or help
anybody as long as it's
conscious you see that's up to
you I think most people would be like
that if they're told consciously hey
here's the problem can you help us solve
it how many individuals not to refute
you and not to say that is not so but
how many individuals upon your planet
are always given conscious opportunities
that they never
take it quote unquote ought to be
obvious in many cases yeah but how often
is it okay thank you thank you at this
timing allow us to reflect back to each
and every one of you once again for the
very first time our deep
excitement our deep and true
thrill at being allowed to interact with
your Consciousness in this way at being
allowed to cocreate with you a tapestry
of infinite
Beauty we thank you for your
interweavings we leave you to your loom
for the time
being we bid you once again an exciting
New Year of your time of counting a fond
and soothingly warm and
loving good day
how'd it go [Applause]
[Applause]
thank you all for being here
tonight thank you all very much if you
want a copy of tonight's tape you can
have it tonight