this evening of your time as you create
time to
exist allow us to begin this interaction
this evening of your time with the
following entitlement this as you say will be a
entitlement this as you say will be a
bit of a
mouthful trust and Clarity in
communication the limbo State
colon what it is and how to use
it you will
I ask excuse me if I am a little bit
long- winded this evening but these
things require a little bit of
clarification and
redefinition now that many of you are
going through the types of changes that
you are going through now that you are
experiencing different levels of energy
within your
Consciousness we can now Define in ways
that we have not defined them before
some of the terminologies that we have
used in our discussions with you in the
past so that you will have perhaps a
more precise insight into what we meant
when we used certain terminologies for
always always always understand there
are many levels many dimensions many
different points of view to the
semantics of any particular definition
or word that we may use in your language
which may not necessarily be accurately
representative of the way we mean the
terminology when we use
it so let us first talk about the idea
of trust and Clarity in
communication one of the primary shall
we say problems or difficulties that we
have observed in your civilization has
to do simply with the communication
between yourselves as to why there are many
yourselves as to why there are many
negative feelings negative interactions
negative outcomes a lot of it is simply
hinged not so much on the idea that
there actually is an insurmountable
problem but simply that your ability to
communicate the
idea is not necessar as effective as it
could be not as direct not as honest as
it could be because you have in the past
created yourself to be a
society that has in a sense cloaked
itself in so many layers of
Consciousness so many layers of
interpretation and
symbology individuals whether they use
the same words or not do not always
obviously understand what another
individual means by what they say
we simply here with put forth a simple
suggestion and it has to do with trust
trusting that you each and every one of
you are only attracting into your
experiential reality those interactions
which do benefit to you and are
attracting yourself to other individuals
in such a way that you do benefit to
them in trusting that this is the
foundational reason for why you find
yourself interacting for why you find
yourself Comm communicating with anyone
you can use the following approach which
may allow a little more clarity to take
place in your conversations in the
future if you can allow yourself to
know to know to
trust that the other
individual always has the best
intention going into the
conversation then you can assist them in
clarifying what they mean you can assist
yourself and allow them to assist you
and themselves in clarifying what you
mean if you simply take it for granted
that what they say no matter how it may
sound to what you have been
taught what they say is meant in the
best possible way so that if something
for some reason sounds shall we say
strange off-kilter or funny to you or
perhaps negative to you you perhaps you
can stop the conversation and simply
suggest now I know I trust that you had
the best of intentions the most positive
intention behind what it is you are
saying therefore I know that even though I
therefore I know that even though I
heard it this way perhaps just maybe you
meant this is that what you meant Oh yes
that's what I meant thank you for
clarifying that so we would not have a
misunderstanding always it is our
suggestion go for the trust of the
intention behind what is said rather
than allowing yourself to be marryed
around by the words as they sound as you
have been taught to think they sound
what you have been taught to think they
mean find out what they really do mean
by shooting as you say aiming as you say
for the intention of the communication
rather than the clothing in which the
communication is wrapped do not react to
the clothing allow yourself to search to
seek the intention itself assist another
individual by letting them know what
they have said does to you how you are
reacting let them know how you are
interpreting what they say and ask them
if they truly meant that or if they
truly meant something else allow
yourself to develop a commonality of
trust based on your understanding that
every individual no matter how they
approach it no matter how they cloak it
no matter where they come from nor when
generally speaking in some portion of
their Consciousness
intends intends that what they have to
share can be used
constructively can be used to add to the
overall creativity of your combined
reality beginning to approach it from
that point of view will allow you very
quickly to discern the intention behind
the communication to know whether it is
truly positive or negative and to allow
you less
misunderstanding so that you will not be
so offended by the different portions of
your Consciousness that you are afraid
to face the different portions of your
Consciousness that you fear that may
have been brought to the surface by
something someone said simply because it
was reflected in a certain way because a
certain Nuance was given that was not
necessarily representative of what that
individual meant but perhaps is what you
needed to hear so that you could face
that certain portion of yourself now
that it has been brought to the surface
by that particular
Nuance allow yourself always to
understand that any conversation you are
having with someone else is an echo of
the things that you are only telling
yourself you need to hear in many
different ways examine explore them
unconditionally unbiased in that way
openly trusting that what you are
attracting in some way shape or form has
an intention behind it that matches your
own the overall intention of the
support and the added accelerative
creativity of your entire
civilization just a
suggestion now the limbo State what it
is and how to use
it we have discussed this idea of a
limbo State many times with you
generally in the conversations that we
have had most individuals will assume
that when we say limbo State what we are
referring to is that time or those times
in your life when it seems you have done
all you can possibly do and now you are
floating you are at as you say
stalemate no particular direction makes
itself more apparent than any other
direction you do not necessarily have a
particular momentum or an impetus to
move in any one particular way more than
another you seem to be at a stand still
for one reason or another sometimes you
cannot necessarily fathom the reason
sometimes you think you
can sometimes you don't want to know but
the idea of the limbo
state has a more precise and in a sense
a much more profound definition that we
have up to this point not necessarily
shared with you we will do so now the
idea generally as we perceive the aut
generally as we perceive the aut
Consciousness has been perceived as
meaning thus a state in which you must now wait
thus a state in which you must now wait
for something to happen having done all
you can possibly do and there is no more
you can do now you are floating in a
limbo state to see what falls out of all
the things you have set up you are now
in a sense
coasting all right all of these are
shall we say real
definition but they do not touch the
essence the mechanics the structure of
what that waiting is all
about the idea can perhaps be best
explained by going back to another
analogy that we have discussed many
times and that is simply called the film
strip analogy we have talked about the idea
analogy we have talked about the idea
that different moments in time are
discreet as your scientists say
quantized that is every single moment is
its own now universe and the next moment
is a completely different reality all
together and whatever it is at any given
moment that you decide you are will
utterly determine what the next moment
will be shape like in a sense how you
will experience that next moment and one
moment does not have to be connected to
the next until you impose upon that
frame and upon that entire the idea that
there must be continuity one leading to
the other we have talked about the idea
that your life and your many lives are
like the frames upon a strip of your
film one frame at a time one life at a
time in linear time it seems they come
one after another but that's the nature
of your physical reality from the point
of view of the projectionist shall we
say hypothetically all the frames exist
right now your entire life is there all
at once all your lives all the frames
are there all at once and from the point
of view of the hypothetical
projectionist which is the same as your
higher self your over Soul any frame can
be viewed at any moment in any order
regardless of the way you think you have
to view it in linear time A to Z doesn't
have to be that
way now this idea of the limbo State can
be looked at two ways again the negative
way and of course the positive way just
as anything can be looked at from one
side or the other
the way we have perceived that your
Society generally has interpreted what
we meant by limbo stake is the negative
idea and this is not meant as a
derogatory statement simply that the negative way
statement simply that the negative way
to look at this is to view the following
analogy let us say you are looking at
your life as a strip of film running
through the projector and playing out on
the screen at a certain
speed most of you when you talk about
the standstill limbo State when things
do not seem to be
happening usually look at this as the
product of the film somehow slowing
down going into a static state where all
of a sudden you are focused on one
frame and you don't know when the film
is going to start up
again the idea of looking at the limbo
State as if your life has slow down in a
sense is the negative way to look at it
let's look at it from the positive point
of view because understand you will get
the same
effect the focus on one apparent moment
the now moment if you understand that
the film is still going at high speed
but that you have accelerated your
ability to perceive the frames has
accelerated and sped up to match the
speed of the film you are now going as
fast as the film it is what you call in
your reality a
stroboscopic effect you have many of you
seen the idea that when something is
moving such as falling water and you
place a strobe light upon it you can
freeze the action and allow one drop of
that falling water to seem to remain
suspended in the air before
you in a sense this is what many of you
are now doing you are accelerating your
perceptive abilities up to the speed of
your creations and so it seems as if
things are standing still seems as if
they have slowed down and nothing is
happening but understand there's a very
profound difference in how you look at
this because if you look at it as if
your life is slowed down if the film is
slowed down then you usually wait around
for something to happen and do not take
action do not move in your
life however if you understand that the
only reason things seem to be standing
still is because you have simply caught
up to the speed of your creation then
you can understand that that point of
view is now a point of power because you
are in perfect equilibrium with the rate
that you are creating your reality and
what this means is as follows when you
are in perfect equilibrium with the rate
the speed at which you are creating your
reality Moment by Moment by Moment by
moment then that means that everything around
then that means that everything around
you is moving at the same rate and that
means that inertia is balanced and
nothing has more ability or less ability
to be moved by you in the direction you
prefer they all have the same rate of
speed you are all moving parallel
synchronized to each other and therefore
there is no great inertia to overcome
because your motion relative to each
other you you and the events in your
life are now moving at the same pace and
you can gently push them in any
direction you want to this in a sense is
the quote unquote secret of what you
call your Martial Arts what you call a
master of the martial arts will tell you
basically that the reason that a small
seemingly weak person can move a
seemingly stronger large person in any
direction they want to is that at one
particular moment in the action of the
movement of the large person toward the
smaller one the smaller one matches the
speed of the larger person and at that
moment they are exactly equal in inertia
at that moment no one is moving relative
to the other person and therefore is a
very simple thing to allow that person
to move in any direction the smaller
person wishes to because there is
nothing to overcome no Mass no momentum
to over come everything is moving at the
same pace and can
interact with each other any way they
want to so this limbo State this time of
seeming stand still now what it seems as
if you have done all you can do is
actually the time when things can happen
most magically most quickly and the only
reason it may not seem to be doing so is
because you're standing there waiting
for something to happen allow yourself
to begin to look at the limbo state from
this point of view truly see your point
of power understand that you are simply
now pacing simply synchronizing the rate
the literal rate at which your
Consciousness is creating the moments of
your reality each and every moment is a
reality each and every moment is a
discrete moment a discret definition a
discrete reality they all flicker one
after another at at an astonishing rate
so fast it seems to be your physical
reality seems to be an unbroken
Continuum of
time but it isn't it is discrete moments
discret definitions and when you find
you are floating in that limbo State you
are at the point of power to allow any
Factor any event in your reality to move
in the direction and in the style you
prefer to all you have to do when you
arrive at that point is act in the
direction you prefer to act in the
manner you prefer to act as the
representation of the reality you prefer
to have things will happen
synchronistically in your life
immediately falling into place
immediately the only thing that would
cause you to
hesitate is perhaps and I do not say
this to set you up the only thing that
would cause you to hesitate is perhaps
when you see that when you're at that
State it is so easy to create the
reality you want that some of who may be
afraid of the power you finally realize
you have and back off a bit from it
because you will realize in that moment
how powerful you actually
are the creation of your day-to-day
reality is second nature to you you are
so powerful in doing it that you have
been able to forget that you you are the
creators of that experiential reality
that's how easy it comes to you it is so
easy that you've been able to overlook
that you are responsible for the
creation of that reality it comes so
easily every single second every single
moment you are exercising choice of what
you believe is the most likely reality
to manifest in that moment every every
single moment that's how powerful you
are when you allow yourself to begin to
match the rate at which you are creating
that reality you will feel like you are
standing still because you are traveling
at infinite speeds and when you move at
infinite speeds you are everywhere at
once and when you're everywhere at once
it's like you're standing perfectly
still because the only way you get a
sense of the motion is when you have a
relative measurement between your
reality and what you are calling another
reality if you know all reality all
events All Creations are equal to you
because they come from you when you
allow them to all achieve that
equilibrium then you are all shall we
say falling at the same
rate nothing moves faster nothing moves
slower and you can move the pieces
around effortlessly because they're all
glid in all together one event one idea and
in all together one event one idea and
you begin to see all the events in your
life truly as extensions of yourself and
I am not speaking figuratively I am not
speaking philosophically I am speaking
physically mechanically literally you
are the creators of your reality the
limbo State what you have called the
limbo state is your point of power it is
living in the present in the now
you are shall I say
allegorically about that far away from
having everything you
want all you have to do is go that extra
little step and of course for many of you and
step and of course for many of you and
again not to set you up that last little
step is the most difficult because
simply you have been taught over and
over and over and over again it can't be
that easy
I can't be that powerful but you are
because you are aspects and reflections
of creation you are made in the image of
God to be made in that image is to be an
echo of God and in that sense you are
that powerful you are creation
itself you are in that sense the dreams
of God the hands of God the instruments
the tools as all beings in creation are
you are as well as we are all the
different ways that the creation has of
expressing itself within the creation it
is it is your
nature it is the very fabric of your
existence to be the power
itself you do not have to develop a
swollen ego to recognize that you can
allow yourself to be at balance with all
things and to still at the same time know that
and to still at the same time know that
because you are at balance with all
things everything is an extension of you
and will move in the direction that you
allow it to because you say so because
that's your
job as aspects of the infinite in a
sense to put this colloquially you are
given the responsibility to create your
immediate reality in the fashion you
desire that's why you have free will
just as a side
note and just referring to some
conversations that we have had with a
few of you from time to time and again
in no way are we in your vernacular
putting anyone down but it seems quite
contradictory to us that there are
members of your Society who insist that
creation instills Free Will within you
and then should at the same time seek to
control your lives with its will you
have free will because you have complete
and un UT free will you can create any
reality you desire that is being made in
the image of
God act as such and you will have Heaven
on your Earth
guarantee remember the present is your
point of power and in the limbo State
you are not waiting you are not at a
standstill you are at infinite speeds
move in the direction you prefer and all
will automatically synchronistically
fall into place I guarantee it and you
will have a life of
ecstasy and
remember there is no such thing as
something that is too good to be true or
too good to
last exstasy is what you are made of it
is the highest energy of creation
reflected and represented through your
physical form live as it because you are made of
form live as it because you are made of
living life you are EX to see itself of
this our civilization has no doubt and
once again we simply remind you because
we love you that no matter what you
choose to think of yourselves we will
always believe in you you can create any
reality you desire and we will be with
you no matter what type of reality you
choose to create but the type of reality
you choose to create will determine
exactly how we are able to interact with
you not that interaction with us is the
most important thing in your lives you
you are the most important thing in your
lives it is simply that as you recognize
that you can serve each other and create
a reality of Joy then you open to us the
invitation that is necessary for us to
have from you so that we can interact
with you and together blend our race and
your race into a larger civilization
that can continue to explore Creation in
ecstatic ways forever for there is no
end to it at least no end that we have
ever found in the thousands of years of
the thousands of civilizations that have
explored creation there has never been
found even the minutest inkling of an
end as far as we are concerned there
never will
be and we rejoice in any opportunity
that you will give us to share Creation
with you but only if you are willing to
be fully who and what you truly are for
if you are not then it is not with you
that we will be
interacting but only with your idea of
what you think you ought to be only with
your own Illusions and perhaps delusions
of self we prefer in your terminology
the genuine article because we know the
genuine article of you are creative
beings spontaneous beings loving beings
that can create anything they desire
including heaven on Earth we thank you
for allowing us to run off of the mouth
this way or shall I say allowing me to
run off of the Channel's mouth in return
for the gift that you have given us
allowing us to share and taste of your
Consciousness in return for that loving
gift I will ask you now in what way may
I be of service to
you begin
share so so that all may share as well
good day to you yes everyone please
speak up every speaker sh sh one
moment shii is a word in our ancient
language which we no longer use the
language that is and shabai simply
represents the principle that you would
perhaps most colloquially boil down to
saying go for it the idea simply is that
in our civilization when an individual
had a focus had a dream they did not
allow themselves to allow anything to
stop them they went straight ahead move
straight ahead
as what you would call in a warrior way
with Clear Vision clear intention clear
Direction and if there seemed to be a
situation where they needed as you would
say perhaps some space to be who they
were then the individual that was on
that particular path would simply at
that moment say shivi and all other
beings would stand out of the way to
allow them the broadest and clearest
possible path to reach and attain the
goal they
desire so Shiva continued
I'd also like to say that it works an
arm Planet too oh absolutely of course
um a brief sharing all right speak up be
I would like to know if the SS
representative for the association of
Worlds could speak on the time relative
time frequency of 1990 1997 of the
Middle East and the year 2013 and 14
after the break thank you very much very
briefly the idea is that at
approximately what you would Now
understand this is how we perceive your
energy now things could change but seems
like the momentum in this direction is
unlikely to swerve at least from the
general ideas of which we are now about
to speak approximately in what you would
call as we perceive your energy now your
year of
1997 there will be what you may call a
tumultuous interaction in your Middle
East concerning their social and
political and religious understandings
that will allow them to reexamine all
that they believe in there may be some
Warfare in that area there may be some
Strife in that area but at the same time
it will form a crucible that will allow
certain soul to shine very brightly very
hotly and our perception is that within
a very short period of time before your
year of
2001 there will be such a major
transformation in that area that a new
light a new understanding a new model a
new template for how your entire world
can develop a government will come will
issue from that area a collective
understanding of how all of you can
interm interact in love and in peace the
idea is that this will seem from our
perception to be accomplished this
laying down of the foundation of what
you would call a world government will
approximately be accomplished by your
year of 2011 to
2013 from that point
forward there will be a speed up of
interaction between your civilization
and many of the civilizations that are
observing your planet now there will be
some revelation of our existence
especially around your year of
1994 but there will be a far more Direct
speed up of interaction after your year
of 2013 because you will have finally
allowed yourself to four a trary or what
you may call A triumverate
Association of what you now call your
three major powers of your United States
your Soviet Union your People's Republic
of China and together as the
triumverate they will set the stage as a
leading example form the proposals upon which
example form the proposals upon which
the rest of your civilization can form
its own world peace world government and
from that point forward the idea of
national boundaries will begin to
dissolve all over a period of the next
hundred of your years does this answer
your question sufficient yes thank you
very much it seems like we're going to
be in for quite a limbo State long that
is up to you remember limbo states are
not only Collective they are personal
and if you find yourself in a personal
limbo State while you may recognize that
you can exist in an overall bubble a
collective bubble you can still as an
individual do many things within that
overall bubble that will allow the
overall bubble to not necessarily remain
as long as it might have had you as an
individual not acted you follow me in
your own personal World things will
change just because there is a
collective limbo State doesn't mean that
you cannot have what you desire in your
own personal reality now the more you
create the reality that you desire to
live in now the faster you will
represent a living example to everyone
else as to the type of reality they can
create collectively too and that will
speed up the whole process so it's
really still up to you it is in your
individual hands remember one individual
can have an impact over the entire
planet you've seen it done many times I
thank you for your Shar I I didn't get
my question yet yes that was last time
real loud last time that we interacted
we talked about the substance for the
seventh and eth sense the sense of
knowingness and you said it was not in
the consciousness of the channel I was
wondering if anything had happened where
that would become a available and I'd
like to suggest um um Cactus uh ala um
and some other substances like sun
Corella um in that nature one more one
more the information to some degree is
there at this time because of shall we
say the wide variance in belief systems
within this particular group we are not
allowed to discuss it for it may be high
misinterpreted but let us say that we
are allowed to suggest that it is in a
sense a quote unquote natural plant
derivative thank you very much thank you shely who's
shely who's
next go ahead go
ahead please read the list those that I
called off so that you're not uh slowing
the process down
good day Bashar and good day to you i'
like to go back to February when you
gave the Legacy yes and hear any
comments you might want to make at this
time to sort of expand on that you got
to speak real loud because the
individual wishes to return to a time
when we talked
about the idea of the blending and the
interaction of your human species with
another alien species and we entitled
that particular interaction that
particular disc discussion the Legacy
this individual simply wishes to know if
there's anything else we wish to say
about it at this time
no now the IDE is that the
information the information however is
coming out through members of your own
Society it is no accident that the
channel spoke tonight of a particular
book you will find more information
about the idea that was discussed in the
Legacy in that book you understand does
that answer your question no not
really you will find that it does answer
your question very strongly if you will
find the passages that you see there
will be a few other books of that nature
and you will be attracted to them it is
simply that the information now must
come through the individuals on your
planet we have in a sense sewn the seed
set the stage started the ball rolling
as you say by suggesting certain ideas
and quote unquote planting them in your
Consciousness it is not up to us at this
time to reveal the furtherance of that
information it is up to you to Discover
It by attracting it in your life through
the means that you already have at your
disposal on your own planet and that
means through the works of your fellow
humans thank you thank you very much we
thank your fellow humans for being
willing to dispense that information at
this time for it shows that you are less
fearful of yourselves and more willing
to discover more aspects of yourself to
allow that information to to light
sharing hello and do you good day talk
real loud please um I have a question
referring to a may I ask you a question
is that what you call real loud sorry oh
do not be sorry um just share with all
okay the closest thing I can call it is
a dream a dream um the elements in the
dream are reoccurring I had this
transparent black mass that transparent
black MK in a reoccurring drein that was
trying to suffocate me trying to
suffocate him did it succeed no no all
right it started out very small started
out very small and then it got more
powerful got more powerful and at one
time I decided that it was my dream so I
took off playing and the night sky
grabbed me and started digging a ditch
with my body oh very interesting in one
episode of the dream he decided it was a
dream and took off flying and the night
sky grabbed him and began digging a
ditch with his body digging a ditch in
what the ground the ground all right and
then what happened progressively got
more powerful more powerful do you mean
the ditch got deeper no the um I guess
you'd call it a nemesis the Black Mass
got more power the black MK all right
and then what it um stopped me from
moving and kept me from Talking stopped
you from moving and kept you from
talking and then what well when I would
wake up from these when it would go away
I realized that um all right your eyes
were open when you woke up and um that's
how I can I can't decide whether it was
a dream or not and I was wondering if
this was maybe a supernatural evil
entity or a supernatural evil entity or
if it was maybe something of my
subconscious or maybe something of the
subconscious all right may I ask you a
question first what is your definition
of a dream a dream yes a dream you asked
me if it was something real or just a
dream what is the
difference the difference is um a dream
to me is something that takes place
while I am resting and sleeping but what
does that mean well when my mind's being
creative I guess are you saying that
your mind is not creative when you're
away well it is but I mean it gets to do
what it wants while I'm asleep it gets
to do what it wants while he's asleep it
does not get to do what it wants while
you arew no why or why not um because
it's usually doing what I tell it and
I'm usually doing what Society tells me
why why why are you usually doing what
Society tells you because that's the way
Society is made you it is the way you
have chosen to be made by Society true
is that what you
choose no what do you
choose um how would you prefer to be is
there anything about the way you have
chosen to be made by society that you do
not prefer
prefer
actually doing what others tell me I'd
rather go off on my own and do what just
um become more spiritual become more
spiritual how by being by myself and
being able to do what do what I want
with the time that I have which is give
me a suggestion what do you want to do
with the time you have meditate meditate
and what will you learn in your
meditations um whatever comes whatever
comes if something should come to you in
your meditation that implied that there
would be something you could physically
do physically act upon would you do
it yeah are you
sure yes I'll rephrase
it if something came in Yoda meditation
that said this thing if you would do it would
said this thing if you would do it would
be the most exciting the most thrilling
thing you could do in your life with
Integrity would you do it if it would
help me yeah if it would help you
interesting statement let me back
statement let me back
up you are
implying that if you discovered in your
life something that was the most
exciting thing you could think of to do
with Integrity that it might not be
something that would automatically help
you why would you think that
I don't know yes you do well I'd be OFW
lary of something that would be like
that why would you be Leary of something
that excited
you if it would give me power I might be
afraid of it as you said before all
right but understand all the things that
you discover do not give you power they
simply remind you of the power you
already are now why would you be afraid to be
are now why would you be afraid to be
reminded of how powerful you are use
your imagination and give the worst case
scenario of what you think would be the
worst thing that could possibly happen
if all of a sudden you were put in touch
with all the power you are to lose it
lose it lose it
where it was taken away from Taken where
by whom someone else someone else where
could they take it I don't know you
don't know may I suggest something all
right do you understand that you are the
creator of your reality now I since I've
been listening to your tapes and video
all right do you understand that what
you call the universe is simply a
projection of what is within you and
that there really is no outside that
everything you perceive is an extension
from within do you understand
that then if everything you perceive is
within you where could anyone possibly
take it that wasn't within you no so are
you still afraid that they can take it
from you
no does it relax you to know that yes
you don't sound absolutely sure about
that well what I am sure all right I'll
take your word for it for now okay now
is there something that has dawned upon
you that would be more exciting in your
life to do with Integrity than anything
you're doing
now what do you mean
is there something in your life I'll use
your colloquial terminology a livelihood
a service a creative project is there
something that you think would be the
most inspiring and exciting project you
could do that you are not doing right
now is there something ever that has
motivated you that you have not acted
upon that is the most exciting thing you
can think of to do magic magic do you
mean in your terminology the idea of
producing illusions on stage no not
stage magic actual magic actual magic
all right you mean the transmutation of
physical Mass all right then I'll give
you your first clue may I do you
understand that magic what you call
natural magic is being done by you all
the time now I don't now you do do you
time now I don't now you do do you
understand that it is not a situation
not an issue of Mind Over Matter it is
in fact that mind and matter are the
same thing different manifestations of
the same energy your Consciousness do
you understand
that do you understand that your spirit
is not something that literally inhabits
your body that your body is your spirit
in physical terminology and that so as
above so
below do you understand
that then do you understand that you are
in that sense magical right
now and do you understand that all you
are saying when you say want to do magic
is you are saying you want to be
conscious of the fact that you're doing
magic already that you want to see the
process consciously and in your
terminology consciously desire and allow
it to happen when you so desire it to
happen do you understand yes now in your
estimation just
briefly what seems to be the greatest
difficulty in allowing you to perform
the magic you want to perform
um I guess as you said before
remembering that it's possible all right
the greatest difficulty is remembering
that it's possible all right is there
are you aware of any individuals on your
planet that in any way shape or form
exhibit any of the traits you say you
desire to exhibit no can you do your
research and find some yes because they
do exist
now it will depend upon the culture you
will find many of them are perhaps a
little more prominent in cultures that
relate more strongly to what you would
call nature such as perhaps what you
would call your Native American culture
some of your Tibetan culture you may
find in these culture practitioners that
already exist that already exhibit a
high degree of what you are calling
natural magic it is our suggestion just
a suggestion that if you can for
anything any of you really wants to do
that you don't think you're capable of
doing now if you can as you say do your
research find an individual that sounds
like they're doing what you want to do
go to that individual watch what they do
pattern your vibration after them now
that does not mean give your power away
to them it simply means mirror their
energy because the only reason they can
do what they do is because they are of a
particular frequency because everything
in reality is the product of different
frequencies different reality different
frequency change the frequency change
the reality so if you go to someone who
is already on that frequency and let
their frequency rub off on you so that
you Max their frequency you will be able
to do exactly the same things you see
them doing no more no less understand
yes that is our suggestion for you allow
yourself to find what could classically
be called an
apprenticeship do do your research find
an individual that inspires you you will
know the individual when you find the
information it will ring a bell within
you go and meet that individual and see
what happens from there and you will be
squarely on the path of learning what it
is you say you want to learn all right
does that help you yes well thank you
very much for your sharing thank
you Shing H you gorgeous being well thank
Shing H you gorgeous being well thank
you very much you Beautiful
s okay where's the
speaker you are the speaker speaker
okay resonate pull your seat Bel
resonate okay um I've got I've got
something I really want to share oh W
right douch and then I've got a teen
teeny weeny question teeny weeny
question did you hear the energy change
I've got something I want to share and
then I got a teeny Meeny
little be bold okay um God everything's
gonna spill out at once and that's okay
thank you um I want to tell you about
this journey that I've been on all right
be brief and the B the journey is like
ever since I started coming here I've
been taking note of all the things that
you've told us about um judgment and
mechanics and all right taking notes
give some of the notes back now okay and
then I've been experimenting with them
right oh all right okay how exciting it
is
extremely so what I've done is I've gone
down through my feelings those feelings
that I normally shun and push out to
scare me yes and I've gone down through
them and I've accepted them and I've
gone down and found the beliefs that
they are holding me as the gifts for me
yes the gifts of the beliefs that I wish
to transform that I put there by choice
yes that's what your feelings are for
are signposts that point to the beliefs
that are holding you to the realities
that you get God they're gorgeous the
beliefs the beliefs that the feelings
guide me to very creative are sometimes
not the most not what you that's all
right nonetheless they are very creative
right and some of them are uncomfortable
and some of them are scary and some of
them are like oh boy no that's not me
all right but by accepting those yes
then change them just just by accepting
them and allowing them and getting down
under them and finding out where just by
accepting them everything is right in
may I ask you a question yes and why is
it that when you accept them you can
change them because they're mine because I
them because they're mine because I
change them because it's my yes because
you cannot change what you do not own
own and that's what denial is all about
denial taking ownership of your Creations is
taking ownership of your Creations is
all about thank you very much and when
you choose to take your own Creations
you bring them right under your just
like you
saido are you sure are you positive I
absolutely I I don't know about every
single time every every without
exception without exception not even one
not even one k wey
exception you know what that is the
first thing that I do is when I when I
see something that I'm creating I go o
God then I'll go okay I created this by
choice and the moment that I say that
that I can gather up that courage and
say that that thing starts to unfold
inside me so fast with such
shity that you would you well it's
remarkable it's
absolutely remarkable yeah and you know
what else what else I found out that I
think you probably said this but I found
it out for myself yes that when I go
down into my beliefs and I get a get
these third density absolutely genius
Creations all right
absolutely is true could not have
created some of the most fantastic
Little Creations that I've got sitting
down there to make sure that I'm going
to experience that belief and when I get
down underneath it yes that third
density reality right yes there is no
other reality but the fourth density is
clap up the other side apparency the
apparency that's underneath it yes is
totally untrue I understand what you mean
untrue I understand what you mean
unpreferred they're all true right all
true right but when I get down to it I
know that that is not my preference at
this time it is not the foundational
existence state of your Consciousness no
and it was because it's not preferred
and because it's an apparency of
something that I put there to kind of
hide it from yes yes yes right yes then
that made it a little bit tricky to find
it so I couldn't find it right away
couldn't change the whole game just like
that but then when I do the most
gorgeous realities open up so
naturally effortlessly and magically and every one
effortlessly and magically and every one
of those every single one of those
boogers be being monsters that I am able
to bring in myself and accept in in
myself changes down at the bottom to the
most beautiful
waterfall beautiful do you know what
what I believe you I know now what's
your question um oh yeah okay
question um oh yeah okay
oh there is this being that um I have
attracted into my my life many lifetimes
oh all right and there is a major focus
on this being even though I haven't um
been together with this being for quite
a while oh right and he keeps popping in
and out of my life all right major Focus
major F there is this one being and I
said right the reason I'm attracted that
being is because that was that being and
in the other time right and then this
other being comes along and I'm went boy
no I know that is finishing anywhere all
right that has got to be that being cuz
I can I can tell the Affinity is the
same is it possible that both beings are
extensions of the Same Soul right yes or
maybe even more maybe even more however
the idea isn't really to wonder who they
are but to allow yourself to discover
Who You Are by the reflections you see
in them oh I I discovered tons of things
well then the question in that sense
does not really need to be asked you
will discover what you need to discover
about the relationship when you need to
Discover it enjoy what you are
discovering about yourself about them
serve them as they serve you live in the
moment with that that's all you really
need to know I am gaining tons by living
in the moment tons of wonderful will you
be able to get out of the
chair thank you very much for your
conviction Your Enthusiasm and your
inspiration thank you very much welcome
our love to you and all the he
all of us you are welcome thank you as
well for your sharing yeah
sharing good day B sure and are you good
day uh quickly could you remind us to
the little can you hear this
individual shout out okay um I remember
listening on one of the Tes a greeting
you had that one moment one moment will
you do me a
favor yes oh thank you very much you
don't have to you know
say now talk at that
level that's not talking that's
screaming not
necessarily okay allow yourself to do
this first three
times straighten your back and now
simply speak with
conviction okay what I wanted to hear
was uh the ancient greeting that you
have mentioned um that dealt with
mentioned um that dealt with
expectation at something to the extent
of oh yes the idea that we might meet an
individual in our society long ago and
we would would say how's everything
going and they would say not as I
expected and we would say well
congratulations now you know you're on
the right path because the idea of
expectation can at times put too much
rigidity upon the reality and not allow
the surprises to come through that truly
bring the gifts of Discovery with them
so when we cease to place such heavy
expectation then we congratulated each
other so when things are not going as we
expected we knew we were allowing
ourselves to be more spontaneously
created
so they'll in a way never go as we
expect it does not mean you cannot have
expect and see it does not mean you can
not recognize what you deserve and what
you desire but the idea sometimes of
expectation especially in your Society
is to put so strong a focus so strong an
insistence upon something happening in a
certain way that you may be choking the
life out of all the other ways that
might actually have come to more easily
so the idea is to relax your demand that
they must happen in a certain way or
they won't be valid and allow it to
happen in whatever way is truly best
representative of what you are putting
out as your overall expectancy desire
understand it Blends in with the idea of
abundance yes absolutely you are
infinitely abundant right now you are
infinitely connected to all of the
universe everything you need and
everything you truly deserve to complete
you to accelerate you to expand you will
always automatically fall in front of
your face as an opportunity to act upon
to get you where you want to go always
automatically effortlessly there are so
many doorways through which your reality
could manifest that you don't
necessarily need to place the
expectation that it must happen in such
and such a way because that is focusing
on the details and when you focus on the
details overly much then you take more
time to create the reality you want more
details you add the more physical linear
space and time you need in which to
examine all the various details you are
analytically focusing on so in that
sense that definition of
expectation is that which fragments and
fractionates yourself into more and more
analytical detail believe me from our
past experience you can always continue
to add as many details to your life as
you want to it will never end You'll
Always Find Another grain of sand to
count if you want to or you can finally
allow yourself to Simply dive into the
expectancy of the experience of the
beach and live it and flow it and know
beyond the Shadow of Doubt that which
grain of sand need to stick to you will
and those that fall away you don't have
to know about it understand said go with
the flow go with the flow but do not
lose your reason it does not mean in
that sense to quote unquote surrender in
your terminology and just become a
Willow the Wisp it means that you with
Clear Sight clear conviction and clear
desire move effortlessly in the
direction of what you
prefer act effortlessly on the
opportunities that present themselves
from that Direction with full trust
knowing that the thing that excites you
the most is the thing that is most
representative of who and what you
are understand yes and the thing that
excites me the most is the
electromagnetic uh bill of the Earth the
electromagnetic field of the earth and
what do you desire to do with that
excitement well to help develop the technology that
well to help develop the technology that
you have indicated you will be sharing
ideas with us to help and what have you
done to this
point um just basically research oh all
right in what way well more in healing
applications magnetic energy oh very
good you exploring synchronized
resonance very good now allow yourself
to synchronize with the Resonance of the
Earth itself itself rather than the idea
of a single individual and you will
begin to create to build within your own
body the synchronized resonance that
will allow you to experience the
levitation in the electromagnetic field
that can occur biologically within you
understand uh I could use a little more
clar um a little more clarification
little more clarification I will simply
give you a suggestion this night
beginning this night for three nights in
a row or longer if you wish but for at
least three of your nights when you go
to sleep imagine in your mind's eye your
beautiful bright blue Earth cloaked in a
bright blue electromagnetic shell of
light spinning spinning in the Blackness
of space concentrate on the spinning the
rotational mass and allow yourself to
fall into sleep with that image and see
what equations and information you get
they may not necessarily come in what
you may call a standard format at first
but see what you wake up with all right
okay uh before I leave real quick is
there a lot of these edies that you have
indicated would help us um get an idea
of the secrets of the electromagnetic
field we have are you referring to the
idea of electromagnetic fores no the
seaweed petrified seaweed deposit that
you talked about a couple of months
ago one more
there are again as we may have mentioned
certain substances that collect in
metallic nodules on the ocean floor that
also carry within them certain
electromagnetic patterns that can render
certain Clues to the understanding of
things that your Society is now missing
about what the electromagnetic field
actually is it is a far more shall we
say solid manifestation than many of you
think a far more mechanical one than you
may think think in terms truly of an
think think in terms truly of an
electromagnetic fluid and you will be
shall we say closer to the
point study the idea of the Motions of
fluid especially what you are now
understanding to be superconductive
fluids the Motions that you will observe
the patterns the currents and those
superconductive fluids will give you a
very strong insight into what is going
on in the electromagnetic field of your
planet all right so how many of these
composes relatively do we have on the
earth there are thousands of
them some of them have been dredged up
as you say by ocean
exploration but individuals do not
necessarily know what they are looking
at and perhaps are experimenting with
them in other ways there's been some
mention of UFO craft actually uh
submarining into the waters yes in near
New Zealand is this all over your planet
are they checking out these deposits too
they are to some degree checking out
many other things most of which happen
to be electromagnetic doorways and
gateways to other dimensions some of
which simply exist below the surface of
your
ocean understand that your entire
universe is in that sense a SE seeping
and leaking into other
universes nothing in that sense is as
solid as it seems the entire fabric is
rent with
holes sometimes in your terms
accidentally you walk through them into
other universes when you create certain
harmonic resonances that are key to very high
resonances that are key to very high
vibrational pitches on the microwave
frequencies you tunnel through those
holes into other universes but that is
enough for now there's a lot to say we
thank you yes for your sharing thank
sharing
good day to
you um real okay my question is very
simple I'm very concerned about the
children of the Earth today very
concerned about the children of the
Earth today why and in what way I'm very
concerned because I see many children
that are very sad very sad all right
okay I would like to know how I could
benefit in healing that area oh thank
you very much are you are you sure you
are willing to do this yes are you
positive yes all right can you go to
these children that you say are very
sad and can you through love and example
teach them that they are powerful enough
to create the reality they desire
without hurting themselves or anyone
else yes can you do that yes is there a
particular way in which you would like
to do that I was kind of hoping you
might tell me kind of hoping
all right I'll give you a suggestion and
now this suggestion can be implemented
by as many individuals on your planet as
desire to implement it it's only a
suggestion your own imaginations will
alter this in whatever way shape or form
you see fit and that will be
correct create your version of what you
may call a primer this primer can
contain some of the basic foundational
principles you are now familiar with for
allowing individuals to understand they
are the creators of their reality it can
be in your terms non
denominational does not in any way
shaper form have to offend anyone keep
it basic keep it simple make it exciting
make it inspirational make it colorful
allow the children to want to understand
the principles give them examples to
follow to do in that sense a workbook
for children understand yes will you do that
children understand yes will you do that
it is up to you we thank you thank you
sh it
well thank you for applauding
[Applause] yourself hello bishar do you good
yourself hello bishar do you good
day last time we spoke yes you asked me
what I would like to be in my future
life what would you like to be in your
future life I asked yes and I told
someone perhaps a little bit
louder I told you a pilot in the
spaceship yes and you remarked that's
where I know you from you elaborate on
that
no anything else yes um last week I was
in Sedona and I was traveling down a
mountain and I looked up and I saw this
big purple light yes was that a figment
of my imagination or could that be a
spaceship was that a figment of Her
Imagination or could that be a spaceship
a big purple light it was in a sense a
Gateway you were seeing the energy of a
Vortex itself one of the doors of which
we already spoke you understand the end
of a tunnel so to speak how did you feel
was there any kind of a tingling in your
head um I thought see what was that and
then I oh my God that wasn't a light and
I didn't respond real quick I didn't put
my brakes on all right but as I thought
about it as I kept driving I thought
well it was something different
something different all right and while
I was there I was looking for rocks and
I looking for rocks while she was there
and I uh hurt my leg and I had about 10
pictures and I was trying
to why that happen and I was thinking
that maybe I was supposed to stay there
longer and that's why it happened one
moment only in a sense not literally the
iew simply is is that you did match
frequencies with a different Universal
vibration and so to some degree became a
little bit clumsy in the one that you
used to be used to being in you
understand yes you misstepped a little
because you are not sure of your
vibrations at that moment it is all
right you will
harmonize well one day you'll be able to
elaborate on that um where we met one
day I will be able to elaborate because
one day you will be able to
elaborate all right thank you well thank
you very much pleasant dreams to you
I'll see you there Shar
hi
M I was interested in your comments on
the opening about assuming the most
positive intentions behind another's
communication yes and I was trying to
reconcile it with the problem I have
whereby I find that people say really
positive things and mean to do things
but seem to not be able to follow
through and this recurs in my life all
the time all right so since I'm creating
my reality yes what am I doing wrong no
one said you were doing anything wrong
again remember many things are
represented by this kind of interaction
first of all an individual can attract
individuals into their life that do not
necessarily represent a high degree of
Integrity not because it is necessarily
represented of the fact that they do not
exhibit a high degree of Integrity also
but simply because it may be your
opportunity to reflect back to them how
they can exercise integrity and not
necessarily have to think they have to
get through life by exercising a lack of
Integrity in other words you could
simply function as a reflection for them
that they do not have to function that
way just because they're in your life
doesn't mean you're doing something
wrong you understand I understand but
one moment I'm not done thank you very
much now what have these kinds of
now what have these kinds of
interactions gotten you to look at
within yourself well it makes me feel like I'm
yourself well it makes me feel like I'm
unworthy unworthy all right why do you
have that button cuz I believe it why
well it's a belief Unworthy of
what um and by the way when you say well
it's a belief that doesn't mean it's a
law of the universe it means you chose
it right I understand all right Unworthy
of what of consideration and follow
through on other PE no the way I phrase
it is having my little fantasies come
through having your little fantasies
come through any particular little fantasies
through any particular little fantasies
you'd care to share or what you like to
whisper them in the Channel's
ear sure um no like I I have a simple on
like I'm going on a picnic tomorrow and
a friend was supposed to bring the
picnic and tonight they told me I was
bringing the picnic so I thought there
goes my little
fantasy stop I have something to share
with you already I have opened the
doorway very wide now this in no way
shape or form excuses other individuals
from exercising a lack of Integrity but
it is our perception that what you are
being told is to take things under your
own power there are many more things
that you could be doing that are
representative of an exercise of your
own power and you are not doing them you
are giving your power away you are
assuming that it is the responsibility
of other individuals to be responsible
for your own happiness instead of Simply
taking it upon yourself to create the
happiness you desire oh that's it thank
you thank you does that help you yes
that's it thank you very much have a
wonderful picnic with yourself now
you will Now understand that if you are
willing to take back that responsibility
and be responsible for your own
happiness in that way and not put it to
other people to create happiness for you
you will now attract a lot of other
individuals who be more than willing to
share the happiness you already know you
deserve to have in your life you
understand yes I do thank you very much
thank you
[Applause]
shanon hi Bard and good day to you
jazzed to be here jazzed
hard to
say um we went ahead and tried to launch
the uh null gravity device yes and it
was a dud dud in what way it didn't
disappear and it didn't lift off ah but
what dimension did you go
into I don't know I was basically there
basically there all the different things
that were going through your mind at
that time what did it allow you to face
what did it allow you to consider what
things did you
think oh that Bashar was a soand so he
lied all right that looks out of the way
what else connections being made with other
else connections being made with other
all right civilizations I will now allow
you to in a sense share a little secret
I am not laughing at you but we were
having a little bit of a
laugh understand the device the device
we have now discussed with you goes
nowhere I just I know it is a doorway I
know you go
somewhere well okay I just got a clue as
to what it might be go ahead it forms a
toroid in a sense which is like the
first geometric solid to to exper to
express self-awareness I understand what you
self-awareness I understand what you
mean it turns back in upon itself and
opens the gateway to another portion of
being yes very good you you are now in that
yes very good you you are now in that
sense such a choid your Consciousness is
shaped in that way the device is not
something that is a mechanical device
that simply in your terms lifts off like
a spacecraft it is an inducer it is in a
sense a folder of space and it folds
your energy into another pattern to
allow you to consider things you didn't
consider before it is a different a very
very reflective and different kind of a
mirror it is a switch to activate
gateways into other dimensions of self
because you see that ultimately is how
the spacecrafts work remember that our
spaceships quote unquote are linked to
our mentality and in a sense are only a
convenient representational symbolic
form with which we surround ourselves to
allow ourselves quote unquote to believe
that we can go into different
universes understand yeah you have now
been in inerted with the first key and
it has been turned what you will now
begin to discover is that is more a
matter of vibrational frequency this
device has simply been a key to open a
lock within you so it's how you factor
in your Consciousness yes we now suggest
that you simply understand that this
device is only a key and you begin to
explore more purely the idea from the
vibrational point of view learn about
harmonic resonance and begin to identify
the resonant frequency of different
objects and allow them to levitate by
matching their frequency in that way
much better way follow much cleaner much
simpler much much easier the mechanical
device is simply a device that folds
Consciousness it is a doorway a Gateway
now it has been opened and you are
constantly folding and refolding
yourself and opening in new ways match
that stream and see what fruit comes
forth from the unfolding of the flower
that you now are okay was was
manifesting that magnetic
electromagnetic choroidal fear field
some kind of a big event on the Earth
was it in a sense in a sense yes but for
now let's stick to the universe that you
are personally and anyone else
personally who was involved because you
are now in a sense your own Earth and
that is something I'm saying to each and
every one of you understand right now
literally as many individuals that are
partaking of this discussion this night
that's how many Earths there are right
now in this room they all a different
Earth literally whatever you think you
are sharing by Common experience you are
doing so because you agree
to you are your own Earth you now have
the opportunity to explore in the way
you wish to explore but now allow
yourself to understand it purely from a
vibrational point of view rather than a
mechanical one so to
speak super thanks thank you very
much shedding good day time to you good day
shedding good day time to you good day
um first off I want to say I am someone
that has done what if exciting me the
most and it is incredible she is someone
who has done what has excited her the
most and she finds it incredible
incredibly wonderful incredibly
wonderful feels real good feels real
good feels real good okay I want to uh
set up a short scenario all right so I
don't take up too much time but I feel
it's important to go ahead about to be
loud about it okay I will be loud thank
you thank you um back in December I
created a scenario for myself where I
was uh shot shot and in what area in my
back lower back right side that came out
in my right
um I guess breast area no all right okay
did it give you the push you needed and
then so all right you go on okay from
that as you say if you give me a push I
went from A to Z back and forth a few
times and have since then put a lot of
pieces together no understanding I
understand okay um I had always had um a
leaning a desire to be a um a desire to
be a um sorry a conduit for some sort of
channel for electrical um healing to
other people who felt they needed it oh
thank you thank you um and what has
happened recently is someone invited me
to a meeting by a woman named Louise
Hayes who is doing some wonderful things
with people who have AIDS all right and
uh similar scenarios all right um and
while I went last week before I went the
night before I made a statement to my to
all that is okay I'm going uh I'd like
to offer myself in any way I can and if
it happens it happens and I hope that
it'll be perfect work I show up they say
okay uh we have a bunch of people coming
up on stage for healings if anybody
wants to go and provide a service please
go I go up I look around I say great
this isn't anything like I feel like I
can do uh that is my way I'll put it
that way people were performing by it
was great I'm standing there going okay
what am I going to do I need to be a
little more quiet a little more
oneon-one I pull a curtain back there's
a couch I say hm okay well that's a
little more private well right I'm
waiting for people to come around that I
connect with in some way yes fortunately
there were four male individuals that I
did make contact with I'm thinking what
can I do how can I present myself and
your imagination sir my imagination sits
sit down on the couch have them turn
their back to you and proceed to hold
them right hand over the heart chakra
left hand wherever most of the time it
presented to be itself directly under
the heart chakra as well and what
happens with me is I get a very
strong uh vibration in my hand very
strong electrical current yes and
P very strong my heart pound it lasts
however long that the person needs it I
guess yes whatever yes and then I took
my right hand and put it on their
forehead which I was I heard a couple
days later was Che chair area where a
lot of healing uh energy comes through
all right um in any event yes I was so
happy oh thank you and that night I had
a dream and this is where I I would like
some clarification
you the dream was not your what I call
our everyday dreams where we know
they're they're symbolic of lots of
things and then we think about them
later all right what was it it was um a
lucid dream all right lucid dream a
dream where you know you're dreaming
right uh it was a sort of brown a
brownish gold it was brownish gold it
almost looked like um uh candle light
handled like there were two beings that
I was looking at one two one two one
said to the one in front he whispered
something to him and in essence the
vibration I felt was that he was saying
to the one in front she's come to help
you now this being in
front was like hearing the weight of the
world on him it was like the vibration
of Aid he was eaten was trying all good
to get very and it was coming toward me
but it smiled with all the love and Beed
of love very good but the closer it got
to me I wasn't afraid of it but its
appearance Disturbed me so much that I
woke up that's what I'd like for you to
elaborate thank you very much you are
and your ter is very accurate you were
in contact with what we can call the
template of the IDE idea of that disease
and you made a difference you were
willing to present yourself present your
case present your energy present your
gift you are willing to share you are
willing to make a change to allow a
change to occur and in that sense you
have already made a change therefore it
is now easier From This Moment forward
from that moment forward the moment of
the green it is now easier for
individuals to love themselves back to
health from any disease you understand
you touched the template the template of
the idea in your Collective
Consciousness that is disease and you
allowed it to be loved and you in that
sense therefore allowed it to be easier
for individuals to love themselves and
therefore no longer need to manifest
their Creation in the form of disease
you understand we thank you thank you
one short thing where one short thing
where are up
Ahad um where the bullet entered and
where exed I have Since U had sort of a
pulling sensation however after I I had
this electrical centering between the
people myself yes where the bullet has
exited all the way up to today that's
been almost a week yes does not hurt yes
the other parts
still not hurt yeah the idea is that you
are in touch with the hard energy and
you are using that to heal but remember
the idea of any healing will always
usually work backwards from the latest
to the first you understand yes I do and
that is where in the seed of your spine
the most energy is to be released from
anyway you
understand you are going to assimilate
just fine allow yourself to continue to
love yourself in that way and let the
universe love you and nurture you in
that s back to the balanced state of
your natural healthy self well thank you
very much and I love you we love you as
well people thank you for your
boldness and for allowing yourself to
take off like a
shot and you as
well this I you may all enjoy a short
break we will resume contact in this
fashion in approximately 10 to 15 of
your minutes of pound a
[Applause] [Music]
all right say before we
continue since those that are familiar
with us
know how much our civilization
enjoys things that come in
three I will now simply allow you to
know that this particular format of
interaction shall occur but three more
times once in your October month once in
your November month month once in your
December month and that shall be in your
terminology the conclusion of this
format from that point forward there
will be be
Endeavors
projects that will be suggested through
what you may call the writing format or
different project formats there will be
in a sense a network that will be
established for intercommunication among
people who are excited about doing what excites
who are excited about doing what excites
them and do
it and slowly over what you may call
time an establishment of all those
individuals performing those things that
are very excited will be melded and
welded into a particular Network that
will allow each and every one of you to
gather strength from the central Hub of
that Network through information itself
we will discuss this idea more later on
in one of the upcoming threee
remaining sessions but now is the time as has
sessions but now is the time as has
already been talked about this your year
you are in your year of transformation
itself year of doing in that
sense the year of being what you have
spent so long in
becoming the year of action the year of
change the year of transformation of all
that you knew into all that you desire
this is the balance and the Crux the
double infinity symbol in your Society
of
88 the idea now that you are truly at
the crossroads hence the understanding
we spoke of of the limbo State the
Central State the state of the present
power around which shall we simply say
orbits all possible realities make your
choice act upon those choices now is the
act upon those choices now is the
fter create what you call the future you
desire from the
now there is really nothing that I could
say in that sense that could inspire
you I can send out
vibrations that if you were to match
those vibrations would allow you to
inspire yourselves to truly act to know
that if you did act in the direction of
what excites you the most you would have
the reality you
desire guarantee but I cannot convince you of
guarantee but I cannot convince you of
this I cannot force this idea upon you
but now this entire year this entire
orbit of your world around your central
star is for that recognition and that
realization this entire year the entire
orbit the entire
circuit is the limbo orbit the limbo
State the point present power
use it act upon it great momentum is
there nothing is at a standstill it is
going infinitely
fast but not in any way shape or form
beyond your control never has been is
not now and never will
be ingrain this knowledge within you so
that it is in your term second hand so
that you know it because you use it
and it shall become second nature to you
all for it is actually your first nature
to be creators in that
[Applause] way three more times in this fashion is
way three more times in this fashion is
all that is necessary from our part in
this way to generate the necessary
reflection and momentum to allow you to
draw from what has already been given
for all the tools are there use them as
an entire kit forgetting not one part
when you consider another
but consider them all together every
time you think of applying them apply
them all to every situation
situation
remember your memory is created in the
present know what you need to know when
you need to know it because you choose
to and act accordingly you live in the
moment you always will you always have
and you do so right
now at this tile I in let us continue in
the present Manner and the continuation
of
sharing good even sh and to
you good day it's wonderful to be here
yes transformational one
[Music] um yes yes yes um it's it's sort of
um yes yes yes um it's it's sort of
difficult to explain but um basically in
my life I've been able to manifest some
incredible things I'm I'm so happy about
a lot of things in my life one thing
troubles me a little one thing troubles
her a little and that is um oh oh before
you continue before you continue may I
may I thank you do you remember what
number you were this evening 13 yes you
were the transformational number
13 right now that should start you off
okay well I feel like I'm being
transformed every moment well gu you are
transforming yourself every moment
remember you are the warrior and you do
nothing that is not done boldly this is
true yes um what I've noticed recently
is is that um I don't have a
relationship in my life in terms of a
physical relationship I have a lot of
friends I assume you are referring to a
particular being precisely I do have my primary
being precisely I do have my primary
relationship which I'm uh expressing
fully all right as fully as I can yes um
but I find myself and I I hate to say
picky picky but um I find myself unable
to really get into just any physical
relationship and not be able to find one
that I really feel nurtures um a part of
me that I've I've come to know which
part of you do you feel is not being
nurtured um well it's not that it's not
being nurtured because I do feel very
complete um I just like to be able to
share a physical um
sort of a an exchange with with a bean
because I learned so much about myself
all right well go ahead and pick someone
and share well now well it's not that
easy and it's not that easy oh all right
here come the rules go
ahead what came up on that big
Blackboard you have it's not that easy
well it's just that I've really honed in
on exactly what I want oh exactly what
do you want what qualities do you want
um someone that's very sensitive
understand someone that's very sensitive
and understanding has an understanding
of metaphysics an understanding of
metaphysics and wants to grow in that
area wants to grow in that area capable
of unconditional love capable of
unconditional love um who would possibly
not be um intimidated by my need for
time and space not be in intimidated by
your what need for time and space need
for time and space you mean in that
sense someone who will allow you to be
creative in your own way precisely all
right so you fix me up with an alien of something
now what are you doing tomorrow night
[Laughter] [Applause]
[Applause]
I'll be waiting I'll be waiting One
Moment One Moment don't want you to
wait so I'll make a few suggestions if I
may do you understand something however
that you are in a relationship right now
with me right now because this
conversation is going on I do as a
matter of fact right I've written some
songs to you and about me thank you and
um we've written a few to you thank you
so much thank you one moment before you
go on now do you understand that in that
sense nurturing of the self and joy that
you see comes from giving those
qualities you seek in someone else to
someone else yes I do and I I feel that
I've been able to do that I mean I I
I've become I've become closer to a lot
of my male friends ever all right but
not physical even to the point where you
know even if I were interested 3 months
ago for some reason it's on a different
level all right stop stop stop
stop is there just asking an image a
representation in your imagination of a
particular person that well I'll put it
this way you have quote unquote
fantasized about being in a relationship
with that perhaps you do not necessarily
think is someone who would how do you
say it give you the time of
day uh I I'm I'm I'm sure there you have
to name names I'm sure that there is
someone out there and yeah I have
thought about what um my perfect
reflection would be all right is there
in your imagination in what you may call
your fantasy anyone that does to some
degree symbolize it in my um phys
physical world now yes someone that you
know of perhaps in your terminology
someone that you may call quote unquote
famous someone well known that you have
been using in a sense
to act as a placeholder in that
fantasy not well not well not really I
there are certain things I admire and
respect about certain people but I know
that since I don't really know them as a
person I don't really give them that
much power you know I mean I might well
you're not saying you have to give them
your power no no but I mean I don't say
oh if I could only have Christopher walk
and I'd be happy you know I don't say
that to myself cuz I don't know what
this person is really like I know what
he looks like but you see this is the
point is that if there is someone that
is symbolic that is being utilized
within your imagination that actually
does represent what you think you want
why not find out what that person is
like I could do that could you might be
difficult might be difficult sounds
like the idea of the person that I want
to have a relationship with simply
because of who they are it can't be that
easy they can't can't be in a
relationship with me that way are you
discounting it because of those ideas no
I just don't think that you know I'm
going to meet Peter Gabriel why not why
not who are they why not what makes them
so different in that sense from you well
may I ask you a question sure are you of
their vibration I feel I am then why
wouldn't you be able to meet them if
you're in the same universe if you're in
the same Universal frequency what would
prevent you from running into each other
synchronistically actually that's true I
guess I could visualize meeting them at
a party or whatever all right now I'm
not saying you have to fix it and I'm
not saying that you necessarily have to
be that specific you could use that kind
of a
fantasization as a key to orient you to
a particular frequency but you can also
simply know that you are of a particular
frequency of a particular shall we say
genre and therefore you do belong and I
do not mean this exclusively in terms of
excluding anyone else but you do belong
to a particular Club just as anyone who
is of a particular frequency belongs to
the club of everyone else of that
particular frequency if you're simply
functioning on that level those are the
people you meet yeah understand but but
but but but but but but but but but but
but but to use one of your language's
favorite words but but but but but but
if you are of the frequency definition
the frequency equation that says I would
like to think I'm of that frequency but
I don't really think I am then that's
why you're where you are well I mean I'm
not really in that much of a hurry I
mean I know you don't have to backtrack
no I mean it's not a desperate situation
I understand it is not a desperate
situation however and like myself I know
you like yourself I like you too but we
are simply answering your question in a
very direct way it is our perception
simply our
perception that you may be creating a
bit of a discount of the images you do
have simply because somewhere in some
level of your Consciousness you do not
necessarily truly think yourself equal
to certain other individuals that you
may actually find quite exhilarating to
interact with in a natural and quote
unquote normal way yeah it's funny I can
do that in my career I'm I feel equal to
every opportunity that comes you know my
way why is this phase of your life not a
part of who and what you are I don't
know maybe I feel like they can't be
inclusive of one another you know I is
that well yes it's very possible to see
a bad way but why should you choose to
create it that way why should you choose
to believe that it is mutually exclusive
maybe I don't trust that I could bance
oh maybe maybe you think you'll chase
them away by swinging your sword around
and you think it is very difficult for
someone in my life to be unconditionally
loving of me when I have such a big
sword swing maybe you think that I do all
swing maybe you think that I do all
right
will allow yourself to understand that
if you want someone to Parry with you'll
find it but at the same time you can
find someone you can attract someone who
understands that all the parrying is
simply for the purpose of learning and
it doesn't have to be in an
argumentative fashion it can be quite
exhilarating quite exciting quite
enjoyable in that way simply allow
yourself to understand that you are not
excluded from any level whatever the
vibration is that you are willing to
totally be will attract the idea of
counterpart Reflections to interact with
you and reflect to you who and what you
are but first you must be bold enough to
be willing to be all that you know you
are and not be afraid that your self
your true self will make it impossible
for someone to relate to you well I'm
really close all right I understand that
I going to say something now that is not
meant as a chastisement and not meant
derogatorily but to think that Who You
Are in that sense would be so different
that no one could possibly relate to you
as a bitty gistic yeah all right allow
yourself to let those other individuals
in by knowing beyond the shadow of a
doubt that no matter how bold you are
there will always be someone to match
you always and at the same time you are
a match for some of those individuals
you don't think are equal to understand
very well all right then thank you very
much thank you forar and
congratulations
sh hello B and are you good day I would
like to ask you your concept of music
music is it uh the universal language as
they say more in a sense because
everything is vibration and therefore
what you call music or the expression of
harmonic tonality vibrational tonality
is one of the ways that you can shall we
say interpret the vibrations of creation and
interpret the vibrations of creation and
all of the shall we say mathematical
rhythmic patterns that are reflective of
different discrete Universal realities
within the overall vibration of all that
is in that sense yes you could say say
it is universal language but more
specifically vibration itself is the
language how you pattern it what is
music to your ears what is music to my
ears can be vastly
different understand yes the ID in our
society at this time is generally
expressed in a relatively simplistic way
I think you would put it we have very
little instrumentation at this time
sometimes there are voices that are used
spontaneously the instruments that are
left in our society are simply very
simple string very simple percussion a
few the idea of wind instruments mostly
the idea of what you would call tonal
Bell structures of a spherical nature
and some of a linear nature mostly this
we now have Although our spacecraft in a
sense can be said to be musical
instruments since they resonate at
harmonic frequencies that represent the
vibration that is used to tunnel from
one dimension to another and when those
craft give off those frequencies when
they surround themselves with that
harmonic resonance field it can set up
from time to time in the atmosphere of a
particular World a most
mous harmonic frequency that in itself
is a type of music the music of the
interface of one dimension or shall we
say in all reality all Dimensions with
all other dimensions and that is most
moving moving that are in a sense within
our reality shall we say now I'm using
this term very Loosely
concerts that are Witness by many
individuals and these concerts are given
by the ships themselves remember that
the Consciousness the shall we say
computers that drive the ships are
intelligent are self-aware are conscious
and in that sense sometimes we'll simply
give off a Radiance a frequency that all
beat around can enjoy the ships will
play themselves and we enjoy that most
hardly you understand yes does that
answer some of the specific ideas of
Music how about the uh the people do
they make the music or adjust your
spaceship no no no as we have said the
idea that there are string and
percussion instruments these are used
spontaneously by the people but also
simply the voice is one way as it is
upon your planet sometimes there are a
few individuals a few individuals in our
society that simply will give in a sense
energy concerts they will stand or sit
in one place and they will create a
resonant frequency similar to the ships
and will give off a particular series of
harmonics that in and of itself is a
type of music and we can listen to that
as well it is also a communication this
is usually done when communicating with
specific entities in another dimensional
realm those entities that you call Kina
energies on your planet we talk to them
by in a sense creating a type of energy
electromagnetic hum by accelerating the
frequency of our corporeal bodily forms
to a certain pitch and when all the
cellular structure the atomic structure
is harmonized it gives off a certain
Radiance a certain frequency that is a
direct carrier wave to that internal
dimension in which those other
non-physical beings reside but there are
residues that are given off in our
atmosphere that sound to some degree
like music does that help you yes thank
you thank you very much
sharing sh and hello to you hi it's been
very exciting last eight months I've
been having with the metaphysical World
last 8 months very
exciting allow them to believe it by
sounding excited very excited oh thank
you very much um I've had very very
exciting experiences um goes with being
excited yes uh with having past life
experience rights uh going to Indian powow power
rights uh going to Indian powow power
wow all right yes
um sharing
um
my
getting just a lot of things getting
through a lot of things all right
that's a keep very exciting I am doing
so because they cannot hear you this is
the only reason I am repeating any of
you I'll speak up thank you okay I've
um took it upon myself
to uh take some advice of friend and
Bashar on exercising my more of my right
side my male side all right and what
happened and I met Whitley striver all
right okay and um I'm an actress and I
uh spoke with him about being in one of
his movies all right man okay um I
thought that this was going to extend my
acting but I learned that it was to just
for my own being to know that I can
approach someone build your confidence
build my confidence which is extending
your acting exactly okay um I went away
on a trip
and I had a wonderful time in Sedona and
in Arizona I came back and I felt like I
was back in this like box this cubicle
once again once again dealing with this
reality of of of facing trying to find
work all all right and I feel very
closed in and what I feel like I'm
looking for an
agent and I feel like I've been looking
for the last 100 years oh One Moment One
Moment some of these people are thinking
look under a rock great that's exactly
my feeling I mean I I I know they're out
there but I feel that I don't have
enough confidence to go find one and may
I ask a question well than you very much
why do you need
one everyone says I need one everyone I
know producers and I'm in the business I
know directors see one moment I must
check on something do you mind check did
everyone in this room say she needed
one then I guess everyone didn't say it
there are a few people who didn't say it
what do you mean you said everyone says
I need one well there are some
individuals here that didn't say it so
it can't be everyone said
it do you mind if I tease you a little
bit no I like it
oh thank you very much I have several
you
know I've noticed thank you so do you
you know yes what is acting after all
except absolute belief in another of
your personalities
yeah what's that have to do with going
into what it has to do with is that one
of your personalities is also an agent
and it takes an agent to know
one so why don't you be an agent and
attract an agent if that's what too hard
when I go out and find when I've gone
out on interviews yes I can't believe
the people I am facing they should not
even be in the business I see okay I
feel like I can do a better job and at
Time One Moment One Moment One Moment oh
you are so very honest say that again I
feel I could do a better job yes yes
then what do you need an agent for if
you can do a better doin Bank hand
because when I came up
against against a part came up against a
part okay when I had the opportunity to
uh help a r in a heart um it came to the
point of getting the wrong reading for
the wrong part reading for the wrong
part okay so I felt if I had had an
agent yes that they could have called up
and said look she's reading for the
wrong part and Willie striver said this
was the part she should be reading for
and and why could you not have said the
same thing because it would have been it
had wouldn't have been protocol I beg
your par it would have not been
appropriate for may I ask you a question
I think that's where I draw the line all
right all right it's your line to draw
but you won't get Beyond it as long as
it's there now the question I would like to
there now the question I would like to
ask if I may
yeah it seems sort of shall I say a
little bit of an odd thing to be
thinking so strongly about such a thing
as
protocol when you're talking about
playing a part in a movie that
represents the meeting between a human
and an alien which half of your world
doesn't even believe is
possible where's the protocol in fact I
believe in that well all bets are off
then you decide where the protocol is
there doesn't have to be any sort of
protocol in this issue at all what needs
to be needs to to be where it fits it
fits who you are determines where you
wind up speak up for yourself if you
don't believe that you have placed
yourself in the proper representative
frequency Place yourself where you
believe you belong be your own
voice understand yes and I feel like I
have been but I
feel yes I don't know I just feel like
things are stopping me and I get
frustrated frustrated all right all
right all right
one
moment someone wants me to ask you a
question and if someone wants me to
ask the part that you believe you were
correct for what do you believe you would have
for what do you believe you would have
discovered by playing that part
that I have the ability to play the part
maybe nothing more than that what do you
believe you would have discovered about
yourself by playing that part in being
that person for the time you are playing
the part would you not discover the same
things that that person
discovered but for yourself in your own
way do you understand the question that
is being
asked you are being asked to play a part
in a film one must assume that the
character you are playing is going to
discover certain things about themself
in that role you understand yes now if
you are for the moment being that person
what as that person would it be that you
would be discovering as that role
unfolds what does that character
discover um I think through her rage
maybe confused
of what's going on with her life she
discovers uh self selfworth self-discovery knowing
uh self selfworth self-discovery knowing
that it's okay what she's going through
is is simply all right I I don't know
I'm not I I didn't get to read the whole
script so I I'm not sure what the
character it was a there of a group
discussion all right one moment
the question I am now being asked to ask
is if in your terminology this situation
had happened to you in quote unquote
real life your own life how do you think
you would have
felt would you have to put it again in
your vernacular been able to handle it no why
not um because I'm experiencing a lot of
things I mean I experienc spaceships
over my apartment that freak me out
freak you out so I am not willing to
accept all that yet do I freak you out
no I like you all right why do they
freak you out I am being asked to ask
okay the Unknowing One Moment One Moment
they have something else to say are you
ready ready
who are you
scared no why not cuz you're amusing me
I'm amusing you all right why do they
not amuse you I am being asked to
ask because of the unknown what is
unknown well I don't know if the
reticulum or plaing or I so what are
they friends I don't know you don't know
do you decide that you will only attract
those that are I suppose if they're over
my apartment they're friends you suppose
do you know it but I don't know how to
get rid of the fear I I understand that
they're friends I all right one moment
we'll get to that in a moment however
let us backtrack for a second and simply
explain that if you are not ready to to
live that role you certainly are not
ready to play that role you understand
yes all right
now do you believe you have a need to
attract anyone in your life of that
nature that would be other than a
friend no I don't have the need to
attract anyone that wouldn't be a friend
do you have the desire to attract anyone
who wouldn't be a friend no
then why does it matter that they are
unknown the specifics do they have in
order to Simply know in the overall
sense that you have decided to only
attract those that would ultimately be
friends you just opened up
another thank you very much it's you
I've been experiencing producers that
I've known that are doing movies right now
known that are doing movies right now
and I feel like they're not being a
friend to me by letting me read well
it's not that they're not letting me
read for something but I they won't when
they say they'll be there they won't be
there when they say they call me in I
feel like they're honest all right U and
personally I don't know if they're my
friends stop remember this it is believing is
stop remember this it is believing is
seeing not the other way around if
that's the reality you're getting you
went into the interaction with the
belief that that would be the most
likely reality you would attract you're
only reinforcing your belief by
attracting the reality you believe to be
most likely and then you are using those
situations to reinforce the belief you
already had and simply say see I told
you so this is all you get and
perpetuate a cycle you don't like break
the cycle by knowing that the situation
occurred to show you not the stuck with
that reality but simply that you went in
with that belief and therefore that's
what you got if you don't prefer it
redesign the belief and go in with that
with full conviction but you're not
going in with full conviction as long as
you are afraid of the
unknown you
understand if you redesign a reality
that you prefer and yet you seem still
not to get the result of that reality
it's because you're not applying that
belief by fully believing in it
when you still fear the new reality
because you fear the unknown you are
still buying into the old reality and
giving it your power you're saying it is
more likely that the unknown will
produce something distasteful and
unpleasant than something joyful and
sweet how can I
become friends with the unknowing I mean
how how can I feel comfortable how can
what steps can I take
[Applause]
friends with the unknown friends with
the unknown the fact that you have even
mentioned that there could be such a
concept shows that it really isn't that
foreign to you does it not you have
considered the notion I could be friends
with the unknown now if that were really
not the most likely reality why would
you even think it might be
possible why would you prefer it if that
were not the most likely reality is that
the reality you
prefer is that the reality that excites
you the most no I I prefer it to be
known no no no no no no no no listen
listen listen do you prefer to be in your terms
listen do you prefer to be in your terms
scared of the unknown or friends with
the unknown no I prefer to be friends
friends with the unknown all right
do you like what you call in your
world holidays I love holidays birthdays
and Christmas yes do you like getting
Christmas yes do you like getting
presents of course of course do you know
what I'm leading up to no I don't if I
were to hand you a present since you
seem to enjoy me so much and you were so
delighted that I had given you this
present and I said open this on your birthday
and I said open this on your birthday
and you will have a wonderful surprise
and your birthday will say all 3 days
away would you not have a thrilling and
exciting time enjoying the anticipation
of waiting till your birthday to open
that up and find out what was in that
presence yes and I know what you and if
someone were to sneak up to you on the
second day and say it's a such and such
would you not say you ruined my surprise
you made what was unknown no known to me
before I desired it to be
known I now have no joy of Discovery no
Thrill of the interaction the way it was
intended to be do you understand yes the
idea is to understand that you do know
what you need to know when you need to
know it you know everything you need to
know to be who you are but the
specifics that are unknown are are
simply for the purpose of allowing
yourself your whole self to be known
through the energy through the mechanism
of
self-discovery through
Revelation that is the mechanism of
growth if you in that sense simply quote
unquote knew it all in the way you are
implying you want to you would have no
need to be here no reason to be here no
reason to experience the joys to
savor the Ecstasy of this particular
reality in this way you simply assuming
that the term unknown must be a negative
and not allowing yourself the delicious
anticipation of self-discovery that
comes with the timing of the gift that
you are giving to yourself in the way
you're doing
it comprehend yes Delight in your
timing Delight in the surprises that you
give yourself nothing is to be feared
you're only going to discover more of
yourself and this is the way you have
chosen to do it even what you call a
master Delights in the simplest
surprises because that is life because
life is always growing that's the
Paradox creation
exists it all exists and yet at the same
time it it is being created a new
ongoing forever it will never all be
complete in that sense and yet it is all
complete within itself a paradox that
may be but that's the way it
is do you
understand yes I understand are you
having a good
time did you know I was going to say
this no are you having a good time
somewhat somewhat I'm getting there
getting there where is it there there
how far how many days how many miles how
many steps
away and if I may ask when you get there
won't it still be here no I'll be there
when I get there it
will are you now having fun yes are you
now teasing me yes
are you delighting in that definitely
well thank you very
much thank you very much Bashar by the
way yes they love
yes they love
you whether You' got the part or not
they love you thank you and they know
that you are learning what you want to
learn and they are helping you
understand just because it's not quote
unquote in the movie you're are still
playing a part in the unfolding drama of
that entire interaction you understand
yes I know that now thank
you action we find you thank
action we find you thank
you act this timing allow us now to roll
the credits as it were we thank you for
the expression of your sharing and we
remind you from many
consciousnesses do not be afraid to go
in the
ocean do not fear the waves of your
reality they carry you to places that
may seem
Uncharted but when you land treasure
will always be found fear not the depths
of your ocean for in the ocean swim
happy beings
happy hearts and happy Minds you are all
an ocean of
souls swim in the dream of the reality
you desire all of our
desire all of our
personalties from all aspects of the
overs soul that we are sends you love
and light and greetings our love to you
all and a fun good day [Music]
how'd it go great
thank you all very much for coming and
enduring the uh summer
heat it's all supposed to be perfect
isn't
it if you like a copy of tonight's tape
you can have it tonight you see Pamela
was back there making