I say how are you all this evening of
your time as you create time to
exist allow us to begin this interaction
this evening of your time with the
entitlement cleansing flame this idea
that we have entitled cleansing flame is
a reference to the idea of the deep
emotionality that many of you feel many
times which manifests in the format you
call anger the idea of your anger can be
used in a positive way as a cleansing
flame to align you to orient you to
strengthen you and allow you to begin to
learn to act with true deliberateness in
your life for this is a very strong key
and a critical key in terms of creating
the realities that you want the
realities that you prefer the act of
deliberateness utilizing this cleansing
flame is to allow you the opportunity to
see where you stand relative to all the
different kinds of events all the
different kinds of realities that you
perceive all around you in your daily
life your daily World your daily
civilizational experiences these ideas
these perspectives you're seeing what
other people are doing you relating to
them you deciding from what you see in
them as to who you are what you are and
sometimes most importantly in seeing
what they are seeing what you are not
can help you really align the idea of
deliberateness in your life to truly act
out as we discussed last week of your
time truly act out the reality that you
prefer to be well cannot in your
terminology stress enough the whole
notion as we discussed last week of your
time of acting out your imagination
acting out your dreams physically
physicalizing acting out setting up the
props creating a physical picture seeing
yourself in that reality setting up the
props going through the motions playing
it out saying the lines doing the part
acting it out to really lock in the
physical reality to acquire the new
habit ual rituals that are more
representative of the realities you
prefer this acting out is critical to
allow you to take your imagination your
non-physical imagination and truly
physicalize it as you say bring it down
to earth to lock it in to your
neurological system so that you now act
differently than you used to so that in
acting differently you will attract
different things things that are more
representative of the new you that you
prefer to be rather than the old you you
no longer prefer to be this is a true
physics equation a true mechanical act
and it is something that will allow you
to really transform from one style of
living to another style of living and in
changing that attitude in changing that
approach you change everything you
experience in life because as we have
said many times all circumstances and
situations come into your life
fundamentally neutral and can go either
way positive or negative depending upon
the type of person you create yourself
to be utterly determines the type of
effect you get out of those neutral
situations and circumstances that you
attract in your life
the cleansing Flame the act of alignment
the act of self-awareness
self-recognition who you are what you
prefer to be sometimes because your
Society has been used to exhibiting its
emotionality in negative terms that does
not mean you cannot turn it around in a
very simple way in a very easy way and
allow it to work for you in a positive
sense you do not have to feel victimized
by your negative emotions you can turn
them around they are in that sense also
simply props they are only reactions to
things you believe to be true that is
what emotions are reactions to things
you already buy into definitions you
have bought into for your entire
lifespan and sometimes for many
lifespans you can use your emotions if
you find them coming up in a negative
way you can still use them you can give
them vent you can give them free reign
not in a way that damages you not in a
way that damages other individuals but
in a truly creative way as a brush as an
artistic Implement as a device to paint
the picture you truly desire to burn
with conviction to burn with resolution
to burn with deliberateness and see very
clearly in your mind's eye in your
imagination the you you prefer to be if
you find yourself in circumstances and
situations in your life where you feel
angry that you do not have what you
really believe you deserve to have use
that anger clarify yourself with it let
it burn through you allow yourself to
take that anger and allow yourself
perhaps in what you may call a remote
location so you may not perhaps disturb
other individuals yell it out at the top
of your lungs give voice give vent it is
similar to the idea of acting out your
dreams take it and give it voice stand
on a cliff toop perhaps overlooking one
of your oceans and allow yourself to
build up all the anger all the
frustration all the guilt All the Rage
that you have bought into for your life
and give it voice give it vent air it in
that sense give it to the universe
acknowledge that it is yours acknowledge
that you own it and in acknowledging it
give it voice so that the universe may
see that you are owning it that you are
willing to display it in that sense that
you are willing to know it is a part of
you it is a valid piece of you a valid
portion of your overall energy expressed
in a certain way and it is a statement a
statement as you say a Manifesto giving
vent just in a long idea a long noise a
long scream a cry let it release in
tears for that in many ways is a prayer
the idea of letting it come out in a
full and strong voice in the same manner
that you did as a child when you
screamed the idea of what it is you
needed when you announced your presence
in that way with the full conviction of
your lungs let it come out and be a
child in the hands of the universe that
way you are not giving up control by
doing that but you are in a sense
allowing yourself to truly ride the ways
of universal creation so that control in
your life will then be effortless from
that point forward remember we have
talked about the idea many times that
the only reason many of you feel that
quote unquote surrendering to the flow
of your life is losing control is
because most of you are used to the idea
of control coming with resistance and
therefore when things flow effortlessly
in your life you don't think you're in
control but in fact when you go with
that flow when you really be who you are
and give it voice and conviction your
life becomes effortless in that way when
you express yourself to the fullest idea
your life becomes effortless in that way
and it may feel as if you no longer have
control it may feel as if the universe
is doing it for you but in fact you are
doing it you are fully in control just
so effortlessly that you do not
necessarily equate it to the idea of
control give voice to that cleansing
flame Let It Burn through you let it
unite everything within you because you
see when you do that when you create
that tonality when you in that sense cry
to the heavens cry out loud reverberate
to the Earth you are creating a tonal
pattern a true acceleration of the
electromagnetic energy out of which your
physical form is made and as you ring
with that tone as you cry out in that
way as you give full voice to the
heavens and the Earth you create a
pattern a vibratory pattern that aligns
your entire cellular structure your
entire molecular structure you vibrate
with the idea of who you are you are
willing to express the conviction of who
you are you are willing to announce
yourself to the universe and take full
responsibility for the you you chose
supposed to be you are in that sense
willing to take responsibility for being
the fullest you you possibly can be and
when you do that when you release in
that way that cleansing flame you will
know yourself as lighter you will in
that sense allow everything that could
come to you in your reality to be
lighter and to come to you faster more
quickly in a more accelerated manner you
are turning on your own Inner Light you
are shining you are being willing to
shine as the beacon that you are as the
reflective mirror that you are as the
love light out of which you were created
we realize at this timing that much of
the information we are sharing with you
at this particular moment may seem to be
coming at an accelerated rate the idea
is to understand that you are absorbing
all this information on whatever level
you need to we are not in this sense
allowing the information to come through
at this accelerated rate because we wish
you to miss anything at all you are
missing nothing we are doing this on
purpose at this time because most of you
understand this is not our normal rate
of delivery but we are doing it this way
at this time so that your analytical
mind will not have quite as much to
grasp onto so that you will be listening
with your intuitive levels and with each
and every laugh you open up more doors
that allows you to relax into the
assurance that each and every one of you
is truly a flame of creation and that
each and every one of you is a facet of
unconditional love and deserv ability
and deservingness each and every one of you
deservingness each and every one of you
is a light in the eye of the infinite
each and every one of you is an IE of
the infinite acceleration is the key the
infinite acceleration is the key the
conviction that burns within you no
longer do you have to fear to give it
voice no longer do you have to fear to
be who you know you are who you have
always known you
were no longer do you have to judge
yourself nor accept the judgments of
others in that sense as long as you
know as long as you know
that you are doing the best you can with
all the Integrity you believe is at your
disposal if you know you are powerful
enough to create whatever you want
without having to hurt anyone else or
yourself in order to do that then act in
whatever manner you find appropriate for
you are not doing harm in that sense and
if for any reason you slip out of your
integrity in what you would term an
accidental fashion an unconscious
fashion then know beyond a shadow of a
doubt that you will create the
individuals or the circumstances to
remind you that you have done so and so
you still have a governing system and
you don't have to watch yourself so
closely every step you take you don't
have to it is not required that you
place such a guard upon yourself you are
co-creators with the infinite You Were
Meant to create in a flee flowing way
allow yourself that opportunity allow
yourself to feel that flow you deserve
it it is what you are made of you
deserve nothing less and the universe
the infinite the all that is at any time
never never was a decreed that you must
function as less than you are as less
than you can imagine yourselves to be
your imagination is the key what you can
conceive you can be that's why you can
conceive it you're not capable of
conceiving something that you cannot be
the universe does not work that way it
would not be so cruel it would not be so
pointless it would not be so extraneous
it does not work that
way if you can imagine it that's who you
are be it act like it be the cleansing
flame be the flame of conviction burn as
bright as you can you will never burn
out never you will never burn out you
are infinite and eternal for that is the
nature of all that is and you are
extensions of all that is along with
every being in creation you are made of
creation itself we thank
we thank
you for allowing us to carry on
so but we simply wish to impart to you
that once again no matter what you have
chosen choose now or will ever choose to
think of yourselves we know you can
create the realities you desire we have
absolute faith in you that isn't one
single shred of doubt in our minds about
what you are capable of doing not
one we do not stop and think about it
for a moment we know the type of world
you can create we see with the changes
that are going on in your civilization
the type of world you seem to be headed
for in terms of your desire for peace
and Harmony it is our perception that
you are creating that world although now
you are going through the last vestiges
of your old negativity getting it all
out of your system bringing it all up to
the surface appearing to be more violent
more escalation of negativity but you
are getting it all out of your system
that is our perspective we choose we
choose to
believe that you are headed for Harmony
and peace if we did not perceive that to be
peace if we did not perceive that to be
so if we did not believe that we would
be interacting with you in a short time
on an equal level as co-creators and
Harmony and love in all likelihood these
conversations would not be going on your
civilization's vibration would be far
too unlike our civilization's vibrations
for us to be able to interact for you
cannot experience what you are not the
vibration of all vibrations attract the reality
of all vibrations attract the reality
that is indicative and representative of
who and what you believe yourself to be
that is why conviction is so critical
you always have it you always have trust
you always have conviction I there has
never been a second when you have never
had it remember once again that your
civilization defines doubt as a lack of
trust we do not Define it that way we
Define doubt as a trust in the
negative allow yourself to remember
therefore that you have always trusted
in
something it is now up to you to decide
whether or not you wish to trust in the
positive or continue to trust in the
negative in the negative definitions
those definitions that say it must be so
it has to be this way because that's the
way it is that's the way it's always
been those are simply beliefs they are
your definitions you have created them
you can change them we know you can
because you always do when it suits
you let it suit you to create peace upon
your planet now there is much
acceleration going on there are many
more opportunities coming up for our
civilizations to begin to more blatantly
interact with your civilizations but we
do not tell you this because it is
necessary that we interact with you we
tell you this simply because because it
is our perception that you are creating
the type of world that would make it
more conducive for us to be able to
interact with
you your world for you is first do not
run from it you chose to be born on your
planet you chose to be alive on your
world not so that when you recognize the
idea of the power of what you call the
Heavens to run away from your planet but
to bring that power down to your planet
to create literally your heaven on Earth
that is your service in your
transformational age and that is why
each and every one of you is a flame so
as brightly as you burn will you then
create a beacon that others can see and
reflect back to you in the mirror that
each and every one of you
is we thank you for opening your
doorways we thank you for your
invitations we accept them gladly to
interact with you we thank you for the
gift of your sharing for it is truly a
gift to us we thank you for your
conviction for the you you already have
chosen to be and for the you you will
choose to be in what you may call your
future our deepest and unconditional
love is always sent to you all your
imagination may make use of that energy
in any way shape or form it so desires
it is up to you it is
unconditionally sent
unconditionally in return for this gift
you have given us in return for
functioning as a ambassadors and
representatives of your society and for
allowing me to function as an ambassador
of my respective
societies I ask you now in what way may
I be of service to
you B and you good day my name is Sandy
speak up so that all may share okay
within a period of three months I had
three experiences can you all hear this
individual adequately and if this was not a dream
adequately and if this was not a dream
experience maybe you could shed some
light on it for me is exactly what it
may have been do share okay one evening
I laid down to go to bed and the next
thing I know I see a light coming
through the window I get up go stand in
the window the light enters into the
room the light fills the room and it
fills my body and I never felt so much
love in my life as I did at that moment
then I woke up and no more than 4
minutes had passed time from the time I
laid down
the second experience was I had gone to
bed again and the next thing I know I'm
getting into an elevator yes and when I
get into the elevator I panic I hit the
elevator doors very hard and say this is
too real to be a dream the elevator
comes back down who says that dreams are
not real that that was it after that I
realized I wanted to go back after I
panicked it brought me back down let me
out and no more than two minutes had
gone by the next experience um
I was lying in bed to go to sleep again
I raised I got up out of bed my feet
were about 6 in off the floor I
levitated through the bedroom through
the bedroom door down the hallway out
the front door guys my body turned
upward Towards the Sky as I got upward I
I lay there and I wondered if I was
going to go any further the next thing I
know I'm getting up off an operating
table I'm talking to people in this room
lights seem to be coming from behind the
wall yes and um I don't remember what
people look like I felt friendly towards
them yes I had gauze on my ears it's
like I had some type of surgery in a
sense next thing I know I'm back in bed
and no more than 12 minutes it passed
the time I close my eyes was this a
dream experience or well do understand
now we are discussing the idea and the
whole issue and have been for quite some
time that as you blend your physical and
non-physical reality into what we call a
dream time you will understand that your
dream realities have always been real
not that what you remember as a dream is
always exactly literal to the experience
you had but it was real a real
experience nonetheless which sometimes
you interpret or symbolize when you come
back into physical Focus however all you
are describing are excursions into what
you call the astral state which operates
on a higher time frequency than your
physical state so many things can happen
there much more quickly than they happen
on your physiological level you can
experience in many ways entire lifetimes
in certain levels of the astral or
ethereal or AAL States and come back to
find that only a few minutes have passed
in the physical terminology because
you're so highly accelerated in the
astral non-physical State now the idea
is that as you loosen up and disconnect
from the idea of the physical reality
are not so tightly locked down to this
solid dense physical reality as you
begin to take more excursions in the
lighter more ethereal physical Realms
you find that you are far more malleable
far more able to travel what you call
distances because truly you are creating
those distances anyway with your
Consciousness and you can go as you say
hither thither and ywn in the wink of an
eye and you can visit many different
states many different beings who operate
almost exclusively in what you would
call the Ethereal vibratory Realms which
by the way is almost exclusively where
we do our civilization the civilizations
of the association operate what you call
the Ethereal Realms the Ethereal levels
that is our frequency our vibratory
frequency being that much more
accelerated than what you you typically
call physical dense matter that is why
contrary to what your world considers to
be popular opinion it is actually easier
for us to interact with you in your
dream state than to materialize in what
you call your physical reality which is
one of the reasons why there have not
really been Mass Landings yet the idea
is that we operate on that higher
frequency and when you are in your dream
state and you detach so to speak or
shall I say expand into your
non-physical Realms there you are truly
meeting us in what you might call our
home turf our home vibration you are
meeting us halfway and it is much easier
to interact with you now the idea of the
so-called operation is that yes you
interact with many different of these
ethereal beings many of you call us
etherians extraterrestrials the
nomenclature does not really matter but
you interact and with your agreement go
through shall we say energy adjustments
that you interpret as physiological
operations sometimes these energy
adjustments on the astral body will
actually leave physiological scarring on
your physical body because you will have
such a strong impression of the reality
of the situation because it is real that
you will transfer that impression to
your physiological form when you
reconnect with it not all of the
majority of the idea of the so-called
abduction what we prefer to call
detainments temporarily involving your species and
temporarily involving your species and
other species involve true physiological
operations or interactions many of them
take place on the astral levels and
because it is real to you you interpret
it as a physiological experience in your
physical Dimension so yes adjustments
were made upon you operations were
performed with your agreement to allow
you to be more representative of the
level of energy in your physical plane
that you wish to operate on you would
have given assistance in that sense
understand yes I do does this help you
yes it does thank you pleasant dreams to
you
[\h__\h] from the part of you whose name
is Eric peace to the part of me whose
name is Bashar well thank you very much
for being such a lovely
reflection that is the truth Bashar hey
is it true in absolute reality absolute
reality yes in absolute reality let me
see if I can find it
first go ahead that in order for me to
make my Ascension that I must first
accelerate my physical body to such
extent that if I so chose I could
sustain it in the physical eternally
instead of a sin in a sense yes the idea
once again is similar to what we are
already talking about as existing in
what you may call an etheric state for
we do many of us have a type of
physicality but it is not the
physicality you are used to it is more
what you would call the ascended state
of physicality now you may not remain
there in that sense forever per se
although of course shall we say
parenthesis everyone always exists
eternally on every level there is to
exist upon
simultaneously close parenthesis
but speaking about it linearly you may
not choose to remain there forever but
the idea is basically yes that as you
allow more acceleration to take place as
you live more in the moment more
spontaneously you uplift your vibratory
awareness you take quote unquote your
body with you and you exist in a more
refined physiological state which we
have called fourth density which you may
call the etherion state now do
understand once again that the idea
isn't really that you quote unquote take
your body with you the idea is not that
your spirit and your body are two
separate things your physical body is
your spirit in physical terminology your
spirit does not inhabit your body
literally your body is not Hollow in
that sense spiritually speaking so
simply the more you allow your natural
spirituality to accelerate then your
body form can Ascend with with it by
stepping up its vibratory experience
perhaps to illustrate this most simply
and most clearly there is a saying that
exists upon your planet that goes as
follows you are not human beings having
a spiritual experience You Are Spiritual
Beings having a human experience you are
Spirit expressing yourself in human
expression just as we are the same type
of spirit expressing ourselves in EP T
expression therefore as you live more
fully in the now as you live more fully
vitally in the now as you express the
tress of yourself everything you are
every expression of yourself can
accelerate along with that living in the
moment you understand yes I understand
what you're saying and what provoked
that question is that some say some
schools have thought that in order or
they say that when the time for
Ascension has come that a person would
not even be able to sustain the physical
body that there would be an automatic
Ascension and to me it seems like that
would take away a person's Choice which
youve taken away the choice taking away
the God not really the idea is simply a
matter of semantics again it is an
acceleration which doesn't necessarily
have to be perceived as having the same
body you used to okay you will in the
astral level in the etheric level still
be able to perceive yourself as having a
body expression but in no way shape or
form is it actually the same type of
expression you call a body now so in one
sense you you can still keep it with you
and in another sense you really don't
have it any longer at all it takes away
nothing it is your choice you simply go
to whatever level is most appropriate to
the vibration you are and that simply
makes sense to you at the time because
wherever you go you feel that you fit so
you do not feel like you have lost your
choice because you will simply go to
whatever level is appropriate for the
vibration you are and it will feel
correct when you are there in whatever
manner you choose to express yourself
that will also feel correct all of this
idea of Ascension and taking your body
with you or leaving it behind is truly
in many ways a third-dimensional matter
of semantics and is in a sense overall
quite arbitrary understand you are
arbitrary understand you are
Consciousness itself remember also in
connection with the idea that your
spirit isn't really in your body
remember that your Consciousness is not
really in your body your body the idea
you call your body is in your
Consciousness so no matter where you go
you're simply going to be the
Consciousness that you are expressing
yourself in whatever way feels correct
to
you you will still have attachment in a
sense to everything you have ever been
because that's the idea of Ascension you
don't leave anything behind you gather
everything up and in a sense take it all
with you it is an inclusive idea not an
exclusive idea you become more than not
less than understand yes I have you does
that help yes it does uh would you as I
take leave would you say anything at all
about how to perform the marriage
between Heaven and Earth seem since that
seems to be connected with the whole
idea of Ascension in the now you know as
opposed to waiting well live on earth as
if it is heaven create that expression
be the Gateway through which that energy
comes so that all individuals who see
you will say there goes an angel we must
be in
heaven understand yes I do thank you
thank you
[Applause] sharting before we can continue
sharting before we can continue
remember the whole issue simply comes
down to don't create a definitional
difference between things you don't want
to be separate see them as one thing
sheny hiar and who you good day um thank
you for spending your time answering
these somewhat insane questions oh but
you see that is our Natural State of
Mind anyway
so this is all quite typical all quite
shall we say normal for us good good I
feel at home now oh thank you you are
okay thanks um I'm sort of caught in
this triangle of sort of caught all
right triangle of troubles that all
shoot off of one another my my a
triangle of troubles how poetic thank
you would you care to Define okay I I
have been having trouble trusting my
instincts on stage which I don't
understand why I can't trust my
instincts when I have fun doing it what
do you
trust uh oh
God is that too insane of a
question well that that leads onto the
other two points of the triangle oh all
right perhaps you should simply Define
the whole triangle and let's approach it
as a whole rather than a collection of
Parts all
right okay uh I have a relationship with
two different men one being the writer
and somewhat producer of my standup
which is where I'm having trouble
trusting my instinct and the other is a
friend of mine who I love very much and
is very supportive and I can't
understand why I don't trust his my
relationship with him all all right time
and the third point that that was the
third point two and
three the director writer person is the
second and the the other person who is
dear to me and supportive is the third
all right would you like names that make
it easy unnecessary
okay now you obviously because you do
create your own reality have attracted
all of these circumstances and
situations are you learning about
yourself by having done so what are you
now affording yourself an opportunity to
see and learn about
yourself that
that
my how do I put this I know that my
whatever I believe is true is true and I
follow that and I've been changing that
way over the past six months or so it's
very strong in my convictions that's why
it's difficult in not trusting my
instincts on stage to relate to the
audience there's like a very thin may I ask you a
there's like a very thin may I ask you a
question yes thank it might be another
insane one is that all right that's
perfect all right are you confusing the
issue of trusting your instincts with
the notion of making a conscious
decision are you saying that making
conscious and deliberate decisions is
not trusting
Instinct because it is you know in other
words if you simply decide consciously
what is true for you and as you say go
for it it is in many ways the same thing
as simply trusting your instincts you
are simply making a decision sticking to
it believing that that is the decision
you prefer to make and in very many ways
that is the same thing as trusting your
instincts well because you are having
deliberateness in your
life is there some confusion between the
idea of making a conscious decision what
may sometimes appear to be analytical
and the idea of allowing your instincts
to be in the Forefront yeah the the
being instinct take no time in making a
decision in other words you allow things
to be obvious yes and you simply act
accordingly on what is obvious yes right
yeah all right but you see making a
decision can be the same way you know in
your life the idea of who and what you
are and what excites you the most and
what you prefer decide that that is your
life and if that is your decision then
why not simply trust that the things
that are going on the relationships and
circumstances that are going on in your
life are the product of having made that
decision and not an interruption in that
decision and therefore extract from the
relationships and the situations
whatever is there to be extracted rather
than assuming that somehow these
relationships do not serve the decision
you made to be who you want to be many
of you have certain expectations that
allow you to disbelieve that the things
that happen in your life after you make
a certain decision are actually
representative of having made that
decision say oh no no how can this
possibly be representative of who it is
I decided to be
you don't have to always have analytical
recognition of how it fits just trust
that it does fit and allow yourself to
be in the relationship for what it is
rather perhaps than what you think it
ought to
be is this helping it all so
far I know that I mean what you're
saying I know I mean I in your
terminology where is the difficulty in
in
uh because the two the two men are like
diametrically opposed in their opinion
well they obviously are in through you
well yeah so obviously you must contain
something that is a reflection to each
and every one of them to both of them
therefore perhaps in you they can learn
to integrate their own opposites their
own polarities through you perhaps that
is the service you are providing they
don't know each other oh yes they
do they would not be interacting with
the same person if on some level they
didn't understand yeah so whether they
understand yeah so whether they
physiologically are consciously aware of
each other or not is not the point the
point is that you are functioning as a
fulcrum as a goet between them can you
just tell me if this is an ongoing thing
going from different lives and stuff it
is okay you have danced many times with
similar individuals of The Same Spirit
similar or the same I mean similar
personas same Spirits oh okay in other
words you have played out many of these
kinds of Triad Reflections before with
them and from time to time with many
other individuals was I schizophrenic
then only in the sense constructively
that you can represent different faces
to each of them the faces they need to
see to be served by you to allow them to
integrate the polarities within
themselves in that sense yes
schizophrenic but it is a constructive
idea in this case okay well thank you is
this making some sense to you I think it
will
eventually all right you can begin by
trusting first of all that you did in
fact attract yourself into the
relationships and that you are being of
service and that they are serving you
allow yourself to learn more and more
about who you are by being in contact
with such diametrically opposite
individuals because it allows you to see
that you contain both of these sides so
that you in being shown those opposites
can function more as a whole integrated
being and by functioning as an integrated
and by functioning as an integrated
being can reflect back to each of them
the polarities they need to integrate to
allow them to understand who they are to
serve them in that way that is a large
portion of the reason you are having
these relationships to be of service in
that way understand yes
now when you allow what you are
receiving from
them to be reflected to you in a way
that allows you to integrate them into
one being and blend those polarities you
will then begin to act like more of that
whole being and in acting like more of
that whole being there will be much more
obviousness to your instincts and your
decisions with everything else in your
life do not pull yourself apart when you
see different pieces of yourself
reflected in both those individuals do
not think of yourself as schizophrenic
that word using that word is a very
strong clue to the fact that you think
of yourself as composed of separate
ideas ideas start to realize that all
the seemingly separate ideas that are
reflected to you in your life means that
you are one whole thing that can
manifest in all of those ways that you
are that multi-dimensional bring it all
home own it all own all the reflections
you attract in your life and you will
have your instincts very clear in front
of your face own it all now that doesn't
necessarily mean that when you attract
someone in your life that's doing a
certain thing acting a certain way that
they are necessarily a onetoone
reflection of what you are doing or what
you need to work on directly but still
nonetheless if you attract them they do
reflect a portion of you they do reflect
an idea own it all own that you
attracted them own that you are learning
more of who you are integrate be the
Fuller being and then your instincts
will come naturally they will be very
obvious because you'll be operating on
what you may call a higher level of
perception understand because you will
contain once again remember you will
contain all the interactions within you
and that will give you a
source of information to draw from to be
whoever it is you wish to be at any
given moment and it will be obvious you
will be
inspired you understand yes pleasant
dreams to you as well thank you very
much
Shing hello Bashar and to you good day I
almost chickened out but I decided to uh
experience this chicken out all right
but it's fun this is this is good did
you feel that you might lay an
egg yes right yes but I if I do that's
the way it is all right uh I have a
question I a lot of things have been um
information has coming to me recently oh
exciting well it has me a little worried
I don't I don't quite understand it um
it it has to do with a man named
Jonathan May and the uh devalue of the
American dollar all right something to
happen the restructuring of the whole idea of
the restructuring of the whole idea of
abundance in your Society yes right I
guess it was was I haven't heard
anything about it before and I was given
a tape and it was It was kind of
shocking to hear oh shocking yes and I
wondered what you had to comment about
there are many changes going on in the
tools that your Society uses and your
Society is beginning to realize that you
can simplify many of these tools that is
all what for now in many ways on the
surface because of your old ways of
looking at things seems like the
destruction of all you have known is
simply the
destructuration of many of the old tools
so that they can come become simpler in
your Society so that you can recognize
that the whole issue of exchange can be
a more direct idea without necessarily
needing as much of a middle symbol to
represent the exchange as your Society
has had in the path our society does not
have money at all doesn't need it we
interact directly in that way so all of
the signs you are seeing now in some
senses are simply representative of the
fact that you are destructuring yourself
so that you don't need to put your faith
in as many tools and can put the faith
back in yourselves back in creation
itself that it works to begin with and
you don't necessarily have to feel so
cut off from creation that you need all
these different tools to hook into the
idea that it works to make it work it
works just fine if you let it ah I guess
well the the thing he was saying was
that it was going to bring Mass
Devastation upon us well that depends on
how you approach it the idea is that if
you believe if you buy into the idea
that you will not be able to have what
you need
that other individuals will not be able
to get what they need because of what
you call the devaluation of that symbol
in your Society then that may be the
reality you experience one of want and
destruction and panic and frustration
but if you understand that it is simply
phasing out as a symbol and that there
are other ideas other ways that can take
its place other methodologies of
approach other methods of interaction
and you begin to look for them and begin
to believe in them and begin to use them
then you will find that the entire
change will probably take place without
so much as a notice by those individuals
using those new methodologies oh money
oh yes well it was here a moment ago
well I didn't really notice its passage
you see didn't mean to miss the funeral
I'll send
flowers but you see I've been so busy I
have been so focused on the idea of
direct exchange or any other methodology
that I found did work well the old
symbol simply faded out and I didn't
really pay much attention it can go both
ways it really depends upon attitude it
really depends upon approach really
depends upon the the individual and the
belief systems they have bought into for
you see that is the foundational
currency of your Society what you
believe okay understand I understand
does that help yes it does thank you
thank you very much remember anything
you read anything you find out anything
you hear can always be taken in a
positive or A negative way and whatever
way you take it is the way you will
experience it in your reality because
all situations are fundamentally neutral
and do not have a built-in meaning they
are neutral props the meaning you supply
determines the effect you get out of it
this is simple
mechanics and it always works that way
thank you thank you very much
Shing good evening bishar and good Daye
to you the last time I got up a few
weeks ago I said I was nervous as hell
this time I Define it as being very
excited oh thank you very
much um I want to thank you for that
interaction a few weeks ago I probably
didn't get it as much at the time as I
did when I listened to the tape a few
times at home all right but you got it
all yeah yeah especially the part about
realizing that um that I couldn't
experience a reality that I am not the
vibration of it made me start uh
relaxing and trying not to control as
much and therefore not trying you mean
right right and therefore not uh looking
for the conflict and the res thank you
thank you thank you thank you um thank
you for choosing ease and effortlessness
in your life thank you okay well now
this question relates to not choosing it
oh all right you're choosing something
else how about thinking at least in
positive terms if you're going to choose
a negative at least say it's a choice
okay okay instead of not a choice of a
positive okay I want to choose the positive I
okay I want to choose the positive I
want to choose the positive all right
okay what this question concerns is it
concerns Prosperity Prosperity abundance
yes all um now recently uh uh let me let
me just give a little little story of
snipet of what's going on like snipet
all right you learn from me I taught you
right you learn from me I taught you
freak out last time um yes freak
out if you ever need a translator um
have one thank
you um I recently uh a few weeks ago
made a goal okay I set goal and I was of
the idea that I can commit to that and
therefore bring that to come about um
then a couple weeks after that I decided
okay well maybe in setting a goal you
you need to realize that you can't have
like a pipe dream um you can is that
something you'll
smoke some people do do that no right um
but it's like I fell into another
conversation about it afterwards it's
like I thought okay if I say I want this
yes I can have this but then later on I
thought okay well maybe in saying I
wanted that that's more of a pipe dream
if I get more realistic then I can have
that all right okay it makes sense to me
we are doing our best to translate what
you are saying into our understanding do
continue um anyhow so what I did was I
cut that goal down and I just realized
recently the reason I can't go beyond
what I've gone beyond is cuz I met that
smaller goal and it's like I therefore I
guess cut off the reaching of the higher
goal um all right okay now recently I
had some spiritual information given to
me that you know concerning Prosperity
concerning having enough money to do the
things I want to do is that your
definition of prosperity no but if I had
enough money to do the things I want to
do like uh you know things I want to
study things I want to you know travel I
want to do da da d da yes if you have
the ability to do what you want to do
yes right
um and so what the spiritual information
was was that to just conduct my life as
if I had what I needed yes to do what I
want to do because you okay but I fall into
into
yes what no reason for name calling here
um
um well so what I do though is I get to
the point where I say but I've got to be
reasonable I've got necessarily will
happen that way but that it is just as
possible as any other way and if that
way really is the path of least
resistance then that will be the first
one that happens if the money is the
path of least resistance that will be
the first one that happens automatically
as you say out of the blue so what
you're saying then is to just like go by
what was told to me keep going for
everything I want without trying to feel
well I need to be responsible and not
you are responsible you are responsible
utterly responsible but that doesn't
necessarily mean that you have to do it
by someone else's definition of the
game you are responsible for the
everything you experience in your
reality you can be responsible for a
definition of reality you
prefer understand responsible doesn't
mean that there is one definition of
reality that you have to pay field to to
that isn't being responsible that in
many ways is simply giving your power
away playing someone else's idea of what
you should play that is not being
responsible that's not being true to
you whoever it is you really are you are
responsible for and whatever type of
reality you need to create to be who you
are is what you're responsible for so
act upon whatever opportunities come to
you with full excitement and full
Integrity act upon the ones that excite
you the most whether they seem connected
to what you think you want or not
because the excitement tells you they
are connected act on them with Integrity
act on them with inspiration do whatever
you are capable of doing and let the
circumstances come to in whatever way
really does represent the path of least
resistance if money is that way nothing
will stop it but if something else can
actually happen quicker let it so I'm
not being unreasonable at all to just
keep going for all of the things I want
to do the things that excite me
regardless of what my bank statements
says anything just keep going for those
things and if if the money is the least
resistant way it will come it'll come
and if way let me back up I'm I'm yes
yes yes yes you are understanding what
we are saying but also remember that you
do not necessarily have to spend the
money you have to act on the abilities
that will bring you what you want in
other words the idea of acting
prosperous doesn't always involve the
actual physical exchange of money or the
spending of money in that way do
remember that many of the individuals on
your planet that you in your colloquial
terminology consider to be rich
individuals in many cases actually spend
far less money now than they used to
before they were physically Rich because
they simply flow ideas through
themselves and a lot of times the
so-called exchange of money is simply in
your terms on paper and doesn't actually
physically happen the idea of someone
who is really acting abundantly is not
actually someone in many cases who
Hoards or has a lot of physiological
money but someone who flows ideas
through themselves and is using the tool
in whatever way represents the path of
least resistance they don't necessarily
actually have to have it in order to get
things done things get done around them
because that's who they are and that's
how they act things get done because
they do
things understand I understand um I just
want to you know feel this as a part of
me before I sit down and so if people
are demanding money from me for the
things that I want yes
then um sometimes you will need it allow
yourself to recognize when you are made
that kind of an offer treat it as an
offer not a demand it's an offer it's
one way of of exchanging with them one
way so I suggest other ways you can
suggest other ways to them that is the
most direct idea you can say well you
know I've just had an inspiration how
about this sometimes you might be
surprised they might go for it oh you
know I didn't think of that wish I had
thought of it that's wonderful I like
that even better I don't need money from
you if you'll do
this you never know give it a shot
you'll be surprised and then after a
while maybe not so
surprised but be bold act with
conviction give them an offer back say
how about this how about this how about
this if it comes right down to the idea
that nothing else will happen within the
exchange except the money then assume
that that one will perhaps need the
money and you will have the amount of
money you need in some other way by
doing something else that excit you you
will bring whatever money you need to
take care of this but you may not need
as much money as you think for all these
different ideas narrow it down so that
you don't necessarily have to think you
need great sums of money to do things
that you could be doing right now
without the money and let whatever
amount of money you really need for the
things that really require it come to
you it doesn't necessarily have to be as
great as you
think thank you okay thank you thank you
very much you are very welcome sharing
Bashar and to uh your fellows fellow
beans of esani I want to take this
moment to tell you that I personally and
probably most people here if not all of
their being do love you unconditionally
too oh thank you very much thank you
very much if we did not feel it we
probably wouldn't be interacting with
him and neither would
we um I spoke with you a a couple of
weeks ago very briefly about some things
I had been experiencing within the past
year all right can you all hear this
individual adequately no okay do be bold you got
adequately no okay do be bold you got
it that I am all
right past year was filled with so many
wonderful and on this Earthly level uh
miraculous Andor incredible things that
I just feel like
I'm zooming around
yes and if I if I were a person that was
into candy I would be buried in a sea of
candy eating my way out feels that good
all right all right I take your meaning
thank you therefore I don't have a
question well thank you very much I
thought you'd like that but I want to be
open to whatever you might have to say
to me well I love you unconditionally
too well thank you thank you for
choosing to function as an equal and
making a statement of conviction about
who you know you are we perceive that as
truly impactful and accelerating in
creating more conduciveness in the
ability of your Society to see reflected
in you that degree of conviction so that
they can have that degree of conviction
within themselves we thank you for
working with us therefore in increasing
your society's ability to trust
themselves in a positive way thank you
well thank
you sheding
hello Bashar and you good day okay I
want to I want to thank you first of all
for starting the evening out with a talk
about the sort of the the blade of Rage
because I wasn't here last week because
that's what I was doing I was raging
away at the universe so it felt I felt
at home here oh all right could make a
little connection I wanted to talk to
you a little bit about what was making
me at R all right I think it has to do
with something uh with a polarity
dealing with with the individual me
being me okay and yet my desire to be
blended with all that is and in the
physical world that I live on here on
Earth I want to represent that in
community and so I have been drawing
into my life since last summer um well
not just since last summer it's been an
interest of me and when I talk to my
friends about it it's like you know they
kind of go you know they're really going
to sleep on me and I can't I can't
communicate to anybody what
how essential this is and and how it
really means something to me all right
but do remember before you go on that
many individuals because they are not
used to functioning in a fully conscious
manner will need to become unconscious
before they can really hear you because
that's where they listen Okay well see
that that's what was going on okay I've
been drawing all this into myself and I
I had a real beautiful experience of
finding out what it means to be in
community with a whole bunch of people
they're actually 44 okay 22 men and 22
women by accident okay there are no
leaders there are no there are no belief
systems there are we there are belief
systems yes there are but I mean we can
do anything we want and and we can make
Community any way we want and it was a
very powerful experience for me because
I got in contact with the fact that I
didn't have to do anything I just had to
be in that particular moment all right
one of the things you understand that
doing is critical but the idea is that
when you are doing what you are it is an
effortless flow that simply allows you
to feel as if you are simply being but
it doesn't stop doing as long as you are
projecting yourself as a physical
reality doing is a critical way to
express your beingness okay what what
happened there was I tend to in a group
you know like I'll see I okay in the
colloquial term I'm a high school
English teacher in an inner city and I
am confronted daily with a lot of human
pain all right and so when I'm in a
community I'm aware of a lot of this
stuff and like there's this little part
of me that would like to fix people's
lives and a little part of it yeah great
big part anyway I really got to get in
touch with that and not have to do that
because it puts a big strain on me okay
so I taking responsibility for other
individuals is a strain being fully
responsible to them is not and that's
what I meant by that being I was with
them okay it it was really exciting
thank then I challenged myself a little
bit more and I thought this is what I
want to do in my classroom okay yes okay
I talked to you a year ago about
teaching and anyway so I you know and I
I got into this and I I I drew a support
team it has to do with like pure
communicators and it mean it was it was
beautiful and all this so then I gave
myself a challenge of really being with
teenagers and adults and administrators
and building a community and they had
this little workshop okay it was guys
anyway so I went and I really wanted to
do this and it was horrible in what
sense I was raging the whole time I mean
and I was well good you were bringing up
things you needed to look at yes that
was happening and I know that but why is
that horrible well no one of the things
that I was doing is like I would say
things and I wasn't communicating I mean
I would say something and then somebody
else would like try to mirr it back to
me and it's like well no that's not what
it's all about and it wasn't just then
when I got back you know to the my after
the weekend with the people that I was
working with and I was sharing with them
things I couldn't they there was nothing
I feel like I wasn't talking like
they're not hearing me and I felt while
I was there like I didn't want to be
there and yet I wanted to be there was
really bringing in all this polarity
stuff iess yes give you more of an
opportunity to really learn to
communicate with yourself and to also
learn that the strongest form of
communication is not in the talking but
in the
doing no no
no no I that's what that's that's the
part that I see in real life okay it's
like my what I do yes I mean what I'm
doing in my classroom what I'm doing
right here it isn't so much what we're
saying that we're communicating yes but
what I felt there is like this total
isolation here I'm with all these people
and I want to be with these people and
I'm feeling totally disconnected I don't
know why I create that can be for many
reasons can be as simple as learning the
difference between the reality you now
are as opposed to the reality you used
to be simply could have been a very
graphic demonstration of old ideas that
you no longer buy into and so simply are
no longer connected to could be that
could be once again the idea of learning
to communicate with new parts of
yourself that you hadn't necessarily
allowed yourself to see and now that you
are seeing them you can integrate them
so you can do more as the individual you
really choose to be and that will be the
communication that you will be doing can
be that can be many things first
suggestion would be to not label it as
being horrible yeah okay I knew you'd
say that but I I I felt like being
honest okay that's what it oh yes
absolutely do own it if that is what you
created by all means and the rage and
the disconnection that I felt made me
like last and I mean this went on the
weekend before and by Thursday I was in
such a rage about the whole thing that I
really didn't even want to be here and
you I mean I know that's hysterical and
extremely dramatic but that was what I
was feeling my raging at the Universe I
mean I if I could have like disconnected
not just from this lifetime but from all
being because I had made I I feel like I
was really I'm really trying with all of
my Integrity to be here and and
integrity does not require trying no I
know but I mean I was being real there I
mean I knew I was and I wasn't there and
it bothered me where were you I don't
know I mean I I will I mean I I like I I
could feel myself saying I mean I mean
I've been here and I hear this and I and
it's like I want to you know live my
life in the present and I could see
myself every moment escaping and I keep
bringing myself back may I ask you a
question sure I would like it well thank
you when you went into that Gathering
did you bring a number of expectations
in with you well that's what a lot of
people are asking me I didn't I just
went there okay I I I I didn't seem to
think of
anything that I was expecting except the
reactions you wanted from them and I got
a lot of well I got a lot of reactions
within me that maybe surprised me why
did you expect any particular types of
reactions from
them why did you necessarily assume that
when you went into the group and said
what you wanted to say oh I didn't do a
lot of talking you know the only times I
did talk is when they really made me do
that you well I mean if I were going to
cooperate in this and so I did want to
cooperate and so like they'd go around
they'd say how's everybody feeling you
know and I wasn't feeling raw raw all
right stop back up all right your rage
according to what we have understood in
our translation of your language began
when you according to what you have
explained to us did not receive the
feedback you thought you
should okay yes I don't know I I the
feed the feedback that I thought I
should I don't know from
them you were saying you felt cut off
but there was no communication going on
but you were expressing certain ideas
and they were not responding in the way
you thought later on when I left during
the weekend I felt like I was doing that
like I didn't I thought what am I doing
here with these people you know I I
didn't feel connected to them all right
then once again backtracking to what we
have already said does that give you
some understanding of the fact that you
do not necessarily need to place
yourself in circumstances that are no
longer representative of who you really
are okay that's what I probably I I why
can't we be in community with every
being oh you can but do remember that
right now on your planet because it is a
time of transition you are still
exhibiting in your Society a multitude
of very diverse and sometimes
diametrically opposite belief system yes
I know I'm living it every day yes your
it your civilization has not yet learned
on mass to express validity and true
equality to the infinite diversity
within your civilization the idea
therefore I is that you can be aware of
all the different variances in belief
yes and the way to experience an
equality with that is to Simply listen
to what another individual has to say
without the expectation that it has to
make any connective sense at all to what
you believe yeah okay you also said one
other thing which to some degree is a
vital clue about your expectation
because you said that what you have to
share is essential for everyone to know
why oh okay why no it isn't correct
right so don't bring that expectation in
and you will not get the idea thrown
back at you okay understand yes thank
you that is true unconditional sharing
and that's when the real Community
starts when you share because you are
that person
regardless of what they share back with
you what they share back with you is
just as much of a sharing as you gave to
them expecting that it must make logical
connective sense to what you already
shared is to some degree an expectation
okay that says that they should involve
themselves in the same level of
perception that you have initiated which
they don't have to do all right one
thing that you said see it bothers me
this bothers me about what bothers this
new age stuff okay new age stuff okay
it's like what you said to me okay so
you're getting a reflection we have all
this diversity and maybe you're not
there and I'm thinking you know why are
we so high and mighty from everybody you
don't have to be that's is a Jud hear
okay I'm hearing that I'm hearing that
well because in many cases once again
even the new age thought going on on
your planet takes its format from any
old age definitions no no I was hearing
it in a sense from something that you
were saying about such as I was getting
a reflection of maybe where I'm not of
where I have been and maybe what I'm why
why am I putting myself in something
that's not for me am I hearing but I was
I hearing you right to some degree but
perhaps a more precise way to formulate
that question is why are you defining
that where you put yourself has nothing
to do with who you are I'm not all right
then you will not have the reaction that
you have
had you could not have the reaction that
you described to us that you had right
without the idea of the definition that
you somehow in that sense did not fit or
they did not fit the idea is that you
can go and experience that Community
feeling you want to but if you want to
experience that Community feeling then
let them be a diversified Community yes
and that's what I want I mean that's
that that's what this is then why did
you react to their
differences in a negative way well this
was what was upsetting to me because I
asked for what I wanted and I got it yes
and I don't want to be a part of
it you do not want to be a part of the
definition you created to yes create
another definition right create the
definition you prefer and live it that
way and this will help me with a lot of
the things not just if you let it yeah
it doesn't have to it has no mind of its
own it cannot force you in that sense to
accept the principle you must use the
tool consciously in that sense now you
can recognize again that other
individuals may for now have belief
systems that do not have much to do with
the belief systems you prefer let them
have their belief systems and in letting
them have their belief systems that's
actually the quickest way to allow them
the opportunity to align with yours yes
yes but I think that what I became aware
of too was the terrible loneliness I
felt there but why I didn't have I
didn't share with anyone else like why
do I always feel so different I mean
like I don't really feel like I fit here
either but everyone is different right
that's what I was dealing with the
differences in the individual and our
ability to be together and flow together
like that energy that came through for
me anyway yes two weeks ago when
Galactic that's the name the galactic
there was this feeling of really flowing
with all of this energy but that is
because the energy of the galactic
recognizes that recognition of
differences is what connects you
together not the other way around okay I
I really truly believe that that that is
what I do then act like it you cannot
have a reaction as you had if you did
believe that to have that kind of
reaction you have to believe something
else to feel lonely by recognizing
differences have a all right well then
you allowed yourself to realize that you
may have still bought into that belief
system and now you don't have to anymore
okay you gave yourself the opportunity
to discover that aspect of yourself that
perhaps you did not know you created now
you do now you don't have to choose it
anymore so that is a very wondrous thing
not a horrible thing yeah okay does this
help yes thank you I appreciate it well
we thank you very much one moment yes
this evening of your
time ask when you are going into your
dream
state for the next at least three of
your nights in a row for assistance from
your guides and specifically also for
the assistance of dolphin energy to Aid
you in taking you on what might be
called a little astral tour so that you
can understand and recognize the whole
idea of the interconnectedness of
differences from another level to see it
from another perspective in that sense
to see the unifying factors so that you
will be able to truly know it has
infused itself within you not just as an
analytical principle but as a true mode
of life
expression they will help you blend this
idea and accelerate this idea within you
they will in that sense assist you in
homogenizing understand yes thank you
well thank you very much
Shing Bashar daring darling you are so
beautiful I can't tell you well you just
did thank you very
much let me tell you
again I I can't I can't tell you how
much um our interactions have meant to
me and just your presence we thank you
very much for your co-creation one
moment all of you
thank
you I've been really deeply moved by
your your service we and um I sufficient
I have a question yes uh there's been an
an aspect of I imagine it's a a myth
that exists um I would assume it's a
myth it could have been real I have no
idea but it keeps recurring in my life
and that is the Lilith aspect of
femininity yes and I was wondering if
you could tell me a little bit about it
I seem to have uh sort of been drawn to
um it is an archetypal substream
Collective Consciousness that you have
expressed in more blatant ways in
several of the lives you have lived more
than you are expressing it directly now
you are expressing other ideas now other
archetypal consciousnesses now through
this particular life stream aspect but
the Lilith aspect you have been in touch
with in many other lives in many
different ways it simply is now that you
are integrating the idea of the boldness
and the warrior aspect in with the idea
of masculinity and femininity you are
simply recalling some of the attachments
you have had to that energy so that you
have a shall we say reference point of
the feminine idea you have expressed in
a very strong way in the past so you can
bring that up to the present and
integrate the idea of the masculine
aspect and The Feminine aspect in one
life now making it autonomous sort of
yes and that whole idea once again of
having a very sharp blade in a velvet
sheath you you recognize me oh yes you
are
unmistakable vibration fairly
screams it's true it's true um I have
just one other short question all right
and it's for everyone we need the
perfect birth control method on this
planet yes can you help us out
absolutely conscious communication with
the individuals that can be your
children so you know what the timing is
so you know when you will and won't get
get pregnant so I can just say no no
Spirits welcome the no no no no
no the idea is to be in conscious touch
with the agreements you have made
already so that you are aware of your
timing I mean yes in a sense you can
make an agreement this is not for me but
the idea is to be in conscious awareness
with the agreements you have made so you
recognize the wise and the wherefores of
what the timing is for having decided or
not decided to Bear physical children
and what the spirits are what the
Consciousness is that you would be in
touch with in having made that agreement
with them and why it would be playing
out why they may need to be born to you
what you have agreed with them being
aware of all these levels of agreement
will simply allow you to understand that
when that agreement is not time you
cannot possibly get pregnant and when it
is time you cannot possibly do anything
but um but being in touch with the
timing knowing that inner sense of
communication with that Spirit which of
course at this point is not really a
child in your vernacular being in
communication with that spirit will
simply put you squarely in intuitive
touch with what your timing is you may
not have made an agreement to have
children in that way it is up to you you
may have made agreements to have what
you may call temporary physiological
lives because sometimes there are
consciousnesses that do not necessarily
need to experience what you call a full
lifespan but the idea of being in touch
with that consciousness and feeling that
recognition and feeling that
communication intuitively will simply
allow you to understand beyond the
shadow of a doubt when your timing is
and when it is not also being in touch
in that way can also regulate in many
ways for many of your feminine beings
the whole issue of what you call your
periodicity you know you do not need to
experience it at
all
H if you can flow the periodicity in
terms of the idea of a full blending of
your masculine and feminine side into
one expressiveness you will find that
there are times when it may speed up at
first but then it will begin to slow
down and slow down and slow down and
slow down and you may find that you
rarely experience it when you are in
touch with your timing when there is all
the conviction of the absolute idea of
your timing of the relationships and the
agreements you have made when you begin
to operate on that level that doesn't
mean you have to have analytical
awareness of what all the Agreements are
just when you are in the flow of knowing
and trusting your intuitive side then
you can realize that those kinds of
Expressions those kinds of clearings and
cleansings can be experienced in many
other ways and expressed in many other
ways and it does not at any time in any
way have to be experienced in pain ever
ever ever ever those ideas are from
times in your history when many of you
in that sense bought into ideas that
were less than you are when you cut
yourself off in many ways from the
actual flow of nature of your Blended
masculine and feminine cells when you
reclaim that idea that polarity and
homogenize it into one idea within each
and every feminine and masculine being
there will be no pain there will be no
need for that particular type of
periodicity well now so one moment the
idea also is to align what you have
called your sub and unconscious cells
into the recognition that you are simply
one Consciousness and that the terms
subconscious and unconscious are simply
in many ways terms of convenience for
things that you don't want to look at
the idea is therefore why it is
psychically tied to what you call your
lunar cycle the once a month idea is because
cycle the once a month idea is because
your moon represents in what you call
the nighttime aspect the idea of all the
things that are buried within your
subconscious bringing that to the
surface will mean that you have Blended
the night and the day and you'll be able
to function in conscious harmony with
all the cycles of nature inside such a
way that that power can be expressed in
Creative flows without pain and without
the type of biological flow that you
experience it as
now but the only thing that um has me
concerned is that I'm not really totally
aware of the agreements that I've made
but you do not have to have absolute
analytical awareness of what they are to
sense the timing be intuitively in touch
with the timing get into a meditative
State know that you are in communication
with all those consciousnesses you are
making agreements with or have made
agreements with and just must let them
communicate with you on the level where
you can feel the timing of the agreement
get to know it as you say practice with
it feel the idea see it play out in your
life with regard to certain events that
happen so you can cue and key into that
feeling when a certain event happens and
it will train you to recognize what that
feeling is to recognize the flow of that
feeling to recognize the flow of that
timing so you'll get used to what it
feels like so you will know when you are
on timing and when you are not in that
sense understand
treat it as what you all call an extra
sense it is very natural within all of
you it is not extra it is a part of what
you are you are completely in touch with
nature in that way the actual expression
in many cases of what you call your
feminine periodicity is actually having
cut yourself off from many aspects of
nature that is why it represents itself
that way well i' I've embraced that I
you know I I'm not really concerned
about that aspect but the thing is I've
never felt uh a desire to have children
and yet I've been on the pill forever
because I don't know what else to do
stop when you talk about the idea of
children first of all many times the
lack of Desire can in and of itself be
indicative of the fact that you may have
made an agreement not to have any
biologically also when you think about
the idea of children sometimes it may
for many individuals and you are very
connected to the type of energy that is
common to many individuals who feel the
following way that even when you think
of the idea of children what may seem
more natural or Fe feel more natural to
you is not the idea of biological
presentation but
adoption you may find that you have in
many ways the ability to bring into your
sphere other individuals who may on some
levels be considered your children but
who do not necessarily have to interact
with you from physical birth MH who you
may run into when they are already a
little bit older that would be very nice
much better all right but uh like I say
I just still don't know exactly if I'm
all you have to do to find out all these
timings is take that sword and put it in
the sheath it's in there all right a
velvet sheath yes it is still sharp it
will never get dull you are still the
warrior but you are in that sense a
peaceful one I hope so what I'm sure I am thank
one I hope so what I'm sure I am thank
you a warrior says I know so I know so I
hope so remember that A Warrior's first
blade is the blade of
conviction understand I've got my hand
on it I know I do thank you very much
it's it's just been the most incredible
6 months of my life and I didn't think I
would be able to go on without you I
feel umbilically tied to you but we are
all connected but remember all of you
any energy you feel quote unquote from
us is your own energy we simply put out
a vibration that is up to you to match
if you feel the energy you have matched
it so you can create that energy for
yourselves anytime you want because it's
it's your energy you don't need us in
that sense but we are always all
interconnected also when many of you
talk about the idea of going through
this process and that process and taking
this amount of years and this amount of
years to go through these processes you
can change those definitions to perhaps
make it seem as if it really hasn't been
all that much time think about it in
terms of
orbits oh well 10 years it has taken but
it has only taken 10
orbits just 10 times around our Central
Sun that's not very much not very much
at all it makes you all very
young understand yes and I thank you for
thank you very much you may all at this
time enjoy a short break we will resume
contact in this fashion in approximately
10 to 15 of your minutes of counting
[Applause] I say before we continue with question
I say before we continue with question
allow us to share a little idea
from my past
civilization we have discussed many
times that we had language that we used
to use that we no longer use in our
civilization because we are now in your
terminology mostly
telepathic but the idea is when we had
use of a vocal language there was a
concept and a principle a custom which
we'd like to share with you now since we
have been talking about the idea of
boldness of expression and conviction
and deliberateness of
action all of those principles were
expressed in one word that word in our
ancient language was shivi shivi in that
sense was an entire ritual unto itself
an entire principle unto itself that
represented boldness and deliberate
action with regard to any aspect or any phase
with regard to any aspect or any phase
of life if an individual allowed
themselves to become immersed in
shivi then they were in a sense giving
themselves up as you say stealing
themselves to create a certain type of
momentum a certain type of focus a
certain type of momentum Direction and
deliberateness in their life so when an
individual decided to walk the path of
shivai they would have what would be
called an energy meal that would
symbolize or represent the idea of
taking that path this is of course when
we used to eat physically the idea of
this energy
meal would be done in three
phases and each phase would blend
another level of the power of the spirit
and the emotion and the
body and after each phase the individual
would lock in that particular expression
with that word with that conviction sh
and would go on to the next phase all
three times and then that individual in
focusing that way that type of
deliberateness would then live boldly
all the actions of life now there would
be from time to time things that you
would call well perhaps missteps slip
ups but it was all allowed within the
overall idea of shivi and all the other
individuals in the culture allowed it
when they recognized that the individual
was on that path they gave them room as
you say gave them space as you say to
feel their way through through that
conviction to support them and nurture
them to know that they were as you say
shooting for a straight idea going for
the goal in that sense all the way to
the star and all an individual had to do
at any point in the society if they were
moving on something moving through
something even walking through a crowd
if they felt that there was something in
that sense that stood in their way all
they had to do was say shivi and
everyone stepped aside and allowed them
through to Express and experience
themselves in true spontaneous action
within the society and they were
cherished and nurtured in this way and
nourished it is very similar to the idea
in many ways that you spur on an
athletic competition a runner a
longdistance runner moving through life
in that way with that boldness step
after step that conviction these
individuals simply played this idea out
in the actions of their life rather than
consolidating it into what you would
call a temporary sport shivi was a whole
way of life a whole principle and now in
a sense is is a whole way of life for
all of us all the time so we don't have
to say it anymore because no one lives
any differently in our society at this
time shivi is the way of our life and
now simply means that
shivi
Shing hi hi hi my name is Ivan all right
good day to you and uh I want to know
that you just um pick My Name by chance
or did you have a you know personal
message did you did you um I did not do
the picking you don't do the picking you
cocreate what you call the random access
of your
name all of you together support each
and every individual that is chosen as
each and every individual stands where
you are standing now every other
individual supports you and lives
through you and nurtures you shivi
so I don't I don't really have any
questions um then make a statement what
what can you tell the person that has
all the answers do you know you have all
the answers well I think I do do you
have all what you need to be who it is
you prefer to be yeah do you know you
are a complete kit yes do you act like
it yes nothing I can tell you except
once again thank you for being an equal
because that's a assists your planet in
giving all the energy of Your World more
ability to live that way for themselves
as well being a living example is all
that it takes to make great changes and
have great impact on your planet that's
all it takes one individual can change
and does change the entire planet
because you're all connected anything
you do touches everyone else um are you
telepathic in our society yes can I
communicate with you telepathically
right now it will depend upon the
vibrational frequencies more often than
not they will be
dissimilar and the idea also is that
what you call telepathy telepathy has
many conditions that are required to be
spontaneous setting it up in that sense
pointing it out calling it out to be
done at a specific time in a specific
place for a specific reason does not
always work well I want to just try for like 10
work well I want to just try for like 10
seconds and that'll be it all right you
may try all you wish right doing it will
be the thing I'll do it all right do so
it is simply our perception that what
you may call heart of hearts Burning
Heart flaming heart Sacred Heart you
have an involved in the idea and the
issues many times in many lives of what
you may call a crusade now in this life
you have allowed yourself to understand
that that flame that burns brightest in
your heart is something that can
actually nourish rather than have to in
a sense burn out all things that are
seen as opposition or all things that
are seen as different now you know that
the flame of your heart is something
that is an embracing energy of
unconditional love this is what we see
in you in that way and there have been
many associations in many lives where
you have had what you may call the
nomenclature of
Christopher in that sense you do nurture
and support and carry across the stream
and have carried across streams in life
many individuals in that way this is the
vibration we are picking up in this
sense from you at this time represented
by the holding of the lantern lighting
of the way the idea in that sense is
that you have function in many ways like
what you may call your mythologically t
Ro hermit holding up the lantern knowing
that you are alone but knowing that you
are connected to every being as you
stand upon the icy Snowy Mountain toop
of clarity in your life the ideas now
that you know you are functioning as a
lighthouse standing upon the Rocks so
that all who may pass nearby will know
the ideas illuminated by your beam that
may await them in the depths of the
water as they approach so that they can
with due conscious consideration
consider all of the pitfalls that may be
there for them to understand and
integrate within their own lives the
burning heart the flaming heart is the
lighthouse beacon in this sense just
simply allow it to burn Rosy and golden
and bright and at the same time exude
with every breath the idea of the blue
white electromagnetic Light That Binds
you all together that immerses you all
together in telepathic contact for
remember that what you call your minds
your telepathic Minds is simply the
interaction or intersection of your
Consciousness with the electromagnetic
field of your planet and that your world
is one Consciousness one mind Tel
empathically speaking and that the whole
issue of telepathy is as we have coined
actually tathy which means that as you
vibrate in accord with another
individual As you move on their
frequency as you love them
unconditionally you know who they are
you know what they are you read them
very well and you know each other and
create the same thoughts at the same
time telepathy is not actually directly
reading each other's mind it is thinking
alike simultaneously this is our perception
simultaneously this is our perception
for now of the idea of your unfolding
your UNF flowering and in that sense of
your gift for which we thank you thank
you for your affirmation thank you very
much
shoting greetings bishar and to you good
day and greetings to Blossom who is my
future connection all righton I sound
funny because I'm in the cleansing fire
here the Shiva of the flu shivi shivi of
the flu um I want I wanted to share with
you uh that it's been wonderful to come
and talk with you
over the last couple of years and we
thank you for your co-creations thank
you and uh this evening and tomorrow we
are experiencing the galactic energy yes
astrologically and I think it's kind of
wonderful and synchronistic and perfect
that Galactic is coming through now yes
always in perfect timing by the way
mhm Now One Moment One
Moment understand very very clearly what
we are about to say please do not run
around saying bishar said this bishar
said
that many of you have now in your
electromagnetic shifts experienced what
you call small Earth Tremors there will
be a few more within the next week of
your time because it is representative
of changes in your electromagnetic
Consciousness and because of the
intersection of your individuality with
the galactic energy you are now coming
into alignment with certain ideas of
what you call Galactic centers these
cause small adjustments to be made it is
not something to fear it is adjustments
and they are true clearings and true
openings of doorways you will have
perhaps a few more
adjustments feel these
adjustments as you drop away old shells
old ideas and truly allow your cores to
stand vulnerable and
strong continue well thank you I wanted
you to give us some new fourth dimension
definitions for the astrological
symbology that we have here third and
that was a good one the idea of what you
call astrological symbology is simply
the recognition of shall we say for now
colloquially Frozen vibrational patterns
crystallized vibrational agreements that
represent the agreements you have made
as individuals and Society they are
slices of crystallin vibrational
agreements that is what the symbology of
astrology is right and uh this Saturn Uranus is
is right and uh this Saturn Uranus is
going to be tomorrow and then again I
think it's July and October I know
there's other astrologist I think that's
what it is so we we're experiencing this
Galactic connection now yes and we're
going into Capricorn this Earth feeling
and then we're going back to the
galactic and
then out of it again and back through it
so uh can you tell us a little bit about
that you are experiencing both ends of
the spectrum of childhood and true
adulthood true maturation for in no way
sheap or form is what we about to say
meant as a derogatory comment but you
are as a species still to some degree
immature so you are fluctuating back and
forth between the idea of the birth on
Earth the child of Nature and the true
Galactic maturation that you also
contain as a spirit you are fluctuating
back and forth so that you can arrive at
a midpoint and be the ascended ethereal
beings of your fourth density
reality understand yes no
maybe uh can you tell me
more not at this time okay
um I don't know why I'm drawing a blank
I'm feeling very extraterrestrial myself
oh all right then allow yourself to be
fulfilled with your recognition of all
the connections that all of you have to
all of the things that represent who you
chose to be right now in a sense because
you think of yourself as building blocks
of Personality then you may encounter
from time to time blocks or aspects of
those blocks that go into making up your
physical Persona and many of them for
all of you are going to be
extraterrestrial as you say in nature
because none of you are original to your
planet anyway so happy Hunting
thank you you are now all of you when
you look into a mirror recognizing that
your mirrors have many facets you're
going to see many different kinds of
faces looking back they're all you all
of
them no matter what else you connect up
to what you perceive in your reality is
all you does that help oh yeah I I know I
you does that help oh yeah I I know I
wanted to ask you Uranus is one of the
planets is the nature and one of them is
the Awakening Uranus would be the
Awakening yes because it represents the
idea of the blending of what you call
your subconscious and unconscious
mentality so when you bring that into
full Consciousness when you know you are
only a one Consciousness
being then it will have fulfilled its
symbolic import for you but we're really
not too close to that collectively yet
are we as far as I am concerned you are
look at it this way from this
perspective you have spent many tens of
thousands of your years segregating
yourself from your own self-awareness
and recognition within what you now call
the next 50 of your years you will have
a completely Blended Society not very
long at all 50
orbits after tens of thousands of
orbits not very long at all and the
galactic Point that's the direction that
our whole association is going to that
we're conjunct right now is that right
there are many phases to the idea of
conjunction with the galactic energy you
are going through the first initiation
stages there will be many more to come
and our society is going through many
ourselves it is an ongoing NeverEnding
process of ecstasy joy and
self-awareness and connection to the
infinite we thank you happy joy and
everything else always
sharing hi bash and good day are to you
perfect and you uh I'm fine um I had the
opportunity I had opportunity to talk to
you last month that was January right
and I asked a question general question
about Uranus Uranus what how you say
does not matter understand the idea you
gave a perfect definition of it now this
time I would like you to give definition
of our planet Pluto thank you and it's
transit to yes since it represents quote
unquote the limit of your solar system
it is an absolutely transitional gate
from the cradle you have always known
the womb you have always known of the
Earth Solar System in that sense for
tens of thousands of years to a true
transition once again towards the
galactic energy and true maturation you
will understand many things about the
polarity within the planet you call
Pluto for it has what you call a small
Moon you call shaton and there is a very
unique relationship between Pluto and
Chiron electromagnetically that you have
yet to discover the idea however is that
it truly does represent as your
mythology tells you a river across which
on the other side lies all of eternity
and true maturation as a
species it represents the transitional
gate in that sense it is very similar to
what you call your number
13 oh that's
beautiful does that suffice it does nowk
there is something else on my mind oh
all right do you have in your Society 10
commandments like we having down here
there are no Commandments of any kind by
the way what your Society calls
Commandments were not originally
delivered as Commandments it was put
into that framework because that's the
way your Society understood things at
the time you better do this or else the
actual delivery of what you call the Ten
Commandments was an astral
recognition and as the information was
or Ally delivered it was simply a
recognition of the state of existence of
natural existence which then became
interpreted in the idea your Society
understood Commandments rule be ruled in
other words for example we will not go
into any more than the first idea just
as an
illustration your first commandment
generally reads as follows I am the Lord
thy God Thou shalt not have false gods
before me the idea generally is that the
way the information was originally
delivered was in the following way there
is only one all that is anything you
think of as separate is still the same
one all that is and is not really
another God that was interpreted by your
society as I'm the only one you better
worship me or
else and if you don't and if you worship
something else you're going to get into
trouble because that's the way your
Society thinks or thought back
then all of what you call the
Commandments are simply recognitions of
the Integrity of existence itself and
were simply translated in terminologies
that your Society understood based on
the type of society you had at the time
so we do have the recognitions of
existence we understand shall we say the
following binary
principle one all things exist as a part of all
one all things exist as a part of all
that is is the Infinite Creation there
is only one Infinite Creation and all
things are aspects of it two the only
overriding principle on that that is
common to every single being within
creation is the following principle what
you put out is what you get back that's
it everything else as you say in your
language is your ball game everything
else is your definition your
interpretation your game your agreement
your arrangement and it's all based on
the fact that you
exist and what you put out is what you
get back nothing else is common
throughout creation that is the only reality that
creation that is the only reality that
is true for everyone everything else is
a relative truth and all truths are true
and that's the basic Foundation as we
perceive existence that's it okay um in
our Bible there is constant um um uh how
shall say uh mention of devil yes what
you perceive as the devil in a sense is
the combined negative consciousness of
your planet it is given life in that
sense you know it is its own
Consciousness you know but in a sense it
is only fed by your belief in it your
Collective belief in it the entire
Collective positive side of your
civilization is called
Christ the entire negative side is
called the
devil understand yes that's it thank you
very much we thank
you
shoting hello Bashar and you good day
I'd like to share an experience I had um
all right speak up so that all may enjoy
all right um I went and I was swimming
with the dolphins swimming with Dolphin
yes yes and it was really so much fun oh
yes and uh one of the things that
occurred I went in uh to several uh
different pools of them yes and yes yes
okay and um uh each experience was
fantastic but the one that I wanted to
share uh and not take up too much time
was this one the last time that I went
in and I went in uh with a group of six
dolphins and a
hexapod what is a
hexapod I mean what does that represent
is there a symbol for that pod is the
nomenclature for Gathering of dolphin
hex means six in your language oh all
right hexapod okay thank
you um so anyway I had swam with these
before this same group and the second
time I went in the first thing I
realized is that they recognized who I
was right way and um one of the things I
wanted to do swimming with them is I was
hoping to be able to understand their
language enough to be able to write a
story from the Dolphin's point of view
life exciting yes so did you no I
haven't yet well I've had so much
happening since I got back this was a
couple of weeks ago so pardon
a in other words I see yes okay um I
would call it a distraction but I'm sure
it's part of the process but whatever um
so uh see where was I oh okay so and so
when I got in the water with this group
of six um one of them came up to me and
she put her face next to mind so we were
cheek to cheek and eye to eye and she
just spoke with me in her um uh from the
top of her head with the the whistles
and the clicks and the different sounds
and I could actually understand there
was a certain pattern repeated once or
twice and um um what was occurring is I
was feeling uh emotionally very much um
I just felt you know her her vibration
or um whatever the right term for it is
her her beingness and um
that is the strongest point of their
communication once again it is tell
empathic yes I was hoping to get the
clicks but anyway um I mean the
definition of them oh thank
you all right and um so she did this for
about a minute maybe two minutes I was
hard to tell in the water but for some
period of time and uh so and then the
next thing that uh happened is I I went
um further away to see if you know just
figuring that the a dolphin would come
up and interact with me um and it would
be the right interaction so I moved away
from the area and uh I believe was was
saying one it's hard for me to
differentiate still but um she um swam
up to me and she gave me the fin on her
top to hold on to and so I thought what
she was going to do is just bring me
back to um where I got in the water but
what happened was that as I held on to
her fin immediately two other Dolphins
came and we were side by side our bodies
touching one on her side uh she her in
the middle at me and one right next to
me and the next thing that they did is
they went straight up in the air taking
me holding me with their form um up into
the air and then we splash down into the
water and then down into their
environment now the thing that happened
why is
communication yes but I think I might
have gotten more out of it by by far
because what happened because each one
is like um I was told 6 800 lb so it's
with with all of us going up the splash
I've never been in a splash that big
that I can recall this instant anyway
and um with that Splash before that I
was aware of myself and the three
dolphins and all of us touching but with
the Splash and the motion and everything
that occurred there what occurred for me
is I no longer was aware of myself here
I became it was like we were one yes and
um we went down into their environment
and then back up again
and um it was just a fabulous experience
so if anybody wants to go swim with them
it's quite amazing oh and and part of
that same interaction actually is one of
them came um I'm not sure which one
again uh but she laid on her side in the
water and they have the fins on the
sides like their we would call arms and
so half her was in the water half was
out for me to hold on and so then um you
know I just held on to her and we swam
front to front in a circle she just
stayed in that position and did a circle
I can't remember this two or three times
but um it was a fabulous interaction the
one of the things that I realized
swimming with them is that in their
environment um
they they have uh as we have an energy
field about our bodies they also do and
their energy field is so full of play
and love and joy that when you enter
into their environment you become part
of that that's the whole idea
yes but I had to experience this being
in there I guess one of the things that
occurred on that interaction is um I
deal a lot with um releasing um uh
emotions or pains or whatever it is in
the past and with past lives and with
this interaction was particularly fun
for me because what it did was it I
remembered a lifetime that had that joy
and all of the the uh the vibration the
feelings about it well thank you yes it
was was fabulous well thank you for
making such a big
splash all right and um now my question
at the same time that I was having this
interaction I was um in there I went for
a week um I was also having dreams every
night with uh the Dolphins and orcus and
in the dreams however I had no fear
whatsoever when I was in the water with
the dolphins but in my dreams I seem to
have I was dealing with fears with the
orc little trepidation yes well they
Auto since as we have said the samurai
or Sorcerers of the sea the polarity
black and white if you deal with them
you must face many
things so there may be a little
trepidation from time to time within a
few of you when dealing with that much
reflection of your own power but that's
all right all right well that is what
happened when I got back I was
immediately dealing um with the that
those aspects were for me yes and um
thank you very bold
yes I'm M remember in a sense oh yes you
can choose to but in all reality quote
unquote Once you walk that path there's
no turning
back well I met them in the dreams you
know yes that's real to them you know
yes all right um they live their dreams
all right and this was actually a dream
that I lived for me also very much
making that Splash was living and
sharing in the energy see the dream sea
that dreamer often talks about oh okay
now I was wondering also um I have it
seems in my I have an energy I'm working
with releasing some energy in my heart
area my throat area um and I they are
helping you you know yes I do know that
all right and um my preference is to
have it be a real smooth harmonious
opening is there the more you play the
more you laugh the smoother it will be
okay thank you thank you [Applause]
[Applause]
sharing hello Bashar and you good day
much appreciation for your presence and
your help for all of us Reflections back
to you on equal
measures um my question has to do with
uh how unconditional love is expressed
between uh the sex as me men and women
on esana
unconditionally I had a feeling you'd
say that thank you now yeah the idea
generally first of all of course even
though what you may call our sexual
expression used to be similar to your
own it really no longer is in all
aspects in no way shape or form is the
idea of any particular form of sexual
expression considered quote unquote more
right more wrong the idea however is
that for a long time our society has
been very clear about the idea of the
blending of the masculine and feminine
energies within each and every physical
male and each and every physical female
so that when a choice is made in that
sense to be born physically male born
physically female it will usually be
with the conscious understanding that as
that particular biological form it will
interact sexually with its
opposite but the idea does not
necessarily mean that there is not much
in the way of what you may call exchange
of energy and expressiveness between all
forms of life on our
civilization could you say something
about how the practice of unconditional
love as it unfolds here will affect uh
the concept of monogamy or marriage or
traditional male female relationships we
can only give you what has happened in
our civilization and we can project that
there may be similar ideas that will
happen in your civilization but your
civilization is unique like any
civilization and may come up with its
own expressions of course the idea
however is that in our civilization
every single individual on our world is
quote unquote married to every other
individual on our World therefore any
relationships that occur no matter how
they occur we know they occur for a
positive reason we allow them to be what
they are rather than what we think they
should be and in that sense therefore
all relationships that occur in our
civilization all occur within the
marriage understand yes and therefore if
there are going to be what you would
call monogamous relationships in our
life well we simply don't know that
they're monogamous until we reach the
end of the lifespan and say well no one
else showed up I guess that was a
one-on-one wasn't it
but since we know that we love each
other unconditionally and we serve each
other unconditionally then we know that
whatever relationships occur occur for a
positive reason and we learn about Who
We Are by interacting in whatever way
shap perform those relationships
manifest knowing that all relationships
mutually enhance each other and are not
mutually exclusive understand yes does that help
exclusive understand yes does that help
it helps uh one more thing can you speak
of uh the emotions that very often come
up when there are uh monogamous
relationships that begin to change
jealousy possessiveness expectations been
possessiveness expectations been
traditional yes many of them are old
definitions many of them again are self
invalidations many of them are lack of
willingness to recognize that what goes
on in your life is actually what is
there to serve you rather than assuming
you have to hold on to it in a
particular format in order to have that
service done which is quite
contradictory in that sense the idea
also is that what you call jealousy is
simply the belief that what you see in
someone else is something you don't
contain the idea is that if you can see
it in someone else you must contain it
or you couldn't perceive it in them the
idea is to take it as an inspiration not
as a lack of faith in the self not as
having done something
wrong the idea is to trust that whatever
natural changes occur in the
relationship are there to serve and
expand the relationship in the way it
really needs to expand to allow you to
really be who it is you want to be to
understand that by being fully complete
and not quote unquote needing the
relationship out of desperation you will
have all the types of relationships you
really desire in exactly the way they
will be most fulfilling because you will
be functioning as a complete individual
and will be able to interact with other
complete individuals as equals rather
than as desperately needing them in
order to be complete
understand yes does that help very much
thank you so much thank you for being in
this relationship with us and
sharing Bish and to you greetings desani
good day we talked earlier during the
break about the project we're working on
thank you okay you will require that
there be alternating top and bottom
plates that are insulated as was
discussed mhm the idea also of course of the
mhm the idea also of course of the
common brush or Junction at The Rim mhm
will allow there to be a fulcrum Point
through which the shifting in polarity
will occur sure so that it is in your
terminology a teeter totter effect mhm
on off on off yes
yes more the idea
of on off on either side taking turns
being on off sure but something always
being on when what you call the
commutator is in touch with one of the
plates on either side so out of the 20
there'll be 10 on top and 10 on bottom
that is positive ends of each coil yes
okay and of course okay that's really
what we wanted to know the idea is that
there is an overall field that is
created but it acts as a mobious loop it acts as
but it acts as a mobious loop it acts as
a figure eight in that sense and passes
through the center of the configuration
so that the field will mushroom out as
you say on the top and mushroom out as
you say on the bottom even within the
overall spherical field that is
generated these lobes will be created
and it is those lobes flickering on and
off that create much of the effect you
desire interacting with a magnetic field
yes because it creates its own
interaction within itself you see there
is the spherical field and then the loes
top and bottom positive negative
switching on and off that create a what
you may call 90° Vortex pushing effect
within the overall spherical field you
understand sure we've talked about this
before yes does that assist you
sufficient yes very much we just want to
make sure before we went to the next
step yes well thank you very much our
greetings to your planet again and to
yours as well thank you at this timing
we would wish to
extend there will be next week of your
time the
entitlement Legacy and we will discuss a
certain idea that we have not been
allowed to discuss before regarding our
relationship with you we thank you our
love to you and we would remind you in
this way that the idea of the changes
and the Transformations that are going
on within our interactions with you the
changes of modality of format as you
say will represent
a shift in your timing a shift in your
Consciousness a shift in your
acceleration yes in a sense you are
being weaned so that is the whole idea to
weaned so that is the whole idea to
allow you to understand that you have
every right and every Power to stand on
your own two feet there will be from
time to time interactions such as this
they will be less frequent the
interactions that we have with you will
be more direct more concentrated and
more in the format of learning to apply
the idea here with once again
deliberateness and conviction that is
the whole key we would simply like to
remind you from your future selves that
you will look back on all this and
realize that it was very easy all
along we thank you for your recognitions
your self-awareness your Reflections
your dream gifts and the sharing that we
are together I bid you a fond and
unconditionally loving good day and also
to all of you individually and
collectively a hearty
shivi thank you [Applause]
how' It Go [Applause]