Thank you.
First of all, I want to say
thank you all so much for coming today. You might be
doing a lot of other things, but you took the time to
come here.
When I speak to a new group, I usually
start by talking about what channeling is and how I started channeling. [Music]
In most channeling,
as far as I know, people who start channeling
start by making an agreement before they were born or in a past life.
And they start by
remembering something upsetting at some point in their life,
to fulfill that agreement. Every
person is different, and they
live a different lifestyle, so how they
remember that is
different for each person. The way
each person becomes a channel is
different, but there
are many commonalities.
And channeling doesn't
necessarily have to be the way I do it.
Channeling, as Bashir says, is
about making full use of the imagination that each person has.  It
comes in this form, like passing energy through, so it
's not something you have to do with the person you're talking about. The
state of being that you're channeling
is mainly called channeling, but it
can be used in art and in many other fields.
When a person opens their heart to a part of themselves that is higher in consciousness, they may
encounter other beings who are already at that higher level.
Even if they haven't done so before, if they do so
now, they
can allow other beings to come out and express themselves through them.
Many different beings can express themselves through them,
but most of these
beings don't have physical bodies.
Higher levels of consciousness exist within ourselves
at all levels. Apart from that, we
can also make contact with people who have existed in this world before but don't currently have physical bodies. We
can also make contact with beings who have never had a physical body like us, beings in other dimensions.
And lastly, there's the extraterrestrial
contact, which is what virtual contact is like.  They
're extraterrestrial beings that exist elsewhere. They're
not higher or lower than other people or other beings or anything like that, they're just a different type.
Generally, there are different types in our own reality.
In virtual reality, they're generally
similar to us, they have physical bodies, but they're
a little different. But they do have physical bodies. My first encounter with
this kind of thing
happened about 15 years ago. I
encountered the UF twice in one week, both times with a
ba. The first time I was with four
friends, and the second time I was with two friends.
70 meters is 230 meters. It's called a
triangular scout space, and it
's a small one that looks like it comes to play. It's triangular. I
didn't understand it at the time, but I do now.
By seeing it with my own eyes like that, it
triggered me to study and learn enough to remember the consent that was in my subconscious. And
the EVENT was in Channel WhorePR at time.
After that encounter with UFOs, I started studying various things on my own,
such as metaphysics and UFOs. I
also became involved with people who were actually channeling.
One channeler I met
taught many people who wanted to channel how to do it.
At that time, there weren't many books on this sort of thing,
so I
went there to learn what channeling was all about. I never
thought I would become a channeler.
As I was practicing channeling, I was
talking to other entities, and
Bashar came to me.
LIFE remembers Who were they? Why were they?
And the moment we made contact,
Bashar and his disciples told me who they were and
what role I should play for them. I had
completely forgotten the conversations we had had in the dream,
but all of that came back to me. I want
want
never to have that conversation again. After that,
something came to me through telepathy.  But I
still want to continue with that agreement. There
is always a choice, and you
can always make your own choice. I
thought about it for a while, and it
didn't seem like it would make any difference, so I
decided to give it a try. I've
been channeling for four and a half years, and
one thing I want to emphasize is
that I personally
know what Bashis are, but those of you who are
here don't necessarily have to believe in them
because I can't prove it. Right
now, Bashis are more
in the background,
and it's more important for them to give you information
than to prove who they are.
But I said this because in this society,
sometimes people
cling to the messenger or the person who sends the message and
don't listen to the message at all.
According to Maya, in about 10 years,
they will actually come down and we'll be able to talk face to face.
That will be after humans
understand that they are truly corresponding with themselves.
So what's the point of this session? I want
you to listen, take away information that's useful to you,
and then use it in your own life.
And it's important to note that Bashir and Bal
's own opinions are in no way more important than yours.
They've already done a lot of the things that people on Earth are exploring now,
so I'm just
saying that if it helps, then please use it. It doesn't mean that you have to insist on it or
When I channel, I
enter telepathically, but when I do this,
my own consciousness gradually becomes scattered and
goes backward.
According to Diff, all energy
vibrates at its own frequency.
So my frequency gradually
rises and becomes closer to theirs, so it
's good to feel like I'm imitating them, or copying them. We're in similar circles and we
match.
Their civilization is at a higher, more subtle vibration than ours, so I
raise my frequency and they lower it a little,
and we meet in the middle.
I use myself as a model and see Bashar through Darryl,
so we have a telepathic link. It
's not like he's here; I'm
more like an interpreter. He
doesn't speak; he
sends out thoughts, and I understand and interpret them and speak to him in English.
That's the kind of interpreter I am.
Bashar said that the
human biology works better than a machine or anything like that,
so that's what I'm choosing now.
When I enter a trance state, as Masu-san said earlier, it may
look like I'm in pain or suffering, but I'm
simply aligning my energy with Bashar's energy. What I'm
actually feeling is just the energy
moving through my body.
So once again, I want to thank you all so much for being here today. [Music] I really
really
hope you all enjoy today.
The more you give, the
better Basi can convey the message he wants to convey to you.
Well, I'll see you all later.
Especially for those in the front row, when Basi comes in, the
voices will suddenly
get really loud, so don't be surprised. Ah [music]
Hello, it's T. You can all answer, too.
That's how I'd like to proceed today.
Today, I'm going to talk about emotional liberation. Each and every individual [applause]
is an artificial creation of consciousness, but that doesn't mean it's
not natural.
But your true self is
not physical.
This physical dimension
is part of the universe that our consciousness can express, but it's not the whole of it.
When your consciousness is focused on this physical dimension,
this is what happens: you
place yourself within the framework of time and space. And when you do that, you
begin to see many separate parts of what is actually one.
And each of those separate parts is what you see.  This
transforms us into what we call a personality. In order to live a particular life, we
create a particular personality.
Consciousness, in essence,
contains many lives and many
personalities.
If you take one side, you see that one life ends and there's another, and there's
another.
If you take the side of time, which
is an illusion, you can also take the side that all of those lives are happening now. So, if you
look at it from the perspective of one whole consciousness, all of those lives are happening now. [Applause] Each individual life is like a whole. From the perspective of whole consciousness, its parts blend together and
become tiny crystals.
And the various personalities that you all possess are like prisms. They receive pure white light and separate it into various spectrums, various colors. So
your personality does the same
thing. They receive one uniform light and
separate it into various personalities.
Just like a triangular prism, your
personality also has
three aspects. What are they made of? Ideas,
emotions, and thought patterns.  There's
no need to say sorry, translator.
Ideas are just like blueprints,
like a blueprint for reality. Emotions
activate those blueprints, and
thought patterns are what
bring those blueprints into actual reality.
So ideas are the first
concepts, and
emotions are what make them happen.
And thought patterns determine how to make them
happen, depending on each individual's style.
So the emotional part
contains most of the energy.
To make something happen is to create emotion, which in English is to
create energy into motion.
Our beliefs and thought patterns
can also allow emotions to be positive and regressive.
Thought patterns are the things that are expressed in physical reality.
These are the filters that determine how we use our emotions in the real world. So, the type of emotion you experience
depends on your initial blueprint
and your thought patterns.
These three are all related. Only with these
three does your personality come into being. And the
And the
human part of your personality is
created, and you can change it whenever you want to.
As I said, the emotional part
is the biggest activation principle, so you can change
it by how you use your emotions. By using
your emotions
more clearly in the direction you want to use them, you can change the
rest of your beliefs and thought
patterns in the direction you want to take them.
But there's something important to
understand, and I want you to understand that.
The moment you change your beliefs and patterns, the reality you experience from then on will
also change. What I
'm talking about today isn't philosophy, it's the
principles of the physics of reality.
Just below reality are the three things I mentioned earlier:
ideas, emotions, and thought patterns. They
're right there.
So, if you change any of these three, the
reality you're creating in your life will
change immediately. And here's why: The
various events you experience are
all there is. No
situation has an inherent meaning. [Applause] The
meaning in an event is something
you've been taught before, that when
something happens, this is what it means, and you
give it meaning yourself.
When you were a child, in this society, ideas that say this is good are already formed from a young age.
This is something parents almost always tell their children through telepathy. And by "this is
not just my own," I mean. So,
as you grow up and start to walk your own path in life and
begin to take responsibility, some of the subconscious ideas you've had up until now that
no longer fit you will emerge, and you will
look at them. But that
doesn't mean we should reject old ideas or that they're useless. It
's just that you yourself are evolving.
And these ideas
change as we evolve.
There are many different ideas, some very
common, some not so common, and some different from one individual to another. I
'm not saying you should throw them all out the window,
but right now, this Earth
is going through a period of great change.
This period of change is the
result of the imbalance in civilizations that your society has built up over thousands of years. Some civilizations,
civilizations,
some cultures on Earth, focus too much on the emotional side
and ignore the intellectual, mental, and physical aspects. Some
people are even anti-sexual.
[Music] Now that we've experienced almost
all of the different civilizations on this planet, we can
blend them together to create a
balanced whole. When many individuals
many individuals
seek higher consciousness, they often make the mistake of thinking that the physical level is
n't that important.
Evolution is a process in which the entire civilization evolves.
You will gradually evolve from your physical body, and the
time will come when you will no longer need it. But that does
n't mean you have to run away from this physical body now. [Applause]
Evolution doesn't come by denying or discarding emotion. You
evolve by embracing and integrating it.
The less separate you are, the
more integrated you become.
Emotions are very helpful in achieving this balance. [Music]
[Music]
Expressing emotion does
n't have to be melodramatic. You
don't have to cry or laugh every time you think about something. Expressing emotion
Expressing emotion
means knowing you are connected to the infinite. And
expressing it in the things you create, without suppressing or repressing a part of yourself. Let's
talk about the emotion that is most common among your species: fear.
Fear is common at the baseball stadium,
but it is expressed in many different ways.
Of course, there are also great expressions of love.
From our observations,
most things are fear-driven,
driven, and angry,
and the things that need to be done because of fear.  The
biggest fear in this world is that you are not worthless of what you want. It
may seem good, but you yourself believe that
your own existence is actually
worthless. This sense of
worthlessness is what we see most in this civilization.
In order to exist, to
survive, you must do something. You believe that
you have no value in survival, that you have no value in existence. If there was no
value in existence, you would not exist in the first place. This is because the
Infinite Imaginator does
not create anything meaningless.
If you exist now, then
in the eyes of the Infinite Imaginator, you
have some value. The
only thing you need to do
is to live your life with the same respect. Fear itself, the energy that fear carries, is
very strong. I
think you probably understand that.
But as I said earlier, all events and
phenomena are neutral, so if you
respond to them with fear, you will only feel more fear.  If you
approach things with love, the opposite of fear, you
will attract more love towards you.
Many people may think it can't be this simple,
but in reality, the principle is this
simple. There
are two things that exist in all imaginable existence, and these are common to everyone.
But there are
only two foundations. The first is that
you exist now.
And the second foundation is
that what you give comes back to you.
Many people call this karma.
Karma is not your own, and it does not
judge you. It is
not punishment.
What it means is simply
balancing energy. So, if you
feel that you need to balance something within yourself,
whether in this life or another life, you will balance it.
When something negative happens and you decide to do something negative to balance it, it does not necessarily have to be something negative that comes to you.
By consciously thinking about balancing it and taking positive action,
that energy will be balanced.  The
two important words here are
desire and action. Desire and emotion
emotion
are the tools that break through all reality. Emotions are the elements that break through it. Desire
is the element that creates that fire. In that fire,
everything comes
out of the molten liquid, and what you want and desire can
crystallize and emerge. [Music]
What's important is for you to get in touch with your emotions,
and what that means is to get
in touch with that part of you that is connected to the infinite, and
feel that as a positive, not a negative, feeling.
Learn to consciously take action. Don't just
live in unconscious reaction, but
learn to consciously take action. Regarding self-denial,
in this civilization, hatred is thought to be the opposite of love. But it is the
opposite of love, but it's
not the opposite. It's not really the opposite. The
opposite of true love is guilt. And
guilt is something that needs balance.
When balance is broken, you
have to fix it. I'm not talking about the natural guilt that comes from that. The
guilt I'm talking about is the
guilt that denies your very existence. No
matter how small that denial is,
even the tiniest bit of guilt can kill an entire person. Just
like how even a tiny amount of poison can kill a person, so please
speak up about your fears
and start trusting your inner self.
This is ultimate trust, infinite trust. When I say
ultimate trust, many people
get scared
because they think that ultimate trust is so difficult and impossible.
They often say that in this world you can't trust everything 100% all the time. Many people say that there will always be
a little bit of doubt, a lingering doubt.
But when we look at you from our side,
you can't trust yourself 100%.
[Music]
From our perspective,
there hasn't been a moment, even a moment, when you didn't trust yourself.
In your society, doubt is
defined as a lack of trust.
From our perspective, doubt does not mean a lack of trust. When you talk
talk
about doubt, it's a negative way of looking at 100% trust. So,
when you trust something negative, it becomes
doubt. But you think negative doubt is
But you think negative doubt is
very powerful.
Instead of positive trust, what most people do is to
move their trust to 100% positivity. So
when I say, "Start trusting 100%,"
you don't have to feel
like you have to learn something new that you didn't already know. All you have to do is
take the trust that you had in the negative and
move it to the positive. It
's very simple, very simple, and
very fun.
And you can become powerful again, connect with infinity, and
remember once again that you are part of this larger imaginary being.
So you won't have to feel separated from all your imagination.
I think there's one word that can describe the focus of your fundamental emotions:
excitement. It's the feeling of excitement. It's your physical transformation, the
vibration that represents it. Whoever you are, excitement
is a word that describes your very existence on a physical level. [Music]
So many people are desperately searching for their own place in life, wondering
where they fit in. They
're waiting for their mission in life to happen.
And when something exciting
taps you on the shoulder, you
often say, "Shut up, shut up! I'm
searching for my messenger, so do
n't get in the way. Don't distract me with fun things."
You all know very well that your
mission is a very serious one, and
that you have to work hard at it.
But you were actually made from an oracle bone.  The
vibration of your being
is a very high vibration,
so when you raise and match that vibration,
you become the same vibration as you imagine yourself to be.
When you do, you become one with your true, authentic self. And
And
speaking of your excitement, I don't
mean you have to jump up and down every week.
Just by recognizing that excitement, you can feel the peaceful part of yourself. [Music]
But the key kanji is contentment. It's
aligning yourself with the true truth of what you imagined. Remember this: Remember this:
[Music]
Never, never, never, never. It's never, never, never difficult to
become your natural self. [
Applause] So when
you feel like your life is filled with pain, suffering, and
fatigue,
where does that come from? It comes when you're trying so
hard to be someone other than your true self.
All that pain and suffering comes when you resist becoming your natural self.
Mental, conscious pain, spiritual
pain, spiritual
pain, emotional
pain. This pain
comes when you resist becoming your natural self, because
by definition, your
natural self
fits perfectly into this imagination. You may think that you are a separate individual,
but your imagination is 100%
homogeneous, not compartmentalized at all. When you see something that seems
different or separate from you,
it happens when you
see it through the interpretation of your own imagination.
Herein lies the paradox. When you become as
individual as you can, not at the expense of others, but
when you express 100% of your individuality, you become one with the whole. You use 100% of your talents, and
each
part is fulfilled there.
This allows you to touch other parts of this imagination. You can get
really close to the church that you have,
and you can understand what this church line is made of.  This is
created by the definition in your mind.
This separation at the physical level
doesn't really exist apart from what you think it does. It's your mind.
I say there's no such reality, but some of
you may think it does exist.
However, that's because you have said that this
physical world must be like this in reality. Your
Your
consciousness, what you are actually doing, is simply dreaming. The
dream I'm talking about now is not the dream you have when you're sleeping. You
say that this physical world is different,
but that's because you have defined it as different from a dream and
decided it to be different. That's why it's
different in this way.
I said that changes are occurring in the world you live in,
but this is also a change in which the physical level, the material level,
and the non-material level are becoming one.
What I mean is that this physical
origin is
becoming more detached from the solid and softer,
and the dimension of the dream you are dreaming is
becoming more solid and condensed.  The
time of conscious dreaming is approaching, and
in it, everything you want to experience,
everything you love,
can be immediately manifested.
You can break free from the feeling that you are completely disconnected from the universe, that you are
always barely surviving within the mercy of the universe. All beings,
all of that infinite existence, are expressed in many different ways,
and every individual contains the whole. Every
individual
expresses the whole 100% in their own unique way.
[Music] All Dimension All Be
All Dimension All Be
Blend As One. This is when
all of those parts blend into one in an exciting emotion. This
doesn't mean that the ground has to disappear from under your feet at that moment, but you
but you
can use this state as a tool in your life.
[Music] This will allow you to cut through the parts of yourself that deny you, the parts that deny others,
and express your true, original self, living a
passionate life.
[Music] You can
eliminate fear and truly connect with your whole self.  We
can enjoy what we call " Power."
Everyone can imagine what they want, and we can do
so without harming ourselves or others. You
don't have to believe me, of course,
but if we do this, we
can make things work very well. I can't
prove it to you,
but you can understand.
Once you understand that you create your own reality, that you imagine it, you can imagine and create your own life, the life you love, without
sacrificing anyone else. There is
more to this universe than you need.
Otherwise, all of this wouldn't exist.
So, I would like to do a meditation to tap into your passion and excitement. Please
sit as comfortably as possible
and close your eyes. If you want to keep your
eyes open, you can do
so.
Before we begin, there is one thing I want to do. May
ALSO: What I say here and there
may bring out various aspects of your imagination. Let it
Let it
be. This exercise, this meditation, is first about yourself.  This is
also a meditation to help you trust in the universe, so please
believe in what comes out.
Your imagination is a gateway to
infinite connection. It
's a tool and key for exploring your own vibration. Your imagination
imagination
offers you all the things you need to get what you want, so
even if your internal image changes as I guide you through this meditation, trust it. You each
know where you're going, and each has their own unique interpretation.
unique interpretation.
Everyone is different, so there's
no need to force yourself to fit in.
[Music]
So, first, take three deep breaths.
As you breathe, feel your body relax.
Set aside all expectations and feel as if
you're slowly floating. [Music] There's
no need to worry about doing this meditation wrong. You're
doing it right, no matter how you do it. We
're communicating through words, but we're also having many conversations on a telepathic level.
Everything you need to know will
come out within you, and
you will absorb it, and you will do it perfectly. Whether you are
consciously aware of it or not, your consciousness is doing it, so don't worry.
You don't have to do it for me, for yourself,
but for me, I want you to
relax your analytical consciousness a little. If
you want it later, you can pick it up later and then
go home, so for now, just relax a little. Now, I'm going to call you out, but you
but you
don't need to go as deep as before.
Keep your consciousness deep, and keep breathing deeply. How
can I put it? Try not to overinhale and collapse. [Music]
Now, imagine a sea of ​​stars, blue and transparent, and
very shining. You can
actually imagine it as you
feel it. There's
no particular image, so just imagine it as you feel it.
And try to feel
what it would be like to become the Q of that energy.
How would it feel if you yourself were that energy?
What would it be like? [Music]
[Music]
And then, of this planet, continuing to infinity.
Ocean. What does that look like? All All
EXP. You
may hear a voice trying to stop your senses from expanding. Do
n't worry about that.
Now, let's turn our eyes inward.
All the stars are not outside this time, they are
all inside. [Music] This
[Music] This
Earth, as you call it, is
just one point in this book. If
you feel joy, let yourself feel it. If
you feel fear, acknowledge your fear.
Acknowledge it. Don't deny it.
Feeling emotions is not difficult. They are
not something that will ever happen in your life. When we deny that negativity, it
creates difficulties. [Music]
If during this meditation your consciousness
becomes 30,000, acknowledge that.
Acknowledge that you are creating it. Know that these 30,000
states are not falling on you, but are
simply coming through you. [Music]
As you continue to breathe, the stars will
expand out of your body as you exhale, and as you inhale,
they will return to you. The
infinite, truly far-away
stars will come closer to you as you breathe.
Feel the energy coming in and converging into your center, your skin, in the minutes. Then
it comes to the middle, collides, and explodes again,
passing through your energy skin and flying off into infinity again.
Millions of years pass in the space of one breath. [Music]
This happens as the universe expands and contracts again.
As the universe expands and expands, feel the energy inside you
cool down.
And as the stars all come together and
collide in your center again, you
feel an intense heat inside you, like you're in a furnace. You
see a blindingly bright, dazzling light inside the sphere.
This is the heartbeat of the universe, the breath. [Music]
Now, slow down a little, relax, and feel this heartbeat of the universe. [ Music] Breathe Music] Breathe
out
and up in a steady, slow, steady rhythm.
As you breathe, hear this sound physically.
Feel this physically and emotionally.
All, fill all your imagination now.
All and all imagination fills you.
You fill yourself and fill others.
Fill your imagination as it fills you. Imagination
Imagination
demands of you to be filled. There
is no one side.
You are both. And
as you breathe in the star, feel something else. The Love.
Feel the first love and passion that was there when you were conceived. Feel it. With each breath,
feel how the universe is blessing you.
You are a very lovely being for this imagination.
You yourself shine like a star.
You are a very wonderful, shining
soul. You
are Light. You are all made of living light. Breathe
light into you. Let it sustain you.
Breathe light out
and you sustain it.
All
is one. Feel yourself wrapped up in the warm womb of this imagination.
Feel yourself gently held in the arms of this imaginary mother.
Feel the warm breath of the creative father.
And feel yourself as a child. Feel the
child who loves and feels, who is trusted and trusting.
Feel the child who is imagined and imagined. The
eternal, infinite child.
So let the image of what you want, the image of what
you need, come naturally. Do
n't trust it, even if it says it's not true. Don't doubt
that what you need is rising now.
Doors are unlocking within you now, and you will
gradually see yourself in your life and in your dream life.
For some, it's big steps, for others,
small steps.
But these are not planned
or judged.
All stages are equal, just as all individuals are equal. [Music]
Now allow yourself to think this way.
Your reality is and your dreams are reality. Let
what has happened within you over the past three days be realized, and
know that you have changed.
Don't try to find it with your analytical mind.  Let
change find you.
By letting it do that, you
can receive it in the most natural way, allowing you to become your most natural self. [Music] You
can put it out in the way that best suits your needs, and you can give yourself the agility of your imagination.
Feeling is release, and
feeling is change. Feeling is
confident action, a
consciously crafted confidence, a direct action, knowing that
because you choose to do it that way. You don't
have to look at every single step just because you don't trust yourself. It will
naturally fall into place.
All love will fall into place within that natural flow. When
you act within that flow, it will
naturally fall into place.
BRE: Now take three big, deep breaths. [Music]
[Music]
And as you breathe now, a
golden key is handed to you from your imagination. It
's beautiful and so bright it's blinding. And you
know it!  There's a
keyhole in the middle.
Insert your key into it. There's
no need to be afraid.
Turn it.
And step back a little.
And trust that when that door opens, as
much as you feel comfortable with will
come in, taking the time it takes.
The universe will never
give you more than you can handle,
because the universe loves you infinitely. And enjoy
yourself. Come back into this room at your own pace. And some of
you
may doubt whether you're the same person, but you're the same person you were
two minutes ago.
Your ideas and emotions have changed, so even if things look the
same in detail, you're actually different from
who you were a little while ago. So enjoy that.
Now, let's take a short break,
about 10 or 15 minutes.
You're all very excited right now, and I'm
here to tell you all
[laughter].
And in the second half, I
want you to use that excitement in a special way.
Or, even if you're not really excited yet, you
're excited to be excited.  I
think that will be enough. We
will be discussing the evolution of consciousness and the types of changes that can go through. In the second half, I will talk about the evolution of your own consciousness
and the
various things that happen as you evolve. It is said that we are living in an
age of change, so I
think that this is necessary.
Of course, you are always evolving, and
this will accelerate even further. I
will use this excitement in a very light way.
When we did the emotional meditation, we had you experience various doors opening.
There are many things I will talk about,
but please
take this in a lighter way than what we did last time,
and listen with a more expanded and joyful attitude. Consciousness is
Consciousness is
not something you possess. You yourself
are consciousness. I will talk about one very important foundation. I
will create an atmosphere. You have created this three-dimensional reality
as a representation of the various separate things you hold in your head.
And we define our everyday lives in many different ways, in many
separate ways. We
attach many different labels
and define things in many different ways.
When we define things in this way, they do
n't become one and
remain separate. As a result, we
can only see something from one fixed direction. The
evolution of consciousness
is the ability to see one thing from many different angles, because you already
have the qualifications to see all of these different perspectives,
as you were created as infinite aspects.
You are essentially holographic, and there is
something called a laser that creates a three-dimensional image,
and it's like that.
What this means is that each individual
part already contains information about the whole. I think you
can understand this concept in the following way.
Imagine existence as a child. There are
many lines passing through it like this,
and there are lines passing through it from this side, pointing out. There
is information. Let's
say you want to grow and evolve.
And up until now, we've been trying to do this by learning more and gathering more information, so that we
can expand our consciousness
and receive more awareness of the universe. Well, that
's not the case, but sometimes it can feel like this: when we think of
ourselves and other things as
separate and isolated in time and space,
occupying this space and time, we feel like
in order to keep learning, we
have to go to all the different points of this child and learn from them.
And to cover each point, we
have to travel very far and for a long time,
because this child continues into eternity,
continuing beyond the horizon. So when we reach the horizon, it
continues even beyond. We
pick up all the emotions, and we
walk and walk, and we get tired easily.
And sometimes we sit down and
think, there must be an easier way.
And so, this may come to mind: A.
In my imagination, I see a shiny, beautiful
metal number 9,
similar to a ball bearing in your world.
And if you place this shiny, mirror-
like ball on top of the child, you'll
see this:
All of a sudden, all of those photon
intersections are reflected in this little ball, like a mirror.
So all of this information is visible in this one point, this
ball. And that's
you. Everything is contained in one point in time and space.
Those who are seeking spirituality,
those who are seeking it, that's just all of it. [Music]
So when you start the journey, please forget that you
have to keep walking no matter how much you lose your shape. You are
beginning a journey into the realm of reality. I want to
talk a little bit about how changing your inner allies can dramatically change the real world.
For years, even centuries, you may have thought that your spirit or soul
is inside your body,
but that's not literally the case. You may have thought
for centuries that your consciousness
is inside this body,
but that's not literally the case either. You only experience your
spirit or soul as something inside you
when you experience it from the physical side of yourself.
You all think of things in stages, so you
think at different stages and different levels.
So
when you have consciousness at that different level, you think you've left your body.
In BODY Spirit terminology, your soul  The
parts are not inside the body, and the
body is the soul's physical, three-dimensional expression. The
soul's parts are in the three-dimensional plane, and the body is the soul's expression on the three-dimensional level.
When the soul parts leave the body, we
think of it as separate from its origins in the three-dimensional plane, but
when we think about it in that way, it
happens. Consciousness is not inside the body either. The body is actually within
consciousness.
Wherever you look, what you are actually
seeing is simply what you have realized within yourself, and you are
looking outward.
Everything that exists in this physical plane has been
created by your consciousness. The
various things and people you see in this world, and
all of these are yours, created within yourself. When you
look at it in this way, you can see that while you are an individual, you are
actually connected to others and are one.
Your individuality is
separate from others and an illusion,
but because everything you see
is something you have created yourself, you
realize that you are everything, and at the same time, everything. So I
'll say the opposite, but
this is true for each individual.
So what you see is
just one aspect of that infinity.
You are all part of your imagination. You
are just one of those eyes looking from a different place. All eyes are actually equal, they
just look from different places and angles. So the
evolution of consciousness
means seeing with many eyes.
As I said before, evolution
accelerates.
But as change accelerates,
you discover what you have been experiencing in this dimension. The
idea of ​​evolution is that you
discover what you have been experiencing, and that
you exist as a part of that world. So let me
talk about that for a moment.
Here's what is happening during this time of change and transformation.
As I said before, you are the ones who create your own reality. Of course,
what exists exists,
but what you think you are experiencing is
something you create yourself. The
parts of yourself that you think are unique are uniquely created, and they are different from other people.  The
part of your life you live is a part you create.
This physical reality is an
extension of your thoughts. It's
born from your thoughts.
What you think crystallizes and emerges into the
reality you see.
So this physical reality is
something you
create; you
are yourself. Until now, the idea that you live in this real world was common. But
recently, even physical scientists have
begun to say the same thing. They're saying that the
physical reality we see exists
beyond our consciousness. They're
beginning to say that reality is not something separate from ourselves, that it's created by our consciousness. They're
saying that the
observer and the unobserved
are both
entities that exist within the observational system, and that they can't be separated. [Laughter]
[Laughter]
[Music] This is
getting pretty complicated.  Let's
say there is something that you see. You
are the one who sees and the one who is seen. But in reality, your true essence
is this entity in the middle.
This is something that is divided into two parts: the observer and the non-observer.
Evolving consciousness means
bringing your consciousness into a new dimension.
In other words,
expressing yourself in a new way.
Until now, you may have felt that you were within this dimension,
but as you gradually become aware, some people
realize that it was just another aspect of themselves. You may also realize that the
newly evolved part of you is also another aspect of yourself.
So, when we talk about evolution, it's
ultimately just about you discovering various previously unseen aspects of yourself. As you
As you
see it at this level, there
is an individual consciousness at each level, and there is the whole process of evolution, not so
much the process of discovering something truly new.  I
said that, but in reality, it
's about remembering parts of yourself that already existed. You just remember more parts of yourself, so it's
clear, isn't it? Well,
only one person understands this. I
think the person who laughed just now understands. What I
mean by "remembering"
is, in English, "remembering" something. Raising your own vibrations will
lead to that exciting feeling I mentioned earlier. I think your life has taken many different forms. [Music] It
started with imagination, and has now reached the first, second, and third
densities. It goes
through minerals, plants, and the third,
human form that you all see.
These are the three stages. Of course, the
third and fourth levels of consciousness are
not just human forms.
Looking at the universe as a whole, there are many different forms. There are
two types of
creatures that come from this planet.
One is the species called humans.
[Music] The other is
whales and
dolphins. They
are not animals as you would expect. They have the same consciousness as you, but in
different forms.
When we go to other places, other planets, looking for something similar to ourselves, there's usually at least one in our backyard.
And by joining
together with other animals through telepathy and other means, we
can create a single, uniform consciousness here.
Speaking of reincarnation, there are many
former humans, and former humans were dolphins.
This was exactly what happened
3,000 to 5,000 years ago, in your time, in the world known as Atlantis. It was
about 3,000 to 5,000 years ago, and this was around
that time.
And it was around that time that Lelia existed in the Pacific Ocean.
From that time on,
humans on Earth's land began to change.
[Applause] The ground is
a little harder than the ocean, and it's not very flexible.
And gradually, we began to forget that we were connected to the things that live in these other oceans, or to the
infinite consciousness. And so, as
this began to happen,
our consciousness began to exist on various levels.
However, the
dolphin race has not
yet lost contact with humans and other beings at many different levels and far away. I'll leave the
dolphin story here.
Up until now, there have been many changes, advances, and evolutions in your consciousness, and you have been in contact with
many different levels of consciousness. In
this time of change, you yourself are in
contact with many other civilizations. Just
because you say "from" doesn't mean you came from there. I
once said that all life is happening simultaneously, and the fact that you
are on Earth right now means that
you are also part of the Earth. You
You
don't really come from anywhere, and it's also true that you come from everything, from everywhere, and from all
places.
Time and space are reality when you are embedded in them, but they
are an illusion. These words are very limited,
but please remember that everything exists in the present, just as
please remember that everything exists in the present, just as
everything was reflected in the ball bearing I mentioned earlier.
The Earth itself is gradually changing.
And here's what's coming up. [Music]
You've become quite stable on this third level,
and now you're getting ready to go to the fourth level, which
is a more flexible, less physical dimension. We're already
in the fourth dimension, the fourth level, where we live.
This fourth density, the fourth level, is the final level that you can
experience on a physical level.
So we're now at a place where we go from a physical existence
to a totally non-physical existence.
In your time, there are 23,000 years left, and you will
go from the fourth to the fifth, just as we are going through
now. But what I want you to do now is not to
escape from the third
level, but to lift it up. All right, let's connect that to other civilizations that we're not intending to pull you from the Earth but to allow you to go down. We have
these different civilizations, extraterrestrial civilizations and all these different
civilizations, and
making contact with them is
not about escaping from Earth, but about allowing you to go down.  This is what we
do to bring a different energy onto the planet.
[Applause]
This is EXP, so bring your awareness to the planet and the plane, and keep your
feet firmly planted on the Earth. The
evolution of consciousness,
as I said before, is about balance. It's about balancing this level with other
levels, bringing everything
together.
Evolution is about integration, not distribution. It
looks like he needs a little bit of energy, please give me some water.
So, everyone, make yourself comfortable. [Music]
And take three breaths again. You
might feel a little tension in the drop,
but that's
okay. You're just breaking down old definitions of reality little by
little. Just
remember, this time, keep it light.
Express joy and your generosity.
Imagine an energy doorway at the drop of your water in this meditation.
This is your doorway to your intention,
and it's a doorway that will lead you to your future self.
Open your third eye and your head.
This energy connects from the top,
and creates balance from this physical part of yourself.
Imagine yourself as the physical beings that you are picturing in your imagination.
This is the primal part of your being right now. This
is the
atomic mirror of your imagination. [Music]
[Music]
Now look at yourself, piece by piece, and see
this physical body of yours becoming an energy form. See it
wrapped around your body.
And see your body take on any shape you want. Not
just one, but
two or three. It can be anything you
want. [Music]
Just like energy is
moving through it, like doing aerobics, your energy
body can take on different shapes.
Allow [Music] [Music]
energy
from your body to
take on different shapes. Now imagine an axis going
from your head to your feet, and this energy body will slowly begin to rotate.  It
's just like doing a spin on ice.
Turn, in your imagination, and
spin faster and faster.
As the rotation gets faster and faster, the
material part of yourself will gradually fade away.
Spin at a constant speed that is comfortable to you.
Keep spinning at that constant speed. And
And
keep spinning at that constant speed. Notice that
even as you spin like this, your consciousness is not 30,000, but
one. Feel that you are looking
at your existence itself
with eyes of great enjoyment.
You have your senses just as usual,
and you can think of many things. Be
amazed by this.
Just as you do this,
feel that you are becoming more imaginative than usual. Gradually, the
material part will fade away. You will
gradually become transparent.
Now, start spinning a little faster than you are now.
Not because you have to, but because it's fun.
Spin faster and
faster.  You will
notice that you are approaching the vibration of your own true being.
As you spin faster, you will notice that the sound is
getting higher and higher. As you
spin, look up and
focus your eyes toward infinity, the direction you are going. There
is infinite light there, and it is shining and
celebrating you.
PER And as you continue to spin, a
disk-like thing will appear in your heart and in the grooves.
This disk will begin to spread outward from your body.
Just like a laser disc,
various colors will appear on the disk, from blue to red.
It will change color over and over again.
The disk will continue to
spread outward, spreading outward until it reaches the other side of the earth.
Yet, unfortunately, that soon feels like no longer spinning.
And as the spinning continues, it will become
even faster, and at a consistent pace,
so it will seem as if you are not spinning at all. You will
feel as if you are seeing all directions in an instant, all within yourself.  You
are feeling yourself in a way you never imagined possible. It is as if you have become the wind. It is as if
you are no longer material, but simply
consciousness. You have
become the energy of your soul. You are living light. living light.
[Music]
Feel yourself connected to all existence.
You are now spinning faster than the light. You are experiencing all dimensions.
Feel yourself filled with power.
Feel yourself filled with joy.
And you will feel an abundance of gratitude for discovering a new you.
Kiss that imaginary light,
and it will kiss you back. The
whole universe is now filled with flowers.
And just like those flowers,
your roots are firmly planted in the ground. You are
now absorbing life itself, its life fluid, through your roots. As you let
this energetic water
flow from your roots and up your stem, it crystallizes and
becomes like crystal.
In this way,
you become completely and extremely radiant.
And as the wind of imagination brushes against you,
your existence will begin to ring.
You are the music of existence.
Your life is the song of imagination.
All the forces within that absolute whole are
musical notes you can hear now. Just
like listening to an orchestra,
you are now becoming an instrument of beauty. You are now
fulfilling your very
delicate yet powerful roots.
And in that sound, light, and your
joy can now well up.
Clap your hands three times. That's okay.
You are now entering a new field in your consciousness. Your
guides will come to you on a
well-guarded path. You will be
guided by the highest part of your consciousness you sense,
and that light will lead you in the direction of your most enlightened self.
You are creatures of inspiration,
enlightened beings.
Nothing can stop you from the evolution you desire.
Change is the only constant in existence.
Allow yourself to recognize this. Sometimes
change comes quickly, sometimes it
comes slowly. But allowing change
will help you stay stable.
Ask yourself questions like:  Are
you more stable when you try to stand on one leg,
or
when you walk on two?
Movement is evolution.
Evolution is stability.
Grow, change, and love.
Be. Be yourself.
Become who you imagine yourself to be.
Take bold action with confidence,
but don't forget to include kindness and passion in it.
Change yourself when you feel it is necessary to bring about change in the reality around you. Place your consciousness
your consciousness
in the place where you want to change, and the
reality around you will connect with it and
disappear, and move in that direction.
Light. Now, take three light-filled, love-
filled breaths.
You are all artists who create your own lives.
Paint it using the colors you like.
By becoming the individual you want to be, you can
connect with others and become one.
When every part is as strong as it can be, the whole
can become that strength. This is the direction your world is heading in now, the
direction of evolution,
and the many, many dimensions of change.
That's the direction consciousness is heading.
All reality is moving in that direction. To
discover yourself, to
discover yourself as an absolute whole.
And to find yourself as an absolute whole is to
become infinite. An absolute whole
absolute whole
knows that all of the various parts are within you. An
infinite being knows that you are, that
everything here is one. You
are that absolute infinite consciousness. This idea
This idea
can be applied to every moment of your daily life. [Music]
[Music]
Feel this physical reality of yours. Feel it all
emotionally, physically, mentally,
and intellectually.
This is a blessing to existence,
and it is equal on all levels of reality.
This transformation is
about creating
your own paradise. And it
starts with each of you.
When you can be a model for others as beings of love, everyone who comes into contact with you
can benefit from that.
[Music] You can benefit from knowing you are free.
All you are is different from who you were a moment ago.
Allow yourself to think that it's no longer the case.
And remember this:
When you
change the definition of your current thoughts,
you become a truly different person.
When this happens, you
change your future and your past.
No matter who you are now,
when you allow yourself to be defined in a new way, you
can decide the direction you want to go in. We
can all experience all realities, but in the end, the reality you choose is your own vibration. You
vibration. You
cannot experience a reality with a vibration different from your own. The
reality you experience is the reality of your vibration. If you don't
like that reality,
find the vibration you are imagining and creating. The
strongest idea within you is
that reality.
What kind of idea do you need to have to attract this reality to yourself?
Ask yourself this.
And when you find that definition, if
you don't like it,
redefine it again.
Use your imagination as a tool.
Imagine what you want to achieve. Knowing this
Knowing this
can be a very positive thing. When you
find something exciting in your life, and you stay
true to that excitement,
and you're doing it
with as much integrity as you can within your present consciousness
[music], and when you create a new definition for yourself,
know that this new definition is what you receive, and that you're walking down that path.
See and Like
That. Imagine yourself as you want to be,
and then act as if you were that person.
Use all of your senses as that person would,
as that person would feel,
as that person would see, as that person would hear, as that person would
taste, as that person would smell.
Feel it all as you are now.
If you find something truly exciting, feel that excitement,
and you can become it.
That excitement will allow you to become who you want to be.
That excitement
will be the fuel that allows you to become who you want to be. There's
nothing mystical about this, it's
just physics, it's just mechanics. What
you give out is what you receive,
but what you put out and what you give out is what you receive.
Be clear about
what you are receiving, be clear about what you are receiving, and it will be crystal clear to you.
Clarity is key. [Music] [Music]
So,
imagine a silver light in your mind,
and this silver key is coming into your hand.
Imagine that there is a pyramid of consciousness in front of you, and you
put your silver key into the opening of the key.
Turn the key,
and then step back and
wait. Only the amount of light that is most comfortable for you will come
out through the door. A
pale blue light that is connected to all beings, the
telepathic part of you, is coming out now as pale blue light. The
emotional part that is connected to all reality is
coming out as a rose red
light. A green light that is connected to all nature is
coming out of it. A
pure white light that is connected to all consciousness is coming out
of it to you.
LIFE. Feel your life drift with the flow.
Use your desire
and allow your desire to take you. Don't be
Don't be
trapped by the ideas you've been told to think, but instead take everything that comes out of you in a
positive light. If you
interpret everything that comes out of you in a positive light, when you see it,
you are sending out positive energy and everything you
receive
is positive. Someone, someone else
might try to give you negativity, but if you see it in your dream, you will see that
only positive things happen in your life and you
will receive positive things from it. I
want you to remember, everyone, you are dreaming right now.
Wake up and live your dream. It
's your choice after all. Dream the dream you want to see. Your reality has always been made
by your choices,
and it still is, and will continue to be
made by your choices. Remember, there's
no need to rush.
Life is meant to be enjoyed and to
nourish yourself. If you
can live in the present, if you truly
exist, the present also exists, and the future also exists.
You are part of eternity, which
means you are eternal beings. So why are
you rushing? What are you rushing?
Enjoy yourself to the fullest. There's
no need to rush or deny your existence. You don't need to rush to get to where you want to be in the evolution of consciousness. The
fastest way to change your reality is to learn quickly.
But when you feel like you can't be patient,
when you think your patience is running low,
it
's because you're convinced you have to be patient. Patience is a very good thing.
However, when you lose patience, it happens when you wait, thinking that
something else is coming soon, rather than what's happening around you
now. You lose patience when you look closely at what you're creating in the present
and you're not in that place. When you
have questions or doubts about how to move forward in your life,
and you're confused,
keep your consciousness simple
and live each moment
without complicating your consciousness. That's when your consciousness can expand the most.
When your goal is to live in the present, all the details
will naturally work. Wait in that place
and it will happen.  It
's the opposite, but the evolution of consciousness
actually means living 100% in the here and now, with all your passion
and all your desire, with your
feet firmly on the ground, with faith, with
faith, with
all your love, with all
your trust, with all the confidence you have.
Or when there's something you desire somewhere and you
just can't see it coming,
and you start to question yourself and wonder why you're letting this reality, this beautiful
reality, be yours.
When you start to doubt yourself and
wonder why you're letting this reality be yours, ask yourself, why ca
n't this be?
Whatever is being realized has already been
created by you in your image, in your imagination, and it wouldn't be there now.
So take three breaths. Take
three breaths, boldly and confidently.
Sit up straight in your chair and breathe
very humbly, but with pride.
Take pride in being alive,
and be grateful for the opportunity to live this passionate life.
Civilization, your civilization, and our civilization.
We thank you for this
opportunity to interact and have this conversation with you today. We
thank you for being here as an ambassador for your society.
[Music] We also thank you for accepting
me today as an ambassador for our global federation. There are
millions of beings on our side who are
so happy to be aligned with you in this way.
We thank you for giving us this opportunity to identify with you in this way. May
Now, simply
to the reality that is no longer the reality it used to bear, we are walking
through a door every second of time into a and
brilliant world. From now on, you will be walking through a door
every second of time into a brighter world.
Every week, you will be walking
into a new you.  This
is the third and final time. Every week,
you will step into a new you.
This time it went well,
so thank you very much. And when
you come back to yourself,
please feel free to share anything. If you
have any questions or anything else about what happened today, please ask. [ Music]
Please. If you
have any questions of your own, please feel free to ask. Yes,
is this the first or second time? I'm sure you've become stronger,
become stronger,
but this time, it
was heavy and you couldn't break it, so you were able to carry it. [Applause]
What remains? I
said there is no right or wrong way. No matter what is
happening, it is a way to discover a new you.
In this society, energy is a
material thing.
What you just said
just now means is that when it gets really big, we
think that big things are heavy and we
have the idea that we can't hold it in our hands. Remember that
material can easily be turned into either one or the other at any time.
So, if you have a lot of energy,
Holding something means you can get rid of the idea that it is too heavy for your body to handle.
Think of yourself once again as light itself.
Light has
no weight. Light itself has no mass, it has no weight. In any case, light is what
what
makes up all things.
When light becomes particles, it can have weight. When it becomes an element, it
It is the most basic unit from which all reality is made. When you see it as light, no matter what
happens, it does not need to become heavy. Therefore, there
is a lightness behind it.
And if you do not compare it to anything, the
concept of thought does not arise. When you
become this basic light and it
loses its weight, you will no longer be able to plan anything.
So, in your imagination,
in your image,
become the light from which all things are made up. The
various atoms and other things that arise from it
can have weight,
but at their most basic, they have no weight.
So, do you understand now?
Yes, thank you very much.
I'm just talking about this, but it
's turning into a big white thing, and somehow, I feel like
I've gone ahead and I
have to come back, and
then I feel like I have to gradually come back, and it doesn't
fit. Horizons were
clear, since I've been there and done that. I can come back and do many things, and I can come back that way. Once again, as I said before, you don't have to follow my words in detail. Just let your imagination flow naturally. [Music]
Sometimes my guidance is
quicker than you imagine.
This is because if I follow it too closely,
your analytical mind will get in the way.
So
by going a little faster, I'm allowing the natural part to
come out more. See What happens
in a Dream of Time. That's Where Many of the things that took place may come out. You'll probably start to see the changes that happened today in your
dreams tonight. I
think you'll see them more clearly that way.
Because when you dream, your analytical mind is
relaxed and doesn't get in the way as much.
So you can see more of the natural world.
What do you think? Is that okay?
Well, have a good dream today.
Others, yes, yes,
please.
Dreams.
Many people interpret this energy as sleepiness.
By doing so, you can put your normal consciousness aside,
and just like when you're dreaming, you
can absorb only what you need. Some people are
very picky, and they like this and don't like that.
When you put that part aside, you can absorb only what you need.
In either case, your overall consciousness
already knows what it's doing, so it's okay to be wrong. You're
collecting what you need on each level, so
just know that you've received everything you need,
and when various things start to come out, you'll naturally understand. What do you think? Is that a
good enough answer?
Thank you. [Music]
So, I'd like to express my deep gratitude to you all again. And the
sound of release and the sound of change are what we're going to do next.  It
sounds like this. Please remember this. [Applause] A
sigh like that.
And the laughter.
Love To
All. All our love to you all.
And I hope you all have a really good day.
How was it?
[Applause]