Say how are you all this evening of your
time as you create time to exist.
Allow us to lay down a few foundations
for this interaction this evening of
your time. If you wish you may use the
entitlement acting it out.
Well, we have discussed many times with
many of you the idea of your imagination
being utilized as the template to design
the reality you prefer to have over the
one that you no longer prefer. And we
have discussed many times various
methodologies in utilizing that
imagination as a blueprint as you
say in order to see how you can bring
that blueprint into physicalized
manifestation. We have discussed the idea of
We have discussed the idea of
junctioning with your imagination
creating in your visualization
capability the you you prefer to be and
then in that sense junctioning all your
senses into it knowing what it would be
like to think as that person to feel as
that person to act as that person to
have the attitude of that person to
smell taste touch see as that person
would and thereby to acquire those
patterns for yourself to become that
person you see in your imagination. You
say you desire to
become this patterning, this
identification, this mirroring, this
mimicking, this copying, very strong
technique, very impactful technique. But
we would like to carry that a step
further if we may at this time. You are,
as of course we have acknowledged many
times, physiological beings in a
physiological world.
You relate still in many ways very
strongly to the idea of the presence of
what you call a physiological solid
object. What you say you can touch with
your hands, see with your eyes, hear
with your
ears. These ideas therefore have a great
deal of impact. These physiological
symbols, these tools, these
representations of ideas in physical
form have a great deal of impact upon
what you may call your nervous
system, your electrical
conductivity. You place great deal of
importance upon the idea of physical
solidity. Therefore, let us use that
importance. Let us use that idea to
further the impact of your ability to
create the reality you prefer over the
one yet not.
Therefore, in acting it out, in
junctioning with that imagination, you
that you you prefer to be after
conjuring up, as you say, an image of
who you would like to be as opposed to
who you believe you are right now. In
conjuring up that image, in watching how
that person, that imaginary you acts,
the kinds of things that imaginary you
does as opposed to the things you have
been doing in your past that you no
longer want. Remember everything is
vibration. Actions, attitudes are
indicative of certain vibrational
frequencies. And the lifestyle that is
representative of those vibrational
frequencies will be the only lifestyle
you can experience. The only
circumstances and situations you can
experience in your life if you only have
the frequencies and attitudes and
vibrations of the person you would
rather be rather than the person you
would not rather be.
Now to help physicalize it all the more
we have talked about many times the
whole idea of act on it act it out but
again how many of you have taken that
quite literally all right a few here and
there but how far how deep we have
talked about the issue that many of you
already realize the idea that life as
you say is a stage you are actors but
how many of you really act out in any
way shape or form you can what your
imagination tells you is who you want to
be is who you are really physically. Act
it out. Now some of you have perhaps
other terminology for the same idea.
Some of you say mock it up. But
sometimes that only means a mental
exercise. Perhaps the idea will be more
precisely said in what you may call
feeder terminology, block it out. Not
meant in the idea of suppression. The
idea of having a stage area and as you
say blocking it out, deciding where
things are, where physicalized objects
will be, where your props in life will
be to aid and assist the play that is
unfolding. So when you get an image, a
vision of the you you prefer to be,
physicalize it to the best of your
ability, symbolize it in physical
objects. Let us say you have a great
desire to be as you say president of
multi-million dollar corporation. All
right, fair enough. It exists on your
planet. The idea therefore to assist you
in accelerating your ability to be that
individual. As we have already said, of
course, do all the things you can do,
act upon all the things you can act upon
that really excite you. Because
excitement as it is connected to the
ultimate idea, the ultimate goal, the
ultimate picture that really excites
you. Anything that comes along that is
the most exciting thing you can possibly
do is connected to that idea and will
get you there, will lure you there if
you act on it with
integrity. But the idea of acting on it
doesn't necessarily mean that you have
to just wait for an opportunity to come
along. You can create an opportunity and
it doesn't even necessarily have to be
in your terminology a physicalized
opportunity that is connected to anyone
else. Create the opportunity. Create the
atmosphere. Create the
scenario. Find a space, a
place. Fill it with all the props you
can, whether they are in your
terminology the real objects or not.
Draw a picture. Literally paint a
picture. Draw a picture of you in that
reality. The more you can physicalize
what is in your mind's eye, the sooner
you will get into the habit of acting in
that vibratory state. Paint a picture or
even take it one step further. Make it
threedimensional as you say, since you
live in a three-dimensional world.
Perhaps you can find a friend who
already has an office and perhaps when
they have gone to lunch, you can play
act in the office.
Get in touch with what it would feel
like to put your hand on your desk, to
walk your floor, to look out of your
window over your multi-million dollar
empire. Get in touch with that. Learn to
play as a child plays. That's how they
create the reality they grow up into
anyway to begin with. That's how you
used to do it. What stopped you? When
did you forget how you created the
reality you have? You were taught out of
it by many of the assumptions that your
society has. Remember it, relearn it,
learn to play again. It is very
constructive. It is very impactful and
it is very
accelerating in any way, shape or form
you can block it up as a
prop. Even if it is not the actual
material, you ultimately will be in
touch with physically create as many
props as you can. Create the scenario
and the atmosphere to the extent you
can. And we understand we are not saying
that you have to necessarily do it in
front of other people who might in your
terminology think you have flipped a cog
as you say, but talk it out. Go through
the motions. Literally talk it out. In
other words, if you are in what you may
call your corporation office and you are
now, as you say, responsible for the
comingings and goings and interactions
of many different individuals and you
have a particular project in mind, then
act it out. Get all the information
together. You already have the ability
to get together all the scheduling, all
the ideas that would be exciting to you,
pulling the projects together and
imagine go through imaginary dialogues
with all the types of individuals you
believe you would have had to have hired
to work with you who will be willing to
assist you. All right, you do this and
then this needs to be done and here I
think this probably would find a good
time for this. Act it out literally all
the way through as if you are reciting a
play. It is the play of the life you
want to live. Act it out as fully as you
can in every way, shape or form your
imagination can bring it into physical
as you say blocked up reality. Create
the props. Do that and very swiftly the more
props. Do that and very swiftly the more
you as you say dissolve into that the
more you become that idea. You will find
that those props will very rapidly be
replaced by in your terminology the true
symbols the real event. You will become
accustomed and acclimated to being in
that vibratory awareness and you will no
longer have the habit of someone who is
not. You will acquire the habits of
someone who is used to being in that
environment and that is what will
radiate from you and attract the true
situations in your life to give you an
opportunity to play it out as you say
for real. But play it out for real while
you are doing the play. It is for real.
Get into those habits. Allow yourself to
acquire the traits and you will be that
person. And when you are that person,
you will attract that
lifestyle. So you cannot have anything
in the universe except a reality that is
representative of the vibration you are.
And you cannot have a reality that is a
vibration you are not. When you change
the vibration that you are in that way,
when you surround yourself with all the
representations of the things that
really reflect who it is you say you
want to be, you will be that person. And
that person will then have absolutely no
other ability but to attract all the
things in your physical reality that are
truly representative of that person, of
being that individual. So act it out.
Get involved. Pick up your building
blocks. Once again, the ones that now
are represented to you as adult building
blocks. Use that imagination and
physicalize it in any way, shape, or
form you possibly can. If you will take
some time, perhaps if it is of interest
to you, you may recognize in what you
may call some of the personal histories
of some individuals on your planet who
have in your terminology achieved high
levels of abundance, high levels of
recognition, that that is exactly how
they got there. when something excited
them, they took the time on their own.
Perhaps if there were friends present
who could help them, then that is of
assistance, too. But they took the time
on their own to as best as they could,
as you say, block it out, set up the
props, and get into the habit of
actually doing that thing by surrounding
themselves with the physical
representations which would kick off the
neurological responses in their body. So
that there would be no other way their
reality could be that there would be no
other truth for them at that
time. It will work. It always
does. We thank you at this
timing for allowing us to illuminate and
reflect to you one more methodology, one
more way that you have of creating
yourselves to be the way you prefer to
be. Remember that there is no one right
way. There are as many ways as there are
individuals. That is why there are as
many individuals as there are. There are
as many facets to the multi-dimensional
crystal as you can possibly imagine.
That is what is being an infinite
creator is all about.
infinity at this
time. In return for allowing us to
interact with you in this way, in return
for functioning as ambassadors and
representatives of your civilization, in
return for allowing me to function as an
ambassador and a representative of our
respective civilizations, in return for
that gift of sharing. I ask you now, in
what way may I be of service to you?
Hello, Bishar. And to you, good day.
Good day. Um lately I've been excited
about uh checking the uh checking the
Bible. All right. And uh checking your
Bible. Yes. Suddenly uh with all the
teachings that we've been receiving from
you and everything uh a lot of a lot of
things uh make sense. All right. You are
looking at certain things in a different
light. Yes. Yes. And uh one thing that
is not clear for me or maybe you spoke
about before but I didn't hear is about
uh what is exactly the meaning of
another name that we could call the this
the Holy Spirit. Holy Spirit. The Holy
Spirit. Yes. Thank you. And the idea of
what you may call holy spirit from our
point of view in a sense is the
collective electromagnetic mentality of your entire
electromagnetic mentality of your entire
planet. It is the electromagnetic sea of
energy consciousness in which you are
immersed as individuals. It is what
connects your minds to each other
telepathically. That is why the idea of
holy spirit as you say electromagnetic
mentality is connected with inspiration
the acceleration of that blue white
electromagnetic light that ignites your
combined telepathic mentality. That is
why the idea the phenomena you say
speaking in tongues which is simply yes
an archaic reference to telepathy in a
sense has been relegated to the idea of
a holy spirit because when you are at a
high accelerated level of that
consciousness when you match that
frequency of your combined
consciousness. When you match and align
with that level of entity awareness,
then you are one united planet in
thought, in heart, in spirit, you begin
to recognize that you are in fact a
world spirit. And that all the idea of
individuality is not forsaken within the
idea of unifying as a world spirit, but
is in a sense reinforced, is
strengthened. Each and every individual
becomes a literal individual flame
representing the entire world flame, the
world energy, the world light, the world
spirit, the electromagnetic mentality,
the electromagnetic consciousness. Do
you understand? Yes, I do. And uh does
the sound sometime we listen to in our
ears like that? Does it have to do with
that? I mean it's about represent the
same thing.
Sometimes you can have what you may call
sonic translations, auditory
translations when you tap into certain
levels of awareness. Sometimes it is
representative of many different things.
But yes, certain frequencies, certain
tones, certain information sometimes
sounding quite literally conversational
can be representative of tapping into
and aligning with that higher vibratory
electromagnetic energy. Okay, that does
not mean it doesn't have a consciousness
of its own. We do not mean in that sense
to depersonalize it. It is very aware of
itself as an entity, as a being, as a
consciousness. But at the same time, it
knows of itself as made up of your
collective consciousness is for remember
all of consciousness is
multi-dimensional, holographic, and can
be approached from many different
directions, any different direction. And
it is always a matter of it being both
this and that, as opposed to having to
be this or that. Yes. Does that assist
you? Yes. Thank you. May I ask you
another question related to this? Okay.
Uh what is the relationship exactly with
this with the infinite creator? It is
simply one of the
manifestations, one of the phases. Let
us say on a gradiated level, you may
simply talk of the idea of the whole
infinite. And you may, just to be
colloquial and brief for a moment,
simply consider that it has rendered
itself into varying degrees of
collectivities, parceling itself into
further and further compartments in a
sense, arriving at what you would call
the physiological level last. So simply
the idea of world spirit is, shall we
say, a step above the breakdown of
individual consciousness. You follow me?
In terms of your physical reality. Yes,
I see. Okay. That is a very colloquial
way to look at it, a very symbolic way.
It is the best way that it translates
into your language. It isn't necessarily
perceived exactly that way from other
dimensions of consciousness, but that's
the way it makes the best sense in your
language. You understand? Yes. Thank you
very much. Thank you very much. Sharing.
Hi Bashar. And to you good day. Thank
you. Speak up so that all may share. Um
several months ago I had put out to the
universe so to speak that I was ready to
receive any information um you know from
our space brothers that might be
necessary to heal you know the planet
and our fellow man at this time. In the
past several weeks I've had some
experiences in my home that seem I don't
even like to use the word you know
extraterrestrial really but the the
energy seemed to be that way and I'm
wondering what is the best method of
communication? Does it need to be an
out-of- body experience? No, it does
not. In a sense, because once again, you
are a physicalized being, shall we say,
for now, the best method of
communication is to trust that whatever
your imagination is getting is what you
need to get and to act it out, to act on
it, to do the thing in your life that
excites you the most. So that through
your actions, through your service, you
will then continue the flow of
information to be played out in whatever
way represents how you need to play it
out as the individual you chose to be.
In other words, by doing you learn
everything about all your connections
because the more you do, the more you
make room for more information to come
through. And that way you receive the
totality in a conscious sense of all the
things you need to know by doing, by
being fully who you are. You understand?
Yes. And by trusting that your
imagination always provides you as the
gate, as the conduit, as the connection
source, as the communication source, all
the information you need in the way you
need it. Important line. in the way you
need it to be able to apply it in your
physiological reality. It isn't that it
can't come in any other way. But you see
that is not the most efficient way. You
can receive in information but then if
that information does not come in a
format that would allow you to apply it
in your physical reality, you'll just
sit there with it. Oh, what do I do with
this now? So the idea usually is that
when it comes into your imagination, it
doesn't always appear to be coming from
someone else because it has already been
translated into a format that makes
sense in your reality. So you can
immediately apply it because that's
efficient, right? But what about the
ones that do not seem to
that do not seem to
uh apply to the way I regularly do
things? I mean, the ones that I don't
even like to say bring up fear, but an
an unknown kind of situation.
Self-reflective. That's for your own
growth. That's so you can face the
things you have been suppressing within
yourself, the old habits, the old ideas,
the old definitions, and decide whether
or not you want to keep them or whether
or not you want to change them. That's
self-reflective. Remember, that's part of the process,
Remember, that's part of the process,
too. The idea of being in communication
with other levels of consciousness is
never meant to be at the expense of who
you are as an individual. And your pace
and your growth will always be
completely as important as anything
that's coming through you. So when you
are comfortable with being who you are
and when you expand the notion of who
you are by definition, then more
information and higher levels of
information can come through. You
understand? But that information will
always wait for you to be comfortable.
Understand? Yes. And now and then
therefore sometimes the information will
be of the style to give you an
opportunity to decide who you next want
to be. And let's say for now what
station or what program you decide you
want to tune your dial to. You
understand? Yes. Does that help you?
Perfectly. Oh, I hope pleasant dreams to
you. Shutting.
Hello bizarre. Oh, goodbye to you. I
have a question. I've been going through
a lot of uh personal personal turmoil.
Oh, how exciting.
Unlike uh great change
and I seem to have about three or four
different career choices all the time.
Three or four career choices. Yes. Uh I
love music. They I love to act. I've
made money doing both. I also like to uh
do a few other things, but I I have been
feeling stagnant here. I keep Why I keep
flying from one to the other, not really
concentrating. So, I've been thinking of
moving out of the Los Angeles area up to
Washington State to Seattle to get a new
perspective cuz I feel like the energy
doesn't that excite you. That excites
me. And yet, I I hope that I don't run
into the same up there. I'm trying to
find out how do I how do I land on what
really excites me? How do you how do you
choose that one thing? You may be under
the misumption that when we talk about
the idea of what excites you the most in
life that you have to pick one
particular thing that will be the most
exciting thing you will ever do for your
entire life, one overall career. That is
not what we mean. It can be that. But
the idea is that at any given moment
what it is that excite you the most, do
it. Remember also that many different
things that many of you call careers may
simply be different methods of doing it.
the overall category that excites you
the most. Creative expression may simply
be it. It may be as simple as that. And
perhaps singing and painting and acting
and all the other ideas are simply
different ways, different tools you have
to express the thing that excites you
the most. Creative expression in any way
you can do it. Redefine your category.
See what your category is, your broadest
category. The idea doesn't mean that you
have to absolutely forsake one endeavor
for all other endeavors. that you have
to make one be absolutely more exciting
than any other. If you do fluctuate in
that way, get in touch with whether or
not the fluctuation is due to your lack
of definition, lack of clarity of
definition about who and what you are
and what you really prefer. If you find
that the fluctuation still goes on after
you have clearly defined what your
strong intentions are, then take it for
granted that the fluctuation is
representative of who you are and not
representative of being indecisive about
who you are. You understand? Many of you
are becoming generalists now. You don't
necessarily have to become specialists.
Mhm. Do you think it would help
location-wise though? Do you think where
you are? It can give you perhaps a
clarity of perspective. It can allow you
perhaps to begin to see as you say the
forest instead of the trees.
Thank you. Thank you very much. The idea
is to simply trust your instincts and do
not analyze yourself to death. Allow
yourself to trust that you are all of
you are creative expressions, creative
being and you have many different ways
of expressing that and no one
methodology has to take precedence over
all the others. If you find that you can
use them all to express the overall idea
of your creativity, then by all means
use them. You do not have to be so
mutually excluding or selective in that
sense. All right. Hello. Shutting. Yes.
Continue. Okay. Yeah. I've been uh doing
a lot of expanding
and very exciting things, but uh it
seems like the more exciting the thing
is and the more perfectly it is what I
want to do, the more I have a resistance
to it. like part of me. Well, that's
what I'm wondering. I think it might be
some kind of subconscious programming.
All right. What kind of resistance do
you experience? Just nervousness. Just
nervousness. Lack of poise. Lack of
poise. Poise. Well, internal poise,
energetic poise. My energy goes
really unstable. Like if I have a job
interview, if it if did you catch that?
If it's a job I don't care about, my
energy is fine. But if it's like the
best job and I really want that job a
lot and it really excites me a lot, then
I get really nervous about um creating
the perfect Oh, all right. May I ask you
a question? Yes. Thank you very much.
You're saying
therefore when it is a job you don't
care about in your terminology, no
problem. Yeah. Right. All right.
You are therefore saying when it is a
job that does not represent you, no
problem. When it is a job that does
represent who you are, that is when you
start getting as you say, jittery. Yeah.
But if you stop to think about it, you
can reverse the circumstances easily
because the job the job as you say, the
idea that doesn't make you nervous has
nothing to do with you. The idea that
does make you nervous is who you are.
And you can start to translate what you
call nervousness into the recognition
that it is simply excitement. Do you
remember that anxiety and excitement are
the same energy? One from a different
point of view and the other. Right. I I
do understand. I was wondering that how
how you polariz
allow yourself to begin to
realize that when you feel that feeling when you
that when you feel that feeling when you
feel that energy that you are calling
nervousness. Mhm. That energy is there
telling you this is who you really are.
You have hit it as you say squarely on
the head. You are in perfect alignment
with who you chose to be. That's why
you're getting this energy. Right now
the only reason at that point it would
translate into nervousness is if somehow
you doubt that you can be who you are.
Right? How can you be anything
else? How can you be anything but who
you are? Can you answer that question?
Uh, no. Maybe you'd like to consult my
subconscious mind for the programming
that All right. I agree. I understand
that. One moment. One moment. Let's take
it a step further, shall we? Yeah. Let's
assume right now simply because it is my
preference to assume this. You don't
have to assume this if you don't want
to, but it's my preference to assume you
do not have a subconscious
mind. How does that feel?
Well, I feel more in control. Thank you.
Thank you. Exactly the response. Because
if you realize you don't really have a
subconscious mind and that's simply a
convenient label, then all of a sudden
you realize that the truth of the matter
is I am choosing consciously choosing to
believe I cannot be who I am. Why would
I choose that? I don't know. Maybe I
don't have to choose that anymore. Thank
you very much. I won't. I'll choose to
be who I am. This idea, this game of the
unconscious and subconscious mind, oh
yes, it can have real effects, but you
have created it as a convenient label.
This whole idea of programming, it can
have a real effect, but it is only the
product of a definition, a belief in a
definition. And once again, if you
remember that when you know you have a
program, when you know you have a
pattern, when you know you have a habit,
you don't have it anymore. A habit is
something you do, you don't know you're
doing. That's the definition of a habit.
When you know you have it, oh, maybe
it's a program. Oh, maybe it's a
pattern. Oh, maybe it's a habit. Once
you make the realization, you're beyond
it because you have to be outside of it
in order to know you had something like
that. So once you recognize that it
might be what has been responsible for
your behavior. Once you recognize that
you are beyond it and you don't have to
assume that it has any inertia or any
momentum on its own. Anything that then
repeats from that point forward is
simply your choice to believe that it
must for some reason that your society
has taught you and that you have bought
into. So forget about the subconscious
idea and the unconscious idea. Once you
recognize that you had a habit, you
don't have it anymore. Ask yourself,
well, does it serve me to continue to
believe or buy into this notion? No, it
doesn't. It's not what I prefer. What do
I prefer to believe in? I prefer to
believe this. Then act that way. Then
use the idea we have already explained
of junctioning with the you prefer to
be. You will develop a new habit. You
will create it right then and there
consciously. And you won't have to
assume that you really have some
unconscious or subconscious barrier to
break. Now some individuals can create a
very strong fixation on that and in a
sense therefore in essence they do have
that to break. But the creation of the
subconscious, the creation of the
unconscious is your creation. It is
simply a convenient label that gives you
a convenient place to put things that
you don't want to look at. But it's all
right there. It's all right there. You
are one consciousness. Knowing that you
are one consciousness, as you say, lets
you know you're really in control. And
it gives you the opportunity. I say
opportunity to take responsibility for
having chosen to believe in negative
things. So that once you take
responsibility for having believed in a
negative definition, you can decide that
you no longer want to believe that you
can decide what you do want to believe.
You can act accordingly and you can get
that reality. Understand? Okay. Does
this help you? It does. And I just
wondered if you could it helps a lot.
And I wonder if you could give me any
maybe like meditational techniques to
help put more trust in the positive
sides in. All right. But let me ask you
another question as a response. Okay.
Why do you need any special tool to put
trust in a positive side when all you
need is the same energy and the same
amount of power you have always used to
put trust in the negative side? Why not
simply just decide that you will now put
the trust in the positive side and that
will take care of it? Why not just
decide? Can that be a sufficient
meditation? Just
decide. Can that be sufficient for you?
Or do you believe that believing in the
negative somehow is more intrinsically
easy than believing in the positive? If
you do, then examine why you have that
belief and that can be your meditation
too. Remember remember what your society has
Remember remember what your society has
labeled doubt to be is lack of trust. It
isn't a lack of trust to trust in the
negative. Mhm. So if that's not your
preference, why trust in the negative?
Just decide, is this what I want? No, it
isn't. I will now trust in the positive.
That's my decision. It will stick.
Nothing else has a mind of its own to
change this until I choose to change it.
That can be your meditation if you wish.
Okay. just decide. I've been doing that
a lot and a lot Why a lot? Excuse me?
Why a lot? I suppose I haven't been
doing it all the time, right? Well,
sometimes uh I do it and then Yes. And
then like I get a reflection of of maybe
a reality that I don't want to have
anymore. Nope. No. Cannot happen. You
cannot do it and get a reality that is
not reflective of what you really are
doing. Uh-huh. So if you are getting a
reality you don't prefer, you are still
choosing to do that idea to buy into the
negative idea and it's giving you an
opportunity to see that. Also however
here's a tip as you say here's a clue.
Do not immediately just because of the
way it looks assume that what you're
getting is a negative reality. Remember
all situations are fundamentally neutral
and do not have built-in meaning. Just
because it may look the same as it
always has. If you really are a
different person, why would you assume
it has the same meaning just because it
looks the same on the surface? Yeah. So,
don't give it that meaning and you will
not be being an example of the old
habit. Understand? Yeah. Does that help
you? It does. I just like to share
something with you though that that
that's really good advice and it it
works for me. It really does. But I'd
like to say that it's really a challenge
when uh like you know your your car
breaks and it's going to cost $1,000 and
you're broke and you don't have You make
a difference, it will have the effect of
being different. As you take these
things and say this is now different
from this, this is more of a challenge
than this is. As you make that
differentiation, you get the
differentiation. That's a definition.
Why is this more likely to have more
strength to remain in your reality than
this? Why? Ask yourself why you are
making the differentiation and that as a
self-reflective meditation can help you
understand why you have the definitions
you have and help you equalize all
situations. All right. Okay. You understand what we
All right. Okay. You understand what we
are saying? Yeah. When you say well but
this but this but it's so much harder to
overcome this than this. Oh, this I can
handle but this. It's all the same. It
is all the same. If they are all neutral
props with no built-in meaning, they are
all the same. They all weigh the same.
They are all empty shells. Yeah. It
helps to have kind of a a detachment
like they talk about. Very good.
Attached detachment. Mhm. Put into it
what you prefer to. Any meditation you
desire and this can go for all of you
can perhaps take the following form. and
any event happens and you feel what you
may call the old tendency to start
reacting, step back for a moment. Say,
"Wait a minute." All right, let's
look fresh at this. What is this really?
What is the prop? What is the neutral
situation? Define the neutral situation.
Simply explain where all the props are
in what relation they are to each other,
but give them no
meaning. Then decide, all right, I could
give it this meaning. I could give it
this meaning. Which of these meanings do
I prefer? I prefer this. I give it this
meaning. And in your meditation, assume
that you have unlocked yourself from the
time cycle. And until you make a
decision that you will give it a
particular meaning, nothing will go into
play until you decide here's the
meaning. Start time rolling now.
Understand? Mhm. Get into that habit and
see what happens. Okay, great. Thank you
very much. Thank you very much.
Shedding. Thank you, Bashar. And good day to you.
Thank you, Bashar. And good day to you.
Good day. Um, I was extremely inspired
by last week's session and have been
listening to the tape over and over
again and the idea of the difference
between spirit and will and conscious
commandment. Yes. And being able to take
conscious control Yes. of my destiny
rather than, shall we say, turning my
life and my will over to the care of
God. Well, it is in a sense the same
thing. What you call surrender is taking
control. It is simply going with the
flow. The only reason it feels to your
society like you're giving up control
and why so many of you rebel is that you
don't feel like you're in control if
there's no resistance. Wow.
Wow.
Understand? So we even create the
resistance to give us the feeling of
control. Yes. So when you know you don't need to
Yes. So when you know you don't need to
feel that resistance, you will go with
the flow. And going with the flow feels
like you're not doing anything because
it is effortless. It feels in that sense
like the universe is doing it for you.
And in a sense it is. Remember it's
always both this and that. Not this or
that. The idea that it's got to be here
or there, all there all here is again
the product of that polarity, that
dichotomy in your society. It's both. It
is there and here because you are an
extension of all that
is. So when you are in harmony with that
notion, you flow. The universe supports
you and you're in control. And the
thoughts become the things effortlessly
because they are one and the same. And
there's no differentiation between
physical reality and non-physical
reality. No differentiation between
thought and thing. It is one idea.
Remember the issue is not one of mind
over matter. It is that matter and mind
are the same thing.
Does this help? Very much so. Um then
then I'm going to ask you a different
question. All right. The um the area in
my life that I um seem to create the
most confusion around at the moment.
Yes. is has to do with some
relationships that that I have with that
I feel an enormous amount of love. Yes.
Um and so
I have a hard
time just enjoying it. What do you
expect it should be?
That there should that it should take
some form? What form?
Other than the one it has naturally.
My fear is that it would take a sexual
form. All right. Why Why are you afraid
of that? And why do you necessarily
assume that it will?
And if it did, if that was natural, it
would still be something that reflected
something to you. If there was the fear,
it would reflect what you need to work
on perhaps. And perhaps your working on
that would reflect to the other person
what they would get out of the
situation. If it doesn't, then perhaps
there is something in that for you to
consider as well. But all these things
are equal. Why is there fear in that idea?
equal. Why is there fear in that idea?
Well, first there's fear in even talking
about it right here. Oh, all right. But
you're doing splendidly. Thank
you. Um,
you're only talking to yourself after
all. Thank you.
Thank you.
Um, no wonder it's so satisfying. All right.
Self love is where it all begins.
Back to what we were talking about. Yes.
Um, so go ahead.
Well, I think
I part of it is with these particular
people, they happen to be women. Yes.
And so there's a certain um fear that I
have um
of being rejected. Oh, all right.
Uh as what? What they don't expect? What
they don't expect, what they don't want.
May I ask you a question? Please do. Do
you believe in a sense, I shall put it
on this level, that the most important
thing is to be who you are rather than
someone you're not? Yes. Then if they
are rejecting their expectation in that
sense, if the you you prefer to be is
not in that sense who they desire, why
do they attract you into their
reality? If you are someone whose
strongest desire is to be who you prefer
to be, then they in attracting you into
their reality must be keying into that
on some level.
Now, it is up to you, both of you, all
of you, to decide whether or not all of
you are really going to be who you
really are or whether you're going to be
who you expect each other to be. If you
simply be who you expect each other to
be, then you're not in a relationship
with each other
[Laughter]
anyway. A not you is in a relationship
with a not them.
understand? Yes, I do.
Um, is this helping to work some things
through a little bit? I think part of
the the dilemma is Oh,
dilemma. Oh, all right. I will put on my
dilemma hat.
Oh, good. It's like
It's like
um guys,
I
I'm seem to get bogged down in words and
in form and
in what's really going on and how to
express it and all right ask you
personal question.
Yes. Thank you.
Is there simply an action? an action of
integrity that you believe you could
perform a physical action that would
explain everything about who you are and
then simply allow them to get out of
that what they wish to if I had the guts
to do it. Yes.
Guts. That's what it feels like to me. All
right. May I ask you a question I asked
you already?
Yes. Is it most important to be who you
are? Yes. Then why do you need guts to
be who you are?
All right. Well, it's kind of like what
what you said to the other fellow. Yes.
Um it it it seems to go with territory.
What territory?
Of just being who I am. It's it may be
something that you need to face that you
need to integrate, but you don't need to
suffer any longer than you decide to.
Yes, it's up to you. You in describing
it as territory, you're the one who drew
the map. Yes. Fill it in the way you
want to. It's your territory. How do you
want it to read? Just redescribe it.
Yes. Redefine it. That's all. Just
redefine it in the way you prefer to.
And remember, if it's a matter of fear
of
rejection, well, the idea is that if
they reject, it is usually because you
do not fulfill an
expectation. But if you do not fulfill
an expectation, it means that you are
simply being you.
Now if you attempt to not be you just to
meet their expectation then you are
rejecting yourself and you still have
yourself and you still have
rejection. Understand? Yes. The only way
you cannot have rejection is be who you
are and not accept the invalidations of
others. That's their reality not yours.
Understand? Yes.
So does that help? Very much so. Well,
thank you very much. Thank you.
Shutting. Hi Bashar. I do you good day.
Good day. I recently took a class which
talked about the platonic solids. Yes.
And that they're contained within an
image that apparently is on an Egyptian
wall about maybe 4,000 years old called
the flower of life. Are you familiar
with that? To some degree. And that this
um flower of life if you dissect it
rather than with spheres you dissect it
with lines it contains within it all the
platonic solids. How many does it
describe? [Music]
[Music]
Uh seven. Correct.
Although you can call a sphere the
eighth if you wish. Right. Exactly. Um
and that um your society thinks
generally that there are only five. H
there are seven that these platonic
solids the geometry that he described it
uh in this physical reality was that uh
things grow everything grows and
manifests along a combination of both a
binary uh expansion and a fi fibonic
progression or or the fi ratio case um
that is in what you
call your physi
ological mathematical ratios sometimes
referred to as your Fibonacci series.
Right. Exactly.
Fibonacci series. Yes. Yes.
Um he proposed also
that the geometry or the building blocks
like the tetrahedrin all that in what he
described in the flower of life and the
platonic solids is the geometry for all
dimensions. Yes.
All right.
right.
Um, anything you would call a
manifestational dimension basically
follows that template. Well, even a
non-physical dimension to some degree.
It is simply in your terms more
rarified, not as solidified, not as
crystallized, shall we say. Uh-huh. And
that even uh interestingly enough the
way cell division occurs in well the
example was used was human cell division
follows the same similar pattern in a
sense uh recreating all of the seven or
eight actually eight would be eight um
octaves. The idea that everything is
vibration therefore is recognized as
moving in octaves generally speaking.
Yeah. musical or art or color and that
there are um there are other tonal
scales but those usually represent
overlaps from one dimension to another
right eight and then another eight and
the next higher eight. We are talking
about the idea of musical systems that
in your terminology may have 12 tones
and the like. There are such musical
systems or five tones but these
represent overlaps from one dimension to
another. Usually the octave is the
actual barrier shall we say or
definitive line between one dimension of
reality and another. Do remember however
that many different dimensions of
reality usually, shall we say, vector
off of other dimensions at 90° angles.
So there's always that factor to take
into consideration. It is not a linear
progression of dimensions. Many of them
in that sense are holographic, shall we
say, to the side tangentially in between
what you would think of as your real
moments of time are all the other
dimensions of experience. Okay. I Yeah,
I followed that. Um would
uh I was following it and forgot where I was.
was.
Uh he talked about that some of this
information was given to him by a man
named Toth I believe who's 52,000 years
old. It is an archetypal consciousness.
Yes. And still existent. And still
existent. Yeah. Of course. Okay. Since
it bridges dimensionalities, it is not
too dissimilar from what we have
discussed as kacina energy not too
dissimilar. An interdimensional being as we have
An interdimensional being as we have
said an extraterrestrials's
extraterrestrial that which is in
between the plains of what we consider
normal dimensionality and that he himself is
dimensionality and that he himself is
from on some dimensional level uh calls
himself a mechedc.
There are ancient Orion connections to
some of that and it evokes what you may
call some of the priesthood phenomena
that has occurred upon your planet to
some degree. It is recognitions of old
connections. It is recognitions of
temporal patterns upon your planet. It
is recognitions of the vibrational
agreements and arrangements and patterns
of energy that go into making up your
physiological dimension. It is to some degree
dimension. It is to some degree
therefore a gatekeeper type energy. Huh.
That makes sense with all of the
plutonic solids as being in some sense
uh the stepping stones from one gate to
another. Yes. Thank you very much. And
which is what then the whole point of
showing all of this to us in this
seminar was to then to tell us about a
uh a meditational
technique in a sense visualizing some of
these platonic signs. Yes, they can act
as keys to, shall we say, align you with
different dimensional vibratory states
to elevate your consciousness. Yes, it's
doing that. Thank you very much. Um, in
my life, the idea now of being brief
will be of assistance to many others.
Sure. Thank you very much. Thank you.
Shutting.
Hi, sweetheart. and the most joyous day.
Do you? Uh, first of all, I want to
thank Carolyn. She's allowed me to be
her tonight. Oh, right. Which is a very
interesting experience to start off. All
right. How does it feel? I love it. It's
great. We're really hot tonight. Right.
Don't you think we're hot tonight? You
give me what's that funny looking
expression that you're giving out there?
Deciding whether to be in your
terminology hot or cool.
I wanted to continue down memory lane
with you. All right. It's uh lead the
way. It's been fun. Uh I was reviewing
many of the times or recreating many of
the times that we've had together. Oh,
one moment. One moment. Yeah. Simply the
identification that many individuals
later in your terms listening to this
tape will request.
Strawberry. Yes. Now they know who is
speaking. Continue.
You know, a lot of people have asked me
how I got that name, and maybe I ought
to share it on the tape because they
keep coming up. But again, it's fun for
them to come up anyway. Yes. But one of
the fun times was was a number of years
ago when I asked you if you wanted to
ask me any questions. Remember that one?
And you asked me what my favorite fruit
was, and I said strawberries. And you
reflected that that uh meant that I
thought life was very sweet and you
started calling me strawberry ever
since. So that's for the people uh that
don't remember that. Thank you very
much. Well, I wanted to get into, you know,
Well, I wanted to get into, you know,
many of the fun times. You know, I was
thinking over all of the really exciting
times that we've had together and they
all involved around a lot of spirit of
play where we're talking about flying
carpets and uh sailing down Hollywood
Boulevard. In a sense, I have actually
only had and still I'm having one
exciting time with you all. A that's
terrific. There has been no break in
that excitement. Well, you know, along
that line, I was thinking if you would
like, um, I would be happy to give to
some of your Essani people a workshop in
limitation master. They have already
taken it.
They have already attended and found it
most rewarding. Yeah. Okay. Well, it's
fascinating to be able to split things
up and not know that they're not a whole
thing, you know. That's, you know, you
know, so I thought you might enjoy that,
you know. Thank you. We did.
Okay. Well, if you, you know, if you
ever want to, we're still real good at
it. You know, we're still the masters of
that particular area. So, anyway,
continuing along the flow, I wanted to
uh express my enjoyment of of the real
concepts where the dolphin first came
through and we got to swim with the
dolphins and the idea of our telepathic
brothers and I guess sisters and
sisters. Sister dolphins. Yes, they
exist, you know. Yeah. Well, then it
would not be baby
dolphin. Good point.
Well, we're real funny tonight. If
you're reflecting us, you are hysterical. And
hysterical. And
anyway, that's all been real enjoyable.
I just wanted to mention a couple things
on that. Thank you very much. And leave
you with my uh my interesting question.
Yes. which is on this planet, you know,
uh speaking of uh the ability to be
prolific, we are producing vast amounts
of bodies, you know, and crowding them
into uh small areas. Yeah. And I noticed
that on your planet you said you had
what population? A couple million
something of that sort. We spread of
what you may call a permanent
population. There is approximately the
notion of 230 million. 230 million. The
idea is that the rest of the population
will be temporary in nature. either in
your terminology, individuals passing
through or individuals temporarily
taking on the form of our bodily mass so
they can have an experience upon our
planetary dimension temporarily and then
simply converting back into energy when
that experience is over. Right? But the
permanent population approximately is
230 million of your counting. Although
once again at any given moment fully 2/3
are within what you call spacecraft and
not on the surface of the planet anyway.
Right. And the concept is very nice, you know,
And the concept is very nice, you know,
with regard to our civilization evolving
into a similar park-like environment.
And I wanted to get your reflection on
how you felt that we would evolve in
this area in terms of handling the
quantity of bodies we've produced
without um limiting the number of spirits. I
um limiting the number of spirits. I
guess you have a come and go type of
sense situation. How do you see us
evolving? Well, the idea first of all is
to recognize that you actually have more
than enough room. It's simply that you
are in your terminologies cramming
everyone into a very small amount of it.
You do not really have overpopulation.
You have restriction of space that is
much land upon your planet that when
converted into what you may call a
natural park-like state will be more
than sufficient for the amount of bodies
you have on your world, plus quite a few
more. Plus again as you develop your own
technology to move out in what you call
the stars there will be more than enough
room. Okay. So you see it according
moving in that kind kind of. Yes. Good.
Also eventually you will be in your
terminology incarnating less and less
and eventually in what you may call a
few of your thousand years many of you
will be sharing bodies since you will
not need a full lifespan experience.
Lovely. Okay. Well, that makes a nice
smooth evolution. Yes. Good. Thank you
very much. My pleasure. Thank you,
Bashar.
Sharing Bashar. And good day to you. I
have been listening to you for several
years now on tapes and being here. All
right. Do speak up so that all may share
what you have to say. Be bold.
All right. Uh what I wanted to say is uh
I've never asked a question or anything
here but uh and I don't have one now but
I want to say how much I appreciate you
being here for us. Our unconditional
love to you and your willingness to
discover all that you have created
yourself to be and were created to be.
Thank you. I'm definitely not the same
person I was several years ago. Not the
same person you were a moment ago.
That's true.
We thank you. Thank you. Our love to
you. Peasantry
shooting. Good evening, Bashar. And to you, good
Good evening, Bashar. And to you, good
day. I wanted to thank you for all the
beautiful energy you bring out in us.
Oh, and you you you you for do
understand we reflect to you an energy,
a level of energy. If you feel that
energy, it's because you are choosing to
match it. So what you're feeling is you.
Thank you.
Uh recently I started work working with
a uh audiovisisual brain synchronizer.
Yes. And I'm very excited about it even
though very little if experimental uh
research work has been done on it. All
right. Perhaps you can expand the field
with your own experimentation. Uh I'm
very excited about it and the people who
uh are doing it uh like it and I was
wondering uh what you could tell me
about it and what you're feeling about
it. One of the ways, not the only way,
one of the ways that you can convert
what your society has defined as left
and right hemispheric activity into one
homogeneous interaction because you are
one brain. The idea now again is that
you are consolidating all your
differentiations into one homogeneous
idea. So it can blend and balance what
has for a long time thought to be
segregated hemispheres into one idea.
Creating a flow, a pattern flow of
information exchange so that your brain
can function as it was truly designed to
holographically consciously
holographically so that everywhere has
access to everything you need and that
one area doesn't necessarily have to be
as limited in its capacity as it has
been defined it ought to
be. So it can synchronize you that way.
Also what you may call a very simple
brain synchronizer is the following
idea. Allow an individual and this is
very very impactful for individuals in
your terminology that experience what
you call
epilepsy, stuttering,
dyslexia and many similar
manifestations. And the idea of brain
synchronization can be this simple. When
you are speaking to that individual,
simply take your hands and do
this and allow their vision, not that
they have to follow it identically, to
simply be aware of the fact that you are
doing that. And as you do that at a very
that. And as you do that at a very
relaxed pace, while you are speaking
perhaps to that individual, let us say
for now just because it is a strong
indicator that they have
stuttering. While you are doing this,
you will begin to notice that it will
subside. And as you do
this, you will begin to allow them to
homogenize, taking visual cues from your
suggestive motions. They will not stutter while
motions. They will not stutter while
they speak to you. Generally while you
are doing this if they are keying in on
in what you're
doing as soon as you stop they can
choose to continue that flow or they may
break it and go back to the stuttering.
But while you are doing this they will
in that sense
subdue the short circuiting that causes
the effect of the stuttering. And when
you do this they will be in harmonious
communication with the totality of their
brain and will exhibit a flow. This can
aid to some degree in epilepsy as well
and dyslexia and many other
manifestations. Do understand
however there are many different kinds
of manifestations of this idea. This
will not necessarily work for
everyone. And also do remember that what
you call many forms of channeling is
simply a coherent and cohesive
manifestation of what when
shortcircuited is what you call epilepsy
because it is a type of electrical
conductivity that in epilepsy it is
simply cross-wired and shortcircuiting
inwardly and when channeled is
coherently flowing outwardly. It is much
the similar phenomena
understand. Yes. Does this assist you?
Very much so. Uh also I was thinking
about using positive suggestions and
subliminal suggestions while the person
is using the synchronizer. Uh how do you
feel about that? It can be effective.
However, we would suggest that you be
very clear about your own intention. Be
very clear about what the other
individual's belief system is regarding
your integrity because they may
interpret some of your suggestions in a
negative way and that may in your terminology
way and that may in your terminology
actually accelerate some of the negative
experiences they might have. We would
suggest that your suggestions remain
basically on what you would call the
conscious level. They will absorb into
what they have created to be other
levels whatever they need. But allow
them to know everything is absolutely
out in the open. They are in control and
they are co-creating with you a
manifestation, an event. They are not
actually relinquishing control. They
have control. They always have control.
They are allowing you to be a guide. We
would suggest that you remain as a guide
in a conscious state for them and allow
them to understand that is up to them to
absorb whatever they want when they feel
they need it. And it won't be a matter
of you implanting subliminal suggestions
in that sense. It'll be a matter of you
giving them a wide range of frequencies
and allowing them to pick in their own
timing on whatever level they want to
what they want when they want it. Just
let them know they will key themselves
where they need to when they need to.
You will just put it all out there. You
will give them all the information on
all the levels all at once. In a sense,
that's what we're doing with you right
now. There are many things about these
interactions between us that you do pick
up on as you say
subliminally. Much of what you
experience as the gestures in the
physiological channels hands are
actually representative of levels of
conversation you are not hearing but
only seeing. The idea is that we are not
in a sense actually giving you
subliminal suggestions but we are
vibrating on many different levels. You
will take out of all those levels what
you need when you need to. We do not
have to purposely plant a subliminal
suggestion. You understand? The
information is there when you decide to
open a door. The information will rush
right in when you need it in the way you
need it and only at the pace you say you
can use it
best. Understand? I understand. They
hear the uh the subliminal suggestions.
they first hear them so they know what's
will be uh heard subliminally and if
they okay it my question was would it be
more effective if it can be for some
individuals we will allow you to leave
that up to your discussion with them and
their discretion
okay uh can I ask another personal
question brief okay uh I was in a
relationship with somebody uh very
intense relationship two year two years
ago and then the relationship dissolved
and it changed transformed
Right. And somehow uh I haven't been
able to connect up with anybody else in
all that time. And what about yourself?
Well, I I I didn't connect with anybody
else in two years. And uh last week he
called me again and uh but he's not
interested in reestablishing the
relationship and somehow there's a lot
of excitement in me about it. You mean
in the old way?
Uh in whatever way he's just not
interested. I don't know why he called
but that is an establishment of the
relationship. Uh I I still feel that there is a
Uh I I still feel that there is a
tremendous connection there. There
always will be. Just because you may not
necessarily physiologically be together
doesn't mean there isn't a connection
doesn't mean there isn't a relationship
going on. Somehow I have a sense of
impatience like I want to be released
from it uh or uh be together again uh
but not to just somehow hang in the air.
Then have you established firmly as you
can the relationship of yourself to
yourself? Are you being fully the person
you want to be?
Uh, I'm getting there.
How long will it
take? Just because you may not be
physically doing certain things that
someday you will be doing, doesn't mean
you can't be fully being who it is you
are right now. Understand? Uh, I'm
really very happy with everything I'm
doing. I'm very excited about everything
I'm doing and this person energy-wise
doesn't really fit into my life because
he's bored with life and he doesn't have
the energy. Then where is the impatience
coming from? Get on with the life. I
don't know. I don't know. Somehow I
still feel like I'm um I'm not released
from that relationship and there's
something there that pulls me and kind
of May I ask a personal question? Sure.
What did you learn about yourself by
being in that relationship in the way
you were in it?
Um, oh, many things, but I can't think
right now of a specific thing because an
overall idea, an overall definition, an
overall category that all of the many things fit
category that all of the many things fit
into. What did you learn by being in
that relationship? I learned that I can
love unconditionally. Right.
And uh even though
uh this person that I'm so connected to
is not excited about things I can wait
for that individual to catch up.
Sort of. Yeah. Sort of. Somehow it seems
that way like like there's a waiting.
I'm not waiting with my own life because
I'm very excited about everything I do.
All right. You have been connected to
that individual many times in many
lifetimes. Their reestablishment may
simply be an opportunity for them to
begin to face certain things that they
feared to face before. You may simply
actually only be feeling their own
impatience, not really yours. Uh-huh.
Understand? You may simply be
identifying telempathically with them.
It may not really have anything to do
immediately with your life. Let them
work out their own timing. Be willing to
be of service. Be willing to be a
reflection. That's all right. It will
not hinder you. You don't have to feel
that there is any unresolved idea within
yourself. Let them as you say bounce off
of you, reflect off of you as they need
to. You can still willing to be of
service to them in that way without in
any way, shape or form decelerating the
life you prefer to be, but they may
still need to see certain reflections
from you in certain ways to learn about
who it is they want to be. You may only
be picking up on their idea that they
are waiting to be who they are rather
than it having anything really to do
with you. Do you understand? Yes. Yes.
It seems that way because it just comes
out of the blue. I'll be involved with
something. Then do not worry about it.
Get on with your life. Okay. Be who you
are and let them work out their own
timing with you.
Thank you. Oh, thank you very much. Yes.
This timing. You may all take a short
break. We will resume contact in
approximately 10 to 15 of your minutes
of count.
How's it going? Fine. Good.
Quick announcement. Someone is parked
back here in the little alleyway back
here. before before
beginning again.
Allow dreamrer
consciousness communicate few ideas to you. Timing
communicate few ideas to you. Timing
now timing your month call
March month especially mid March month
15th day you call I of March gate of
transition gate of connection very
strong blending human consciousness
dolphin consciousness consciousness Yes, very
consciousness consciousness Yes, very
strong energy gate once again connection
you especially
California Shasta Japan Fuji
Hawaii connection triangle of Pacific
energy flow consciousness blending of
human dolphin extraterrestrial.
Oh March M be swimming in dream be
accelerating dream blending society
dolphin and human and whale into one
acceleration of energy open dream
doorways ID of march especially strong
for receive energy of acceleration
bonding of civilization as one we swing
to gallary very active that night and
all through March month of your time for
acceleration thereafter. Time of change,
time of
facing many idea come to the surface of
the sea that you are to bring to surface
in sunlight to lay out and float upon
way for all to see. Be not
afraid. It'd be pieces of your past,
pieces of your present, pieces of your
future blending together to form in
light of sun, new sustenance to sustain
you, new food for thought and blending
of heart and telempathic waves of
consciousness. We thank you for timing
of acceleration and for timing of
ascension into one world, one harmony.
So we swim in same energy. See our
heart, our play, our life, our love with
you now and dream time
forever. Thank you and share you light
and love.
At this time we shall say continue.
[Music] For new people would you care to give
For new people would you care to give
some information about dreamer idea that
is called dreamer is in your terminology
a physiological male large gray Pacific
dolphin that
usually inhabits the coastline of your
New Zealand area but has been known to
wander throughout the Pacific basin. Any
dolphin consciousness which we perceive
as the other alien society upon your
planet other than human
life is called a dreamer when they have
taken upon themselves the actual job of
interfacing not only through telepathic
contact and dream contact but
physiological contact interfacing with
your human species as well to blend your
civilization into one civilization made
up of two distinct species. You are very
very in that sense fortunate, very
blessed in that sense to be a world of
two species. For you have right, as you
say, on your own doorstep an unlimited
and beautiful opportunity to really
learn to interact with what you may call
nonhuman consciousness without having to
travel to the stars to do so. That is
the first alien contact that will take
place. And when your world is blended as
such, it will do much in the aiding of
the accelerational ability for us to
interact with you as well as
offworlders. But dreamer is simply the name given to
But dreamer is simply the name given to
any dolphin who chooses to interact with
your society in that way. Although this
is a reference to a specific
physiological dolphin in your Pacific
waters. We thank you. Continue.
Hi Bashar. Thank you. Good day. I'm
excited to be here. Oh, we are very
excited you are there. Thank you. Um I I
Hi. Hi. Oh, thank you. Very profound.
Yes. Yes.
[Music] Um, I've been doing a lot of processing
Um, I've been doing a lot of processing
and a lot of expanding and a lot of a
lot of uh really growing in my love
personally and unconditionally. All
right. Can you all hear this individual
adequately? I'll step closer. Thank you.
Yes. Um, anyway, one thing that I've
been feeling that comes and goes, but
but uh anyway, is that it it's like I'm
swimming Yes. in the ocean. Nice. But
but I'm not going from one side to the
other. I I I get a little lost. Lost.
Yes. Because partially I guess what I'm
doing is making a judgment on that you
should be getting somewhere. That I
should be getting somewhere. Right. What
about just enjoying the swimming? Well,
yes, I am enjoying the swimming. But
well, you know, it ties into my my whole
thing with abundance. Yes. Yes. And and
in these years that I've been
uh expanding and growing and just
enjoying being and doing I I have a
sense that that externally I should be
reflecting more I realize this but I
should be reflecting so that I can see
what I'ming internally externally
and and what I'm experiencing a lot
which I am manifesting ing externally.
There's a lot of abundance with a lot of
people that are out there providing me
with a lot of things that that keep me
going or that I need or want and I'm
experiencing a lot of abundance that
way. All right. However, what I'm
feeling is is that I really deserve to
be able to do that for myself in
additional ways such as as being able to
create money abundantly. All right. May
I ask you a question? Yes. In their
providing of service to you, do you
provide service to them? Yes. Lots. All
right. Yes. Then it is in your
terminology an equal exchange.
Yes. No. Maybe. Yes.
What other idea could you expand into,
as you say, beyond that to allow other
methods of abundance to show themselves
to you in your life?
If I can answer that this way. See,
that's where I get a little lost because
what I feel that I've been doing is
is really touching into my excitement.
Um, it Well, what I mean is what I what I
it Well, what I mean is what I what I
mean is that that that staying real
sensitive to it so that I can so that I
can be clear what excites me in the
moment that I can act on and so forth.
And you are acting on it. Yes. All
right. But I'm not getting the results. It's
But I'm not getting the results. It's
terrible. Can you be specific? Um,
yeah, I can I can uh I can specifically
u bring up one thing which is real
symbolic to me in a lot of things in my
life and that is a project that I came
up with. um which I which I basically
took from just an idea and I created it
and I created it real well and I got it
to where I wanted to to to have it and I
just really I put a lot of a lot of love
and effort into it. So then I realized
well in the sense of of completed myself
in the sense of of completed myself
because a lot of times it's really easy
for me just to get excited about
something and then get excited about
something else. So I chose that since I
was really excited about this and I had
a lot of love with that that I was going
to continue that. All right. So then I
realized symbolically in my life that I
was real attached to a lot of other
things and one reason why my particular
little project was not in its little um
was that I was real attached to it. So
then in that I I let it go because I
realized that my love was attached to
it. it was really mine and in the
process of letting go and coming up with
a value of that then I could kind of
complete a circle in receiving. So I
what what I've basically done is to is
to really be sensitive to that which is
exciting that I can act on only I'm I
feel now that I'm doing I'm not doing
something that I could be doing because
I'm not I don't know that's probably why
I'm asking you this question is because
that's I feel I feel a little lost
because I'm I'm I don't know. I don't
know. Perhaps you are for a while simply
becoming involved in the process itself
and realizing that the process in and of
itself is a valid place to be just as
valid as any other place you could be
going to with the process. The process
in some senses is its own destination.
I understand that and but that's where I
have been and I'm really feeling that
that I don't need to explore that
anymore. I feel that I feel it's a step
beyond that only I'm not manifesting
that externally. Do you have the
visualization of where you wish to go?
Yeah, I do have I do have a
visualization of where can you define
it? Do you have a particular direction
that you can define in words or
symbology at this time?
Well, um
I'm not exactly sure exactly what you
want me to say. Oh, all right. Yeah,
I'll rephrase. Thanks. Now that you are
immersed in the process itself and now
that you have used this process so
sparklingly for many other ideas, is
there you say a feeling as you say there
is a feeling that there is this
particular direction you could be going
in. Well, is there a definition for this
direction? Is there some particular
thing you would now allow yourself to do
that you have not done before that you
would really like to do? Yeah. What is
it to totally divert now?
Um I I feel like Yeah. In fact, I
stepped back from my project because I
now feel like putting some attention to
my to my writing which is what I feel
like doing right now. And that's what I
feel like doing right now. Yes. Then why
aren't you doing it?
Well, actually, I am doing it in a sense
because in a sense, well, what I mean is
I haven't actually put it to paper, but
it's in I'm I'm doing it. I'm just not
with pencil and paper yet. I see. What
did we talk about blocking it out?
Right. So, I got that. All right. I got
that. Will you use it? Yeah. If you do
that, very Yeah. Will that satisfy the
urge? Yes. Will you feel like you are swimming
Yes. Will you feel like you are swimming
in a particular direction?
Well, yes. Yes. I It's just that I I do
that. I get real involved in what I'm
doing and I really get into a direction
and I really block out. Yes. But then
somehow somewhere it doesn't back me up.
I don't know. That's In what way do you
think it ought to back you up?
Uh well, if I'm really doing what what
what excites me at the moment that I can
act on. Yes. Then I should be able to
should That's right. Yeah. Right. Should be
That's right. Yeah. Right. Should be
able to do what I felt I I I felt or I
feel when I really immerse myself in
something that Stop. Yes. Thank you. You
have opened a small. Good. Good.
There may be in many cases. Now let us
simply be general for a moment. In many
of these cases as many of you discuss
with us the process each and every idea you
us the process each and every idea you
go through may in and of itself be
simply a process and that may be
sufficient. In other words, you may
think maybe that there is an ultimate
end or conclusion or goal to a
particular endeavor that you're doing,
but you may find at the same time that
doing the endeavor, that particular
portion of it may be sufficient to give
you what you need. And that may be the
only reason you did it to begin with to
have that experience and not necessarily
carry it to what your society says is
the fruition or the representation of
true fruition. In other words, just
because you sit down and are very
excited about writing at one particular
given moment doesn't necessarily mean it
has to be published as a book. It may
have been the writing itself is what was
exciting. In other words, perhaps for
you what for some people is simply a
detail, a step on the road of the thing
that excites them is for you the true
thing that excites you and is not a
detail. The work itself, the doing itself may in
The work itself, the doing itself may in
and of itself be what excites you. And
if you focus on the understanding that
you may simply be a server in that way,
that you may be a facilitator in that
way, then individuals can hire you for
your ability to do the
process itself because you are so good
at the process. And that may be what
excites you. Rather than really feeling
like you have to have this come to this
conclusion or manifest this way in your
society, it may be the process in and of
itself that for you is the goal and
sufficient at that.
Understand? Mhm. Now, how does that
feel? Yes. No. Maybe.
We're not saying that there cannot be
certain things you would like to bring
to fruition. We are simply saying that
there may be these certain things, but
you may be assuming that everything you
do must follow that suit.
No, I that that uh that resonates with
me and I do I do do a lot of things for
the actual process just doing it and I
and I get a real thrill and excitement
out of that. And can you do that for
others that do not find those processes
exciting?
H that doesn't really excite me. Oh, all
right.
Um, I guess I'm just feeling real
consciously that that that I don't want
to just process.
It isn't a process if it is your goal
itself. If sitting down and being
excited simply about writing something
is your goal, then that is the doing of
the thing. It doesn't have to be looked
at as a process of getting to somewhere
else. Oh, no. I can Yeah, I can. I I've
got that. I mean, I I understand that.
Do you wish now at this point in the
conversation to discover whether or not
anything else as a quote unquote goal
has reared itself as being more
specific, a direction you would really
like to go in? Has anything else arisen
during this conversation within you as a
particular direction in which you would
like to proceed that you have not
proceeded in yet?
Um, who would you really like to be?
What would you really like to be?
Really? Okay. Well, that I can I can
just take that and leave that with our
conversation right now because I can I
can take that on my own and just
meditate on that and really go into
that. Oh, okay. I'm not going to let you
get away that evening. Oh, I had that
feeling.
Can you answer the question?
What would you really really
really like to be?
What would I really?
No. Really?
Um, what I'd really really like to be
Yeah. would be I'd really like to be a
writer that could put together my whole
project and just go through the whole
process and put it through. Whole
project? My writing project? What is it?
Well, I don't have a specific project.
Why not? Well, because what do you
really really want to say?
Until you understand what you want to
say, you're not going to move in a
particular direction. Yes. Maybe that's
the crux. What do you really want to
say? Get in touch with that. That can
very easily define who you really are.
What do you really have to say? Yeah.
So, I've got three things and what I'm
what I'm going to do then is is is to
focus in on the one that I really want
to do and really do it. Thank you very
much. Thank you very much. Keep it
simple. Shutting.
Hi, Bashar. How do you good day? Um,
I've been feeling very uh separate and
lost and I was wondering how do you feel
a sense of safety and connection with
all that is? Do you know that you are an
aspect of all that is? Yes. Are you sure
you know that? No. All right. Why don't
you know that?
I don't feel it. You don't feel it?
Thank you very much. Do you know what a
feeling is? Yes. What? It's a internal
energy. But where does it come from? How are
But where does it come from? How are
feelings created?
I'll give you our definition if you
wish. Yes. So the response to a belief,
an unconscious response to a belief
doesn't have to be
unconscious can be a choice. Now if you
know Oh, first of all, do you believe
that? Yes. Really? Yes. All right. You
believe that feelings are a reaction to
something you already believe? Yes. All
right. So you say you feel cut off from
the infinite. Yes. So what does that
mean? It means you believe you are cut off
It means you believe you are cut off
from the infinite. Yes. Why do you
believe that? What definition would you have to
that? What definition would you have to
have inside you that you have bought
into that would be your choice to say
you are cut off from the infinite? Is
that what you prefer to believe?
No. If you do believe that since in a
sense you obviously have chosen to
believe that it's all right to own that.
You know, you do not have to deny it.
Denial of anything that you have done is
the key to cutting yourself off. So
don't deny your denial first of all. So
if you have created a belief wherein you
have denied your connection to the
infinite, own it. Don't deny that. Own
it. Say, "All right. All right. I did
choose to believe I was cut off." Now
you can ask yourself, "All right. How
did it serve me to believe that?" Go
ahead. Ask yourself. Did you get an
answer?
You created more aspects to experience.
All right. Was that enjoyable?
No, not right now. Did you learn
something from
it? Did you learn something from having
created more aspects of yourself to
experience? Anything at all? Name one
thing you learned from having created
all those different
aspects. How about I don't prefer to do
that. I think what I would like to learn is
I think what I would like to learn is
that they uh stop hating each other.
That who stops hating each other? The
different aspects. How can they have
minds of their own? Well, they seem to
have their own opinions. Yes, they seem
to, but it's your opinion. Why is your
opinion of yourself that way?
I don't know. Take a guess.
[Music] What kind of an opinion would one have
What kind of an opinion would one have
to have of oneself in order to feel cut
off from the infinite?
No. That such a thing doesn't exist.
Such a thing as what? All of it is the
infinite. Doesn't exist. Yes. Oh, all
right. Do you exist? Yes. Oh, all right. Are
Do you exist? Yes. Oh, all right. Are
you conscious? Yes. All right.
Do you have an imagination? Yes. All
right. In your imagination, have you
been able to conceive of a concept that
is called all that is?
Not that. You were just talking about
it. That doesn't mean you have to have a
conscious analytical awareness of all
that might be. But do you have within
your imagination the concept that there
might be something called all that is
that represents everything there could
be? Yes. Do you understand that you
cannot imagine
non-existence? Do you want to go over
that again?
Do you understand that you have not got
the capability of imagining
non-existence?
I don't really agree. I think that you
could imagine it. Oh, all right. Give me
some sort of an example of
non-existence. Just blankness. That's a
concept and therefore it's something
that exists. Nothing is still something.
It's still a concept and therefore it
still falls on the line of something
that
exists. You see, that is what I'm
getting at. There is no way you can
describe non-existence because if you could
non-existence because if you could
experience true non-existence, you
wouldn't know it, would you? No, you
wouldn't. Therefore, anything at all that you can
Therefore, anything at all that you can
possibly conceive of must fall on the
other side of the line. It must exist.
Yes. Yes. So, if you have any kind of a
concept at all of all that is, it must
exist simply because of your capability
of imagining
it. Does that help? No, I don't. Why
not? Is that too convoluted?
Yes. It seems to me that it's too
intellectual. It's just a game. Ah, just
the game. All right. It can be that, but
it is more than that. You truly cannot
conceive of
non-existence. Let me put it this way.
Your society has this notion that that
which exists can perhaps somehow become
non-existent and that things in that
sense which now exist somehow came out
of non-existence.
But you see that is not quite precisely.
So you have this notion that there is
something and that there is nothing. For
now let us just say for convenience sake
that nothing represents what you call
non-existence. Even though that is not
precisely so. All right. Okay. So you
have nothing and you have
something. But you see what many of you
forget is that there is a larger
category to both of these and that is
everything. Because nothing and something are a part
Because nothing and something are a part
of
everything. And you cannot have the
concept of everything if you just have
nothing or you just have something. You
have to have both in order to fulfill
the concept of everything. And that's
really all all that is is everything
that is. Whatever it is, it is all that
is. That's all it is. Now, if you're
conscious, you are an aspect of whatever
it is that does exist. If you have
consciousness, that is a reflection of
the fact that everything else has that
too. It may not have it in the same way.
It may not express it in the same way,
but everything there is is in you
because the universe is holographic.
That is basically saying the whole is
contained in all of the parts.
You to be aware of yourself are
reflecting a basic attribute of
existence itself. If you exist and are
self-aware, everything else in its own
way must be too because you are
representative in your own way of
whatever it is that exists because you
exist. You have that basic property and
you share that property with everything
else that
exists. That
fundamental is a basic property of your
existence. If you
exist, then anything you can conceive of
is an extension of you and you are an
extension of it. It does not have to be
looked at as a mind game. I understand
that sometimes it can seem that it
translates into your language that way
or what you call language that way. But
bring it down to its basic level. These
are concepts of selfawareness. No matter
how it translates, it's not a game on
that level. You are aware of yourself.
You know you exist.
You therefore, even if you were the only
therefore, even if you were the only
thing, would still fill would still
fulfill the definition of all that
is. If you perceive that there seem to
be separate things and do not
necessarily believe that they are
connected to you or that you are
connected to
them, if that were true, truly not
connected, if there were truly a real
gap in between you and something else,
you would not have the capability of
perceiving it because you cannot
perceive what you are not connected to.
It can't be done by in a sense your own
definition. So if you can perceive of
it, if you can even conceive of it at
all, then it is a part of you. It is an
extension of you. You are an extension
of it. You are connected. You are one in
the same event, one in the same
concept. Everything you imagine in a
sense is a reflection of what you are of
your universe. The universal reality of
existence. You are anything you can
conceive of is contained within your
awareness of
self. Does that make sense? Yes, Bashar.
But I feel like all of this is just too
intellectual. Like I'd like to feel like
a personal feeling of connection and
this is just um you're not getting me. I
understand. We're getting there. We're
getting there. Now, you have heard us
discuss many times perhaps the issue of
doing what excites you the most. Yes.
Yes. Have you ever felt excited in your
life? Yes. Real excited? Yes. Real
happy? Yes. What do you think that
feeling is?
Pleasure. What does that mean?
I like it. All right. You like it, but
what is
it? What is that feeling? What is that
energy? Or let me put it this way.
Why can't that feeling be your
connection to all that
is? What do you assume that connection
would be like that? That that level of
excitement wouldn't be
sufficient. Do you imagine it ought to
be bigger than that?
Do you have a concept for how you think
it ought to feel?
More like a personal friend. A personal
friend. Do you know what it feels like
to have a personal friend? Yes. Then why
not simply apply that feeling to the
universe? What stops you from feeling
that way about the universe? That's your
choice. You see, you can have whatever
type of relationship with all that is
that you want to. All that is doesn't
care. They're all valid to all that is.
If you want to feel that you have a
personal friendship with all that is,
act that way. All that is will respond
in that manner. But don't wait for it to
happen. Make it happen. Create it to
happen. Be that idea. Be that
relationship. The universe will reflect
that to you. If that's what you want,
act that
way. Does that make sense? Yes. I was
wondering how do you feel your
connection with all it is? Any way I
want to any way at all. because I know
they're all real. They're all true.
They're all valid. And I know they're
all representative of the all that is
that I am. Any way you choose to relate
to it is representative of the all that
is you are. Because remember from my
point of view, you are simply one of the
ways all that is has of relating to
itself. You see, I don't see a
separation at all between you and what
you call all that is. I see you as all
that is relating to itself in this
particular way and that particular way
and that way and that way and this
way. We are all all that is relating to
itself in all the ways it can because
that's the definition of all that is can
be anything at all it can imagine itself
to be. It can even
be an all that is that doesn't feel
connected to
itself, but it's still all that is
because by definition, anything you can
conceive of has to fit in the category
of all that
is. That's what it means to be a
multi-dimensional creator. So if you as
the all that is you are the all that is
that has been experiencing this idea
this notion of being disconnected from
itself wishes to feel a connection in a
particular way create it be that all
that is and you'll have that feeling
you'll have that relationship you will
be that
idea it is as simple as that you can
generate that feeling generate it
generating the feeling is the creation
of that relationship it is not a
standin. It is not proxy. It is not one
step removed. It is the relationship
because all you're doing is being in
relation to yourself. The all that is
that you are in whatever way you want to
be. That's why you have free will. You
can choose. This is how I choose to
believe I am related to all that is. I
wish to experience it as a close
personal friendship. Then whatever that
means to you, act that way. That's the
way you'll experience it and that's the
way the universe will feed into you.
Understand? Yes. Does that help you?
Yes. Are you sure? No. But I feel like
I'm taking up too much time.
Why? Why do you feel so
undeserving? Do you believe you are
worthy of love?
I'm working on it. All right. That's up
to you.
All that is loves you unconditionally so
much that it will allow you to work on
the idea of self- loveve as long as you
want to. It loves you that much. It is
that much of a personal friend that it
will allow you to be whoever you desire
to be. That's how much it loves you. You
see, that is to some degree the
dichotomy in your society in your
dimension of experience. All that is is
so willing to support the you you really
prefer to be that at times you can't
feel it because it is so
non-interferive, so
nondirecting, it will let you be whoever
it is you are working on being in
exactly the way you want to. As soon as
you decide that you are deserving of
love and want to have that close
personal friendship with all that is, it
will be there for you instantly. But
until you decide yourself with your own
free will that you deserve it, all that
is loves you so much. It will let you
spend as much time as you want figuring
out that you do in fact deserve it. And
you don't ever have to figure that out.
All that is will still love you
unconditionally. Even if you choose to
never figure that out, that's how much
it loves you. That's how much of a
friend it is.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you also for
being our friend and for allowing me to
be yours in whatever way I choose to be.
Shilling, thank you for the work you do for us. I
thank you for the work you do for us. I
I don't know how to say it. It's so
wonderful to have your attention and
your love here. Oh, I thank you for
yours as well and the work you all do
for us. Good. Thank you. Um my I'm one
of those fortunate people who was doing
what excites me. But it only happened to
me about 10 years ago when I came upon
some knowledge about the human voice and
making it stronger. Been very exciting.
Can I say the way you handle uh the
channel's body is wonderful. You widen
the rib cage and tighten the diaphragm
and make great space so that it's
exciting to listen to you. You make
Thank you. You're a perfect example of
how people should use the body for
speech. Anyway, I'm very fortunate to
have that. But I noticed most people
most people in the world today are not
using their full voice. They're they're
inhibited from childhood and in life.
They're shy now. They have a fear of
having a big voice. My job is to give
them big voices. And I'm willing to do
it. And they are going to Thank you. I
always talk fast. I get so excited. You
do, by the way, teach them the
difference between big voice and being
obnoxious. Yes.
Well, I I teach a lot of young rock
singers, so some of them are a little
obnoxious, but at least I show teasing,
right? No, it's a good it's a good point
there because I do that. But I'm always
hoping that I will save them from
hurting their voices. But the thing is,
people have a fear. They will they will
come to me for a few lessons and get
great progress and then just when
they're about to really make a
breakthrough, they will have something
come up in their lives and they won't
continue. And it seems to me there is a
fear of having a big voice. There's a
fear of speaking in public. Of course,
because then you get noticed and then
you have to back up what you said. Yes.
And not that many individuals in your
society yet have that much conviction
about who they are. Yes, I guess that's
true. So, I'm trying in a way to do
something for them. They may not be able
to have, but at least some of them can.
But I want to ask you a question here.
Please, before you do, I have a
suggestion if I may. Yes. Thank you. You
can remind them that some of the tiniest
little animals in your world have some
of the biggest voices. They're not
afraid at being who they are. That's
good. Yes, indeed. It is all right. You
can remind them to be exactly who they
are, and they can still announce it
quite boldly. Good. They do not have to
meet anyone else's expectations before
they allow themselves to announce who
they are, no matter who that is. Great.
Also I find that as they get bigger
voices they get healthier and their
their body their health improves. Yes
and vice versa as you say and people who
listen to them feel very good. It has a
healing effect to listen to good voices
just like yours is for us. But they say
things they say things like when when
they crack on a note they say oh I
should be shocked or that destroy I
should be banished. Now is was there a
time in our history when the voice was
so important perhaps used for healing or
survival that if you had a bad voice you
were shocked? Well, yes and no. Let me
put it this way. The idea of individuals
fears sometimes is that they recognized
when an individual knew the control, the
vibrational tonality, what has now come
in your society to be called an
incantation that changes dimensions.
when they realize that much power, that
type of energy very often set up fears
in other individuals and they very often
kill the individuals who really knew how
to use that tonality. Yes. So, in a
sense, all that is to some degree in
many individuals in your society now is
a selfreflective condemnation of the
time when they knew how to key in to
that idea and are simply being cautious
because they do not want to offend other
individuals who might resent them
expressing that much power when no one
else seems to want to do so. Very true.
Very true. I believe Seth at one stage
told us that uh the pyramids were built
by the sound of the human voice. And
I've been hung up on that for a while.
The older ones, not what you may call
the more recent ones. Some of them by
what you may call the voice,
incantations and chantings, tonal
vibrations. Some of them through
instrumentation, some of them through
vibratory sonics, crystals, and the
like. But all the same principle,
vibratory tonality. Yes, sonics in that
way. Sonic levitation. Now your society
is beginning to discover that again in
many different ways and there can be in
time similar kinds of symphonies that
took place in the past. Let me describe
briefly the construction of certain very
ancient structures some of which do not
exist on the surface of your planet
anymore. Some of them subsided with the
idea of the submergence of Atlantis and
other island masses. But this idea can
occur once again when you recognize that
every particular different object has a
signature vibration and you find a way
in that sense to map that frequency to
harmonize that frequency and unlock it
from what you may call the gravitational
effect it will then float levitate into
place. If you can, shall we say, take
all the elements of a building, find the
signature vibration of all the
structural elements and then find out
what the signature pattern would be if
all those elements were locked together
in their final form and project that
final signature pattern. All the
elements will simply rise up and lock
into place and that will be it. Wow. You
will have built a building completely
through sound and it will be a symphony
to watch. Wonderful.
Thank you. Thank you so much. Now, a
little personal question. I want to get
I want to get this technique out to the
world if I can. And I'm having trouble.
I seem to be getting people to assist me
who don't have my same dream and I make
mistakes in choosing personnel. This
year feels good. Does it seem like this
year I am on the right track? This is
the year of conviction in your society.
The idea once again is to remember that
you are one event. Simply allow yourself
to attract all the individuals that are
also representative of that event. And
do understand there really are no
interruptions. Learn what you can from
anyone you interact with. But also
remember while other individuals will
interact with you, they interact with
you and you interact with them as
service to each other. It's not that you
need each other to be the complete idea
you already are. Let them give you the
gift of serving you. At the same time,
remember they have their own ideas and
serve them by allowing them to extract
out of your combined interaction what
they need to further their ideas even as
you extract from them what you need to
further your ideas. You are serving each
other but you do not need each other to
be complete. Do you understand the
difference? Thank you. Thank you so
much. Well, thank you very much. We like
you very much. Our unconditional love to
you.
Good evening, Bashar. I beg your pardon.
Good evening as time is on our planet.
Oh, thank you very much. Good day to
you. Um, I'm very happy and excited to
have had my name picked. One moment. I
didn't believe you. I'm very happy to
have had my Well, I am. Oh,
and I just want to take the opportunity
to tell you how um coming here has meant
a lot to me. I thought about you a lot.
We thank you very much for your
creation. Thank you. Uh my question was
going to be about my Thursday night
meditation channeling group which has
been going on for about a year and a
half. All right. And most of us came
tonight as a field trip. Oh, field trip.
All right. And half have left. So, um,
I'm beginning to feel that maybe my time
with the group in as concentrated effort
as I had been putting into it perhaps is
should be lessened. All right. Why? I'm
finding that I'm interested in other
ways of developing. All right. Do you
believe that all ways are valid? Yes.
All right. Um so my basic question has
to do with my own personal interaction
between groups and individuals because I
do find a lot of many different things
exciting and I like to explore and some
of them are extremely different from
others. All right. And somehow I feel
um not a toolbox be versatile. Yes. All
right. Okay. Well a toolbox. Yes.
can exist within an environment that is
sometimes um the same environment. So what my
um the same environment. So what my
question is is sometimes I feel
disconnected from other people on a more
on a continuing basis since I have so
many shortterm
now you can recognize that someone may
have a very different preference from
you but that doesn't mean you have to
feel disconnected. Can you not feel
unified in your diversity? Oh, yes, I
do. All right, then. How do you feel
disconnected in that sense? Or are you
simply talking about attached
detachment? Oh, I think I've mastered attached
Oh, I think I've mastered attached
detachment. All right, then that's
another tool you can use and you can
teach it as well. Yes. I would now like
to move into a different area and a
different experience which I have not
had too much of such as which is more of
a personal integration with other
people. In what way? um more sustained
uh working together, more projects
together, perhaps socializing on uh
rather than just scattered individual
times. Well, then why not simply design
the project that is most exciting to you
and assume that it will attract the
individuals that will necessarily remain
in that project with you for the
duration of time that feels correct? So,
you mean kind of like a
business type of project or that's up to
you. Simply understand that if that is
your strongest desire, then if you give
free reign to your imagination and
follow it and trust it, then the project
you design from your imagination will
obviously be representative of your
desire and will be designed as such to
attract the individuals to interact with
you in the way that satisfies you. Why
would you design a project that would
not satisfy your desire?
Well, what if my desire were marriage?
Not that it is. This is a hypothetical
question. How would you design such a
project? There are many definitions to marriage,
There are many definitions to marriage,
but we'll let you proceed for now. Okay.
Cohabiting with someone. Yes. Okay. And
so, well, having not anybody
particularly in mind, how do you begin?
You begin first of all by understanding
what it means to you, how you define it,
why that particular manifestation, if
that is a particular manifestation in
your mind, is the one that represents
that feeling, that idea. Remember first
of all that the first marriage once
again is of yourself to
yourself reflect back to you the
radiance you are giving off understand.
Yes. And there can be many versions of
the idea you call marriage. Yes. But
again if you really feel that you are
precisely in tune with a true inner
knowing about what it is you will
attract in your life to really represent
who and what you are. Then once again
all you have to do to attract it is
simply start acting like who you know
you are and you will attract it
automatically. Someone will be
fascinated by the you you allow yourself
to be. You understand? Yes I do. Thank
you. Does that satisfy you? Yes.
You don't believe me?
Just checking. It is
you want to be sure that the
understanding is also not hypothetical.
No, I think I do understand and I feel
that maybe with me it's just timing. You
know, I'm still working on being who I
am and I'm not really ready to have
someone yet. Do you really understand
that even while you are working on being
who you are, you're still being who you
are? Being who I am. Yes.
But when I'm when I'm the one when I am
who I am where what excites me is having
a quote marriage. Yes, there will be
one. Yes. At the same time do understand
that very often not in every case what
you call a marriage is not in and of
itself necessarily a goal. Being who you
are and doing the things that represent
who you are as an individual is what
usually automatically attracts whatever
kind of marriage needs to be there to
reinforce who you are as an individual.
Yes. Does that help? Yes. Thank you very
much. Thank you very much. I now
pronounce you you and you. Thank you.
Hello Bashar. I don't you good day. I
want to thank you for your sharing and
beautiful reflections to us. You as
well. Um my question is I'm very excited
about healing in the arts. Oh, healing
in the arts. And I wonder if you could
reflect some of the relevance that you
see from your point of view um about the
five element theory in oral medicine and
shamanism and crystal healing and one
more really brief on each one. So brief
and um metastrology.
My my my
five point is the symbol of humanity and
the extension of the physical senses and
how they all simply funnel back into the
core connection to
nature. The idea of the balance of the
polarities in that
sense. Shamanism is much the same.
The connection to nature, the connection
to the vibration of your crystal
dimension. Your dimension is a
crystallization of the infinite. One
particular crystallization of the
infinite. Everything in your physical
dimension is representative, especially
in what you call astrological terms,
representative of, shall we say for now,
frozen patterns of energy that represent
your original agreements of interaction.
So in the reading of the stars, whether
medically or in any other methodology,
what in a sense you're doing is looking
at a
slice through a constantly changing
holographic structure, a frozen slice of
vibrational reality. And then you can
look at another slice and another slice
and another slice and you can see what
you call a continuum or a progression or
an evolution if you wish, which in a
sense is an illusion.
But all it comes back down to all the
methodologies you have described is
recognizing fundamentally that
everything is a matter of different
frequencies of one primal medium out of
which everything is crystallized. Okay.
Now, if you have affinities to different
signature approaches, different
signature methodologies, then that is
you getting in touch with and through
different faces you have experienced in
your multitudinous lives. And at
different times, you may have to put on
a different face to relate to a
particular person that comes to you for
assistance. Okay? So the integration of
what I'm feeling within myself is also
why I'm being drawn to different areas
so that I'm able to different
differentiate when someone comes to see
me healing what methodology match like a
mirror their vibration so you can be of
best service to the them they are okay
by being so versatile a tool yourself
okay understand yes you are in that
sense a lovely instrument that can play
many tunes okay thank you very much. We
thank you. Thank you.
Have a shower and a good day. It's good
to be with you and it's good to be with
everybody here.
Um I am excited. Oh all the way through.
Me too. Great. You too. Good answer.
um in listening to you and reading
communion and hearing about reticulum
energy and being aware a lot more of my
dream state both in my sleep state and
in my waking state. I had a dream last
night and I woke up at 3:00 in the
morning to realize that I really didn't
wake up other than to go into another
level of a dream. Oh, what? And what had
happened was earlier in the evening I
saw a picture of you that I saw in a
magazine and thought had the thought to
take it out and put it under my pillow.
So as I did that and I woke up at 3:00
in the morning thinking that I was awake
but I was at another level of my dream.
I thought oh get the picture of Bashar
and realized that I could not move and I
was completely uh vulnerable meaning
naked and in the fetal position and I
was just wondering kind of what was
going on. I realized that there was a a
form of letting go in the form of like
vomit but it was not that. It was just a
release of things. I was just curious if
you can give me a little feedback on
that. You are in a sense, shall we say,
gaining practice or exercise the plasmic
ethereal material of your higher
dimensional self. You can no longer move
in the physiological sense. Your
commands to physically move do not play
out the same way in the plasmic
material. It is more simply an idea of
changing your perspective or your point
of view or your attitude. That's how you
move in that level.
So you are practicing walking with new
legs, shall we say, that don't really
exist in the physical sense. You are
being reborn into another level. In a
sense, it was a type of umbilical
material. Mhm. What was interesting is I there was
Mhm. What was interesting is I there was
another dimension of me that was outside
of it looking at me, not being able to
move and going through that whole. Yes.
You are beginning to experience the
multi-layeredness of your consciousness.
It is infinite. Yes. As far outward as
you wish to go, you will always find
that you are capable looking back as far
into the infinite into the center as you
wish to. Right? You occupy all those
dimensions. All those dimensions occupy
you. All of you. All those dimensions
occupy you.
Mhm. Also, and then when I really did
wake up, I also get the sense lately
that when you really did wake up,
when I went into my waking state of
dreams state
um I get the feeling of like expecting
to see many people around me um from
whether it be many bashars or uh
Richard, you know what I'm saying? Yes.
Um and that's been going on a lot. Is
there a lot of activity? Oh yes, of
course. Okay. There is consciousness
everywhere. Once again truly understand
when we talk about the holographic
structure of existence every single
thing you could call a point is
conscious. Mhm. And you can
differentiate that as many times as you
want to. You can have a million, a
billion, an infinite number of points of
consciousnesses and they all can connect
into true dimensions, full dimensions of
reality. Great. What I've noticed um
that I've actually been doing for years
as a as a child all the way up to now is
that I
picture energy moving in the form of a
pyramid down in the middle half of my
body. And I've been doing it for years.
The pyramidal form is the lens, the
representational lens for
electromagnetism in your physiological
dimension. And it is once again
representative of the template upon
which all physiological reality is
built. Therefore, all electromagnetic
force, shall we say, flows along those
lines and is focused by that particular
symbolic shape. Okay. So in doing that
that's actually I'm actually asking
it and drawing it in closer to me. Yes,
you are looking through a particular
shall we say type of glass into other
dimensional realms. Some of it may be
refracted and reflected a little bit
distorted here and there based upon how
it translates in your dimension of
experience but nonetheless you are
opening doorways in that sense. You are
learning to see with a different kind of
eye. Great. Well I do it in this area.
Should I look down? No.
I get what you're saying. We thank you.
Thank you very much.
at this timing. Allow us to extend
also based upon some of the information
we have just discussed
that within what you may now call the next
within what you may now call the next
two of your weeks of
time because there is as we have already
discussed and outlined a format change
within our interactions with you and an
acceleration on different levels. There
will be in the form of what you might
call a
wrap-up some guests in the next two of
your weeks to finalize and crystallize
before we go on to the next stage. Some
acceleration of energy
and some unexpected
things. For now truly, we are
approaching the
idea where
conviction conviction can play itself
out in a far broader and a far more
profound and a far deeper and more
affecting level on all levels of
reality. And where by example there is
sufficient blending for stronger changes
to take place, for stronger examples to
be given, for stronger energy to be
shared, for it now can be
absorbed. Even though it will be in a
sense more energetic and more powerful,
it may be experienced as being a little
bit more subdued because it covers such
a broad area as you understand such
things in terms of time and space.
The very fabric, the very vibrational
reality of existence itself has
consciousness. And there are many
different doorways that have yet to be
opened. Through the next two
interactions, we shall begin to explore
and open some of those new doorways and
lay the path and the
foundation for some of your own
openings. This is now why the event of a new
This is now why the event of a new
format of the workshop idea will truly
allow you perhaps if you wish to begin
to understand the true simplicity of
application for that is all wisdom is
taking the knowledge that you have and
applying it. Allow yourselves the breath of life
it. Allow yourselves the breath of life
that is always yours that ignites the
flame within all of your hearts.
Allow yourselves to shine, for truly you
have never really gone out. And we see
your light and we love your light. For
it is by your light that we found you.
We thank you for being such a beacon.
And we send you our unconditional love
and good day.
[Applause] Pepper.
Time to go.
Thank you all for being here tonight.
This blending of higher
densities. Those who want a copy of
tonight's tape, please see Pamela around
the corner. And uh Darl and I discussed
recently that may have your attention
please for just a moment. Just one more
minute, please.
Um uh we strongly suggest the
preparation for the workshop this big
change that's coming up
uh that the self-empowerment workshop is
the preparation for that. The new one
will be an acceleration even above and
beyond that those of you who attended or
know about that. So we have that in
audio and video form uh available at the
front desk or at the back. We'll be here
for two more Thursdays. We strongly
suggest you come and hear what that's
about. Thank you for coming.