First time about 150 ft distance, second
time about 70 ft distant, a craft
triangular in shape about 40 ft on the
side of a very dark gray metal. Now,
what I didn't understand at the time,
aside from having seen what everyone was
calling a UFO, and what I understand now
through a series of events that have
happened since then, is that that
sighting, those two sightings were
Bashar's way of sort of tapping me in
the subconscious memory to get me to
start learning the things I needed to
learn to fulfill the agreement. Because
after I had the sighting, I started
getting real excited about the whole
idea of UFOs and I started really
delving into research on UFO
phenomenology and metaphysical studies
to see what I could find out about the
whole idea. As the years went on and I
began to at least become somewhat
familiar with the whole idea, eventually
someone offered or introduced me to
several channels who were practicing at
the time and one of the entities coming
through one of those channels offered to
teach channeling for whoever was
interested because several people were
even then I took them up on the offer
not thinking that it was
I wanted to learn more about the whole
idea because there really weren't very
many books out at the time and I thought
if I went into the class I would see
something contemporary in action.
When I was in the class in a receptive
state under the guidance of the other
entity is when Bashar and his people
made the telepathic connection with me
and as soon as they did make the link
the memory of having made the agreement
came back in full. Who they were, who I
was to them, why the ship sighting had
occurred, dream conversations that I had
had with them for years that I had
totally blocked out of my memory all
came flooding back into that one moment.
And what the telepathic message had to
say was basically that now that you
remember you made the agreement. Do you
still want to fulfill the agreement?
Because it was a choice and it always is
a choice for everyone who makes that
kind of an agreement. It's not something
that's forced on you. Obviously, I said
yes. I agree to it. And that was about 4
and 1/2 years ago now. So, I've been
channeling for the last 4 and 1/2 years.
Now, Bashar presents himself as a member
of an extraterrestrial community. They
do have a type of physicality. It's not
identical to our own. And they do not
exist in the same kind of dimensionality
that we do. They're a little more
accelerated, a little more rarified, a
little closer to non-physicality, but
they are perceivable as physical beings.
Um, I have along with the sighting and along
I have along with the sighting and along
with many other events that have
happened since then, I have my own
validations for him being who he says he
is at this point. But the one thing I
especially like to stress, particularly
to new people, is that there is
absolutely nothing about this
interaction in any way, shape, or form
that insists that you have to believe
that he is who we say he is. Because
there's no way I can prove this to you
at all at this point. Within perhaps the
next 10 or 20 years, Bashar has said
that people of his kind and perhaps many
other civilizations, depending upon what
changes occur here, they may be far more
able to be able to meet us face to face.
right now they're remaining in the
background on purpose for a lot of
reasons but one of the main reasons as
he stressed it is they've noticed in
observing our society that we have a
tendency or have had a tendency in the
past to sort of lock onto the messenger
and throw the message in the garbage can
and idolize the messenger and they don't
want this to happen. So they're
purposely remaining in the background so
that the most important thing you have
to pay attention to is the information
and nothing else. So the whole point of
this interaction is that if the
information that comes through is
something that you feel works for you
and you can apply it in your life and
you get the results from the
application, then by all means use it.
If you find that it doesn't work for
you, don't use it. Don't worry about it.
You'll get what you need somewhere else.
This is not something to prove to you or
to force upon you the idea that his
points of view or his beliefs are any
more valid than your own. He's here to
reflect to each and every one of us that
we have the ability to live the lives we
want to and that we have the answers to
the problems in our lives right within
us. And he's here to help us find those
answers to find that we have the ability
to access those answers all the time.
It's a lot of very powerful information
which can be applied but it completely
depends upon how you use it and how you
want to use it. That's completely up to
you. Um the word itself Bashar is not
actually his name. In their society now
they're pretty much telepathic. They
don't have names as such. They don't
really use their language anymore. But
he knows that we use names as a
reference of convenience. So he chose a
word out of one of our own earth
languages that at least represents what
he's doing and gives us something that
we can call him buy in the conversation.
Now the word itself is Arabic partly
because that's my background and it has
a lot to do with the connections that we
have. But even though it's not his name,
several people who are familiar with
Arabic have told me that it does seem
apppropo because one meaning of the word
is commander which is something similar
to what he is in his society. Another
meaning is simply the man or the being
and on a broader sense humanity in
general. Perhaps I think though the most
appropriate meaning is that in Armenian
the word bashar means messenger and
that's basically what he's doing is
being a messenger and a leazison between
his world and our world. So it is
appropriate and it is fitting for what
he does.
Now when he comes through when we make
the link and I go into the trance or the
altered state he will usually come
through and say something that he feels
is representative or indicative of the
collective consciousness of any
particular group. After he is done he
will simply say either how may I serve
you or sharing both of those statements
are his way of saying that the ball's in
your court and it's time to get up and
ask questions. So when he does that
perhaps what you can do is the first
person can get up, line up and then you
know keep at least two or three people
running behind them so that we don't
have a gap in between and uh just you
know come up as smoothly as you can and
as was pointed out speak as loudly and
as clearly as you can so everyone in the
room can hear and so that we can record
it. Before we start there are just a
couple of things I would like to outline
in terms of the interaction especially
again because many of you are new.
Bashar does not believe that there's any
such thing as a silly or a stupid
question. So please, if there's
something you want to talk about and it
really is interesting to you, don't hold
back because you think you'll be wasting
everyone's time because the question is
mundane. Out of some of the most mundane
questions have come interactions that
have really helped anyone and everyone
in the room. So please don't hold back
because you're shy that it isn't
relevant or that it's too personal. No
subject is out of bounds. So you can
talk about anything you want to whether
it's personal or cosmic or universal
whatever you want to talk about it's up
to you. Um
the second thing is what's going on here
is basically a telepathic link up. My
consciousness is diffused or defocused
in such a way that I cannot think
anymore as a personality that allows his
consciousness to sort of lock into mine.
My energy then takes its cue from his
frequency. So what you're actually
getting is a model of his consciousness
wherever he is created out of my energy.
You're getting a translation of his
thoughts. The words you hear is not
because he's actually speaking English
at all. It's because my subconscious is
automatically supplying whatever words
are necessary to match the concepts that
he is sending with his thoughts.
Because this is the nature of the
process and I'm just simply acting as a
translation device. Sometimes the
concepts that come through may sound
funny to us because they're coming
through either from a completely new
point of view, a very alien point of
view, or because the words are not
sufficient to describe the concept that
he has in his society. So whatever words
get used may simply be the best possible
building blocks that are available. The
point of this whole idea is that if for
any reason whatsoever,
something he's talking about doesn't
make sense to you and you want to know
what he's saying, you want to understand
him, stop him. Say, "Bashar, I don't get
it. Could you use another word? Could
you repeat that? Could you go over that
again, please?" He will do that. You're
not interrupting him. You're not
stopping the flow. He wants to know that
you're getting out of this what you want
to get out of it. Now, obviously, that
will be the result of somebody being up
here asking a question. So, if you
interrupt him and say, "I don't get it."
Ask him for an explanation. But I
mentioned this just because it's
happened. Please don't take the
opportunity to sneak in your own
question. Stand in line to do that. just get an
Stand in line to do that. just get an
explanation of what it is he's already
talking about and let him go on to the
next question that is in line. The
bottom line to all of this is once again
as has been said to please have a good
time. The lighter you are in your
interaction, the bolder you are in terms
of what you want to talk about and how
deep you want to delve. He will reflect
that back to you. Exactly. For the
people that are familiar with him, they
know that he's not shy in the least, but
he's not going to pull anything from you
if you don't want to talk about it. He
will give back to you basically what you
put out to him. So treat him as a
friend. Talk to him very very directly
but very informally. He will lighten up
with you. He will kid around with you
and still at the same time exercise what
a lot of people have felt to be a high
degree of compassion in assisting you to
understand whatever it is you feel you
want to get out of this interaction.
That's what he's here. So please have a
good time when you do this. Um, the only
thing I will say before we start is when
I'm going into the altered state and
when I'm coming out of the altered
state, either at the break or at the
end, I will simply ask you when he says
take a break, when he says good night at
the end, please don't start moving or
talking all at once. Let me reorient
before you start doing that. Nothing
about what I'm doing is tiring or
depleting, but I'm very disoriented when
I come out because what I'm experiencing
in the interaction is like being in a
very deep daydream. I don't hear the
words, but I do feel the energy. I feel
the emotion. Sometimes I see pictures,
abstract or concrete.
But it takes me a moment to refocus my
consciousness. And if you all start
talking when he says goodbye, it's like
having a hundred people screaming in
your ear when you're waking up in the
morning in your bedroom. Just give me a
second to reorient. I'll let you know
when I'm back. And then you can jump up
and down and scream and run out the door
and do anything you want to do after
that point. That's up to you. Um,
and also simply when I'm going into the
altered state, sometimes some of you
will notice that my body will go through
a few reactions to the energy. I
mentioned this just because sometimes
people say it looks like I'm in a lot of
pain. I'm in no pain whatsoever. I'm
having a wonderful time. Please don't
worry about me. It's very energetic and
it's just an automatic adjustment to the
changes that are going on.
So, please have a good time. Thank you
very much once again for coming and I'll
see you all later. Did I forget
anything? Did you mention one question?
Did you mention one question?
Well, Vince did I'll I'll reinforce that
just just briefly just just for the
purpose of allowing as many people to
interact as possible. Make an attempt to
solidify or consolidate your idea into
the single most important question you
want to talk about and really rely on
the fact that a lot of other people are
going to be asking questions that may be
similar to what you want to talk about
also. though you may get other questions
answered just because other people will
have similar ideas that they want to
talk about as well. So it's always very
good to pay attention to every single
person that's up here because there's no
accident that each and every one of you
are here in this room together and many
times people will find that the
coincidence or the synchronicity of what
other people have to share will
literally cover almost every other thing
they wanted to talk about. So focus on
everyone's question because you're sort
of all part of the same event and you
all are working hand in hand whether
you're conscious of that or not. So once
again, thank you and have a good time.
I'll turn this back around.
You can leave it kind of half so I can
Okay, I'll fix
[Music] you.
you.
I'll do that
before we start. Oh yeah. All
right, I'll say how are you all this day
of your time as you create time to
exist. Perfect.
Perfect.
Are you all alive?
Thank you. Allow us to begin by laying
down a foundation for this interaction
this day of your time. It can if you
wish be entitled inspiration and
individual impact.
Now each and every one of you obviously
is an individual but now as a society
each and every one of you is beginning
on some level to realize that you are
also all connected as one entity as one
idea as one self-aware consciousness a
global awareness if you wish a world
spirit. This world spirit, this one
mind, this mass consciousness is in and
of itself an entity, a single idea. And
it is aware of itself as a single
entity, a single idea. At the same time,
it is also aware of itself as a
composite of all the individuals that
exist upon your planet. A composite of
all the individual mentalities, all the
individual expressions of consciousness
out of which it is constructed, shall we
say. The idea therefore
The idea therefore
in inspiration and individual impact is
to recognize perhaps a few of the
following points of view.
Each and every one of you as an
individual has the ability to affect in many ways
has the ability to affect in many ways
the whole of your world. Even
physiologically now you know you are
beginning to attain a global
consciousness. No longer are you
isolated in terms of what you may call
villages or cities or even nations
anymore. You are now beginning to
function, although for now it may seem
to be a bit sketchy as you say, as a
united earth in that sense. You are
beginning to overlap your borders. You
are beginning to cross over, to merge,
to blend, to find that it is almost
impossible not to interact with all of
the other nations upon your planet. In
that sense, you are beginning, even
though it may seem for now to be under a
lot of pressure, you are beginning to
blend together, to merge together into
one entity. You are going through many
growing pains perhaps in doing this as a
civilization. But nonetheless, you are
still creating a blending. You are still
exposed to other cultures, other
notions, other points of view. And some
of this does inevitably rub off on each
and every one of you, making you far
more of a unitized, far more of a
globally thinking person than your
ancestors used to be. In that sense, the
idea when you do this physiologically
also creates an effect in your
non-physical consciousness, in your
telepathic link for each and every one
of you is connected non-physically
telepathically. You are all immersed in
a sea of electromagnetic energy that
surrounds your planet. Being immersed in
that sea of electromagnetic energy is
what allows you all to be, shall we say,
in touch with each other on unconscious
and subconscious levels. You can be in
touch with each other on conscious
levels, but your society's habits have
not always allowed you to understand
that this is possible. So for thousands
of years you have relegated that contact
to the sub and unconscious levels of
your mentality. But now now now that you
have entered more global awareness
physiologically consciously you are
beginning to allow that sub and
unconscious awareness of your
interconnectedness to rise to bubble up
to the surface of your consciousness.
And you are beginning to realize that
you are all aspects of the same one
expression of consciousness that is your
entire planet.
Day by day and bit by bit. Many of you
now that you are accelerating in this
direction will begin and perhaps have
already begun to see examples of this
idea in the synchronicity of the events
in the coincidences of events in the
psychic attunement and sensitivity of
your mentality that you may begin to
find yourself experiencing and
expressing in your day-to-day
activities. All of these ideas are
natural symptoms of the type of
transformation your world is going
through. And it can allow you to further
accelerate that idea if you will allow
for more inspiration in your lives and
more recognition of the impact that each
and every one of you as an individual
have upon the whole. Since you are all
connected, any movement, any idea, any
change at all, no matter how seemingly
insignificant any of you make, must by
definition affect the whole. You may
think you are, shall we say, a very
small gear, a very small lever. And in
that sense, yes, there is a greater hole
out of numbers. But even if you turn
your small gear, even an infinite
decimal amount, all the other gears to
which it is connected must turn, even if
they also only turn an infinite decimal
amount. Each and every individual is
absolutely linked with the whole and is
absolutely impossible to be separated
from it. So recognize that the only
thing that does not necessarily allow
you to be aware of how much impact each
and every one of you has is because you
have not necessarily been taught to
focus on the understanding of your
interconnectedness with everyone else.
As soon as you begin to realize that you
are in fact already intermeshed,
intertwined, inseparable in that sense,
then you will begin to be able to see
consciously see the true orchestration
that all of you are together. you will
truly begin to be able to understand
that no motion, no movement, no matter
how seemingly slight, is an accident.
All is synchronicity, all is an
orchestration. It is absolutely from our
point of view, in no way, shape or form
an accident as to who has attended this
interaction. It is absolutely no
accident whom you are sitting next to.
It is no accident what they are wearing,
what colors, what they will say, what
motions they will make. Now there may be
varying degrees of significance to each
and every person about what every other
person is doing. But nonetheless, you
have agreed on a telepathic level to
arrive in this interaction together and
to support everyone else in that
interaction by adding your energy so
that they will get out of it what they
need and in them supporting you to allow
you to get out of it what you need. It
is a cocreation. You are all masters in
that sense. You are all conductors. You
are all creating the timing of the
orchestration of this interaction
between your civilization and our
civilizations. No accidents whatsoever.
Inspiration, individual impact is the product of the
individual impact is the product of the
same understanding. And that
understanding is basically as follows.
Inspiration and impact are the creation
are the products of when you know that
you are connected to the whole. When you
know that you can draw from the whole
and act with that knowledge as the full
individual that you are knowing you are
supported by the whole. If you could not
be supported by the whole, if you were
not supported by the whole, you as an
individual would not exist in this
particular conglomerate because there is
no such thing as an extraneous or a
pointless or an extra or a leftover
creation that does not belong.
Everything that exists fits where it is.
Everything that is where it is fits in
that pattern, fits in that tapestry.
There are no extras. Everything in that
sense is exactly the correct amount.
Therefore, allow yourselves to know as
individuals that each and every one of
you have exactly the same degree of
access to the total energy of your
world, to the total energy of creation
itself because each and every one of you
are equal aspects of the infinite. Each
and every being within creation, if we
may put it this way, is simply one of
the ways that all that is, the infinite
creation has of manifesting itself
within the creation that it is. Another
way of saying this is that each and
every one of you, no matter how
seemingly small and detached from the
whole, each and every one of you as a
part of the whole, contains the ability
to access the information of the total
idea. You are all holographically
structured. We will provide a brief
analogy and an example to explain this
notion of the holographic structure.
Imagine for a moment in your
visualization capabilities that your
world, your dimension that you call
threedimensional existence,
physiological reality, is laid out flat
like a grid, shall we say, stretching to
the horizon as far as you can see. And
on the surface of this plane is painted
a gridwork of lines running in two
directions so that they are at right
angles to each other forming shall we
say squares. Where these lines cross
these intersection points where these
lines cross let us say those points
represent information knowledge that you
may desire to have an access to. Now
let's say you are standing somewhere on
this plane somewhere on this grid. It
doesn't matter where because the grid is
infinite in all directions and no matter
where you are it will appear to be
infinite in all directions. Now let's
say you have a desire to learn many
things to grow in many ways and you take
a look for a moment at the grid under
your feet and you recognize that each
and every one of those squares or each
and every one of those access points is
a point of information that you may
require. Now looking at the grid this
way you may say well this will take
forever to understand anything. And I'll
have to walk and walk and walk and touch
each and every one of those points
before I will able in a sense to access
all of the information I believe I need
to really live my life in the way I want
to. All right, fair enough. When you
look at it from that particular
perspective, however, there is another
way to understand it. And this other
analogy, the continuation of this
analogy actually defines the structure
of existence itself. For this is the way
it is built, shall we say. Looking at
the grid once again as you stand there
now take what you may call a large or a
take what you may call a large or a
small doesn't matter shiny metallic
reflective sphere similar to what you
would call a ball bearing in your
culture. Take that ball bearing and
place it anywhere on the grid. Now
realize that all of the reflection of
the grid, no matter how far it
stretches, is reflected in the warped
surface of that ball bearing. So in
other words, all the information of
every single point on the grid is in
that ball bearing. You can access it by
simply looking at any place around the
ball bearing without having to travel
far and wide to receive that
information. It is all right there in
the same place at the same time. perhaps
seemingly distorted but nonetheless
every single point is there and you can
access it from that point. Each and
every one of you was created to be like
that ball bearing. The total information
of existence shall we say is wrapped up
within you interwoven within your
consciousness your individual
consciousness. What you have done and
what many individuals in creation have
done is to flatten out that
understanding, flatten out that
consciousness into an illusion of
physiological time and space. Your
thirddimensional physical reality is
your projection. You have taken all the
ideas that you are or at least a large
portion of them and you have projected
them into a seemingly dimensional
reality which fills space and takes time
to explore. But now the purpose for
having unfolded in that idea is now
coming to a close. You have experienced
many tens of thousands of years of
experiencing reality in this segregated
remote separated way. Now that you are
arriving at the end of that cycle of
having to perceive your reality in that
manner, you are now beginning to fold up
again. You are now beginning to re pull
all these ideas back into their central
core to reintertwine
with all the other aspects to gather
together all the understanding that you
were created with to begin with. And now
you are beginning to understand that you
have access to things that seem to be so
remote because they are no longer seen
as remote. They are right within you and
have been all the time. Right where you
are, right when you are. Everything, all
the notions of time, all the notions of
space are all within you and created
from you. They are simply your
projections. Even your own physicists
now, at least many of them, not all of
them, but many of them are beginning to
understand that what you have for so
long called physiological reality,
seemingly outside yourself, is actually
nothing more than a projection of the
strongest definition you have been
taught to buy into about what it is. In
other words, physical reality is
constructed of the definitions you give
it. What you believe in most strongly,
either as an individual or as a
collective, what you agree to buy into
as a group, determines how you
experience your physiological reality.
It is the product of your definitions
and in that sense nothing more. This
does not invalidate it. It is a very
worthwhile experience. It is one of the
ways you can experience yourself within
creation and you have done so to a great
degree. The idea in a sense of exploring
The idea in a sense of exploring
physiological reality to the extent that
you have makes you, shall we say, very
well-rounded as far as many
civilizations are concerned because not
many civilizations that we have
encountered have explored the idea of
the physiological dimension to the
extent that your civilization has. And
so because of this, we have invented,
shall we say, a little nickname for all
of you. We call you the masters of
limitation. Now, this is not meant in
any way, shape, or form derogatorily. It
simply means that as you hey have a lot
under your belt. You have a lot of
experience dealing with the idea of
physiological focus of negativity of
limitation of challenge in that sense
and of in your terms transforming those
ideas into positive results. You have a
great deal of experience doing this. You
are one of the most highly focused
civilizations we have ever come across
in that way. And that's why there is
such a great deal of interest in your
civilization now because you are taking
all the focus that you have experienced
for tens of thousands of years, all the
focus that has been placed on negativity
and now you're deciding that you may
just want to place it in a positive
direction. We have used to describe this
transformation on your planet what is
called the rubber band analogy. If you
take one of your rubber bands and draw
it very far back, let us say into
negativity as you have in the past will
recognize that the farther back you have
drawn into negativity, when you finally
decide to let it go, it will snap that
much farther and that much faster into
the positive side. And therefore, we see
your civilization as truly being on the
brink, truly being on the threshold of
monumental and instantaneous and
inspirational change in a positive
direction. Much of what you may now
perceive to be the violence that is
escalating on the surface of your planet
from our perspective in a sense is
simply your civilization getting the
last vestigages of these, shall we say,
tantrums out of its system before you
make the change. You are now bubbling
all this negativity up to the surface.
No longer is it being covert. No longer
are you pushing it down into your
subconscious and being secretive about
this idea. You are bringing it all out
in the open in a sense so that you can
display before everyone these ideas and
so that everyone can truly see what is
going on and say to themselves, is this
the type of world we really desire? Or
do we desire something else? Perhaps a
world of harmony, a world of peace. Now
that we see that we have brought all
this out into the open, you may be now
saying to yourselves on the unconscious
levels, now we can decide that we no
longer prefer it that way. that now we
prefer the idea of creating a world of
joy and allowing ourselves to expand in
that manner in an ecstatic way and
reclaiming your birthright of creator of
ecstasy because you are made in the
image of the infinite. And what that
means is that you are an infinite
creator as well. It is simply that the
type of reality you have experienced for
tens of thousands of years has created
an ability within you to forget that you
are connected to the infinite. But now
that you have played the scenario out of
all the limitation and the
forgetfulness, all the transformations
and the explorations you are now doing
on a spiritual level is the remembering,
the reawakening of yourselves to
yourself, remembering and rediscovering
exactly who and what you always have
been. Many of the things that you are
now learning, it isn't so much that you
are learning something new. You are
simply remembering more and more and
more of what you already know, of who
you already are. That's what your
transformational age primarily is all
about. When any civilization begins to
explore in that particular direction, it
sends out a particular radiation. And
that radiation is picked up by many
other civilizations such as our own that
have already explored those particular
levels of consciousness. And we answer
that radiation as if it were an
invitation to begin to function as
mirrors to reflect back to you the
experiences we have had, how we have
explored the idea of the realms. you are
now beginning to explore. Not so that
you will have the understanding that you
must do it in exactly the same way we
did. By no means, but simply to reflect
back to you that we have explored those
realms and that we can share with you
how our explorations have benefited us
have served us. You will do it in your
own way. No matter what we share with
you, we simply wish to be of service to
you to allow you to understand that you
can explore those realms and you can
explore them to your benefit. We desire
this because in serving you in this way
and allowing you to expand your
awareness of who you are, it expands our
awareness of who we are and gives us new
beings to interact with new
civilizations to explore all of creation
with side by side intertwined and
intermixed. And that exploration
together expands the notion of our place
within creation.
Therefore, we will always, as I will do now, extend
we will always, as I will do now, extend
to you a firm understanding that we
deeply appreciate your willingness to
form and co-create with us these types
of interactions. For bit by bit and day
by day, through such interactions, do
you make it more possible and more
feasible for our world to be able to
interact with yours as an equal? For
that is the only way we will interact
with you. When you know you are equal
not only to us but to each other. Then
you will be the frequency, the vibration
that makes it capable for us to be able
to interact with you on a level that is
common to us both. Until then we are too
different in vibration to be able in a
sense to interact face to face in a
continuing manner. The idea and the
notion is up to you. We cannot force the
issue upon you of interacting with us.
But if it is your desire to do so and if
it is your desire to blend as one world,
then by all means remember you have the
ability to create the inspiration to do
so. You have the power of individual
impact each and every one of you to
change the total face of your
civilization. What you do as an
individual, what you act upon physically
as an individual with regard to
sustaining and supporting the creation
of your world as a homogeneous entity
will have a lot to do with our ability
to interact with you. We thank you,
however, for the opportunity to
experience you as ambassadors of your
society. For make no mistake about it,
that's exactly what you are right now.
For there are many on this end that are
listening other than myself. shall we
say they are plugged in to this
interaction. We thank you for allowing
me to represent the association of
worlds that make up all the societies
with whom we interact. And in return for
your gift of allowing us to share these
ideas with you, I will ask you now in
what way may I serve you?
Hi Bashar.
And to you good day.
I want to talk about the peace event
that just happened around the world.
And I wanted to ask if you had any
numbers for us. We have no way of
knowing how many people actually
participated and took that initiative as
an individual. And we wondered if there
was some way you could tell us
approximately how many people really
tuned into that.
Approximately 15 to 20%.
Of what?
Of your planet.
Understand? Yes. The idea will have fluctuations and
Yes. The idea will have fluctuations and
variations and will not necessarily mean
that every individual that participated
participated in exactly the same way
with full consciousness of one
particular group's project. But there
are enough individuals on your planet
now that are focusing on the idea so
that their focuses overlap
simultaneously thus creating in that
moment an approximately 15 to 20% surge
of acceleration towards the idea of
world peace. You understand?
Yes. Can you explore that a little more
with us and tell us, you know, we're
planning it again next year. Keep going
with it.
Now, the idea is, of course, for you to
rely on your own imagination, for that
is the brilliant key that will always
allow you to create whatever
methodologies will work best for your
civilization. Whatever inspires you is
representative of who you are and is
representative of the strongest impact
you can make. That's why a certain idea
inspires you because it is on the
wavelength of the full being that you
are. And if you act on it, you will have
an impact and you will make a
difference. Now at what you call
your break time, you will be able to
avail yourself also of information that
we have supplied on a project we have
called the peace clock. I will define it
for now and the channel will also make
you aware of it after during your break
time. The idea of the project that we
have called the peace clock is very
simple and it is as follows. You may do
this or any other idea that comes to
mind to assist your world in the
creation of peace. Step one, every
single day of your day of time at your
noon time in your time zone upon your
planet for one full minute at your noon
time in any way, shape, or form that is
comfortable for you. Meditate on world
peace. See your world enjoying the idea
of peace and harmony.
Part two,
take that information, take that idea of
the one minute meditation at noon and
share that idea with as many individuals
as you possibly can.
The basic goal, shall we say, is to have
every single individual, yes, every
single individual on your planet doing
that one minute meditation by what you
call your January 1st, 1990. You
understand? Yes. If that is accomplished, you will
Yes. If that is accomplished, you will
find such a high degree of accelerated
energy around your world, focused on
world peace that you will be able to
have the foundations laid down within
simply the one decade between your 1990
and your year 2000. So that you will
have a foundation for what you would
call one world by that time, no later
than what you would call your 2013 2011.
And by doing that, you will create a
type of conductive and conducive
atmosphere that will allow our
civilizations far more ability to
interact with your civilization far
before your year 2000 mark. To help
accelerate that whole idea along, there
is literature that will be dispensed
upon this idea of the peace clock. You
may each take the idea, take the
literature and in your terms make as
many copies as you wish and share it
with as many individuals as you wish to.
It will have an impact also. Simply
continue to design any idea you wish to
with regard to world peace. Whatever
inspires you, whatever excites you the
most, that excitement is there because
you in doing it that way will have the
greatest impact. That's what excitement
lets you know. That is the signal, the
sign that when something excites you,
that is the thing that if you do it will
be able to allow you to have the
greatest impact upon your planet as a
whole. You understand?
Yes. Does this assist you?
Yes. Well, thank you very much for your
Well, thank you very much for your
sharing.
Sharing. Hello, Michelle.
Hello, Michelle.
And good day to you.
I wonder if you can assist me.
Maybe, maybe not.
Lift the mic up.
Um, I called Lord Clankardi of the British
I called Lord Clankardi of the British
Parliament last week.
And requested that he give you an
audience to the British Parliament.
All right. Now he has done that on the
subject of UFOs for many people over the
last 10 years including myself as
but at this time I learned that he was
suffering from a rare disease
and he is unable uh to carry on his
work. There can be another which will take his
There can be another which will take his
place. The British government has taken
this opportunity of his illness which
consists of a bone disease which has
reduced his right hand to half its small
size has taken this opportunity to
terminate the regular meetings that he
has been conducting with um people
interested in these extraterrestrial
subjects. We understand.
We understand.
So our question is how may we assist
him? The idea is to open up lines of
The idea is to open up lines of
communication, not in an attacking
sense, not in an accusatory sense, but
simply lines of communication now to
allow any and all of your governments to
understand that your public now knows
that such information exists and desires
the idea for the sharing and the release
and the dispensation of that
information. You see the idea now is
that that individual symbolically has
been removed to allow what you now call
the public to take his place. Allowing
there to be more blending between the
idea of what you call the official
government and your public because as
far as we are concerned your public is
your government and there really does
not have to be as much segregation
between the two factions as there have
been. So this in a sense shall we say is
a sterling opportunity for the idea of
your public to be able to follow in the
footsteps of that individual now that
that individual has in a sense opened a
door created a template which your
public can follow which you and many
other individuals who are of the same
desire can follow. So what you can do
perhaps as a suggestion will be up to
you. We're not telling you what to do.
As a suggestion is to contact the
individuals on the public level that
desire for that information to continue
that desire for that information to be
released and then in your terminology
erect a petition for the continuation of
that particular outlet and avenue. You
understand? Yes, I do. Thank you.
Yes, I do. Thank you.
Thank you very much for your boldness
and your willingness.
Now much information is going to begin
coming out in your society from many
different sources within what you call
the next 2 years of your time regarding
the information about us that your
government has known for quite some
time. Understand many of your
governments are very well aware of our
existence. But because of the idea and
the notion of what you have created your
governments to be have suppressed that
information out of fear. Fear that your
public would panic. Fear that there
would be a loss of power. fear that
there would be an upsetting of what you
call your status quo and that everything
in your society would be, as you say,
turned upside down. Now that you are
becoming more adult about taking
responsibility for the idea of your own
lives, you can begin to allow your
governments to know in a loving way that
you are ready and willing to take on the
responsibility of acting like one world
and therefore are more than willing to
interact with other whole worlds and
that they can share with you the
information they have for so long
already known about about our existence.
If you approach it in the right way, in
sufficient enough numbers, in a loving
way, they will in your terms acquies
because they will begin to realize that
it isn't a matter of losing their own
power. It is a matter of gaining
personal empowerment for every single
individual upon your planet.
Shing. Hello.
Hello.
And to you, good day.
Along that line, there are governments
within governments within governments.
We understand the complexities that you
have created in your society
and you have
before said ask your government.
Yes. Which uh
Which uh
but we have also said be your
government. We have said be your
government. Yes. Yes.
Understand?
True. Now remember that if you are of a
particular frequency, if you are of a
particular reality idea, then when you
act according to what excites you the
most in a loving and integrated way, you
will reach whatever individuals you need
to reach because like vibration attracts
like vibration. You don't have to
analyze the situation to discover where
you need to be. If you simply act in a
particular manner, you will
automatically attract all the
individuals that are representative of
the same vibrational frequency you are
on. You understand?
Yes. And that
Done. Okay.
Okay.
Does that serve you?
Yes. Well, thank you very much.
Well, thank you very much.
Another question I'd like to ask is in
regards to the triad.
Yes. If it's
If it's
are you referring to your world of
earth, our world of Asani and the
civilization of Sirius?
Correct. Continue.
Continue.
What is the revelence the reence to um
the reticulum
and the pletes
in relationship to this formed triad? I
mean is is this a
a newer triad from old triads
the triad that is going on now? The
relationship, shall we say, between your
civilization, ours, and the civilization
of the star you call Sirius is for the
express purpose of allowing you to
remember who and what you are, so that
the older connections you have to the
Plleadian systems can be recconnected.
The connections you have to the
reticulum civilization to some degree is
a part of the facilitation of not only
your memory of who you are but the
furthering of your society so that it
can be adapted to the vibration that
your world will become in the
transformation. The interaction going on
between your society and the society you
call the reticulum society. The ones
more often than not responsible for what
you have called the abduction cases in
your civilization.
There is many things going on between
your respective societies. Some things
we cannot allow to be delineated at this
time. However, let us simply say they
are serving you to change in ways that
represent your transformational planet.
And you are helping them change in ways
that represent the transformation they
need to go through. They are functioning
as the physiological lever to allow you
to face to face yourselves with your
fear to integrate them and to go beyond
them to transcend many ideas of your
past limitations even as you allow them
to change in the ways they need to
change that is representative of their
transformation. They are in a sense the
turning of the key specifically to allow
your subconsciousness and your
unconsciousness to become one with your
outer consciousness. Now just as a side
note, the whole issue of what we have
termed these abductions,
we would prefer if you would use the
label temporary detainments
because no one in your terminology in a
sense is being taken away permanently.
And all those interactions whether your
people can remember it or not happen
through agreements that have been made.
Nothing is happening against the
original agreements. You understand?
Yes. Does this assist you?
Does this assist you?
Yes. And along with that line then could
you at this time get into the personal
frequency of a period of time
define myself
myself
in relationship to the pleadings?
No. Second week in March.
Second week in March.
Not at this time. There will be more
information from your guides in your
dream state before we will be allowed to
dispense any information along that line
for you are in mid-process and we cannot
interrupt it. All right. Not at this
time. Not from me. From others.
Not from me. From others.
I see.
Pleasant dreams.
Thank you very much.
Sh. Good morning, Bashar.
Good morning, Bashar.
And good day. Who you?
Uh maybe something a little bit on the
lighter side as far as a question. It
is all light to me.
All right.
This question refers to a previous uh
question from a previous interaction.
Someone asked a question of you to
describe some of the other civilizations
you are aware of and you told them at
this time well okay maybe a few you said
and you gave them a couple of examples.
One of the examples you gave them of a
particular society was a society you
referred to by the name the Dilla.
Yes. And I believe you mentioned that
this uh planet planetary society had as
a product, you could say as a product
for export their humor.
Well, in a sense, I was just wondering
or questioning now if you could in any
way, shape or form give us an example of
some of the humor of the Dylan.
Yes. Oh,
the idea first of all to understand they
are not a planetary society as such as
you would understand it in
three-dimensional terms. You might
perceive if you were in their dimension
that they did in fact exist, shall we
say, upon so to speak, a planet, but
they are of a quasi plastic
physiological etheric astral
composition. They are not physically
understanding. They are very simplified
forms, very malleable. You would
perceive them as simplified, shall we
say, wax in forms with no discernable
features that can meld themselves or
mold themselves into any particular
shape they wish at any particular time.
Even to the extent of blending fully
within the smooth surface of what you
would call their planet, which in a
sense is simply a mass consciousness of
the total civilization rendered into the
same plastic etheric material. You
understand me so far?
Yes. The idea therefore is not so much
that they have a specified humor in the
format you would call joke. It is simply
the idea that they are very high in
vibratory energy along the lines of what
you would call enjoyment of ecstasy of
laughter of that vibration of
enlightenment. And the idea is that
their lifestyle in that sense radiates a
humorous vibration. In other words, if
you were to stand in their vibration,
stand in their frequency, you would feel
that you would be enlightened all the
time. You would feel very lightheaded,
very giddy in that sense. You would feel
that everything was worth laughing at.
You understand?
Are there any individuals on this planet
that have correlation to that?
Many times, yes. Especially the
individuals from time to time that you
call Zen masters.
You understand?
Yes. Yes. because they recognize that
enlightenment is truly the product of
lightening up. Understand? Yes. That
frequency, that energy is what the shall
we say dilla export. They radiate it
because they are in a constant state of
fluctuation becoming this, becoming that
and feeling the ecstasy of the change in
a sense. Now we do not necessarily mean
this to translate colloquially but in a
sense they are simply always involved or
immersed in the energy of laughter
itself. You understand
that energy that feeling that rush is
the energy that binds them together.
They are cohesive within that
electromagnetic fluctuation in that
electromagnetic soup shall we say. It
vibrates at a pitch that radiates what
you would call absolute ecstasy and they
are embroiled in it, immersed in it,
leaping in it. The other aspect of your
civilization that exhibits it most
parallel to the dilla would be the
dolphins upon your planet. You
understand it?
Yes. For they live in a sea and in a sense
For they live in a sea and in a sense
are a part of it. They blend with it.
They are the other alien civilization
upon your planet. And through telepathic
contact and sharing and physical play,
they can give you that sense can impart
to you that sense of ecstasy and joy and
compassion and love. Go and learn it
from them and you will know very very
precisely what the dill feel like. You
understand? Yes, I do. Thank you very much.
Yes, I do. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for your sharing.
Sh. Hello Bashar.
And to you good day strawberry.
How is it?
Perfect. And you?
Wonderful. Michelle, I've encountered a
fascinating phenomena that I encountered
a few times before.
All right. Do she?
Has some wonderful intensity to it this
time. All right. Um, as a little bit of a
All right. Um, as a little bit of a
parallel background, we have the concept
of the past being created from the
present. Yes.
Yes.
And the guy concept of parallel
dimensions that can be created right out
of the present where you're creating a
totally different past from one that you
had before.
Did you all get that?
Well, this went out as very fascinating.
I picked up a book. A book was given to
me by a close friend a couple of weeks
ago. I've been reading the book. It's
called 2150
nice and I have been having the experience
and I have been having the experience
first of all the book was published in
1971 according to the copyright and as
far as I was able to experience this
kind of material did not exist pre at
that particular period of time at least
in my conscious understanding. All
right. And the experience is that I've
been feeling as a great intensity that
this book didn't exist before in the
time stream that I had been in
previously. Not in your recognition oriented
Not in your recognition oriented
reality. No.
Right. Because your timing was not ready
for it.
Well, the traditional method to explain
that would be of course that one was not
aware of that. What is is there actually
you can walk right by something which in
your terminology exists in everyone
else's reality and you can literally not
see it even if you are staring right at
it as far as everyone else is concerned
if you are not ready to see it. It isn't
in your experiential reality.
Yes, I understand. But is the phenomenon
also occurring where we are encountering
things that are creating an entirely
different track that did not exist? So
there's a shift into a parallel
dimension. Yes.
Yes.
Do you experience that? That's an energy
that I've been flowing into.
Yes. Here and there you have been
popping in and out. Although we perceive
you do not know what to make of it quite
yet. It's a lot of fun.
It's a lot of fun.
Yes.
Okay. That was primarily this year. By
the way, do you have any uh games of
chance up on this like we have in Vegas?
No. No chance. No chance.
No.
Okay. Thanks a lot. for everyone in our
civilization always wins.
Thank you, Sherry.
Greetings, Mich and you. Good day.
My name is uh Chan Johnson.
Paul, right?
And you might remember me as the uh the
cartoonist who was working on a comic
strip. Yes.
Yes.
And I've uh made efforts to draw
likenesses of you.
Efforts. Well, uh
Well, uh
did you have a good time?
Well, I got the information from the
channel and I was trying to render an
exact uh or near exact lack in two
dimensions. You are close enough.
You are close enough.
Oh, good. Well, that was the question I
wanted to ask. I did one tonight and I
showed it to the channel
of uh of you and uh any
Yes. And I was wondering if it was uh
And I was wondering if it was uh
exacting enough.
It is close enough. We thank you.
All right.
For your expression, for getting in
touch with that frequency and that
vibration. We desire that the exercise
gave you joy.
All right.
And we desire that that exercise also
put you more closely in touch with your
own expression of self.
Well, thank you.
We thank you.
Um, I was wondering if you could help me
to explore the idea of which larger
extraterrestrial group that I might have
come from before I came to planet Earth.
There are some Orion connections.
But the idea once again to remind each
and every one of you is that when you
talk about origin points, it is a very
nebulous thing. All of you are from
everywhere and nowhere. And in that
sense, none of you are original to your
planet to begin with. Anyway, but the
idea now and then in your lives may pop
up that you say, I feel I have origin
somewhere else.
That recognition on that particular
track is simply representative
of a track that stands out of all the
other trackcts that represent your
connections to everything else because
of the definitions you have created
yourself to be in this present life. In
another life, another track may have
stood out. Do you understand?
Yes. But in this life, one of the strongest
But in this life, one of the strongest
tracks you have is what we have termed
of the ancient Orion lineage. I think
the correct question would have been
another channel I had never met but
through uh a friend of mine I had asked
the question
uh this channel Dr. Peebles told me via
a tape that I was gathering information
for my brothers and sisters off of the
planet and inside the planet. Uh he
didn't uh he wasn't very exacting and
saying who the the beings were.
Yes. Could you help me with that please?
Could you help me with that please?
May I ask you a question?
Certainly. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Are you doing as we have asked many
individuals the thing in your life that
truly excites you the most?
Uh off and on. Yes.
Off and on.
Well, my ideas of this change and have been
my ideas of this change and have been
been changing.
All right. When they change, do you
follow it?
Pretty much. Yes.
Pretty much. All right. Fair enough. I'm
not going to badger you.
But the idea is closely connected to
that information that you seek. Because
only by being the fullest individual you
can be, will you be fulfilling the idea
you chose to be and as such will you be
gathering together the information in
the way that will allow you to be
consciously aware of where you are also
dispersing that information to and whom
you are sharing that information with.
For you are doing so on many different
levels. Yes, many of you are. The idea
simply, however, is that many times
analytical understanding of exactly who
it is you are sharing that information
with can get in the way of simply
continuing to absorb and experience your
life spontaneously. Now there are
connection to other dimensional
frequencies, other dimensional beings.
But we are always going to be hesitant
to place a specific label on those
beings because in many cases it can
render your focus too narrow and not
allow you to continue to experience your
life in a spontaneous manner, not allow
you to be enough of your own individual
if you think you have to work for
everyone else. You want to understand?
Yes, I do.
The idea is sufficient. Allow yourself
to simply feel the energy that you are
to act upon the things that excite you
the most and to understand that you are
dispensing that information to whomever
needs it. The majority shall we say of
the consciousnesses that you are
dispensing the information to from this
life are simply alternate lives that you
are living in other realities. Anyway,
you understand that is a part of the
bleedth through that happens from one
time track to another. You are getting
bleed through from those other lives
yourself as well. But many times you do
not recognize the bleed through any of
you because it comes to you in a format
that seems to originate from within the
reality you exist because otherwise it
wouldn't make much sense to you. So you
don't always recognize that when
information comes to you, it actually
may be coming from the experiences that
an alternate or a parallel reality you
is having. In like manner, the
experiences you are gaining, the
knowledge you are gaining in this life
is bleeding through to other parallel
lives. And this is some the majority of
the other dimensional beings that the
other entity was referring to. You
follow me?
Yes, I do.
Does this answer your question
sufficient? Yes, it does.
Yes, it does.
Remember that you are all
multi-dimensional beings and that the
oversoul that you are has many many many
lives going on simultaneously in
parallel dimensions of reality and they
all interact. But many times you do not
necessarily need or want conscious
analytical recognition of exactly what
that interaction is because that
recognition would halt the process of
the spontaneous experience you are
having in this life. If you all of a
sudden became analytically aware of all
the other parallel lives you were living
in this physical state, you wouldn't be
able to budge.
You understand? You will be overwhelmed
and shortcircuited with electronic
overload. That circle
That circle
relax. Relax. The more you enjoy the
life you are, the more you expand in
ways that allow all the other lives you
are living to be able to merge and blend
with you in the softest possible
interface. Thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you, sir.
Sir, sir. sir.
Thank you.
In closing, yes.
In closing, may I say that the past two
years that that I've had the privilege
of interacting with you in the Sasani uh
has been a real adventure and uh one of
which I've enjoyed very much in terms of
uh wins and losses. Well, my expansion
has been phenomenal and I'm enjoying
every second of it.
We thank you for allowing us to
experience also a high degree of ecstasy
in the interactions with each and every
one of you. We thank you and our
unconditional love to you for
remembering more and more of who you
are. Shutting.
Hello Bashar. Good day to you. My name
is Ken and I got a personal question.
No. All right.
Uh what just what is my mission here in
this in this particular line?
What is your mission? All right. Now
you have briefly heard us discuss the
idea of excitement. Yes.
Yes. All right. Let me put it on a
All right. Let me put it on a
foundational level for each and every
one of you so that you can understand it
this way and so that all of you can
apply these ideas to your own version of
this question.
I will give you a definition.
Excitement. That feeling you call excitement or
That feeling you call excitement or
knowingness or certainty.
Feeling like you are where you belong.
That feeling, that excitement, that
knowledge. These ideas translate as
follows. All of this is the physical translation
All of this is the physical translation
of the vibratory energy that represents
the path you chose to be in this life.
In other words, the reason something
excites you more than anything else is
because that's who you are at that
moment. And therefore, that's what you
need to act on at that moment. Let me
put it this way.
You are all reincarnational beings. You
have many lives, alternate lives, past
lives, future lives.
However, the you you are now only has one life to
the you you are now only has one life to
live. You have never been this you
before and you will never be this you
again. Therefore, the fundamental
purpose to your life is to live this
life to the fullest that you can.
Therefore, the way you go about that,
fulfilling your mission, is to
live your life to the fullest by
choosing out of all the opportunities
that present themselves to you in this
life at any given moment, the one that
excites you the most and acting on it
with full integrity at every moment. If
you do that, you will be fulfilling your
purpose and your mission in this life.
For understand many of the projects,
many of the missions, many of the
purposes that many of you talk about,
the goals, the services, the
interactions that you play out in this
physical life, they are not specifically
the purpose of your life. They are the
methods through which you express the
purpose of your life. Any particular
mission that you might come up with in
your imagination that feels correct to
you will not actually be the purpose of
your life. It will be the way you have
decided represents the easiest way to
fulfill the purpose of your life which
is living it to the fullest and being of
service in whatever way you say
represents your ease of creation and
gives you the highest degree of
abundance and ecstasy. You understand?
I hope so.
You hope so? Not sure. All right. Hope
implies doubt. Let's clarify the issue.
Well, I am Go ahead. Go ahead.
All right. I will simply continue by
asking you, are you doing in your life
the thing that excites you the most or
not? Not necessarily.
Not necessarily.
Why not?
That's a good question.
Well, thank you very much.
Do you have an answer?
Why not? If you are able to conceive of
something that would be far more
exciting and far more ecstatic than
anything you're doing now, why aren't
you doing it?
Good question. I got to work on that.
If you say so. But it doesn't have to
take a lot of time. Unless you feel that
you want it to. Do you want it to?
No, not really.
Well, all right. Then why work on it?
Why not create it and realize it now?
Good idea.
Do you have something you can share with
us that represents something that you
are not doing that would be very
exciting to do?
I suppose so. Yes. I uh
Do you care to share it with us? You
don't have to.
Well, I'm a chemist.
Yes. And I would uh like to get into the tree
And I would uh like to get into the tree
planting business.
Tree planting. All right. What prevents
you from doing so?
Say that a little louder for everyone.
Money. Thank you very much. What you
mean is abundance?
Something like that.
Something like that. Yes. The idea is to
understand that you can redefine the
issue of abundance. We understand the
notion of money upon your planet. And in
no way, shape, or form are we
invalidating it. For it is one of the
ways that your planet has of expressing
abundance. However, it isn't always the
only way, and sometimes it isn't the
easiest nor the quickest way. So why
insist that money must be the way if
other ways can actually come sooner? All
we are saying is that when you allow
more than just one way to be
representative of your abundance, then
very often you will actually get what
you are asking for in exactly the way
you imagine you would get it because you
are open to allowing it to happen in any
way that it could rather than insisting
that if it doesn't happen this way, it
can't happen at all. Let us give you a
broader definition of abundance and see
if this assists you. Abundance dot dot
paying attention. Are you paying
attention? Have a good
Are you paying attention?
Oh, you bet.
Abundance. The ability to do what you need to do
The ability to do what you need to do
when you need to do it. Period. Hey,
didn't say anything about money in that
definition. Where did the money go? One
more time. The ability. Underline.
Underline. Underline. The ability to do
what you need to do when you need to do
it. Period. That's abundance. Now, money
can be one of the ways in which you can
develop the ability to do what you need
to do when you need to do it. But it
isn't always the only way. If
you take it a step at a time, very
methodically, very, if you wish,
scientifically, you can do it as
follows. At any given moment, if you
recognize that there is a particular
thing such as your tree planting that
really is more exciting than anything
else you are doing now that you really
want to do but you do not immediately
see a way to do it. You do not
immediately see an avenue upon which you
could act in order to activate that
reality. Then look around at all the
things you are capable of acting upon of
doing something about. Out of all the
things you are capable of doing
something about, pick the one that
excites you the most, even if it appears
to be completely unconnected to the idea
of the tree planting. On the surface,
its appearance does not have to be
connected. The fact that it excites you
more than any other thing you could do
is what connects it to the other thing
that excites you that you cannot do
right now. If you act in this moment on
the thing that excites you the most with
full integrity and full trust in a
positive sense, it will lure you, no
matter how it seems, it will lure you
into the appropriate circumstances
automatically to give you the ability to
do the other thing that excites you the
most that you could not do before. And
what you will experience by going
through that route will give you the
tools you will need when you are capable
of doing the other thing in the process.
You understand?
Yes, sir.
All excitement is a thread. It leads to
all other excitement. It is all
intertwined. No matter how it appears on
the surface in the most unlikely
circumstances, you will be automatically
led into the appropriate situation to
give you the ability to do the thing
that excites you the most. And it isn't
an issue when we talk about trust. It
isn't an issue of using something you
have never used before. Many individuals
when we talk about the idea of using
trust say, "Oh no, that's hard. You mean
I have to be totally trusting? Everyone
knows how difficult that is." Oh no,
trusting. I'm a bit rusty on trust. None
of you none of you are rusty on trust.
You have all always yes always without
exception at every given moment used
infinite trust in everything you have
created and attracted in your lives.
It's just a matter of whether you are
trusting in a positive point of view or
a negative point of view because what
you call doubt is not actually a lack of
trust. It is a trust in a negative
belief. You have always used trust and
it has always worked flawlessly for you.
So all you're doing now is redefining
the direction of the trust. You are
saying I no longer trust in the negative
belief, the negative definition of my
reality as being stronger than the
positive one. Now you are saying that
the positive one is stronger and
therefore that is what shall occur.
Understand? Yes, I do.
Yes, I do.
Does this assist you?
Yes, it does. Then we would simply
suggest if you are willing that you send
our love to the trees that you plant.
Very good.
And we thank you for sharing your love
with them, for sharing your chemistry
with them and for allowing them to share
theirs with you.
Thank you very much.
We thank you.
By the way, these ideas we are
discussing, they are not airy
philosophies. They are not simply a nice
way to think. We are discussing
mechanics. We are discussing physics.
Every idea that you put out determines
utterly what you get back. It is
absolutely a mechanical idea as far as
physiological reality is concerned.
Attitude is everything because you are
the creators of your experiential
reality. Proceed.
Proceed.
Well, hello. Hi. Well, hello to you.
I can see I'm going to get in trouble if
I ask you what my mission is.
Oh, but I promise it will be a lot of
fun. About 22 years ago.
About 22 years ago.
Yes.
I had an experience like Daryl.
All right.
Only I had it for a much longer period
of time.
All right. Will you care to share and
define your experience?
Well, I also connected up with the
flying saucers.
Describe. Um, what do you mean describe?
Um, what do you mean describe?
What you are calling the spacecraft?
Describe it.
Oh, it was um uh several.
All right, describe them.
Okay. The first one uh was at night and
it had lights all the way around it. It
was flat and the lights were flashing on
and off.
Completely flat.
Well, it was dark and there were trees
behind it and I could see the trees
behind it. So, I knew it was rather
this light. You mean
this light?
All right.
And uh then after that I saw little
objects floating through the air and I
saw a crystal craft on the ground.
All right.
I saw another craft floating through the
air that landed very hard and I knew it
was trying to show me that it was solid.
No. All right.
And then I've I've seen them in the
daylight and that's how they taught me
that they could read my mind because I
looked out and I could see it below a
cloud and I thought, "You dumbies, don't
you know people can see you?" And
immediately it went up. So,
of course they know.
I know that now. So, anyway, over a
period of about 4 months of of different
experiences of teaching, they vanished.
Thank you. One moment. Remember this
also. However, in any gathering, only
the individuals that are on a particular
frequency will actually be able to
perceive them. Even if someone else is
standing right next to you, if they're
not on the same wavelength, they will
see nothing.
That is true. I was at an airport and I
saw a green one. I could even see the
windows which appeared to be sliding me
in. It was so close to the ground. All
the cars were going back and forth and
no one could see it but me.
It has to do with frequency. You cannot
experience a reality you are not the
vibration of.
Well, apparently I switched vibration
because Yes. So, how do you feel about this?
Yes. So, how do you feel about this?
Well, I was wondering after 22 years
where uh Daryl started his mission. I
was wondering if there was something
supposed to be coming for me.
Supposed to be.
Have you been moved in any particular
direction? Have you been moved to act
upon something and haven't acted upon
it? I haven't been moved to act on anything
I haven't been moved to act on anything
at all.
Nothing at all.
You are saying nothing in life excites
you. No, it's not.
No, it's not.
Do you find it exciting that nothing
excites you?
Well, what I consider exciting might not
be exciting someone else.
Oh, one moment. We did not ask you to
put qualifiers on it, nor invalidate it
out of existence. I simply asked you, is
there something that excites you?
Yes. What is it?
What is it?
Just walking around people.
Just walking.
Yes. I
Any talking?
Well, often there's strangers, but if
there's a little child that comes up to
me, I talk.
A little child. All right. Do you enjoy
interacting with children?
Yes. Do you wish to do more of it? No.
Do you wish to do more of it? No.
Why not?
Because I like it to be a temporary
thing, not a permanent thing.
Why? It's not my not my thing.
It's not my not my thing.
Why?
It's not the way I'm programmed.
Program? You did the programming. Why
did you program yourself that way?
I'm not saying it is positive or
negative. Just asking. It's your
programming programmed by you. Why did
you program it that way?
It just wasn't right for me.
All right. What is right for you?
Well, that's what I'm here to find out.
here to find out. All right. Well, let's
use your imagination. You do have one
yet. Oh, yes.
Oh, yes.
Oh, yes. All right. Well, what have you
already done with your imagination? What
images do you get that inspire you?
Oh, lots of visionary things
such as
a learning experiences in my head and in
my mind, in my third eye.
Yes. What do you want to do with all of
this? Well, I haven't found anything to do
Well, I haven't found anything to do
with it.
I did not ask you what you have found. I
asked you what you want to do.
You see, I don't know.
Yes, you do. I do.
I do.
Yes. Trust yourself. Of course you do.
Perhaps you simply do not believe that
you can. Perhaps you simply do not
believe that doing it would be valid in
the eyes of your society.
Perhaps you have been talked out of
believing that what really excites you
is something you could actually do as a
living. And therefore now, since you
have been talked out of it, you don't
even have the conception anymore.
Possibly. I don't know. I was just
hoping to get a clue.
All right. We're working on it as you
say. Let's start back where you began. Let's
Let's start back where you began. Let's
start with what you did already share.
Let's say now, is your imagination
turned on?
Yes. Is it warmed up?
Is it warmed up?
Very much.
All right. Let's start with what you
already share. Picture yourself walking.
Are you doing so?
Yes. Are you enjoying it?
Are you enjoying it?
Yes.
All right. Why are you enjoying it?
Describe what you are seeing. Because
I'm among trees and there's birds and
butterflies and the lights filtering
there. Oh, walking out in what you call your
Oh, walking out in what you call your
nature countryside. Yes.
Yes. All right. Why does that give you joy?
All right. Why does that give you joy?
Uh, I like the feeling. I like the
essence that's flowing into me.
All right. Is it because you identify
with it?
Probably. Are you sure?
Are you sure?
Be sure. Yes or no?
Talk into the mic, please.
Yes. All right.
All right.
You identify with the energy. You
identify with the vibration. It allows
you to feel your connection to nature.
Yes. Yes.
Yes.
Your connection to the one infinite.
Yes. Yes.
Yes.
All right. Now,
would you
in any way, shape, or form
desire that your entire world felt that
way? Yes.
Yes.
All right. I believe you. I heard
conviction there.
What can you do to assist your world to
feel as you do when you are walking in
nature? Uh, short of writing a book, I don't
Uh, short of writing a book, I don't
know.
Is there anything wrong with writing a
book? Uh, no.
Uh, no.
Does it excite you to do so?
No. All right. Then is there another way
All right. Then is there another way
that would excite you more than the idea
of writing a book? Now, you obviously
were excited by the prospect that
everyone else on your planet might learn
how to feel like you do when you are
among nature. So when you say that, when
you see everyone else learning, how do
you see yourself fitting in to sharing
that idea with them? Do you see yourself
talking to them? Do you see yourself
bringing people into nature to allow
them to experience it? What methodology
do you see in your imagination that
would seem to be the most exciting
methodology for you?
Well, that's why I'm here. I just can't
seem to get all the loose ends together.
There are no loose ends
to how to really serve.
All right. Then perhaps what you simply
need to do is allow yourself I will use
the term for now to practice your
meditation to practice your centering to
allow yourself to open up dialogues with
your own higher self and to ask those
questions of yourself and to allow
yourself to listen to the answers that
are there to allow yourself to take the
time to view all of the options that are
open to you about how to go about
serving in a way that excites you the
most. and to allow yourself to be aware
of these options and then to pick the
one or the ones that truly do excite
you. You understand?
Yeah. Perhaps you simply haven't allowed
Perhaps you simply haven't allowed
yourself to sit still long enough to do
it. Well, all of a sudden I get a vision of
Well, all of a sudden I get a vision of
crystals.
All thank you very much.
Does that excite you?
Why? I love them.
I love them.
You love them. Why did you not say so
before? When I asked you what excites you, love
When I asked you what excites you, love
is included in that definition.
I hadn't thought about it. Oh, well now
you have.
Yes. Do you feel inspired?
Do you feel inspired?
Yes.
What do you want to do about the idea?
I want to get them circulating among
people. Then do so. What's preventing you?
I don't have any.
So, not now. No. But if you are the idea of
not now. No. But if you are the idea of
doing that, then they will be provided
automatically, won't they?
Yes. You believe that? Yes, I do.
You believe that? Yes, I do.
You trust that?
Yes, I do.
Then it will be so it's up to you.
Thank you.
Remember that. I have nothing to do with
it. It's your reality.
But you brought my reality sort of
solidified. I reflected back to you what you already
I reflected back to you what you already
knew.
Yes. The only difference between us is that I
The only difference between us is that I
knew you knew and you didn't.
You see, no matter what you all think of
yourselves, we believe in you utterly.
And that's what you get from us. And
that's the jarring that happens within
you is finally through some crack,
through some opening, through some gap,
you allow us to reflect back to you the
light that you actually are. And that
shatters you, that opens you up and
allows you to begin to identify with the
frequency we are putting out. When you
elevate to match the frequency we are
putting out, the frequency we are giving
back to you, then obvious things come
into your reality. things become
transparent, crystal clear and obvious
and the directions open up. The idea of
the extraterrestrial spacecraft, that is
what they were performing. What we call
the act of identification, sending off a
frequency and seeing how much of it you
bounce back, seeing how much of it you
match. Understand? Yeah.
So
take that energy, fold it inward and
inspire yourself. Raise yourself. Meet
those friends halfway.
Okay, that was my next question. I just
want to know if I if in the future, the
near future, if I could if I would get
my vibration up enough that I could
That is absolutely up to you. It is
completely in your control. We can only
meet you halfway. The best we can do is
provide to you images to inspire you,
ideas to inspire you. But if you don't
act on it, then you will not meet that
vibration. So that is why it is up to you to allow
So that is why it is up to you to allow
yourself to create a decision to create
a decision. Use your free will and say
this is what I prefer. This is what I
want to do. Then do it.
Does that help you?
That helps. Thank you. Well, thank you
for allowing it to be crystal clear
and if it changes, go with the flow,
sharing. Good evening, Bashar.
Good evening, Bashar.
And good day to you.
Um, I know who I am.
Well, thank you very much.
And I I like what I am and I have my own
truth. Oh, thank you very much. I
Oh, thank you very much. I
um I am growing in my truth.
Absolutely. There are thousands of truths.
There are thousands of truths.
Absolutely. An infinite number.
I accept
other people's truths as being truths
for themselves in their level.
Absolutely. But why? And many wars have been fought
But why? And many wars have been fought
over this.
Yes. To put their truth on me. do not accept
To put their truth on me. do not accept
me for what I am. Why is it or will
there ever come a time?
Oh yes, there will.
Maybe there will not be just one truth
but to where all people really accept.
Yes, my truth and me as myself.
my truth and me as myself.
Yes, that is the direction we do in fact
perceive that your planet is headed in.
If it were not so, it is unlikely we
would be able to have this conversation
with all of you right now because you
would not be sufficiently like our
vibration to understand that all the
unity that you do in fact desire on your
planet will need to be the result of the
granting of equality and validity to all
the diversity within your culture.
That's what unity is. The idea is
moving, is changing, is growing on your
planet. It may seem to be slow right now
but do remember that your planet has
lived a life of segregation of
separation. It has forgotten it is
connected to the infinite and therefore
each and every individual does not
understand that every single face it
sees is simply another face of the same
thing because of the separation because
of the limitation that you have created
upon your world. Now this limitation is
dissolving and as it dissolves every
individual will begin to understand that
all the other people they are looking at
is simply themselves in another format
looking back. And as soon as people
begin to realize that that everything is
the same one thing manifesting in all
the multi-dimensional simultaneous ways
that it can there will be no point in
attempting to force a point of view on
someone else because all you'll be doing
is hurting yourself. The idea simply
comes from the fact that your society
has been taught for so long that none of
you are in control. And therefore, if
you do not understand that the control
already exists within, individuals not
wanting to be out of control will seek
to control the exterior environment by
bending it to their will through
domination and forcing their point of
view on everyone else, thinking that if
they do not, they will not experience
the type of reality they desire. Not
understanding that it does not have to
be an issue of this or that. that the
whole of reality is an issue of this and
that, that it is multi-dimensional and
holographic. Your world is catching on.
It is changing. And we do perceive that
within what you call the next 30 to 50
of your years maximum, your entire
civilization will understand this
sufficiently so that they will be
interacting as one world equally with
all of the worlds we are familiar with
and will begin to teach many of these
principles to other worlds even as we
are now assisting you. You understand?
Yes, I do. And that that gives a lot of
hope but
does not give hope gives knowingness.
Although I understand what you mean by
your term of hope in this context.
Yes. Well that that that helps a lot but
still it's
but still
it's it's the people not accepting other
people for what they are to be very
truthful with you. I would like to [Music]
[Music]
this all right. Thank you very much.
Then be the reality you prefer to be to the
be the reality you prefer to be to the
fullest you can and allow yourself to
generate around you the reality that is
reflective of the person and the reality
you believe yourself to be. You see
other people when you see them change it
isn't literally they who have changed.
It is you. Everyone exists already on
all the possible levels there are to
exist upon. There are an infinite number
of earths that you could be
experiencing. Consider them to be simply
different frequencies. Whatever
frequency you are will determine which
earth you begin to experience more and
more and more of. As soon as you start
acting only like the world you believe
to be really true for you and stop
focusing on the fact that everyone else
thinks differently because that
perpetuates the difference. Then as soon
as you focus on the idea of the unity
that you desire and act like that is
there that that is really real for you.
You will shift yourself into the earth
vibration that represents the earth you
prefer. And all of the counterparts of
all the individuals that are here that
are there will be on the same frequency.
They will seem to have changed. It is
you that have changed taking yourself to
that earth. You understand?
Yes, I accept that.
Does that help you?
Yes, it does.
Remember, if you want them to accept you
for who you are, you have to start by
accepting them for who they are.
I definitely do that already. Then do
not take responsibility for the fact
that they may choose to remain on the
earth of their choice. And the idea is
not to run away from that but to bring
heaven to earth. That is the aid and the
assistance that many of you are doing in
the transformational aid. is not that
when you discover there can be a state
called bliss or heaven to run away from
earth to that state but to acknowledge
that that state can come through you and
be dispensed to the earth to allow them
to share in that state. You understand?
Yes, I do.
Well, thank you very much. Unconditional
love is the key.
All right, I accept that.
We thank you very much. Happy traveling.
Thank you.
Go ahead,
Shannon. I'm sure
I'm sure
and to you good day. Speak up so that
all may share.
All right. I'd like to talk a little bit
about the un the subconscious mind. If
you could just give a brief overview,
please. Subconscious mind. Subconscious mind.
Subconscious.
Now, in a sense, from our point of view,
it doesn't really empirically exist. You
are one consciousness. However, because
of the notion, because of the definition
that you are segregational beings,
compartmentalized beings, component
being, you have created the notion that
your consciousness also exists in
components or levels. In a sense, and I
do not mean this derogatorily, please do
not take it that way. In a sense, the
only reason a subconscious mind exists
giving you both the positive and the
negative side is first of all to allow
you to function positively on automatic
so that you do not necessarily have to
have the degree of an you can create
certain things to function on automatic
not having to think about them all the
time. That is the basic function of the
level you call the subconscious. 11. The
majority of that particular creation has
been utilized by your society to act as
a compartment to act as a closet into
which you have stuffed the things that
you fear to face about yourself
consciously to know about yourself
consciously because your society has
been taught that there are things that
are within you that if you discover them
might destroy you, might tear you apart,
might eat you alive.
When you buy into these bedtime stories,
you then are very willing to create a
closet to hide all those things in. And
believe me, many of you have big strong
boards across those closets and they are
firmly nailed shut. When you realize
that you are one consciousness and that
there is absolutely nothing you could
ever discover about yourself that cannot
be used in a positive way, then you will
allow everything that has been
suppressed to come to the surface
because it will only give you the joy of
discovery not fear.
Can you give me some tech or give us
some techniques uh how to bring forth
anything locked in the subconscious that
is is causing us negative patterns
within the life? Well, the first step is
exactly as we have defined to get in
touch with the idea that there is
nothing you could ever discover that
cannot be used in a positive way. Do you
believe that? Yes.
That recognition in and of itself should
do a lot towards ripping off those
boards and opening the door. Because if
you know that everything that is there
can serve you, can give you unending
excitement, I should think that you
would be ready and willing to pull those
board dots with your bare hands just to
guess at what is in that closet. just to
revel it, to dive into it. So you can do
that in your imagination. Create a
scenario. Have a representation of
whatever it is that seems to be your
subconscious, your unconscious. If it is
a closet, all well and good. If it's a
safe, that's up to you. Allow yourself
in your imagination to recognize, to
finally recognize, wait a minute, there
has not been the idea of deep dark fears
waiting in that safe, waiting in that
closet. There are gems, jewels,
treasures, bright and shining gold
waiting in that closet, waiting in that
stake. Pearls of wisdom.
Use your imagination. Rip the boards off
that door. Tear the door off its hinges
with your bare hands and dive into a
room brightly lit full of gems and
jewels of wisdom and knowledge. Swim in
it. Revel in it. Bathe in it. Soak it
in. Feel the ecstasy of allowing all of
that to begin to homogenize and
harmonize with all of you. Then simply
by having activated, by having given
yourself a trigger, a catalyst in that
visualization, know beyond a shadow of a
doubt that as you simply continue to
live your life, all these things will
start to bubble to the surface. And when
they do, do not go back into a fear
reaction. Let it come forth. Know it is
there to serve you in a positive way.
Know it is not an interruption. Know it
is something that belongs in your life.
Integrate it. Find out if you are going
to find yourself fearing it. Why would
you fear it? What definitions of life
would you have bought into that would
create fear about discovering another
portion of your consciousness. Recognize
it is only you. Love it, cherish it,
integrate it, hold it, nurture it, blend
with it, fuse with it, become more than
you were. Grow and expand. Use whatever
methodology in your imagination seems to
work best for you. Then know beyond a
shadow of a doubt that you have
triggered it. Get on with your life and
let them come up as they will. Each and
every experience that comes up that you
integrate will make you that much
stronger and that much bolder and that
much more ecstatic about the next
experience that will come up until you
will find yourself diving headlong into
experiences that only a brief time ago
you would have shunned and shied away
from. You understand?
Yes, I understand. So, go ahead.
Use your imagination. Proceed.
Oh, no. I was going to say that that I
had this idea that as we we become more
conscious that that the unconscious, the
subconscious and the conscious are just
going to meld into one and operate as a
whole. That's probably what is happening
right now anyway.
Yes. You see, that is why many of you
are in a sense facing many different
ideas, becoming unlocked from old
realities, finding yourself in what we
have called limbo states of either
confusion, confusion or depression,
compression. You are gathering yourself
together. You are assessing all the
ideas, all the definitions you have
bought into in your life and you are
reassessing those definitions to
discover whether you still prefer to
keep them or not. Redefine them as you
want to and understand that all the new
definitions will be what the life is you
will experience from that point forward.
You understand?
Yeah. What what about uh mind control
through subliminal suggestion into the
subconscious? Is that possible? Is that
being in a sense? Yes. But do remember this.
in a sense? Yes. But do remember this.
All hypnosis is self hypnosis. In a
sense, you have to agree to the format
or the rules of the game that someone
else can for a while appear to control
you. If you buy into that definition,
then you can play that game out. But all
you're doing in a sense is temporarily
acquiescing your power of choice
seemingly to someone else. You are still
creating the situation. You understand?
Okay. Yeah. One more quick question. a
spiritual de development linear in in a
sense I understand that linear is an
illusion but in a sense that say Hitler
in what he has done while he was on
earth could he have as he left the earth
plane gone onto a plane of of bliss like
the pleades or something like that do
you you understand
I understand what you mean
that particular soul was in a state of
what you would call shock for some time
because of the taking upon itself of the
so much of the negativity and expressing
it in your world the idea therefore is
that There was much healing and
repairing to be done in a sense to that
soul. I am speaking very colloquially
right now, but it will translate best
that way into your language. That being
has not even yet completely emerged from
that state, shall we say, of suspension.
It is, in a sense, being fed new
orientations, new ideas that will allow
it never again to have to or to choose
to funnel the collective negativity of
your planet in the way that it did
before. You understand? Now, should that
being decide to experience what you
would call reincarnation,
which seems likely perhaps within the
next few decades is up to it, it will
then be able, if it wishes to, to
experience exactly the opposite idea and
be a being of unending light and love
and compassion.
So, in a sense, it is linear, then it
does follow an
it can be perceived that way, and that
is just as valid a way to perceive it as
any other way. At the same time, it is
also holographic and not linear. It is
both. It is anything you can conceive it
to be because as we have already
established, all points of view are just
as real as any other point of view.
Okay. Thank you.
Thank you very much. At this timing, you
may all enjoy a short break. We will
resume contact in approximately 10 to 15
of your minutes of pounding.
Let us say continue.
Thank you for being here
and good day to you.
Okay. I have a question about a pattern
in my life that I seem to notice that I
seem to see a lot of other people
struggling to
a pattern. All right.
Yeah. It's sort of a pattern of
perversion. It's kind
enough perversion.
How poetic. Poetic pattern of
perversion. All right.
It's kind of like um the more I say I'm
going to do something, the more I end up
going further away from it.
Oh, all right.
Go on a diet and I end up gaining more
weight, I find out what excites me and I
go do the exactly the opposite.
Is this fun for you?
No, it's not.
And I'd like to know you give me some
insight into why I keep doing it or why
people do it. Let's use your
imagination, shall we?
All right.
Thank you very much. Using your
imagination right now and being as
honest as you can, me, tell me for the
moment, if you were in fact to do what
you really say you want to do, do you
have any particular notion of what the
result would be? Can you imagine what
the result would be of doing the thing
you really want to do as opposed to the
thing you don't?
Well, I imagine I would be much happier
and much more fulfilled.
Are you sure?
Yes. Are you sure you believe that that
would be the result of doing it?
Well, I don't know why I wouldn't think
it wouldn't be.
All right. Do you have
another specific idea? A particular idea
we can use unless you would like to use
one of the ones you have already
mentioned. Another specific idea that
really excites you that you really want
to do, but that you wind up doing just
the opposite of.
Well, like I like artwork. I like to do
art. All right. Art work,
All right. Art work,
right? And um
in what way would you really prefer to
be doing it?
Well, I would like to be doing it so
that I can make a living at it. Um
possibly traveling around or going Yeah.
going wherever I wanted to and I would
be able to feel like I could make a
living no matter where I went.
All right. Is this something that seems
real to you?
Well, it's in there.
It's in where?
In my brain. It's a something that I
would like to do.
All right. But just because it is there,
just because it is one of the options,
it may not necessarily stand out as
something that you believe can be real
eyed, so to speak. Do you really believe
it has the potential to be realized?
Yes, I do. Yes.
Oh. All right. Can you really see
yourself doing it?
Yes. Is it easy for you to picture yourself
Is it easy for you to picture yourself
doing it?
Yes. All right. Then here is our suggestion.
All right. Then here is our suggestion.
Take that picture that you have. Do you
have it still?
Uhhuh. Right?
See that picture of you doing the thing
you prefer to do. Then believe and
understand that that is the real you
right now, right now. Not the idea of
wanting to become that you someday out
there in the future,
but that you are that you right now
simply because you can conceive of it.
And anything you can conceive of in the
present is real in the present. You
understand? Yes. So first step, see it. Now plug all
Yes. So first step, see it. Now plug all
of your physiological senses into it. In
other words, if you can see yourself
being that you, and by the way, this is
a technique of the imagination that will
work for all of you in any way. If you
can see the you you prefer to be. Then
in your meditative state, as you say,
get into the picture.
Feel what it would feel like to be that
you taste as that you would taste. See
the things that you would see, hear the
things that you would hear, feel the
things that you would feel, touch the
things that you would touch in the way
that you would touch them, not in the
way you do now. Notice all the things
that that you does that are different
from what you do now. Then
Then
if there is a circumstance or a
situation in your life that the you
believe you are now doesn't know how to
handle, conjure up that you you prefer
to be, plug all your senses into it. Get
excited about being that you. I would
assume that if you really believe that
that was you, you would get excited
about it. You understand?
Yes. So feel it with every fiber of your
being, with all your physical senses.
Then take the situation that the old you
doesn't know what to do with and hand it
in your imagination to the new you, to
the you you prefer to be and watch what
that you does with the situation. Look
at the approach. Look at the attitude.
Watch the outcome. Observe the mode of
success. Watch the nuances. Listen and feel the
Watch the nuances. Listen and feel the
thought patterns the new you had as
opposed to the thought pattern the old
you had. Observe all the differences
between the way the new you does it and
the old you would have done it. Then
copy the new you.
Do it in the same way the new you did
it. You will be that you. You'll get the
same result. Understand?
That will be put the picture more
intense. Be the picture. Yes. Let it be real. Now
Be the picture. Yes. Let it be real. Now
many of you keep these things at bay
because you add in shall we say an extra
step in the process. You say this is who
I am. That is who I want to be. And
there's a lot of time and space in
between the two. How do I get from here
all the way over there?
the way over there?
Understand?
Yes. But it isn't all the way over there.
But it isn't all the way over there.
It's right here right now. So you can
shorten that distance. shorten that time
span by acting like that you now. But I
do not mean fooling yourself. I mean
acting as if you know beyond a shadow of
a doubt that the you you imagine
yourself to be is who you are. Acting
like it. To put it on simpler terms, do
the things the successful you would do.
Do not do the things the unsuccessful
you would do. You understand? Do not do
the things you no longer want to do.
Remember this when you talk about
patterns and habits. A habit is
something you do. You don't know you're
doing. Once you know you have a habit,
you no longer have it if you're aware of
it. You're already outside of it. You
have to be beyond the pattern in order
to know you had a pattern to begin with.
It is only your assumption of belief
that says that you have to do something
extra special in order to stop a habit
once you recognize you have it. As if it
had a momentum of its own. As if it had
a mind of its own. Understand? Well,
sort of. Sometimes it does seem like it
has the mind.
It may seem so, but that because you
assume that it does because you give it
that momentum. Because you give it that
power because your definition of a
pattern, your definition of a habit is
something that is difficult to change.
It has a lot of inertia. You say it's
hard to transform it into the patterns
and habits you want them to be. But
that's only a definition. It's only a
belief. But it will feel very real and
very solid as long as you continue to
buy into it.
So if you can say to yourself it's easy
to change your patterns and habits,
sooner or later it will get easier to
change. Yes. Because you will begin to believe
Yes. Because you will begin to believe
it.
Now if you find you're going to play the
game of saying, "But that's easier said
than done,"
then allow yourself to ask yourself,
"Why do you prefer to believe it's
easier said than done?" If you can
imagine the way you would prefer it to
be, ask yourself why not believe that
way. Why not? Find a reason why you
shouldn't believe that it is just as
easily done as said.
That can put you in touch with whatever
definitions you might have that are
preventing it from happening. Once you
are in touch with what those definitions
are that you believe do make it harder
to do than to say, then you know what
those definitions are. You can rewrite
those definitions. Once you rewrite
them, they will no longer have an
effect. You understand?
Uh-huh. Does this help you and clarify the
Does this help you and clarify the
issue?
Yes, it does greatly. Thank you.
Apply it in any avenue, in any way, in
any category. It can work for all of
them because your imagination is the
ultimate and prime tool of all
methodology. It will always give you
what works best for you. Understand?
Yes. Thank you very much for being a new you
Thank you very much for being a new you
right now.
One point do remember once again what we
are about to say is not meant as simply
philosophy is not a figure of speech is
not an analogy. I am speaking literally.
Every time you define yourself
differently in the present, regardless
of how you think you look on the
outside, you are literally a different
person. Because person personality
persona is an artificial construct, a
temporary construct of the overall
consciousness that you are. So if you
change any of the factors that go into
making up your persona, you literally
are a different person. And if you are a
different person in the present, you
don't have the same history you used to
have because you can't have the same
history because you're not the same
person. You create the past and the
future from the present. Whatever you
define yourself to be now utterly
determines the effect that the timeline
you have created has upon you. You will
plug into whatever is now historically
relevant to the new person. You are to
support the new person you are in the
present. Shannon,
Shannon,
hello and good day to you.
Oh, since I haven't interacted with you
before. Well, I've never interacted with you
Well, I've never interacted with you
before either.
Oh, just like as a means of
introduction, I'd like to say that I uh
Can you hear me? Okay.
Yes. Can you hear him? Okay.
I'd just like to say that it felt loud
similar to the channel speaking.
I had a broad daylight physical
sighting. Oh, right.
I was flying saucer in North Carolina.
All right. Did you have a good time?
Well, I watched it for a long time.
Yeah. Through a binocular.
Through a binocular.
All right. What did it do?
It just sat there.
All right.
Didn't move. And finally, I left.
Oh, all right.
And so and so ever since that time I've
in looking back on my life I can see
that in an attempt to unravel the
mystery of that sighting I have uh
explored many different areas of
metaphysics, science, computers.
All right channel
and so it inspired you.
Yes. All right.
All right.
So anyway, I interacted with you for the
first time or I went to one of your
challenges in November here in Las
Vegas. Dad, this is still the first time
Dad, this is still the first time
nonetheless. Okay, fine. Whatever you
say. Um, but anyway, I
had a chance to read your book, The New
Metaphysics. We are going to sign the transcript.
We are going to sign the transcript.
Yes.
I would like to ask you a question about
a specific portion of the chapter
entitled Extraterrestrial Consciousness.
All right.
You mentioned a planet known as Wall
Deck. Yes.
Yes.
There's a great deal of information from
several sources becoming available to us
now. And many of us are aware of the fact
And many of us are aware of the fact
that there was a third density
civilization similar to Atlantis that
existed on a planet called Mold.
Yes. Which destroyed itself in a nuclear war.
Which destroyed itself in a nuclear war.
Not exactly nuclear but continues.
Close, right?
Got it.
And more of the idea of what you would
call wave technology, but continued.
All right.
And this formed what we know today as
the asteroid belt between Mars and
Jupiter. Yes.
Yes.
Following up on the principles of
synchronicity that you mentioned in
November, thanks.
thanks.
How what this this event an explosion of
an entire planet like this is a mega
event on a cosmic scale?
Yeah. What sort of events is this is
this is this event unique to this
planetary system or have there been
other planetary destructions of this
nature in other star systems?
In other star systems? Yes. Now and then
that happen.
Would they have been synchronized with
this uh destruction?
Not of your linear time frame. No. In
the overall sense that everything is
simultaneous. Yes. But not in linear
time. No.
All right. And looking at this
destruction as it applies to us today.
Yes. Since since we know that all time
is simultaneous
and that our past lives are stored
within us in our genetic code. So who's
the heat guy?
Don't each one of us on this planet have
the memory of this nuclear this
destruction. I'll say
innocence. Yes.
Yes.
And if this memory were to surface in an
unbalanced fashion
Yeah. would it not lead to somewhat uh intense
would it not lead to somewhat uh intense
experiences?
Well, yes. But that is why your
civilization now is going through all of
the examinations it is about the idea of
nuclear war. You are in a sense
replaying the issue all over again. It
is our perception no matter what it
appears to be on the surface that your
civilization has already made the
decision at least on a mass unconscious
level that it will in fact not destroy
itself again.
I agree. I agree.
That is why much of the violence you are
seeing now is able to come to the
surface because in a sense you know it's
safe to get it out of your system and it
will not lead to total annihilation.
But the issue you are dealing with now
is connected very strongly both to the
issue of Malbeck and to the repetition
of that particular idea within what you
call the islands continent of Atlanta.
Its destruction in it sense was to some
degree a replay on a smaller scale of
Maldc and now you have taken that entire
thrust that entire momentum and have
brought it once again to a global scale.
So that we can say that since this
destruction was on a global scale that
is the destruction of an entire planet.
We in remembering that are we as a
planetary consciousness
creating the idea of a new age in the
sense of healing.
Yes. That destruction. That destruction.
Yes.
Thank you question.
Thank you. You have all done it. Thank
you very much. It is very bold of you to
have arrived at this place once again
and to have had the courage to
understand the difference between the
idea of negative and positive.
Chilling. Hi
Hi
and to you. Good day.
I have a personal question.
Oh, all right. Maybe I will have a
personal answer.
No. Uh
or hope. All right.
Yes. It's regarding my daughter who
Well, she'll be 11 next month.
11. All right.
And um
I would like your assistance in
something I've been trying to
speak up so that all may share.
I think
she Oh, okay. I would like your assistance
Oh, okay. I would like your assistance
in something that I've been um trying to
help her with.
Been very successful. It's a physical
thing. She for several months now she
keeps getting sore throats one after
another one after another with no she
doesn't have a fever or anything like
that you know where where it's the kind
of thing that she needs an antibiotic
for and I've discussed with her how to
and I've discussed with her how to
disturb her and various things like that
and um he hasn't been able to come up
with an answer
and I'm curious about this
have you co-created with this individual
what might be termed shall we say for
Now a soft regression into what you
might call path life.
No one gets ahead of it.
In other words, we perceive that being
what you would call a child, it may not
benefit them to go through what you
would call an intense and a full
regression. But through the nurturing
love of your motherhood, you can guide
and assist them in a meditation of a
soft regression and add to the idea of
the regression whether it is absolutely
analytically recalled or not as to the
connections they are making to other
lives that is connected to this idea.
You can also instill the notion of the
breathing that we have shared with many
of you. The idea of the bathing of the
soothing blue white electromagnetic
light of seeing the body as energy and
allowing that vibratory energy to soothe
and cool and lubricate and blend and
transform all the ideas that may be
shall we say stuck in that area so that
they can pass out pass through transform
disperse dispense dissolve. You
understand? Yes.
Yes.
Are you familiar with the idea of that
technique? the blue white light
technique. Yes, I've heard you talk.
Yes, I've heard you talk.
All right. You can use it soothingly
with your daughter. Also, we would
suggest, however, that in her case, you
begin by allowing her to imagine a
golden rosy light in and around the
throat, a very thick and supportive
energy. Then go into the blue white
light for coolness and soothing and
vibratory invigoration. And then allow
the blue white to change simply to
white. And then if she desires, back to
the gold, gold
light when she feels she is done. And to
breathe peacefully, deeply, solidly, and
to feel the thickening of the
atmosphere, to lubricate all the cords,
to lubricate all the structures,
to allow them to slide smoothly in warm,
thick honeylike energy. You understand?
Yes. to redesign and reform that entire
idea of communication
and to breathe the information out and
to see anything that she would consider
to be a gray or black impurity to come
out in the breathing and dissolve in the
light. to breathe in only the pure light
and to allow any impurity to come out
and dissolve in the light until she
feels she is in a sense purged. She may
in your terms break into a very slight
perspiration. But this is all right.
When she feels that rush
of soothing energy, remind her simply
that all she needs to do at any given
moment if she feels a reoccurrence of
the stress is to simply close her eyes
and think of the golden light, the blue
light, the white light and breathe. And
then open her eyes and speak easily.
Share her ideas easily. Communicate them
smoothly and tell her, remind her ideas
will fit and they will be beautiful like
flowers in a garden, colorful, inventive
and creative. You understand?
Yes. See, of this is of a system.
See, of this is of a system.
Thank you. Can you clarify the thing
you're talking about aggression?
Yes. The idea that if you remind her
that she may connect while she is in the
meditative state to past ideas, so to
speak, there may be images that come up
that are associations to the throat area
or to the whole idea of communication
that may be part of what you would call
past lives, what we will simply call
alternate reality that she may tap into.
Remind her that she does not necessarily
have to analyze and consciously
understand what the images mean as long
as she allows the images to play the
part they need to play and sees them as
releasing old ideas and the letting go
of constrictions.
Understand? Yes. Thank you very much for sharing.
Yes. Thank you very much for sharing.
Thank you very much. And by all means do
send her our unconditional love.
I will. Good night. Good day to you,
Jenny. Hi, Bash.
Hi, Bash.
And to you, good day.
I wanted to uh thank you for being such
a wonderful teacher.
Oh, and you as well do remember all
beings are teachers and learners
simultaneously. We always learn from all
of you.
Do thank you. I would like to know if uh
you are consciously that you can
communicate with developers consciously
now and then when it serves.
Yes. would you uh share with us what you
communicate about what you're talking
about? Of highest priority now is the idea of
Of highest priority now is the idea of
assisting them in assisting all of you
in your dream state. For now, they have
access very strongly to your dream
states because that's where most of you
are open to receive that kind of
communication. They want to share with
you the notion of ecstasy of spontaneous
play to invite you into their world to
become more familiar with them. So we
aid and assist them in entering and
sharing and co-creating with all of you
vibrant dream states, vivid dream states
and interactions that have to do with
letting you learn how to love
yourselves. That is the highest priority
now with the dolphins.
Could you uh share with me some insight
on my own uh personal relationship with
the dolphins?
One moment.
You have in what you may call past life
created many projects involving the
interactions of dolphins particularly in
what you would call Atalantian and
sometimes Leamuran time. You also have
some shall we say for now
extraterrestrial connections that have
involved the idea of interaction with
Dolphin consciousness on another level
on a higher level. There have been some
lies even wherein you have actually
hunted these beings. But those are
interim lies wherein you forgot the
earlier interaction that gave you so
much sharing and love and joy. The idea
however always lured you back to the
notion of interaction with them in their
particular kind of environment. However,
now it can be seen to manifest in a
different way. Reminding each and every
one of you that crystals are only
triggers and catalysts and reflections
of your own power. There may be certain
types of crystals that will also allow
you to accelerate or amplify or focus
your consciousness to be able to receive
more clearly communications
telepathically from the dolphins in your
dream states at first and then
you are the one with the power. You are
the one that is the master crystal and
you are simply for now using an
externalized symbol to inspire you to
find the frequency that they are most
communicative on. follow.
I'll review the uh tape. I haven't uh I
don't consciously remember all my dream
predict. That is all right. Open
yourself up to the idea. Attempt this in
your terminology for at least the next
three of your nights in a row and see
what happens. Just lie down, breathe
easily, and open yourself up to
visualizations of the idea of dolphin
consciousness and see what happens in
your dream states within the next 3 days
of your time. All right.
All right. Thank you very much.
Think of small blue crystals that are in
your terminology octahedral in
structure. That is two foursided
pyramids, one up, one down. Similar to
what you would call fluorite in your
civilization. Would that would that crystal be?
Would that would that crystal be?
It can be. Yes. Especially those of the
blue violet nature as opposed to the
yellowish nature.
Okay. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Pleasant dreams to you as well.
Shoot. For sure. In a dream, I was
For sure. In a dream, I was
communicating with Vince, Daryl, myself,
and a being called Fellows. All right.
Is that a question?
Well, I wanted you to expand on this
dream. All right. First of all, good day to
All right. First of all, good day to
you.
Good day.
Bold individual jumps right in.
Plleadian energy. Plleadian interaction.
You have to some degree a connection in
ancient times to familial connections in
the Plleadian system. You also, as you
already know, are connected through
Orion avenues.
But now, as a child, in a sense, you are
remembering to some degree some of the
lies in a childlike way as a child in
some of the earlier Plleadian systems.
some of the offshoots, shall we say,
some of the cousins that you might have
within those systems. Even as of yet,
you can form stronger bonds with those
cousins, those counterparts, those
relations through your own meditation,
through your own feelings. Not that you
have to once again gain an absolute full
analytical vision of them, but know that
they are with you in etheric
interdimensional senses. And know that
they do assist and guide you in many
ways. and know that they are overjoyed
at your shall we say childlike approach
to life in many ways and this they
always assist you in accelerating with
understand. Yes, I understand. I want to know about
Yes, I understand. I want to know about
the uh the name fellows. Is that the
name or the vibration?
The vibration is close enough and it
refers to a shall we say paternal energy
that is a guide for you.
How about the connection with Vince and
Daryl? One moment.
For now, let us simply say
more of an associate type connection.
Not so much directly familial, but
everyone was, shall we say, familiar
with each other. Not through what you
would call bloodline, but through
association and commonality of ideas. In
many cases in those other dimensional
realms, you understand
the Plleadian realms.
Yes. Early early on, even more towards
what you would call the ancient Lyram
realm before it broke into the Plleades
and Orion factions.
All right. So, the three of us then
and many many more.
Oh, I understand.
But simply, of course, you are finding
discoveries of aspects within the
mirrors of all the individuals that now
do the most to bolster what it is you
need to know about yourself. So those
particular faces of the relationship
will be perceived by you as being the
strongest even though your other
associates may see completely different
things that they need to see to bolster
their understanding of themselves.
Understand? Yes.
Yes.
Will this assist you?
Sure. How about my connection with my uh
my son Nicholas?
Let us for now say it is a
mechanical connection.
What this means is that the individual
has to some degree exhibit in the past a
high degree of mechanical skill.
There have been some similarities
between you many times of constructive
nature. In that sense, you are and have
been, shall we say, architects for each
other in many ways. Certain attributes
of your being now, not that they are
exhibiting now as strongly as they will
in the future, will come up more
strongly when that individual reaches
further into adulthood. And some of this
reflection will be your ability as an
adult to reflect the childlike qualities
that that individual can maintain. And
that individual's ability to reflect
some of the idea of adult nature
construction that you will be able to
apply in your own way. You have served
each other many times. You have taken
turns being child and father to each
other many times. dancing around that
particular reflection. There have been
other beings that have joined that dance
at various places, but for now
specifically, it is of a mechanical
architectural nature in the sense that
you truly do allow each other to build
within yourselves the counterpart
reflection to what the other one doesn't
need to experience as directly in their
life as you choose to experience in
yours and vice versa. You understand?
Yes. Sure. Thank you.
Sure. Thank you.
One moment.
There is something else.
For now, shall we say, think silver,
gray, metallic, and see what you get.
Enjoy your
think or meditate.
Thank you. Think and or meditate. Same
thing. Think relax and up. You're
meditating. Sh.
Sh.
And to you, good day. One moment if you
please. If you wish, some sort of a
reflection to assist you. The substance
you call hematite can be of assistance
in giving you the silver gray metallic
we are talking about. It is a very
magnetic grounding and aligning
substance. Continue.
Continue.
I'm back again. I was going to follow up
on the Plleades question that I asked
you before.
Um,
I don't take it on. I'll just fluff it
off for now. Oh, fluff it up. Um, one
interesting question I have for you is
that I don't think I've ever heard
anyone ask you.
Oh, what?
Uh, in view there's five of you at the
empathy control, I guess put it.
You You make everything sound so perfect
like if it fits in a nice neat little
ball. represent
our original intention. It is simply
that we do not invalidate ourselves for
having taken that court. And so in the
colloquial nomenclature, we do not label
it as a mistake since we understand that
we still arrive at information that is
valuable and useful. Understand? It is
simply a matter of attitude and how you
apply it. It is quite possible for us to
begin with a particular intention and
wind up with something that was not the
product of the original intention but we
understand that there is a reason for
that that it will increase our
appreciation of the idea we originally
intended to discover in many different
ways. So we simply do not fluff it off
in that sense as a mistake. We allow
ourselves to understand, let's say,
putting it this way, that what we now
discover we do not want to know helps us
have a stronger appreciation of what we
do want to know within a specific area
of growth and curiosity and discovery.
The issue simply is that we do not look
upon it as an invalidated idea because
many times an individual will discover a
way they did not intend to go and then
they can recognize it as a service
because then they can tell every other
individual if you want this don't go
that way and so we view that as progress
not as a mistake we view it as learning
we view it as growing as sharing
understand yes you simply that we enjoy the process
yes you simply that we enjoy the process
on every level and everything we
discover is equal we do single something
out as having less value than any other
thing we could have discovered.
Therefore, we are of great value to you.
Oh, absolutely.
I mean, as a whole,
yes. And as individuals as well,
from all the things that many of you
have shared with us, do understand we
are involved in the transformational
assistance of many other planets other
than your own. And many of the things
that you have shared with us, we have
been able to actually apply to some of
those other worlds to wonderful effects.
By proxy, I will thank you for them.
Understand? Everything fits somewhere.
Everything belongs somewhere. And an
answer that you get that does not seem
to immediately apply to the situation
you are interested in still fits
somewhere. And sooner or later somehow
you will find out why you got that
answer when you did because it will be
able to assist someone else and even
yourself somewhere somehow.
Since we are able to slide in and out of
the idea of many different realities,
perhaps we simply have a broader
perspective of exactly where what seems
to be quote unquote wrong answers for
one idea are the quote unquote right
answers for another level. Understand?
Does this assist you?
Yes. May I share something to you?
Oh, by all means.
I had my phobia about two years ago and
here I am talking to you.
Well, thank you very much.
Cheers. I thank you.
Our love to you, Sh.
And good day to you.
I am aware of your many comments made on
the crystal skull.
Yes, I went to see the crystal skull
I went to see the crystal skull
yesterday.
Well, how exciting.
It was very amazing.
And um I am aware of your comment that
the crystal skull was used by the Mayan
civilization to leave this planet
to leave this planet
to translate themselves into another
dimension. Yes. And they left the skull behind.
Yes. And they left the skull behind.
Yes.
As a riddle to be solved by future
generations which now is in our hand.
Yes. And many of us are aware of this
And many of us are aware of this
interpretation and were uh studying the
skull at great length. Right.
Um I'm here to report that no one
physically translated to another
dimension. Not yet,
Not yet,
but we all tried. And the question is
the skull is on display in Phoenix uh
until the end of this month. And we
would like to know if um uh Daryl Anchor
and you can assist us in understanding
more of the uses of that crystal skull.
One moment.
Within the next of what you call 72 of
your hours, there will be specific
energy beamed into that area to
accelerate the process. It will not
require the physiological presence of
the channel. Thank you. I have uh one uh
observation at um all of these skulls of
modern man have 32 teeth. This crystal
skull had 34. Could you comment on that?
There is in many of your ancient races
intermixture with other races, shall we
say, from other dimensional levels. Some
of those genetic patterns, those genetic
drifts still exist here and there, still
have remnant fragments existing within
your BT. The idea also
is that in times past, diet also
required that for the further crushing
and grinding of the vegetable matter
before the time when there was as high
an ingestion of what you call animal
matter that no longer required for the
idea of the flatter teeth, the extra
teeth in the back for the grinding of
vegetable matter. You understand? This
is the result also of the intermixture
since the extradimensional
consciousnesses that blended with your
race long ago were primarily in your
terminology vegetarian.
Thank you. It is one
I will not define it as the absolute
answer as a specific answer on all
levels. One of the ideas of the sources of the
One of the ideas of the sources of the
substance on your planet now that you
call corn is extraterrestrial in nature.
Shy. Hello.
Hello.
And to you. Good day.
Um I want to ask several uh questions
concerning gems.
All right. See if you can consolidate it
into one.
We're trying minerals. Firstly, uh
there's a mineral that has surfaced now
called sujulite royal ael that comes
from the bottom of a maganese mine.
Yes, the violent energy, the violet ray,
the crown chakra.
That's what I was going to ask you.
Okay. And uh has th this is the only
place they found it. Is it possible that
this has just manifested recently upon
the planet and that it hasn't developed
over millions of years?
It has in a sense done both. It has
developed in one plane but vibrationally
it is now concurrent and contemporary
with the vibration of your civilization
so that they can recognize it for the
first time.
This is what I thought.
There is another substance
one is also analogous to the ideas that
existed in Atlantian time as well. The
new one aside from July is also called
Larimar Larimar
Larimar
and exists in what you call your New
Orleans and Caribbean area. bluish in
nature. It has much to do with the idea
of the blending of the female and the
male polarities within each and every
individual. Has much to do with the
increasing of psychic sensitivity. Has
much to do with increasing the
telepathic bond between humans and
dolphin life because it is one of the
things that long ago in Atlantan times
the dolphins brought from the bottom of
the ocean up to the surface for the
Adalians to use. Another substance which
is now coming to light upon your planet
is the idea called mold of ice in that
sense which is extraterrestrial in
nature and greenish in color. It is to
some degree representational of the idea
of the destruction of Malc now that you
are reassessing the idea of either
harmony or peace upon your world and
forming the idea also of
extraterrestrial connections. It is an
awakening stone in many levels.
I found pieces of that. Yes. Sun and uh
it felt like every cell in my body did
an alteration, a total molecular
alteration. And I got the same confirmation as what
And I got the same confirmation as what
you're giving me now.
Uh I've been very uh lately very um
interested in gems. It's so almost
becoming something that excites me so
much and even as a child you had to drag
me away from the crystal cave window in
the museum. It was done with mirrors.
I'm understanding now that the gems here
many of them like the lapis is a
lamorian platform. Is that correct?
In a sense and carried through adalian
time and used for uh amplification of
and used for uh amplification of
manifestation and thoughts on the higher
realms of life
on one level. Yes. Especially the
electromagnetic realm. Yes. I um I work
with uh many people and I give a class
and I understand that the stones here
are gateways to a stones uh counterpart
in the atheric realm. Yes. And connect
you to the rays of consciousness
represented by the color of many of the
stones and also working with the
consciousness of each chakra.
Yes. They are triggers and catalysts and
conduits and channels in that way. Yes.
And then the quartz would be an
amplification or or um it would bring
them all together. It's like a rainbow
in a prism.
Yes. the clear homogeneous white light
as yet unbroken
and the solidite will there be sujuly
will there be any more of that found on
the planet or is supposed to be rare now
and there may be one or two or three other
there may be one or two or three other
areas eventually
and you recommend the blue stones more
for the uh connection with the dolphin
energies yes l yes l
mar
found in your Caribbean and New Orleans
area thank you very much that's what I want
thank you very much that's what I want
to understand thank you
also yes are Are you familiar with the idea
yes are Are you familiar with the idea
of what you may call your honeyccoled
tiger's eye?
Yes, I am.
Are you familiar with what you call your
blue tiger's eye?
No, that does exist.
that does exist.
Mhm.
You can use that in highly magnetic way.
Also, now most auspiciously what you
call a deep red tiger's eye, especially
that which is laced with hematite. Very
magical, very grounding.
Wonderful. Thank you.
Thank you very much, Shirley.
Hello. Well, good day to you.
Well, good day to you.
My question is about the nuclear waste.
Do you know of another way that we can
dispose of a reuse without sustainable
variant in the ground?
Yes. You will find it is our perception
that in time within the next decade or
so or two, you will discover a polymer
plastic substance that has the ability
to literally absorb all of the harmful
radiation. Containers can be built of
this substance in that way and your
nuclear waste stored within. Also, you
will understand that as you begin as a
civilization to translate yourself to
higher and higher frequencies, you will
eventually within perhaps the next 50 to
100 of your years, translate yourself
beyond the capacity of that radiation to
harm your body. Do you understand?
I think so. Pretty much
these are two of the quickest ways we
perceive that your society will go about
transforming this idea.
Okay. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Sure. I love to use the truck.
I'll unfinish your love to you.
I'd like to talk to you about my car.
All right.
When I I have a big truck, a big
suburban truck. And when I got it, I was
Yes. Big.
And when I got this truck, I wrote right
on the dashboard power because I felt it
symbolized my taking back my personal
power. All right.
All right.
The other thing I said is this car is
going to save my children's lives.
All right. This car has been bashed
into, turned over, turned around, and I
don't know what's going on. If it's
trying to get rid of it, or if it is an
old definition of saving lives. I don't
How much more proof do you need of your
own invulnerability?
You have made it a symbol of your power.
Now you can stop proving that your power
is solid.
Thank you.
Understand? Yes. Um, something that's related to
Yes. Um, something that's related to
this. When my right before my son turns
the car over,
I talk to my children about the little
voice within that whispers or speaks and
to listen to it. And he said when he got
on the freeway, the voice said, "Don't
fall asleep in the wheel." Which is
exactly what he did. And I had a wreck
in the car the other day and my the
voice said to me, "Go straight." And I
argued with it and said, "No, I have to
go left."
Oh, right.
Just this knowingness comes in such a
flash. Yes. But there are so many millions of
Yes. But there are so many millions of
thoughts that flash through my mind like
that. You will learn the difference
You will learn the difference
and you will begin to pay attention
because you already know the difference.
You will learn to pay attention.
Well, I've asked it to get louder and
less subtle. But I think the subtleness,
am I correct in thinking the subtleness
and the quietness is what I'm supposed
to be listening to?
Yes. Because it also still gives you the
Because it also still gives you the
ability to decide. You see, it cannot
take away your free will. You can
countermand it if you want to. That's
why listening to the subtleness will
make it sound louder because as you go
into a relaxed and peaceful state then
you match its frequency and it becomes
very clear and obvious what it is saying
and becomes the loudest voice within
you. It becomes your own voice.
Yes, I know it is my own voice on that
level and I do argue with it quite a bit.
and I do argue with it quite a bit.
Why still trying to prove something?
Probably. Do remember this if this will help you
Do remember this if this will help you
at all. blending and aligning and quote
unquote giving in to that voice does not mean
giving in to that voice does not mean
you are giving up your identity. It
means you are expanding it. Sometimes
your ego structure consciousness says
think that by blending and harmonizing
with that higher self that the ego
structure is losing ground that it is
dying that it is cutting itself off
because it has always been told it's in
control. It thinks that blending with
the higher self is losing control. Allow
it to understand by talking gently and
lovingly to it that it is actually
gaining a subtler but more profound
control because that control comes with
a recognition that the higher self in
that sense it is you or can be you and
that your identity will remain. It will
not be lost or absorbed. You understand?
Yes. Thank you. Can I ask you a quick
question about Atlantis? Every people
have said that all of us on the planet
now were also alive in it time of
Atlantis. Well, basically because your
Adalian civilization did cover many
thousands of years, you know.
Okay. The idea of living in Atlantis doesn't
The idea of living in Atlantis doesn't
mean you had one life there and had
several. There's something within me that I don't
There's something within me that I don't
understand. But every time I something
comes up that same little voice and says
I was not in Atlantic.
Oh. Oh. Oh. That could be so. That could
be so. The idea generally speaking is
that the majority of your civilization
has had experiences in that particular
area because you are now intertwined
with the rest of your civilization. Then
to some degree by proxy so do you. Even
if it isn't directly linearly it is
still rubbing off on you. You are still
intershed within that electromagnetic
suit. You understand?
You understand?
Yes I do.
You are a part of what can be called the
collective karma.
I see. I almost have an anger attached
to that.
All right. I understand.
You do. Would you help me understand why
it it feels like a defensive mechanis
because you are being told what you are
and you already know what you are and
you don't need anyone else to tell you.
uh it wasn't for something that happened
directly there that I was involved in.
Not directly. No, not in that way. No.
Good. Okay. Thank you.
Now the idea also is to remember that
each and every individual you are in
every new life has different
connections. You the oversoul you are
can have had lives in Atlantis. That
doesn't necessarily mean that you you
are now has a direct linear
reincarnational connection to it.
Okay. Understood?
Understood?
Yes, that makes sense. Thank you. We
sign very much at this timing. Allow us
once again to extend to each and every
one of you individually and collectively
our reflection of your individual impact
to remind you that you make a
difference. If you didn't, you wouldn't
be a part of the reality you're in.
There are no extra leftover creations
that don't belong. You are a part of the
tapestry. You are a part of the
painting. You are a part of the big
picture. And each and every one of you
is your own big picture, your own
painting, your own tapestry.
Weave the reality you desire on the loom
of your imagination. That's why it's
there. And it will give you what you
prefer because you say so. Be clear
about your definition. Be clear about
your intention. Be clear about your
deservability. Be clear about your
actions. You will get the reflection of that
You will get the reflection of that
clarity. We thank you for the
co-creation of this interaction. And we
remind you that you are in fact dreaming
right now. Wake up and live the dream
you prefer to. You might as well. It's
your choice.
We thank you and send you always our
unbroken and unconditional love. We bid
you a bomb and a loving and an exciting
good day.
I know bread means Frank I think a
different meaning for wine but humility
did not come out of my head so
and then he said something to me my like
I said I don't know what transpired
between you two cuz I could see him
talking to me but I didn't know words or
And mine was
mine was
that I was Diana, the goddess of the
hunt, and that I really am the goddess
of the hunt because I'm hunting souls.
It was a pretty interesting experience
because it was all three of us. And I
think I was allowed to see Uhhuh.
or experience. You were experiencing all
different levels, but I guess
because I was seeing it literally in
pictures. Yeah. You were seeing and I it was I was
Yeah. You were seeing and I it was I was
experiencing this diamond
then I saw some other individual
diamonds was made out of the same before I seen
was made out of the same before I seen
it was a
diamond I can't think of a diamond
but it just seems so fun
I'm seeing