Say, how are you all this evening of
your time as you create time to exist?
Fantastic. We thank you for joining us
in this interaction this evening of your
time and allow us to begin by laying
down a foundation on a particular
subject that is of now paramount
importance in the realization the
recognition of the consciousness of your
society. The idea now is that there is a
growing awareness of the existence of
what you have termed us to the
extraterrestrials in your society's
consciousness. The idea that your
planetary civilization is not the only
civilization within what you call the
physiological universe.
Now the idea of your awareness of our
existence is not something that we wish
to underline because it is more
important than the existence of your own
civilization. We are not saying that you
should be aware of us in order to
increase the benefits in your society.
The idea is that your society, like any
society, is absolutely self-contained
and has all the abilities it needs to
create that society to be anything you,
its inhabitants, desire it to be. And
you do not need us to interact with you
in order to be able to create your
society to be what you want it to be.
However, because your society is now
beginning to explore the idea of leaving
your world and of thinking in global
terms and in exploring different levels
of consciousness, you are now beginning
to break through levels and
barriers and definitional systems of
reality that you have not considered
before. And in breaking through those
levels, in exploring those realms that
you have, as you say, hitherto left
unexplored as a mass consciousness, you
are now beginning to encounter that
there are other consciousnesses that
have already explored those levels in
their own way. This does not mean that
just because other consciousnesses have
explored those levels by the way that
they are all used up and there's nothing
left for you. The idea is that each and
every civilization will explore those
levels, those expansions of awareness in
their own way and every civilization is
unique and will contribute something
unique in its exploration of the same
levels of awareness and existence.
Therefore recognize that as you expand
globally and unify yourselves into what
you might call a one world idea and as
you expand not only on your world but
off your world into the universe. You
will begin to encounter not only
physiologically but also on all levels
of consciousness the existence of other
civilizations and other
awarenesses similar to your own.
Different in many ways, but similar to
your own. Similar in the sense that we
all possess like you. An unlimited
capacity for curiosity, an unlimited
capacity for desire to know ourselves,
and an unlimited capacity to explore and
discover all that every being in
creation was created to be. For there is
no end at least that we have found to
that exploration and there never shall
be as far as our perception has taught
us. The idea however is that now because
you are beginning to explore these ideas
as a society it can no longer be shall
we say kept from you that there will be
and are other civilizations you will
come in contact with. Now the way that
this is being undertaken at this time is
mostly through the opaces of
communication of the nature that you are
experiencing right now because it allows
several things to occur in the easiest
possible manner for you. It allows you
to make up your own mind as to whether
or not the information you are receiving
is something that you want to have in
your life. For we have perceived that
many individuals upon your planet for
one reason or another, and we are not
making a judgment of this, but simply
for one reason or another do not want to
know that we exist. There are many
investments, many belief systems that
many of you have made in your society.
and to allow yourselves to begin to
realize that the rather the civilization
with other belief systems may seem to
many of you to be a threat to the system
of belief that you have been brought up
with. We have no intention of forcing
our systems of belief upon you for this
is not our way and it is not the way
that would allow us to expand as a
society. We would be limiting ourselves
if we chose to limit you to force you to
see in any particular perspective that
is not a perspective of your own choice
and we do not desire to limit ourselves
in that way. So the idea will be
presented in this fashion so that you do
not have to believe that we are who we
say we are so that you can make up your
own mind as a society based on the
information alone as to whether or not
you desire as a society to have
interaction with us. for you can decide
not to and that will be up to you. We do
perceive however that it is usually most
likely that a society that has reached
the level of evolution where it is
beginning to explore all the different
things you are now beginning to explore
about consciousness and the universe
will generally desire to continue to
expand in that exploration and seek to
co-join with other societies like
itself. So we present to you the
opportunity to interact with us in this
way to allow you to see our perspective
of the route that we have taken and the
ideas that we perceive you are now
exploring to share with you how we have
explored them. So that if our
methodologies can work for you or can
inspire you to create the methodologies
that will work for you that you will
undertake these methodologies to expand
yourself and be a willing co-joiner and
co-creator with us in joining with us.
It is our perception and our perspective
that that will expand us as well. So
that together with all the other
societies with whom we have co-joined in
what we call the association of worlds,
we can explore further the infinite
creation. For we see all of you as we
see any being within creation as simply
one more way that the infinite has of
expressing itself. Do understand we
learn many things from you as well in
these interactions. It is not as you say
a one-way street. There are no one-way
streets. Everyone is a teacher and a
learner simultaneously and that is why
every being in reality is an equal
sharer. Now the
idea of our existence has been known to
your society for quite some time and we
have spoken to many members of your
society about the idea that what you
call your government have been very well
aware of us for quite some time in your
terms of counting for at least what you
would call four of your decades.
But the
idea of your society structure, the way
you have created what you call your
governments to be has created what you
call a suppression of that information
because of the fear that too many
changes would occur in your society that
would lead to instability, what you have
termed anarchy or chaos or fear or
panic. We respect this point of view and
therefore have agreed at least on what
you would call a non-physical telepathic
unconscious level with many members of
your society to interact with you gently
slowly to allow your society bit by bit
to get used to the idea that you are not
the only civilization around. So that
soon you will be used to the idea
sufficiently enough so that when we are
then allowed by the state of your
consciousness to make physiological
appearances in blatant ways, you will
not be shocked and you will not think
that your world has to come crashing
down just because another world in that
sense has landed upon it. The idea
simply is that your government once
again is very well aware of our
existence and has been for quite some
time. All it would take for an
acceleration, for a release of the
information of their knowledge is for
you, what you call your public, to begin
to communicate with your governments and
allow them to understand that you are
ready to receive the information of our
existence. Again, not because it makes
us seem any greater than is, but simply
because you are ready now to accept the
idea of your own equality. Because you
are now ready to accept the idea that
you can function in harmony with each
other and in that sense therefore you
are ready to function in harmony with
other whole worlds even as you become
one world
yourselves. Now we do not mean that when
you communicate and open up lines of
communication to your government about
the idea of what they know and what they
have kept from you that you must do this
in an attacking fashion in an accusatory
fashion. We do not mean that you go and
say, "Oh, big bad government." No. For
they are only what you have created them
to be. And in a sense, you are your
government. For they are only what you
can support them to be. And they are
only reflective of exactly how much
responsibility you are willing to take
for your own lives. So you cannot blame
them for being what they are in that
sense. It does not excuse any
individuals in any walk of life who act
outside of their integrity. But we are
not saying in that sense that even if
they have been acting outside of their
integrity that they deserve in that
sense to be accused by you for
accusation is also only an expression of
lack of integrity. You have in your
biblical literature a phrase that says
judge not lest ye be judged. This does
not mean that you will be judged from
outside. It means that all vibrations
seek their own level. And if you start
judging others and invalidating them,
then you become the same vibration of
invalidation and will be judged
accordingly in that sense, you will
place yourself on the same level and
therefore no one gets ahead. The idea
therefore is when you open up lines of
communication to your governments should
you desire to do so, for you may not.
But if you desire to do so, to let them
know that you now know that
extraterrestrial consciousness exists,
that you do wish to know what the
government knows about it, then you can
in opening up these lines of
communication be loving about the idea,
be supportive about the idea and remind
them that the idea of their sharing that
information to attempt to convince
someone that they created a disease. But
that is the first step for a very simple
reason because we have discussed the
idea that you are all responsible for
the creation of reality. So if an
individual will not own what is going on
in their reality, they can't change it.
If they don't own it, they can't change
it. Now many people are not willing to
own such a thing because they are taught
to think that owning it means
blame, failure. Oh, if you did that, you
must really be a mess. You must be a
poor excuse for a human being. That's
the way your society has been taught to
think. So it is no wonder that people
are not willing to take responsibility
for the things that happen in their
lives because they do not want to be
called failure and do not want to think
that they cannot create what they want.
But if you can teach an individual that
if such a thing has occurred in one's
life that there can be a positive reason
for it and if they can learn what that
positive reason
Then they can transform anything,
anything at all. It doesn't matter what
it is. It doesn't matter how devastating
it seems, how unchangeable it seems. It
has been created. It can be changed.
Does this help? Yes. Now, what about
medicines? All right. We never get into
that. There can be many ideas. We have already
There can be many ideas. We have already
suggested some ideas. But the idea of
medicine or what you would call a
physiological cure first of all will
only happen when the belief system will
allow it to happen because the belief
system overrides everything. Cures,
physical cures, medicinal cures in your
society are not possible until a belief
system in the society says it is
possible. So anything we could suggest
and we have suggested many things will
not work anyway until someone's belief
system says it will.
However, there are many methodologies
which you already have at your disposal
of healing. Some of which are in what
you call the medical arts which work for
some people because of their belief
systems and don't work for others
because of their belief systems. and
some of what you simply call the healing
art in a more direct sense, a more
natural sense, so to speak, because
that's what some people believe will
work best. One of the strongest ways to
alleviate physiologically any disease in
your society is to expose an individual
to a very strong aligned magnetic field
that is pulsating at approximately 7 and
1/2 cycles per second because that is
the electromagnetic frequency of your
planet, the natural frequency of nature.
If you can align an individual cellular
structure in a magnetic field in that
magnetic frequency, no disease can occur
within that field. And within such a
field, many individuals can attain a
complete remission of any disease.
However, if they do not continue to
create a belief system which supports
their health, then the disease can come
back no matter what cure has been
dispensed. Understand?
Now, there will be at least two or three
different avenues of research on your
planet that will seemingly come up with
a cure within what we perceive to be the
next 10 to 13 of your years. Some of it
will be genetic.
One will be an understanding that there
are substances within the
enzymes and the acids in certain fruits
upon your planet such as cherry and
peach and berries that actually have the
ability to strengthen the immune system
to such a degree that what you call such
viruses will have no effect. Some of
this work will be begun but may be
discarded when other ideas such as the
electromagnetic idea which will also be
pursued upon your planet and is being
pursued now and the electrical balancing
idea which is also being pursued upon
your planet will seem to show more
promise. The idea is now being
understood upon your planet that the
human body and many physiological bodies
are very much like what you would call
an electric battery and have positive
and negative
balances. Disease in a sense is a
disimbalance of these charges and if
they can be rebalanced electrically then
no disease can exist within such a body
within such a framework. This is now
being experimented with in many areas
upon your planet and will come to very
strong understanding within the idea of
the next decade. Also stronger magnetic
fields will be created now with your
planet's new superconducting
technology. And so these will also be
available. You may find that some
individuals will even find as you say
quote unquote by
accident that by exposing themselves to
certain magnetic fields diseases they
had will no longer exist and this will
lead them in the direction of that
exploration. The idea now of the device
upon your planet you call the magnetic
imaging resonance scanner not only has
the capacity to some degree to diagnose
the idea of disease but also has to some
degree the capacity to cure the very
disease it is diagnosing. Although your
individuals have not stumbled upon this
yet because it gives off a very strong
magnetic field and if it is properly
tuned an individual pass through it can
be cured can be realigned.
All these ideas will begin to be
exploded. But the foundation as always
is that if you understand the basic
reason for the existence of these things
that will alleviate them the quickest.
Now there are many individual reasons
for the creation of a disease. But there
are also some general consensus reality
ideas and to use your example of AIDS.
Our perception of the general consensus
belief structure that has created the
disease you call AIDS upon your planet
is as
follows. The longstanding denial within
your collective
society of the balance of masculine and
feminine energy within each and every
being. The denial of that blending and
the denial of that intimacy within each
individual has created a
condition that now has led to the viral
epidemic upon our planet.
The reemerging, the marriage if you
will, of the masculine and feminine
energies within each and every being
will go a long way to creating an
environment, an atmosphere in which that
disease cannot perpetuate, cannot exist,
cannot continue.
It is only the idea of that segregation
within the cell, that separation of
those two polarity, those energies that
allows you to function in a sense as
incomplete beings. And functioning in
that way on that low energy level makes
you susceptible to all sorts of
imbalances because you are not
functioning on the full energy potential
you all could be. by blending and
balancing and harmonizing and come into
terms with both sides of yourself.
Positive, negative, balance, masculine,
feminine, balance. What you call light,
dark, balance. Finding the
balance. Now, there is a very simple way. There
Now, there is a very simple way. There
are many ways, but the overall simple
idea of finding the
balance is as follows.
It is so simple many of you may miss it
the first time we say
it. Do in life what excites you the most
with integrity. Well, how is doing what
integrity. Well, how is doing what
excites me going to create that kind of
balance and keep me
disease-free? Fair enough.
definition perhaps at least our
definition is in order
excitement dot
dot the physical
translation of the vibratory energy that
represents the path you chose to be.
That's what excitement is. So when you
are doing the thing that excites you the
most with integrity, you are fully
aligned with the path you chose to be.
And when you're fully aligned with the
path you chose to be, you are in balance
and you cannot have the idea of disease.
excitement, that feeling, that rush of
excitement, that
knowingness that you are where you
belong, that you are doing the thing
that you love to do with passion. That
feeling, that
energy that aligns your entire cellular,
molecular, and atomic structure
physically, literally, and makes you in a state of
literally, and makes you in a state of
existence that can only experience a
reality that is reflective of that
balanced state. This is all simple
mechanics, simple physics. You cannot
experience a reality. You are not the
vibration
of. So change the vibration of the
individual by changing the definition of
the reality by doing the things that
truly excite the individual to inspire
and ignite that individual. And they
will burn with a radiance and a fire
that is bright and hot enough to
completely obliterate any disease, any
imbalance. they will be impenetrable.
Make sense? Yes. Does it answer the
question sufficiently? Yes. Well, thank
you very much.
Um, along those same lines, I what if
you don't know what excites you the
most? Oh, thank you very much. Now, when
we say do the thing that excites you the
most, we do not mean that you have to
have an idea of the thing that will be
the most exciting thing you will ever do
in your life. We do not have to mean it
has to be formatted in what you would
call a career, a project of special
proportions. It can be. But if it isn't,
if you do not now know a particular
thing, then allow yourself to understand
you can perform this idea on a very
simplified level, which you would do in
any case. And that is as follows.
do at any given moment the thing out of
all the things you could do at that
moment that excites you the most with
integrity. A step at a time. That's all
it takes. You will always know at any
given moment what opportunities are open
to you to do just on any level. Will I
go here? Will I do
this? I have let's say x number of
opportunities at this moment that I
could do. Now which of these truly
excites me the most with
integrity? Do it. In other words, to put
it on a very simplified level, I will
assume not because it is me, but simply
because you are in this interaction that
this interaction is the most exciting
thing you could be doing at this
moment. If it were not, I would suggest
you do something
else. And when this interaction is over,
I will simply ask you, out of all the
things you could do at the end of this
interaction, this evening of your time,
will you do the thing that will be the
most exciting or will you settle for
less?
That's all there is to it. That is all
there is to it. when you are deciding
when you are at a point in your life and
I do not mean this has to be a major
crossroad just any point where you are
now deciding what to do next when you
don't know assess all the opportunities
that are there allow them to all be
equal and then simply pick the one that
sparks you the
most act on it with integrity it will
Always underlying that word as many
times as you want to. It will always
lead you to the next most exciting
circumstance you need to be led to
automatically effortlessly. And you will also be led
effortlessly. And you will also be led
to the circumstance that will give you
whatever capabilities you need to be
able to take advantage of the next level
of opportunities that will excite you
the most that you will choose from.
These things come automatically when you
act at any given moment in the moment on
whatever it is at that moment that
excites you the most with integrity.
It's as simple and fundamental as that.
Take it a step at a
time. Second
point, many people, now I'm not saying
this is the case with
you, if it applies, apply it. But many
people will say, "Well, I don't know
what excites
me." And that's not
true. They have been taught to believe
they don't know what excites them. They
sometimes don't give themselves a chance
to understand. They know what really
excites them. Many times people will
know very well what really is the most
exciting thing they could be doing. But
powerful word in your society,
but they will have been taught and will
continue to believe that what it is that
excites them is not a valid way to live.
And so they will negate it to the point
where they don't even perceive that it
excites them anymore because they have
been told that's no way to make a
living. Oh, grow up. Oh, don't be naive.
Oh, be realistic. Oh, you're such a
dreamer. Oh, you can never do that. In
order to really make something of
yourself, you have to struggle. You
won't deserve it if you don't work hard
for it. If you don't do it this way,
you'll be a failure. I'll be
disappointed in you if you don't
accomplish this. All of these
definitions, all of these ideas have a
lot to do with an individual who truly
does know what excites them the most to
forget that they know it. Understand?
Yeah. But what about mental blocks? Like
say for example, I want to lose 50
pounds. All right. But why? I want to,
but why? How come I'm not? All right.
Thank you very much. Now, I will
delineate many of the general reasons
for why individuals in your society
create the idea of extra weight. I will
not necessarily address any one of these
to you. You may pick and choose, if any,
which of these may apply because it will
always be your definition of reality
that creates the reality you experience.
And the only reason an individual may
not be able to change it is because they
have not been able to get in touch with
what the definition is that they have
bought into that has created the reality
to begin with. You follow me so far?
Yes. No. Maybe. Maybe. Keep going. In
other words, your physical reality is
created by definitions you have bought
into. You understand? Yes. Many times
you may not be in touch with what the
definition is that is creating the
reality you have. And that's why you
can't change it because you don't know
what the definition is. If you don't
know what the definition is that's
creating the reality you have, then you
can't redefine it and get another
reality. Understand? Yeah. How do you
Thank you. I am going to give you some
of the definitions your society uses to
create the idea of extra weight. See if
any of these apply to you. All right.
Yes. Thank you very much. First
definition, we will take the play on
words that exists in your English
language to underline the first
point. Many
people when they are not doing what
excites them the most in life are
waiting to do what excites them the
most. Okay, people are energy. Energy is mass.
Okay, people are energy. Energy is mass.
If you are not flowing your energy out
into the thing that excites you, you are
holding the energy. And if you hold the
energy, it turns into mass. When you
start doing what really excites you with
that energy, it will start flowing
again. It will turn from mass back into
energy and flow because you will no
longer be waiting to do what you are all
about. That's one reason. Another reason
individuals sometimes who are very
sensitive to higher energies when they
begin to explore the idea of those
higher energies may have bought into a
belief system that those higher energies
are something more than their frail
little bodies can contain. So they'll
put on a few pounds just as an added
extra buffer so that the energy in that
sense that comes through them will not
burn them up or eat them away by the
time they get used to it or understand
what it's all about. Idea number
three. Many
individuals, if they are in a sense not
willing to look at something that may
come from their outside environment that
they need to look at, may put on weight
to act as a buffer zone to keep things
away or to hide certain things in. So it
will be quote unquote more difficult to
find because there is more of you to
look in.
In a sense, it takes the focus off of
having to look for something because
there is so much exterior apparency that
it takes your focus off of the interior
that you don't want to look
at. Now, there are
also reasons of the following
nature. Sometimes an individual will
have chosen in a particular life to be
of service to other individuals in a
particular way in your particular
society. Sometimes individuals who are
able to be of great benefit to other
individuals by sharing information with
them or sharing exchanges of energy with
them will have to come across in a way
that those individuals will trust. What
is one of the strongest associations in
your society regarding the idea of
maternity? The idea of someone in a
sense who has an abundance to give.
So the idea sometimes is that
individuals will choose temporarily to
show extra weight to appear maternal and
comfortable to other individuals they
attract in their lives so that they can
help those individuals and those
individuals won't think that you are
being judgmental of them because they
will understand that it comes from your
heart because you are not holding
anything over them because of the
attention your society puts on physical
looks. That's another
reason. Another idea sometimes is that
individuals when they begin to explore
what their society has told them
are flighty matters will put on a few
pounds to ensure that they remain
grounded. All of these and many more
ideas are the reasons that your society
deals with the issue of weight. There
are many more reasons. If these ideas do
not apply to you, at least they have
perhaps given you an understanding of
how you can begin to explore for
yourself what your definition might be
about the idea.
Sometimes individuals will have experienced
individuals will have experienced
certain things, have created certain
experiences in their early life and the
weight may be a reaction in a sense to a
society they do not really want to
interact with or because they feel that they do
with or because they feel that they do
not deserve to have what they want and
so the weight in a sense will act almost
like a barrier a fence to keep it away.
This is the perimeter. Come no closer.
Stay far away.
These reasons as well exist in your
society to create the idea of
physiological expansion. Sometimes it will simply be
expansion. Sometimes it will simply be
because an individual really feels very
full, very large in energy but has made
a translation into physicality and so is
attempting to fill their oric field with
actual physical mass.
There is that reason as well. And of
course, there are many of the reasons
your society already understands the
idea of feeling a lack of things and the
idea of hoarding because you feel there
will not be enough. There is that reason
as well.
But whatever your personal reason, allow
yourself perhaps as a suggestion from us
to begin by examining what is the
definition in your reality that would be
necessary to sustain that particular
idea. Ask yourself, what kind of a
belief would I have to have in order to
have this manifestation of physical
reality? Meditate on it. Be at peace and
at ease with yourself about what it is.
you will discover. Do not be afraid to
find the answer. Sometimes that keeps
you at bay. That might represent one of
the mental blocks you have referred to.
Although we do not believe that blocks
really exist. The idea
exist. The idea
simply is to be at peace and be at trust
that whatever answer you will find will
serve you in a positive way. You don't
have to be afraid of whatever that
answer is. You will be able to use it
ingeniously. You will be able to use it
in whatever way you want to. And when
you start understanding the definition,
you will be able to redefine it. And in
redefining it, you will see the
difference in your physical reality
because you will begin to act in the way
that is representative of the new
definition. And in so doing, you cannot
have anything but a reality that is
reflective of the new definition you
have assigned to it. Is this all making
some sense to you? Yes, very much so. Is
it of assistance to you? Yes. Very
interesting concept. Thank you very much
and may I wish you pleasant dream
you in your civilization what what is
the basis of your mathematics that we
have we have decimal here what do you
use our old mathematical system used to
be based on what you would call 12 but
we no longer use it the idea now is that
we have more of what could be called an
intuitive grasp of spatial
relationships. We no longer have
mathematics as you understand it as a
regimented structural science. But it
used to be based on the idea of
12. Does it help? Another question. How
far have we gone with electromagnetic
fields and have you discovered monopoles
yet? In a sense, yes, we have discovered
the idea of monopole. However, in our
society, it is recognized as a thing
which can be
experienced only
in a state of existence that you would
call a singularity. Are you familiar
with that term? Yes, within the
singularity whether it is artificial or
naturally created there can then in that reality
created there can then in that reality
which is all realities be the experience
of the breakdown of any one component of
a
polarity but within the physiological
universe there cannot be only one
component. So the idea is that in order
to use the idea of any one side of a
polarity such as a monopole, you must
first create a
singularity which embodies and embraces
all realities, all dimensions and
therefore in which no one dimensional
physics takes precedence over any other.
So that anything in that sense is
possible. Anything is manifestable
through that structure, through that
particular generated singularity. You
can then create almost any type of
physics. We have been able to utilize
electromagnetic fields to create those
singularities necessary for the
generation of that type of power. And it
is that idea that we use in the heart of
what you call our spacecraft to be able
to shall we say tunnel through
dimensions from one to another rather
than traveling in the dimension to get
where we want to go. Does this make some
sense? The idea is that in your physiological
The idea is that in your physiological
dimension, the speed of light or what
you have called the speed of light is
truly an
absolute traveling from place to place
instantaneously is not really traveling
at all. It is in a sense merging with
the fabric of existence in one local and
reemerging from that fabric in another
local instantaneously without actually
having traveled any intervening distance
at all. To do this, we envelop our
spacecraft in a type of
singularity. And within that
singularity, all dimensions are here and
now. And by imparting the slightest
variance in the
vibrational construction of the ship, a
vibrational construction representative
of a particular universal reality, then
our ship will then have an affinity to
that particular universal reality and
space-time local. When we remove the
singularity field from around the ship,
the ship by definition will have to take
up residence in the new universe and the
new location it now has been given an
affinity to. So it simply transcends
from one locationational definition to
another locationational definition no
matter where or when those definitions
are. Space in that sense is rendered
into a complete here and now one point
in the singularity. That is how we have
shall we say bent the electromagnetic
field for we use light itself for all
the power that we need to accomplish any
of these things. It is truly that we are
with light folding the universe to be
able to move within it rather than
traveling in the same way now that your
devices travel through your physical
space. Does this make sense? There's no
linear travel there. Not the way we
travel. No, not even really
fundamentally is there actually linear
travel. Not even when you take your hand
and move from here to here.
This is an illusion of continuity. What
is actually happening is analogous to
what you call the frames that exist in
the medium you call your film strip. You
have discrete frames. When they are
moved fast enough, they appear to be a
continuously flowing image. You follow
me? This seemingly continuously flowing
image is actually made up of discrete
creations. this local and moment, this
local and moment, this local and moment,
and an
infinity of moments in between those
particular places. Because of the definitions of
places. Because of the definitions of
space and time you have in physical
reality, this motion seems fluid and
continuous because of the rate at which
you recreate yourself over and over and
over again, moment to moment to moment
to moment. That rate is so great a
frequency that you do not perceive that
you are actually flickering in and out
of physical reality all the time. All we
have done in that sense is realize that
motion isn't really linear even though
the illusion of it might seem to be. And
that we have allowed ourselves, shall we
say, to go 90 degrees out of phase with
that linear continuity illusion. To be
able to step, shall we say, in between,
quote unquote, the moments of this
reality to discover that in between the
moments of any one reality are all the
moments of all the other dimensional
realities that exist. Each taking turns,
flickering on and off so fast that each
and every reality seems unto itself
discreet and whole and does not
necessarily perceive all the other
realities going on in between all the
moments in time you think of as real.
Make sense? Thank you. Thank you very
much. I am I started in
June. I was wondering if you know this
entity and my concern at this moment is
to step forward and do it more publicly.
All right. The vibration we are
perceiving from you that you have
defined appears to us to be an entity
that is connected to you through your
oversoul and in a sense has a similar
relationship to you as I do to the
physical channel before you. This
relationship can be translated as
follows. Now there may be many
interpretations of this translation but
this perhaps will be the clearest one in
your language that can be made. That
consciousness in a sense is a version of
your future
self. Understand? Similar to yourself
too. I am in a sense the future self of
the physical channel sitting before you
in another dimensional existence. I am
discreet. I am distinct. I am my own
persona. But at the same time we are
aspects of each other and we are both
aspects of the same soul as we are
perceiving the energy you have described
the vibration you have described. It is
similar with you. All you need to do
regardless of the label because the
labels are not that important. They are
only a matter of convenience for you.
They are only a matter of orientation.
Regardless of the label, allow yourself
to trust that you have made agreements
that if you are a person who knows they
are functioning within integrity, then
those agreements will be fulfilled
within integrity. Trust it in that
manner. Let it flow through. It will
only serve the purpose of the integrity
you have chosen it to serve. And
trusting it more will allow it to flow
through in an easier manner. The only
reason that makes it seem difficult is
simply because of the doubt itself that
it would flow through and serve the
purpose that you agreed to serve by
making that agreement. Understand? I do.
Does that assist you? Yes. The concern
about the public is that I've been a
businesswoman for 20 years. Uh this is
not considered and I feel that I should
be a leader of some sort and I'm
wondering if you will be a mirror a
mirror for many individuals. The idea is
that we do not necessarily though we
know what you mean. We do not
necessarily prefer the term leader
because it implies that everyone else
will be followers. You will be a mirror
of leadership to reflect to everyone
their own self
leadership. You can do that. We
understand what you are saying when you
say your typical business world does not
operate that way but things are changing
you know. And the more you become
yourself, the faster they can change
because then you are adding your
momentum to the overall ability of your
world to move in whatever direction it
wants to. Besides all of that, however,
it is your life. And if you are deciding
that what you are doing that is true for
you is being done with all the integrity
you can muster and that you are really
doing it to the best of your ability as
far as you
know then there really is no other
criteria. If you are doing it to be of
service, trust you will be of service
and that everything will fall into place
automatically to bring to you the
appropriate opportunity that will allow
you to be of service. Because there is
no one, no one who has a gift to give
that will not find an audience to
receiver. No one. Because there is no
such thing as an extraneous or pointless
creation. There is no one that has the ability to
There is no one that has the ability to
express themsself that does not have
someone willing to listen to that
expression and be served by that
expression as long as you remember that
those you are serving are teaching you
as
well. Now does that help you?
Remember we know what your society has
created itself to be. But the final
question is who are you? regardless of
what they tell you you ought to be. You
can listen to their advice. You can
listen to their opinions and their
suggestions. And you can thank them all
profusely for sharing their point of
view, no matter how positive, no matter
how negative. Because
negative. Because
remember, even if all the advice you get
is contrary to what you perceive is true
for you, you have still been served by
them because now you know more truly who
you are by knowing more clearly what you
are not understand.
not understand.
Does God help you? It does. We thank you
for your conviction. We thank you for
your boldness. At this timing, we would
suggest that all of you take a short
break. We will resume contact in
approximately 10 of your minutes.
Thank you. Thank you.
How's it going?
I'll say by the way for your further
information just as a little bit of
assistance in relating to us to our
civilization. Though we are now
telepathic and do no longer use the
language that we used to so long ago. In
that ancient language, our people were
called Casani, which in your language
would translate out to living light. Our
planet simply sane as place of living
light. We are of average five feet of
your height of counting. white whitish
gray skin coloration, very wide upturned
eyes. The males have no hair. Females
have hair upon the head, usually white,
though there are exceptions. We are
relatively slandering for as we are
becoming more and more non-physical. We
no longer sustain ourselves with what
you would call physiological food, nor
do we sleep, as you understand sleep. If
you wish to make any comparison between
our species and your species, the idea
would be closest. If you were to think
of your culture, you may call Mongolian,
although this will simply be an
approximation, not something exact. We
are in that sense not human in shape,
but we are in your words
humanoid. Turning that idea around, you
to us would be asaniish.
The idea simply is that we have a
similar physicality to you, though not
identical. When referring to our
society, if you wish, you may use the
term in our own ancient language of
ethani. You may proceed with what you
call second line of questioning.
You spoke of beliefs. Our beliefs
creating our reality. Yes.
What beliefs of mine do I need to change
in order to create more money in my
life? What beliefs do you have about
your life now and what you perceive to
be the lack of abundance in it? Before
you answer that, let us explore the
fundamental definitions of abundance
itself. Because many times we have
perceived in our interactions with many
of you, the definition of abundance
itself can seem to keep it at bay from
you. Because many of you don't actually
know what abundance is. Therefore, you
don't really know what kind of a
definition you have about it. And
therefore, you don't really know why it
isn't manifesting in your life because
you don't know what it
is. If we may allow us to provide our
definition of abundance. May we? Yes.
Thank you.
Abundance. We like to have fun with your
language. Are you all paying attention? Yes. All
Are you all paying attention? Yes. All
right.
Abundance. The ability to do what you
need to do when you need to do it.
Period. Hey, he didn't say anything
about money. No, I didn't. Now, I am in
no way, shape, or form discounting the
version, the form, the tool of abundance
you call money in your society. Our
society doesn't have that particular
tool. That doesn't invalidate that tool
in your society. However, it isn't the
only tool. It is not the only way to
represent abundance in your society.
Because many of you are brought up in
the type of culture that believes that
money is really the only way to manifest
abundance. Then sometimes the degree of
focus you have on needing only money to
represent abundance. That degree of
focus in and of itself sometimes will
prevent you from experiencing the very
abundance you desire. Because your
definition of abundance is so limited to
only one particular manifestational
method that you do not allow yourself to
allow any other method to come into play
and that blocks all methods from coming
into play because you are not allowing
abundance to occur naturally within the
circumstances as they create themselves
in your lifestyle.
Now, the ability to do what you need to
do when you need to do it, that's
abundant. And anyone who has that
capability is just as rich as they need
to be if they can do what they need to
do. Also, abundance in whatever form it
comes will only come to the degree in
your life that you are expressing the
idea you are. If you are not expressing
the fullest idea of the thing that
excites you the most, you don't need any
more abundance to express whatever level
you are expressing yourself at. When
someone starts expressing themsself on a
broader scale and therefore does require
more abundance and more different types
of abundance in order for their
expression to become manifested in
physical reality, then the opportunities
and the styles of abundance come flowing
into your life automatically,
co-incidentally, synchronistically,
synchronistically,
effortlessly. The idea simply takes
action. Action in the direction of the
thing that you say is really the thing
that excites you the most. Another
misconception in your society that
sometimes prevents what you think ought
to be the abundance in your life is as
follows. Sometimes an individual will
focus on the idea of wanting money so
they can do the thing that really
excites them. However, what they're
actually focused on is the money, not
the thing that excites them. So, in a
sense, you are misdirecting energy. I'm
not speaking personally, just generally.
You are misdirecting energy when you
focus on the tool and not the actual
thing that represents what excites you
the most. Example, sometimes individuals
say, "Well, all right. The thing that
excites me the most right now is to have
an absolutely glorious place to live.
That is the thing that I really know is
the focus of my life. The very fiber of
my being right now. I am feeling like
the idea of a home and all the things
that that represents that to me now is
the most exciting thing I wish to be
focused on in my life.
So many of you say, "Now, what do I have
to do to get that home?" Well, let's
see. Homes cost this, and I have to have
this, and I better do that in order to
get that home. Sounds like a lot of work
all of a sudden. Don't know if it's
going to be so exciting after all
because I don't really find myself
excited about having to work for all the
money in order to get the home. I'm
really excited about the
home. Therefore, that's your first clue.
Focus on the idea that is really the
exciting idea, not the means to the
idea, not the tool that you think you
need to have the idea. Focus your
direction on the thing itself.
Then you simply act in the moment on
whatever is the most exciting
opportunity you can act upon out of all
the things that are available to you to
act upon.
then you will attract yourself into the
circumstances to give you whatever tool
you need to be able to acquire the thing
that really excites you. Now the point
that most of you shall we say become
confused or foggy upon is you think that
the circumstance you have to act upon
the circumstance that excites you the
most that you need to act upon in order
to activate that other thing needs to
appear to be somehow connected to that
other thing. On the surface, it doesn't
need to look like it has to have
anything at all to do with the thing you
want. The thing that lets you know it is
connected to the other circumstance you
want is the fact that it excites you
above and beyond anything else you could
be doing at that moment. Excitement is a
thread. It leads to all other things
that excite you. So if something in
particular is the most exciting thing
you can imagine and you find no way to
act toward it, do what you can act upon.
That is the most exciting thing you can
act upon. And that act in and of itself
will lead you in the most unexpected way
into the circumstance you need exactly
to get you the thing you really need.
analogy example once again the house and you
example once again the house and you
think oh no no the money the money I
need the money or I can't have what I
really really want very few of you
actually just want money you want money
more often than not to do something else
yes something else that really excites you
something else that really excites you
isn't the money that excites you it's
the ability to do what you want to do
that excites you. So don't focus on the
tool on the money as the only tool that
can give it to you. To further the
analogy, you are now walking down the
street. You have in your head the idea
of the house. You are so excited about
the house and then you start thinking
about the job you think you have to take
to make the money to buy the house and
you become a little less excited. You're
walking down the street and a friend
walks up to
you and says, "Well, how do you do?"
Then you say, "Well, not so good." "Oh,"
says the friend, "Why not?" "Well, I'm
really excited about something in life,
but I think I have to do something I'm
not really very excited about in order
to get it." Oh, well, that does sound
puzzling. Why don't you ponder it with
me? Oh, over lunch. Well, you know, I
really am far more excited about going
to lunch with you than I am about going
to the idea of a job to make money. That
is not exciting to be able to get what I
really want. But I don't know. If I
don't go to this job, I will never get
the money. I'll never get what I want.
Well, will it really cost you so much to
go to lunch for a little while? You are
hungry, aren't you? Well, yes, I am. And
I really do find that your company is
far more exciting. All right. All right.
I'll go with you just for a little
while. But if I am late, I won't get the
job. I won't make the money. I won't get
the house. Well, all right. I'll make
sure you leave on time. So, you go to
lunch because it really is at that
moment the most exciting option you have
to offer. And there you are sitting
having a good time and you feel a little
more carefree and you starting to focus
on the excitement of the house again.
Maybe maybe every now and then you start
thinking about the job and your
excitement goes down a little bit. But
maybe your friend being a very good
friend put you back on track and say,
"Well, tell me more about this house
idea sounds very exciting." and you get
more excited again and you build up the
excitement and
then all of a sudden you realize oh no
you have been talking about what excites
you so much that you have missed the
opportunity to go to the job interview
and you have perhaps lost the job and go
oh no now I will never make the money to
have the house and then all of a sudden
a friend of your friends comes along who
you do not know and your friends oh what
a coincidence I'll join us, won't you?
And the third new friend says, "Well,
yes." And you are
introduced. And your other friend, your
first friend says, "Well, you know, so
and so here was what you're telling me
about how excited they would be about
this house and so on and so on." And the
new friend's eyebrows raise and surprise
and says,
"What? Well, you are looking for such a
place to stay?" Well, yes, but you see,
now I've missed a job and I'll never get
the money, you know. Oh, but but what an
amazing coincidence. I am leaving the
country and I need someone to stay in my
house. Probably I don't know, 5
years. 10 years. I'm not sure I'll ever
be back, but I really want someone I
really want someone that I feel I feel
would be at home there that would treat
it like I have treated him. Now, I know
this friend and this friend vouches for
you and you have expressed to me the
desire that you have and it sounds like
a very loving desire. Well, I feel I
don't know why I hardly know you, but I
feel I can trust you at my house. Would
you would you live there? Go. Would you
live there? Just take care of it for me.
Maybe someday I will be back. Maybe
someday I will sell it. But for now,
it's a place and I want someone to warm
that place up. Would you? And you go,
"Oh my. Oh
my. Oh
my. Well, this house you are talking of,
where might it be?" Well, maybe you have
seen it. It's on such and such road at
the top of such and such hill.
What? That house? The house that I have
walked by every day for the last month
using as my guide for the type of house
I want to have. You mean that exact
house? I can have that house for dream
come true. Who would have believed is
possible? Well, that's the question,
isn't it? Too good to be true. Who
says that's not the way life looks?
That's a fairy tale. Just a coincidence.
Just an accident. Never happened again
in a million
years. Not in
modern. Every single moment, every
single day, every single year,
forever. That's how life works if you
let it. Because life does work.
Everything is connected. There's a place
for everything and everything fits. And
when you trust it and act upon it, you
allow it to show you it fits. You allow
yourself to have the awareness of the
fact it fits. And you slide
synchronistically into the right place
at the right moment, interacting with
exactly the correct individuals you need
to interact with so that they can serve
the vibration you have put out and you
can serve the vibration they have put
out. For if you were paying attention,
you will recognize that not only did the
person who wanted the house get the
house, but the person who had the house
needed the service in return and
everything fit. And there was an intermediary, a
fit. And there was an intermediary, a
friend who also got the benefit and the
joy of knowing that that friend had
brought together two people who could
serve each other. Everyone benefited.
And that is how life works. when you
focus on the thing that really excites
you and not the tool you think you need
because now it is obvious that that
individual never needed the money and
that the money though sometimes it can
be the path of least resistance isn't
always the path of least resistance to
bring you the abundance you really need
because abundance can come in many
forms. It can be something
exchanged. It can simply be given as a
gift of love.
It can come in the most unexpected ways.
It's just the
ability, just the ability itself to do
what you need to do when you need to do
it to reflect the idea that really
excites you the
most. And all you ever need to do, I
guarantee it 100% because that's the way
the universe is built. All you ever need
to do is have the focus on any
particular thing. If you have such a
thing that excites you and or do at any
given moment the thing you find most
exciting with integrity, it will always
lead you into precisely the set of
circumstances necessary to reflect all
the abundance in whatever way you need.
Does this help?
Well, thank you very many. [Music]
[Music]
My questions are personal. Oh, all
right. Maybe my answer will be personal,
too. All right. I'm very concerned. Yeah. How
All right. I'm very concerned. Yeah. How
about his health? Health. All right.
He had an operation and since
then very depressed, confused.
work. May I ask you a question? What in
your terminology is the nature of the operating operating
operation
and then much too
high up
in what particular area?
I don't know how to
say they cut him too
high. When the separation was cut, right? And comes And comes
[Music] All right,
stop. We will have few
suggestions. Few
suggestions. Now, what is the age in your terminology
Now, what is the age in your terminology
of this person?
Oh, what? One more woman.
Can this individual
sustain to any degree of comfort?
No. Ah, let me think. To any degree of
comfort what you would call a three day
water
fast. Can they subsist on water
primarily for approximately 3 days or do
you think that would be too much for
them?
All right. All
right. Then you can complement the idea
simply with
juices. But for now the idea of what you
would call nothing
solid can be very enriching juices can
be vegetable can be true
juices but juices for three
days that the individual finds
nourishing and agreeable and
invigorating and vitalizing.
And each and every time the individual
feels so inclined to drink a glass of
juice to first before
drinking, hold the hands
approximately within what you would
call 3 in of the glass.
And to breathe very deeply and evenly,
calmly, not
forced, just in a meditative state, eyes
closed to
breathe. And as the individual breathes
deeply to
visualize from the hand, bright beam of
blue white light going into the glass,
into the juice, into the liquid or water
and seeing the juice
glow. Do this for
approximately 10 of your minutes if
possible. Just ease of breathing and the
flowing of this blue white
electromagnetic liquid light infusing
the liquid to be
drunk. Then calmly
Then calmly
breathing and acknowledging the
consciousness within the juice, the
consciousness within the being, the
consciousness of the whole body.
Acknowledging that the body is energy
and is one homogeneous
substance and then drinking the juice
and feeling in the imagination the juice
not only going down the throat and into
what you would call the stomach but
feeling the energy that has been put
into the juice bleeding into every
cell. Feel the invigorating cool heat
going into every fiber, every muscle,
every bone, every tissue all the way
down to the
feet, all the way up to the head
throughout and even to some
degree radiating from the pores into the
energy field, the oric field around the
body. So that the person feels they are
glowing with the energy of the juice and
that they are in complete natural
gratitude with all creation for the
sustenance and the alignment that they
are receiving and allow them to continue to
receiving and allow them to continue to
breathe and feel at
ease. then go about their business until
the next time they feel a desire for
more juice to repeat that idea for three
of your
days and see what difference that may
make in the individual. One more
thing you army and they choose
they choose
to benefit.
This is an issue we cannot touch at this
moment. To some degree, some of this
idea will be connected to his own state
of self sustenance.
For many times in your society, the
notion of needing to receive
compensation or benefits sometimes ties
directly into a lack of belief of being
able to sustain the
self. Allowing to work first on the idea
of reblending and harmonizing with
nature itself and see everything else in life
itself and see everything else in life
change. It may not be as necessary for
certain things to come to fruition as he
may think. They may be able to manifest
in other ways. The changes within him
from what we have suggested may change
his entire attitude approach to life and
may change his desire for how he goes
through life and what he involves
himself in. He may derive a completely
different kind of benefits by moving in
a completely unexpected direction after
he changes the idea of who he believes
he is and what he is capable of doing.
So that issue to us is a very secondary
and superficial issue that hinges on the
first in many ways. Understand?
Also he can understand when he lays down
to sleep that he has like everyone
guides that will assist him. Guides that
will among him that he is energy that
matter is energy. Energy is matter to
allow him to breathe as one with nature
as one with the collective energy of all
that is and to be balanced and to be
healed. For there is
nothing nothing in physical
materiality especially of the nature you
are discussing that cannot be
healed. Allow him to know. Allow him to
focus on the idea in his imagination of
what he believes would represent his
idealized physiological condition. And
then allow him to know beyond the shadow
of a doubt that what he imagines is who
he is. Allow him to start acting more
like that person, the person he sees
himself. He desires himself to be. As
soon as he starts acting more like that
healthy and fully aligned and complete
person, it will not matter what has been
done physiologically in the past because
he will become such a different person,
such a new person that he will literally
have a new past. And whatever he defines
himself to be in the present will be
what his reality physically will be
regardless of anything that has ever
been. Because remember each and every
one of you, you are creating your past
from your present, not the other way
around. No matter how it seems in linear
time, whatever you are now determines
the entire event you are up and down the
time stream in both
directions. Allow him in that way to
drift in a dream and see himself as he
dreams, as he desires to be. And then to
begin to know through the exercise he
have recommended that what he is doing
is creating dream to be real and
understanding that physical reality is
only a
dream. Understand how
emotions and how do we change them and
how are they related to the Now solar
plexus. Thank you very much. Solar
plexus is what you may call the gate or
if you wish the chakra of intention
itself of conviction of putting it forth
of activation and this is where emotions
come in.
Emotion energy motion emotion is the
activator of your belief. You are a
persona a personality.
Your persona, your personality is
composed of three things. Belief,
emotion, thought. More precisely,
definition of
blueprints, activators of those
blueprints and the foundations or
structures or thought patterns in which
those blueprints are manifested
physically. Emotion, all
Emotion, all
emotion is a reaction to something you
already believe to be true.
That's how emotion is created. You have
a belief. You have a
definition. Then when you activate with
your energy, you then create to be alive. You
energy, you then create to be alive. You
activate the belief you hold most
strongly. Whatever that belief is,
whatever the definition is, whether it's
positive or negative, will define in the
activation how you experience the energy
motion. the energies, the patterns
becoming emotionalized into physical
activity. Emotions are reactions to
beliefs you already have. So if you are
experiencing a negative emotion, it's
because it is showing you that you have
a negative belief about a particular
circumstance. If you do not prefer the
negative emotion, then allow the
negative emotion to show you you have a
negative belief. Find out what the
negative definition is. redefine it in a
positive way and you will start to have
a positive reaction, a positive emotion,
positive thought patterns and a positive
reality. It is like a prism, a prism
that allows the white light of your
unbroken homogeneous consciousness to
pass through and be turned into the
diversified spectrum of your physical
reality. Emotion is one of the sides of
the prism along with belief and thought
pattern and it is the activation
principle itself. So the idea is to allow yourself
itself. So the idea is to allow yourself
to remember the following
things. All circumstances, all
situations are fundamentally
neutral, blank, empty, devoid of
meaning. No situation has a built-in
meaning. You are taught to believe that certain
You are taught to believe that certain
circumstances automatically mean thus
and such. And so you have a belief. And
so you have an emotional
reaction. When something happens and you
say, "I feel fear. I feel hate. I feel
anger. I feel joy. I feel love. I feel
happy because of the situation." It's
because of the belief you have, the
meaning you have given, the definition
you have created for that particular
circumstance. But they are all neutral
to begin with. And any situation, every
situation can be defined in a positive
or a negative way.
Now this is a mean that you cannot
recognize when someone might actually be
acting outside of integrity, might
actually be performing a negative act.
It doesn't mean that you won't be able
to recognize that. But just recognizing
it doesn't require an emotional
reaction. That's just observation.
Your emotional reaction is the result of
exactly how you have defined the idea
you are observing and how it relates to
you in that sense. Therefore, you can
now decide, you can now choose
consciously with any situation that
comes up in your life to say, well, all
right, if I am reacting negatively, if
I'm having negative
emotion, what is the definition I would
need to have in order to have that
reaction? Do I prefer the definition? Is
there another definition I would prefer
more than this one? If so, what is it?
If I have discovered what the definition
is I prefer. Do I believe I am capable
of believing this definition as strongly
as I believe the old one. If so, then I
will start reacting in a positive way.
For I will have realized consciously
that I have just redefined my entire
reality, my entire reaction to
everything I have created and therefore
the entire effect that that idea has on
my life, that situation has on my life.
Because you see the definition you put
into a situation which is neutral
utterly determines the effect you get
out of it
experientially. Positive definition in
positive result out, negative definition
in, negative result out. Once again it's
simple physics. You see something
happen and you have a negative reaction.
Then you're going in with a negative
belief. Again, you can recognize when
somebody might be doing something
negative. But that doesn't mean you have
to have a negative reaction. In fact, if
you wish to help the individual that is
doing the negative thing to learn that
they don't have to do a negative thing,
you having a negative reaction is not
going to help them. It's only going to
mirror the negative reality they are
already creating.
To have an understanding, to have a
reaction of balanced
compassion will allow you to be able to
reflect to any individuals doing a
negative act. That you are a centered
and balanced individual. And in being
so, you are giving them an opportunity
to see in you in your reflection that
they can perform and function as a
balanced and centered individual as
well. The whole idea hinges on the following
The whole idea hinges on the following
understanding. And if you will teach
this understanding to yourselves and
every individual in society, especially
your children, then there will be no
more fear, no more hate, no more guilt,
no more
regret. There will be no more
persecution, no more
victims. And the idea is as follows.
Everyone is as powerful as he or she
needs to be to create any reality they
desire without having to hurt anyone
else or themselves in order to
create. That philosophy will
reconstruct your entire civilization.
Right now, the strongest philosophy your
civilization has been taught is that
you're out of control. You're not in
control of your reality. Your life is a
gamble, is a risk at best. Or you can
try, but you never know. At the last
moment, all might come crashing down.
You're not really in
control. Now, how does that make you
feel? Afraid, alone, scared,
powerless. Individuals who commit acts of
Individuals who commit acts of
negativity against other individuals do
so because they believe they are
powerless. because they believe they are in a sense
because they believe they are in a sense
dying and in a sense they feel they are
sinking and they try to take as many
individuals with them as they can
because they don't want to be alone.
They are scared to death because they do
not believe they are in control of their
lives. When you teach individuals that
they are and that the circumstances that
they have experienced in their life have
been because of their beliefs, then they
know they can change it. And once they
know they can change it, they can do so
without having to hurt anyone else to do
it because they know they are a part of
the infinite and they have infinite
power in that
sense. The emotions that you experience
in your reality. The majority of the
emotions your society has experienced
for thousands of years have been the
result of this dichotomy of this idea
that you are powerless people. That is
where all the fear comes from. All the
doubt, all the hate, all the jealousy,
all the greed, all the rage. It all
comes from the belief that you are
powerless. That you do not have the
power within. And therefore, the only
way you can see to gain power is to
manipulate and dominate what you see
outside. Because you have never been
taught to know that the true reality is
created from within. Once you know it's
created from within, you're at peace.
You have
compassion for all because it costs you
nothing. Because the more you share, the
more you get. And that emotion is the
prime emotion and the only real emotion
that exists. Unconditional love. That's
what everything is made of. It is the
prime vibration of creation. That's why
when you feel love, when you're in
love, you are aligned with the infinite.
That's why it's so
powerful. Every other emotion in a sense
to some degree is a condition placed on
unconditional love, a variation of a
love, a variation of a
feeling. In effect, the true opposite of
love is not hate. It is guilt.
Hate in a sense still implies some
deservability. It may be a polarized
expression of love, but it still implies
that somebody deserves something even if
it's only me. Whereas guilt is the
belief in complete lack of worth and
that is the truest opposite of love
which is absolute worthiness.
That is what emotions are all about
basically and all the variations
basically fit into that theme.
Does that explain the issue to some
degree? Yes. I had one more question.
How does um your higher self? Yes. Why
would you choose
to choose a negative definition? The
higher self does not choose the negative
definition. the physical ego
consciousness. Then the higher self chooses the basic
Then the higher self chooses the basic
circumstance, the basic
theme, but the way you go about it is
determined by your physical free will
because there are two levels of free
will. The free will of the higher
consciousness that chooses the basic
theme you will explore and the free will
of the physical consciousness, the ego
structure that decides what to buy into
as how that theme must be explored. If
you buy into the idea that the only way
to explore that theme is through
negative definition, that's the way
you'll explore it. But if your
consciousness physically can understand
that you can explore it positively as
well, then it can be done that way. The
decision as to whether or not to explore
a theme positively or negatively is left
up to the free will of you as a physical
consciousness. That is not determined by
your higher
consciousness. Understand? I think so.
Do you wish clarification on a specific
point? Yeah. Why would the ego or the physical
Yeah. Why would the ego or the physical
choose a negative definition? because it
doesn't know there's any other way as we
just said because you are constantly
taught that there is no other avenue
that it's how do you
say survival of the
f eat or be
eat now what do you think your ego is
going to choose if that's the only
scenario you are given it's going to
choose to try and eat as many as it can
it's going to become as vicious
and as narrowminded as it possibly can
to fight for what it has been taught is
its little limited claim to
existence. Understand? It's a focus of
the tunnel vision of the narrow vision
that many of you have been taught
physical reality represents. Here you
are. This is it. Better grab all you can
while you
can. What's the word you say? Well, I'll
stop. Screw everyone else.
That narrow
vision is what creates the ego to choose
the most devastating and destructive
courses it can because it thinks
everyone else around it is choosing the
same thing and therefore it better fight
with the same
weapons. But it doesn't understand. It
has not been
taught simply that water is what quenches fire
simply that water is what quenches fire
and that fighting fire with fire only
makes a bigger fire and burns everything
up. So the soothing of water, the soft, the
So the soothing of water, the soft, the
compassion, the unconditional
love is what you can now
retrain the ego to
understand that this will bring what we
desire. Oh ego,
darling, love, you are not going to die if you
love, you are not going to die if you
blend with me as a whole. ego because
the whole of our existence is not just
physical which is another thing your ego
has been taught. Then if you seek beyond
your immediate physical idea that the
ego will die because it only exists in
physicality. But identity exists beyond
physicality. It does not have to be
expressed as an ego construct. And if
you can retrain the ego construct to
understand that it is only the physical
representation of the
identity that it is only a name only a
label and that if it's all right to
expand in compassion and the identity
won't die then the ego will not have to
fight and scrape and be so negative. The
only reason the ego is so negative is
because it has been scared to death.
That's the only reason it chooses all
those things. It has never been taught
that there is anything else to choose
that will allow it to
[Music] survive. Does this make sense?
survive. Does this make sense?
Thank you very much
for Could you tell us a little bit more
about the world of
the the dolphins
and and what is you said in a previous
talk that they are very evolved and they
are a sort of alien race amongst us on
the planet earth. Yes, you are planet
earth from our perspective has two alien
species land human and water citation
dolphin and whales. You are a planet
with two alien races one on land one on
the water. So they are of your world in
that sense. Of course a world unto
themsself but you are one world and
therefore the idea is to blend with
them, play with them, learn with them,
become one world with them, communicate
with them in whatever way you find most
enjoyable. They always invite you to
play in the water to learn their
environment. They are highly telepathic,
highly sensitive, highly emotional in
that sense. They can teach you all much
about giving into ecstasy and doing what
excites you the most. They offer this
gift to you in your dreams many times
for that is the easiest place to
communicate with you when the idea of
the ego structure is out of the way.
Therefore, simply the idea for now is to
learn to play with them to love them and
to love yourselves as they know to love
themselves. That's the basic idea for
now. is to form a union of one
is to form a union of one
world inclusive of the two species
apart. All right.
All right.
Yeah. Um I've been working toward a
certain career goal for many years. Oh.
All right. And may I ask you a question
before you go on? Is it the thing that
excites you the most? I think.
All right. Continue for now. Okay. I've
run across three obstacles. Oh. One,
two, three. nicely defined. That's the
type of person that I am. This is where
you're going to have to help me out. Oh,
all right. I did all the planning, get
the education, and all of these things.
Yeah. Then I had the fear. The first
thing was that no one would pay me. All
right. The second one was that I'd get
the job and they'd find out I was really
just a fake and I'd be fired. Oh, just
the bank. Oh. And the third one is that
now I'll get it. I'll keep it, but it
won't give me the satisfaction I've been
waiting for.
You're very good at this.
Did they actually teach a course in this
kind of I think I'm the only one that
could possibly teach it because I've
been learning it for a lot of years now.
So, well, now you have brought up an
interesting point, but go on. So,
anyway, I'm trying to I've done
everything. I've quit my previous job.
I've put all my resources here. I'm
ready to go. And I'm absolutely
paranoid. So, I'm trying to decide if
it's what I really want or if I've just
been telling myself that it's what I
really want. first of all or second of
all how I can overcome all these other
feelings to actually attain it. All
right. Well, number one, do you already
understand the principle we have
discussed this evening of your time that
if there is something that really
excites you, then it is representative
of who you are? If it is representative
of who you are, there has to be an
outlet in which you can express it.
There has to be a stage on which you can
say it somewhere in the world and that
you will attract yourself to it. Yes.
All right. So scratch number one.
Now delineate once again the second
idea. The second idea is that I'll get the job
The second idea is that I'll get the job
but once I'm there they'll realize that
I can't I can't handle it or I'm a fake
and then can't handle or defy the idea
of what it means to be a fake.
Well um in their eyes I'm just not
qualified. Not qualified. All right. All
right. Back to the first
principle. If you know you are a certain
type of being and you are doing
something that really excites you and
you develop the skills you are really
excited to develop, then obviously if
you are simply staying aligned with the
idea of who you are and know therefore
that you will only attract the job that
will allow you to express just the
skills you feel are your skills. How
could you be under or overqualified for
what you will attract? You will only be
able to attract precisely the outlet
that will allow you to express precisely
what you are good at expressing.
Therefore, you will be perfect for the
job you will attract if you allow
yourself to attract the job that is
representative of who you are.
Understand? Does that make sense? That
makes sense. Scratch number two. Thank
you. The third one. The third one. You
now have arrived at the idea of being
able to do it. Now you're not sure it's
what you want. No. All right. Does
anything else come to mind?
But maybe I've been looking in the wrong
avenues. All right. Well, use your
imagination. Is there something else you
can imagine? Are you even capable of
imagining anything else that really
would be more exciting?
love you.
Um, I don't really know. And because I
am such a methodical and factual type
person, I don't know that I've allowed
myself to allow myself to find out what
they might even be because I've been so
focused on one thing for all right. May
I ask you a question of basic
parameters?
Do you in the way you consider yourself
to
function, do you trust yourself? No. All
right. Why not? I don't know. All right.
I think I've never um I've never had to
trust myself. Everybody's always told me
what I'm supposed to do.
Correction. You have always trusted
yourself. All of you have always trusted
All of you have always trusted
yourselves
infinitely. When we talk in these
dialogues about the idea of using trust,
we're not talking about something you've
never done. We're not talking about
something you have never used before. Oh
no, now we're talking about having to
trust. Well, everyone knows that's a
difficult thing to do.
No, you have all surprise surprise
always, infinitely, absolutely trusted
infinitely, absolutely trusted
everything. It's just a matter of
whether you trust the positive or the
negative more. But you always
more. But you always
trust. If you did not trust, you would
not have an experiential
reality because what you trust in is
what you
get. Understand?
So, have you always trusted?
Possibly. Let's back up. I'll reverse
it. Have you always gotten an
experiential reality? Yes. Have you
always trusted? Yes. You've always
trusted in something, haven't you? Yes.
But I tend to trust most in what I
already know I can do. Oh, all right.
And sometimes you trust in doubt, don't
you? All right. But the point is, the whole
All right. But the point is, the whole
point is that you're always trusting in
something. Yes. All right. If you
didn't, you could not have an
experiential reality. Understand? Yes. All right.
reality. Understand? Yes. All right.
Now, if you now understand that you have
always trusted in something, what you
are now saying is that there are times
when you have chosen to trust in things
you don't prefer to trust in yet. All
right? If you now know, I'm going about
this very methodically so you will
appreciate the approach. If you now
know that there are things you have
chosen to trust in that you don't prefer
to trust in, ask yourself why would you
then choose to trust in
them? If you
understand that all things are
equal, all things you have ever trusted
in have all been equal to anything else
you have ever trusted in. They are
simply different options. That's all
they are. Just different options. Some
of them you prefer and some of them you
don't. Preferring something or not
preferring something doesn't mean they
are unequal. It simply means they're
different. That's all. So sometimes you
have chosen key word chosen to trust
what you don't
prefer. Since you understand it was a
choice, you can now understand you have
just as much opportunity and just as
much ability to choose what you do
prefer. Since what you have chosen that
has been a choice you didn't prefer has
always manifested, why not assume that simply
manifested, why not assume that simply
choosing what you do prefer will
manifest just as
easily? Understand?
There is no more ability in a positive
or a negative reality to manifest over
the other. sit this
sit this
but this is just air. It's just an idea
too. It's not fizzled into the fabric of
existence. Just an
idea. One of the main reasons your
society has this particular idea, this
particular difficulty is because you
have been taught the following equation.
this or
that rather than this and that.
I understand exclusive instead of
inclusive. I have this one question. Yes, I hear
I have this one question. Yes, I hear
what you say about believing it and
thinking positively as opposed to
negative. But I can do that for a day or
two. All right. All right. How do I stay
All right. All right. How do I stay
focused? All right. All right. Very
good. How do I stay focused? Another
definitional assumption. Having what I want takes
assumption. Having what I want takes
stamina. As if it weren't the natural
order of
things. As if you have to hold on to
that otherwise it will slip
away. Where do these definitions fit?
Why are you defining the idea of
choosing what you prefer as being
difficult to maintain? Why are you
choosing to define it as something you
have to maintain at
all? It's a choice. Once chosen, it
stays until you choose to change it
again. Understand? So if you find that
your reality changes, it's not because you
reality changes, it's not because you
haven't maintained it. It's because you
chose to change it. Because you believe
something because you choose to buy into
a belief that you don't
prefer. Understand? Yes. It's not a
matter of stamina. You don't need
stamina. All you need to understand is that once
All you need to understand is that once
you make a decision, it sticks until you
make another decision because nothing
else has a mind of its own. Just you.
Thank you. Does that help you? Yes. When
you know what? Pardon me. You know what?
What? Thank you very much.
Yes. Yes. In your reality, what do you do
Yes. In your reality, what do you do
with your time in
What I'm doing now is one thing I enjoy
very much. I communicate with many
different worlds and assist them in
their transformation. I am also in your
terminology a technician, a pilot in
that sense. I explore and discover many
other civilizations. I am also
interested in exploring many other
dimensions of reality. Also, I like
sculpture and many other expressions of
what you would call art.
I am fascinated by quite a lot of things
at different points and I simply act on
them spontaneously when as you say the
spirit moves me that is what I do with
my
time understand does that answer the
question sufficiently thank you for
sharing we thank you very much at this
time allow us to extend to each and
every one of you once again our
unconditional love, our joy, our deepest
appreciation for allowing us to
experience the loving
gift, the taste of your
consciousness. It is cherished by all of
us. We thank you for sharing and
co-creating the dream that we are
together. Remember, you
Remember, you
are dreaming right
now. Right now. Wake up and live the
dream you prefer to. It's your choice.
It always has been and it always will be
because you are made in the image of the
infinite creator. And that means you are
infinite creators
too. We thank you for your
shedding our love to you all. Exciting
dream lives and life dreams. A bomb and
loving good day. How it
How it
go? Oh boy.