I don't so many of you have heard of the
idea of a tool called future memory in
order to create the reality that you
want we will be discussing this idea
this night of your time you may use that
as your entitlement If You Wish future
memory but before we begin I will say
how are you all this evening of your
time we thank you for your participation
your participation in the understanding
the comprehension and the experience of
the growth of your own being and the
changes and the impact that that has
upon your world we thank you for your
momentum and your energy let us begin
the idea of creating the future memories
it goes hand in hand as you say with the
notion of creating the reality you want
in very specific terms during the idea
that you have called a workshop that we
have recently conducted with you we
discussed some very specific tools with
regard for creating the specific of
reality that you want to attract in your
life the creation of future memory is
another such tool one that can be used
with quite a bit of precision for once
get it involves the imagination and the
picture making capacity that your
imagination has but in a very different
way approaching it as you say through
another doorway where you may not yet
have placed too many guards too many
ideas of analysis that would prevent you
from being able to use it in a very
fluid manner always always when we
approach these tools and these ideas
with each and every one of you we always
do it from a different direction so that
we can touch on as many possible ways as
there are possible people possible
personas within your Society so that the
same idea the same energy can be
approached from all the different ways
that there are to approach it from from
as many different ways as there are
people in your world so that each and
every one of you will find the exact and
most appropriate way that works best for
you of course it is up to you to do this
specifically within your own meditations
within your own discoveries but we are
more than willing to experience with you
the joy of discovering all the many ways
you can look at the same one thing the
same one energy out of which all
dimensions of reality are
created now the idea of future memory
basically is analogous to the idea of
creating a scenario in your imagination
that is in every way shape and form in
every possible specific detail the
scenario that you wish to have in your
life we discussed this in the workshop
as the idea of identifying strongly with
your imagination scenario creating the
scenario locking into the scenario with
your emotions identifying strongly with
it and then acting physically acting
that scenario through to in a sense
train your physical cellular structure
to develop the habits that go along with
a person who lives in the scenario you
say you want to live in these are the
ideas we touched upon in the workshop
steps 1 2 and three naming the scenario
locking into the scenario emotionally
and physically acting the scenario
through but here this idea of creating
future memory is yet another way to
approach the idea of creating the
specific scenario in your imagination
that is representative of the life you
want to live we call it future memory
because we use the concept that you have
called memory to activate it it is
something that all of you are very
familiar with you all know how to
basically remember something now very
often you say well yes it is very easy
to remember in general terms but memory
is always of something that is passed
something in the past something I've
already done that is not always so
sometimes what you call precognition can
in another way be called future memory
but the idea the way we are going to
discuss it this night of your time is in
using mechanism that you already call
past memory with which you're all
relatively familiar and bringing that
mechanism associating that mechanism to
the idea of projecting ahead in the
following way pick right now an idea any idea
way pick right now an idea any idea
whatsoever of something you know you
have already done it would be a good
suggestion shall we say to pick
something that you found enjoyable so
that you will be excited about it
instead of lamenting it and bringing up
the idea of guilt we would suggest you
find something in your past that
represents a very enjoyable experience
remember it now in the way that you
simply typically remember anything take
a moment to do
so as you are remembering this scenario
roll it around in your mind you find
yourself probably very easily
identifying with it emotionally it is a
very simple thing to plug your emotions
into it because as you say in your
physical lineary it well yes of course I
already experienced it that way so all
I'm actually doing is remembering the
experience as fully as I can no big
trick as you say but remember remember
remember we have discussed with you many
times the idea that memory is actually
being created right now in the present
you don't actually remember the past per
se you create an idea you create a
perception in the present that you call
a memory of the past it is a memory so
to speak it is a recognition it is a
cognition in the present so to speak of
another probable you another aspect of
the total being that you are because you
are beings that have created familiarity
with linear time some of those aspects
of yourself are more easily relegated to
a past some of those aspects of your
present self are more easily relegated
to a future future or an alternate
Dimension Anywhere But Here and Now in
order for you to focus in this
particular reality you have as a society
created as you know a great deal of
Separation to isolate certain aspects of
the total being so that that aspect this
Persona in this life in what you call
your present scenario only has a focus
of its limited self and no other so that
it can get on about the business of
being that specific isolated local
person so that it doesn't get confused
as you say by bleed through from all the
other realities that you are living
simultaneously this is all well and good
and is a very valid experience of course
but now as your Society is expanding its
Consciousness a lot of this bleed
through is happening automatically
because you can absorb more and more you
can have more cognition of all the other
ideas that are going on simultaneously
and that is the point we wish to
underline that this so-called reality of
the future that you desire so strongly
is going on right now simultaneously
with the reality you say is usually the
only one you actually think is going on
right now just as the past is still
happening right now it isn't so much
that they're truly stretched out in
linear fashion before now later but they
are all simultaneously
coexistent and your focus and only your
definitional focus determines that you
experience them in a segregated linear
fashion so just as it is very easy for
you to recall something you have already
done and very simple to remember and
conjure up all the emotions that you
felt then sometimes by the way you will
notice when we talk about acting these
scenarios out that if you are actually
recalling a past memory strongly enough
you will actually find your body going
through the emotions that you did then
as an automatic response to what you
have already done if you identify
strongly enough with it this habit this
strength of conviction the strength of
identification is what we are after with
regard to making that Association to the
Future memory the scenario you create in
your imagination that you say you would
love to have in your life learn to
identify with the ideas in a very strong
emotional and physiological way to
things you have already done get into
the Habit in your meditations of
recalling Joyful events many many
different joyful events things that you
really like about your life list them
out if you want to label them down write
them out so they are clear to you pick
many many events that were very
enjoyable for you and go through them
one at a time take your time enjoy them
do not hurry through them out of anxiety
and Desperation to apply the tool to the
Future memory take your time and really
reminisce as you say walk slowly and
joyfully down memory lane with all those
things so that you are able to extend
your full sensibilities and really smell
and really taste and really hear and
really see and really feel truly relive
those experiences so that your physical
body begins to react to them
then pick the
scenario after you have done that pick
the scenario that you say represents the
very specific reality you would desire
to have and then put it somewhere in
that list you can even play a game with
yourself you can write all these
different ideas on separate cards and
you can mix them all up so that you do
not necessarily know what order the
future memory will fall in with all the
past ones then start at the and go down
the list again do it over and over until
the future memory is as strongly
recalled as the past memories until
there is no difference in your reaction
between the two then you will learn that
there really is no difference then you
will understand that is a very simple
thing to manifest that future reality as
your present reality because it will
literally become something you have
already done and it will be a given you
will take it for granted that it is
already something within you not
something you have to reach for that is
beyond you not something that is outside
of you that you have to travel towards
not something that you have to attain
someday somewhere in that dim dark
future out there you will be retraining
your body your Consciousness to accept
it as if it is already a given already
done all already seen what you say in
your French language Deja Vu you will
create that effect for something that in
your typical reality has not happened
yet linearly speaking but if your body
resonance if your Consciousness
resonance begins to vibrate at a
frequency that says this has already
happened then your reality cannot let
such a vacuum stand in your physical
manifestations if you are saying this is
something that already exists for you it
must be automatically supplied you will
create that space you will create that
vacuum into which that reality must come
and only that reality will come because
that reality as you know is a specific
frequency and you are giving off at that
moment that specific frequency as you
recall the future memory as you
reminisce this idea you want you will
give off that frequency you will take it
for granted that it is already within
you and as such all you have to do from
that point forward is begin to look
around and you will see that the
manifestations of that reality are
already springing up all around you
because they must be there since you
have already vibrationally speaking done
this thing so give yourselves this
opportunity do this as you say homework
or home fun this meditation
and enjoy it fully savor it do it in
whatever way shape or form your
imagination says would be the most fun
that will be the key and then you can
incorporate anything you want to into
that particular type into that
particular list into that particular
approach so that you can allow yourself
to lose your definition to blend your
definition of past and future into one
all-encompassing present in which you
already contain contain everything that
you need to contain to be who you desire
to be you all follow along do you think
you all remember what I said oh all
right that will be up to you we thank
you at this time for allowing us to
share with you that particular
reflection we bid that you have an
exciting time with that meditation in
your own time and on your own timing at
this timing we extend to each and every
one of you once again and our deepest
gratitude at being allowed to experience
your Consciousness at being allowed to
remember you in our present and in being
remembered by you in your present we
thank you for this interaction we thank
you for the sharing in return I ask you
now in what way at this timing may I be
of service to
you and to you good day do remember to
speak up boldly so that all may share
who you are okay uh I'm very excited to
be here tonight um I have a question for
the last couple of months I've been
going through
through
okay for the last couple of months uh I
have been going through a real
vibrational situation with my body oh
right one moment may I interrupt you for
one moment yes yes thank you very
moment yes yes thank you very
much everyone
right now take a deep
breath and repeat after
me one more time deep breath just
breath just
one all right now the idea of that is
for at each and every one of you that is
going to participate in this
communication when you arrive standing
and asking your question will go
and H we'll speak with conviction and
boldness do continue h now I speak with
conviction and boldness thank you um
anyway I have been going through a a u a
whole series of things in my body my uh
uh my pulse would go way up to 120 and
then drop down to 60 and I exciting very
exciting and uh the little roller
coaster quite the little earthquake all
right um and also um I've I've had I've
been having dizzy spells and I have a
lot of electricity that just flies in my
hands in a motor and you know I just
when I go to sleep at night this it's
like I'm functioning within a motor and
um I thought that maybe you could help
me a little bit with this I I'm I'm in a
channeling class that I've been in about
9 months and I find that I have a lot of
just soaring electricity and energy when
I go into what we do in class but
additionally it's just in addition to
that it's just in my life I just go into
these intense things and uh is it time
for the birth then well maybe that's
what I I I don't I don't exactly know
what's what's going on but I found that
it at one point a couple of weeks ago
well it lasted for a couple of weeks it
felt that I was almost in a um in a sea
caught in some kind of a an undercurrent
or Riptide because mental I was just I
couldn't keep my Center in this whole
thing in my mental and emotional process
to go along with my whole body so I what
I was doing ask you a question yes where
is your
Center well it's uh yes I mean it's
within I pretty well have it oh yes
which means well really where I feel my
center is right around my heart area
well all right so but that simply
translates into the phrase my Center is
anywhere I want it to be true all right
now remember that when you are EXP
exploring things that to you seem new
you are going to find you are going to
create a scenario an analogy that seems
as if you are stretching off center
being pulled off center and then perhaps
snapping back to it or through it to go
just as far in the other direction like
what you call a pendulum
swing but the idea is that you're also
expanding the definition of what your
Center is you're expanding the notion of
what things can be called your center of
all the differences that you can now
feel that you now know are still within
your Center whereas before you may have
labeled them as being outside of your
Center a stretch away from your Center
towards something that was not your
Center you are giving yourself an
opportunity to Spring farther and
farther out to create a wider sphere of
experience so that you will understand
that everything within that sphere must
come from your Center so that you can
become more comfortable more famili
familiar with a wider range of
experiences since after all in this
so-called sensitized age on your planet
you are becoming more expanded in what
your senses are capable of perceiving so
you're giving yourself an opportunity to
become comfortable with all the New
Sensations so you will understand you do
have a wider range of sensors to use and
that there are more types of energy to
pick up upon than you have previously
been familiar with you understand me so
far yes now knowing that
does that make a difference in how you
feel about what you're
doing yeah because yeah yes it does all
right all right it does not have to just
because I said it doesn't mean you have
to buy it no so I feel like I'm more in
the roller coaster I'm willing to swing
more than sit rigidly all all right now
is that sufficient for you to trust what
is going on is it sufficient for you to
trust your instincts about what you need
to do to create create a sense of Peace
within yourself about your experiences
is it enough to trust to follow your
instincts when you feel you might want
to attract yourself to interact with
different individuals in different ways
to allow them to give you different
kinds of feedback about what they think
is going on with you and to accept what
you feel is correct and to Simply let go
what you feel is not do you trust this
idea enough to allow yourself to know
that you are taking yourself where you
need to in the way you need to yes
that's so perfect yes yes it is a very
simple thing we have not said anything
at all that is profound it is a very
obvious thing the whole clue in a sense
to anything that you are exploring all
of you with regard to mysterious things
is that when it comes as you say right
down to it they are actually the most
obvious things of all allow yourself to
understand that your inner sense really
after all in many different ways is
simply quote unquote common sense you
follow me right does that help you yes
that helps me a thank you very much for
your sharing thank you very much sharing Robert sharing Robert
[Applause]
goe shivai shivai to you um I would like
to one moment all right all right in our
ancient Society for those that are
simply not familiar with the term in our
ancient language shivi was a saying that
we have shared with many of you and that
is why this individual used it this
night of your time shivi simply is a
recognition of what you might call a
quest a quest for self and when an
individual felt they had reached a point
of shivi in their lives other
individuals in seeing them coming stood
back made way let them achieve a
straight path to their goal because they
were on that Quest so the idea of
knowing yourself the whole idea of being
willing to discover yourself in that way
is simply under the banner under the
label the whole idea called shivi do
continue um there b b okay there are a
couple substances on our planet minerals
one is called mesil trace and one is
called Clark's minerals from Utah and
Nevada Utah all right Nevada all right
and you have talked about the seven
senses and the eight sense of
knowingness yes the transcendental sense
and the Seven physical senses that you
possess physical beings right and you've
talked about how the six and seven cents
are electro magnetic and it with is in
magnetite is the substance in our mucous
membrane that and I would like to know
if iron and manganese are the substance
substances or the six
sense there is some correlation to this
although there is a number of other
things as well one moment
there are many now transmutations taking
place within your bodily cellular
structural molecular forms the idea of
the manganese the idea of the iron but
also the idea you now call silicon is
increasing within your bodily
proportions the bodily ratios to allow
certain kinds of resonances to take
place within the glandular systems as
well One Moment One
Moment some ideas Trace Trace Trace
elements of what you would call Copper
in your body are also acting as
catalysts or shall we say Bridge
conductors between some of the other
more magnetic elements such as your iron
such as the idea of your
mese also to some degree
magnesium very small amounts very
erratic very sporadic but there are
shifts and combinations taking place
within your chemical form now that
involve these substances one
moment Inc to some degree also
zinc one moment for its electrolytic
properties being is that you are still
physiochemical beings in that way high
electrical activities in many
individuals are now being felt now being
experienced because of certain balances
certain combinations of zinc within your
bodies that are taking place one moment [Applause]
[Applause]
for now continue with another direction
if you wish um I would like to know why
the mesot trace is so high in calcium
and magnesium and it seems to be an
ancient kelt bed from 150 million years
ago can you talk about the origin of of
uh mesot trce and why it is on the
planet is it extraterrestrial nature one
[Applause]
moment let us say
simply there were events that took place
what you would call astronomical
events that
changed caused Great fluctuations in the
electromagnetic field of your planet
this fluctuation in the electromagnetic
field of your planet caused certain
pockets shall we say electromagnetic gravity
shall we say electromagnetic gravity
wells in which certain combinations of
elements would then be able to
congregate and
coales this happened over a wide area of
your world with these astronomical
events that change the electromagnetic
field of your planet there are many more
kinds of
representational shall we say fossil
remnants minic speaking that indicate
the fluctuations and changes in the
electromagnetic field One Moment One
Moment a lot of it has to do
specifically in this case specifically
with the
calcium of setting up new
Chains new structures upon which new
forms of life could eventually grow upon
your planet physiologically One Moment
One
Moment some aspects of what you might
call solar irradiation are also
responsible for the
accretions taking
Place solar radiation in its effect and
its mutative effect on certain forms of
life especially within your oceans
especially with its mineral salts and
high electrolytic capacity to cause
congregations of
certain elements as you have suggested
that would indicate the patterns that
were about to occur for new forms of
life new matrices upon which new forms
of life could grow and emerge upon your
planet in the new salts in the new
Solutions of your oceans at that time
this happened in your terms very very
long ago Millions upon millions of your
years ago is this sufficient for now is that
ago is this sufficient for now is that
why there's such an accumulation of
magnesium and calcium in mesot Trace yes
and the last thing I'd like to ask is
um what is
[Applause] the to activate the seven sense of
the to activate the seven sense of
spiritual discrimination is there a
mineral that that can activate
vibrational discernment although I
understand what you mean we simply do
not wish the word discrimination to take
on a negative connotation okay
vibrational discernment is the seventh
sense and is there a mineral for that
and is there a mineral for the eth sense
of knowingness in that sense to some
degree the idea of silicon will form a
bridge between the two even though it
will be connected with other elements
for the seventh sense one moment
[Applause] to some degree the
iron more toward the Silicon side for
the transcendental
a but it functions again mostly in entic
functions in glandular
systems one moment there are other
things that are not what you would call
minerals per se but more the idea of
enzymes amino acids that actually cause
the vibrations that set up the temple that
vibrations that set up the temple that
set up the pattern for the cellular
ability to discern other vibrations
electromagnetically you see there is a
lot about what you would
call enzymatic electromagnetic
encoding that your Society knows nothing
about yet there are magnetic
electromagnetic properties within
certain enzymes and amino acids that
have yet in a sense to be discovered
upon your planet it is not the simple
construction of what you would call
metallic minerals that is responsible
for the vibrational tempo
you understand well is there a substance
for that
then s the terminology does not exist
within the vocabulary of the channel one
moment it continue is horse tail is considered
it continue is horse tail is considered
one of the highest elements in silica is
that a a substance it's an
herb no one moment
no further information at this time
other than the focusing on the idea of
the silica to some degree is what is
responsible for your culture's
recognition that there's a great deal of
vibrational energy inherence in crystall
inst structures an identification takes
place between what is going on within
your bodies and what the crystals
represent to set up a vibration that
allows you to expand your
electromagnetic sensibilities you
understand yes yes does that help you
yes thank you thank you very much one
moment with regard once again to those
Oceanic concentrations you were
discussing earlier certain types of electromagnetic
earlier certain types of electromagnetic
edes were
created you will find that there is a
clue to the structure of the
electromagnetic field of your planet if
you will study how those
nodules accreted the directions of flow
the magnetic alignment of their
molecular structure will give you a clue
as to the variations that have taken
place within the electromagnetic
structure of your planet and will give
you a clue as to the type of
manifestations the type of energy
structures that exist discrete energy
structures that exist within what many
of you consider to be an overall
homogeneous unbroken electromagnetic
field around your planet all right thank
you thank you very much sharing
[Applause] [Music]
[Music]
hello Bashar good day to you be bold and
speak up I was wondering uh my daughter
uh Nicole was killed in a car accident
last year um my daughter Nicole was
killed in a car accident last year March
uh 1987 all right and uh is there a
possibility that I will be used as a
medium that she will be channeling in
the future threw me to uh teach this
reality about other realities already
has in dream realities with you yes uh
right after her accident uh I went to
Sedona and I found this uh medium and
Patricia and um she told me to go back
and write and within 4 months I had 400
Pages written and lot of it seemed like
I was channeling a lot of the
information that came through at the
time and as of six months ago oh and I
keep getting this electrical charges in
my head like I a lot lately and just got
one and
um I put this in uh this this 400 pages
that I had typed aside because my other
daughter needed my help now it's time to
go back to it and I find myself like
going to it and then I I set it down and
I say it's not it's not time yet you're
going through a lot of changes a
tremendous changes every day and right
now is not the time to go back one
moment one
moment right now then you can allow
yourself to if you wish write about the
changes themselves almost as if it were
an interim work an interim book so to
speak it can simply be in the form of a
diary if you wish but it will allow you
to process along an Avenue that you're
already familiar with without
necessarily having to be a part of the
overall work you're already in the
middle of you understand yes that is one
tool you can use so that you can still
use the writing but not necessarily
think that you must continue the
original work until you are done
processing what you are processing now
and then go I will know when it's the
right absolutely of course again that is
obvious everything that you do you
create in your life you create your own
timing you create your own destiny you
always recognize your own perfect timing
if you allow yourself to pay attention
ition you all already know that so allow
it to be obvious whatever comes up go
with that flow trusting your own overall
excitement your own overall direction
but do understand you've already
received many Communications in dream
reality all channelings do not
necessarily have to come in the way that
your Society usually labels these things
you understand yes one moment one moment [Applause] [Applause]
[Music]
[Applause] something that can be of assistance
something that can be of assistance
would be perhaps before you go to sleep
before you do your writing to sit
quietly and imagine visualize meditate
for a few moments on a very beautiful
very supportive very loving violet light and
supportive very loving violet light and
see if that strengthens the connection
any for you and makes things a little
more clear all right right does that
help you yes well thank you very much
thank you
sharing hello Bashar and good day to you
my name is imma Garcia I'm taking um
Nicole's speak up speak up speak up I'm
taking Nicole's place all right um and I
wanted um I don't really have a clear question
um I don't really have a clear question
but okay well you don't need a question
to communicate make a statement okay
well no no no okay oh all right no no no
you found the question all right very
often when you ask someone to make a
statement they'll find a number of
questions okay um I have um I'm involved
a lot um in the community I have um
right a lot of um involved in the
community yeah influence with uh many
many people many many people all right
have the work I do yes it do you find it
exciting it's very exciting all right
but but what is um I guess one of I
don't see it as a prompt but it's just
cuz I I do so many things I I I um I'm
an Entertainer I produce my own
Children's shows and I also do a lot of
production work commercially yes and and
um it's it's real hard for me to decide
um oh god um guys yes what
um what if I should pursue you know my
my acting and um why do you want to
pursue acting you like
running um are you an actress well that's one of
um are you an actress well that's one of
my professions yeah oh then if you are
willing you don't not have to repeat
after me I I am an actress I'm an
actress so if you're an actress what do
you have to
pursue why not simply allow the
opportunities to come as they come and
assume that in the way they come even if
it seems as if you're going back forth
to this and that that all those
opportunities and all those
circumstances and all those situations
that seem by one definition to be a
going back and forth are simply all
various tools within the one overall
idea that excites you to be expressive
and creative and communicative and
assistive and reflective to many
different individuals to help them enjoy
themselves why canot just be one way one
tool that you use within the over for
all thing that excites you instead of
assuming that it is something that in
and of itself must exclude everything
else you love to
do that was a question and that's you
have an answer oh God oh God all right
that'll do let me S do I have an answer oh
do let me S do I have an answer oh
yes are you an actress oh yes of course
when you're acting you're an actress yes
yes when you're doing something else
that's what you are at that moment yes
do you do each of these things to the
best of your ability when you do them I
sure do do you enjoy them when you do
them yes especially when I'm educating
at the same time why then are you're
always educating at the same time all of
you are always educating at the same
time you are never not educating at the
same time why create an assumption that
one expression has to mutually exclude
another and that if they all truly move
you there will not automatically be the
perfect timing in which they will all
fit why do you have to make a
distinction ask me which one might be
more important to pursue now if you find
one of them does really stand out more
than anything else by all means go with
that flow follow what excites you the
most I guess it has to do with um with
uh just being here and listening to you
and um and pursuing this whole
metaphysical this whole new age um you
know um
New Age World New Age world is a very
old age idea it's simply that your world
is remembering what it's forgot a very
long time ago but see I I I'm um I I'm
very much in support of it and support
in support of learning I'm just saying
guys um see whatever I do I share with uh
um see whatever I do I share with uh
other people oh thank you for sharing it
with us and
um I guess I guess what I'm trying to
say is what you're trying to say is that
you know you're doing fine and you're
have nothing to
say except that you enjoy yourself that
you enjoy sharing that you enjoy being
of service that you enjoy growing you
enjoy learning and that's the statement
I was originally looking for and that's
all you really need to say nothing else
really needs to be said you are living
life in the best way you can keep doing
it if that's your choice you're doing
perfectly simply by being the fullest
person you can be whether you know
anything about New Age reality or not
you are doing all you can possibly do to
help that new age arrive just by being
as fully as you can who and what you are
you understand understand you don't ever
have to have heard the term
metaphysics you never had to run across
the term new age to be living a new age
lifestyle you have chosen to be where
you are now you chose to be born at this
timing you knew what you were doing then
and you still do trust it go with the
flow you cannot be extraneous to what is
going on everyone is exactly the product
of the time in which they are everyone
is a piece of the overall tapestry there
are no Loose Ends there are no
extraneous ideas there are no pointless
creations and people that don't belong
where they are so you fit and the best
way to fit to know you fit is to be the
fullest person you created yourself to
be everything else will take care of
itself all you have to do is share and
love and be of service and that will be
a reflection to all other people that
they can then see in you a life style
not necessarily the same format but a
life style they can live too and that is
what creates your world to be a full
world of fulfilled individuals you
understand I understand and I
[Applause]
Shing good evening good evening B and to
you good day have we met
before only in a generic sense only in
the sense that we are in touch
basically with the total vibration of
your civilization that we beam our
energy to many of you and those of like
vibration those of like mind will pick
up Upon Our Beacon our frequency and
sense of familiarity in a sense you are
actually recognizing more of yourself
than you are actually literally
recognizing me you understand yes does
that help yes anything else you wish to
add yes yes I was able to watch the
video cassette of your last session
and I
understand how the Zeta reticulum was
explained all right it is only one
aspect by the way it isn't the whole
picture but go on and for me to
understand that after playing it over
several times guys and to get a glimpse
of the Astro picture from the galactic
energy yes I think one of the reasons I'm up
yes I think one of the reasons I'm up
here tonight is to experience a little
bit of humility humility I believe I
have to ask of your help all right I am
always willing to be of service in that
way on the grand level as I can
understand the Zeta
reticulum if you would move backwards in
astral time to our human time where we
live by
seconds by minutes and by hours yes well
sometimes it is harder for me to get by
day by day in those
moments than it is to project out and
understand the reticulum right you are
forming a strong identification with a
society that in a sense is basically
used to timelessness or a less
structured idea of time that is so but
the idea of quote unquote getting
through it is not the notion having the
idea that you have to get through it is
what makes it hard is what makes it
stretch out and take such a long time
because the notion in and of itself when
you make this comparison this judgmental
type of comparison between where you are
and where you think you ought to be that
judgment in and of itself creates
further separation creates more distance
to travel the idea is to understand that
if you have made a connection then you
are an extension of that and it is an
extension of you and you both coexist at
the same place now and the idea of
allowing your second and minute and hour
reality your temporal real ity the idea
of letting that accelerate is to
understand that the notion of
timelessness exists when you truly live
those seconds those minutes and those
hours to the fullest that you can when
you are completely present in them is
when paradoxically you don't perceive
them it is only when you seek to extend
yourself outside of where you chose to
be that you create the idea the concept
of of distance of
volume live where you are and when you
are to the fullest that you can
because that's where you chose to be
there is no comparison that is made
there is no resistance there is no
measurement taken and when there is no
measurement no judgment then there is no
sensation as such of the passage or the
existence of a temporal state is any of
this making some sense some of some of
it yes all right what is not well
perhaps when I ask my question it it
would it would fit in all right on the
other hand if what you spoke of earlier
tonight about future memory would is an
answer to my question please let me know
and and let me not carry on oh I love
you to carry on you see in carrying on
you then open many more do through which
we can ascertain your vibration and in
continuing to carry on you open that
many more doors through which other
individuals then can share of the gift
that you are giving remember we do not
know everything we only need everything
within ourselves that we need to be
ourselves at that moment we do not know
anywhere to near as much about you as we
know about ourselves you know everything
you need to know about yourself to be
who you are but by sharing that we are
then given permission in a sense by you
to go into certain doorways where we may
then be able to release certain amounts
of information you may not be
consciously aware of yet so do continue
if you yourself by the way have a notion
have a sensing that the idea the concept
of future memory is something that does
in fact strike a cord within you that's
probably your strongest clue that it
does otherwise you probably wouldn't
have recognized it nor thought about it
so long exactly but do continue and and
I do give you permission to inform me of
the answer to the question since it
would be the way you give me permission
is by
continuing do I move to San Francisco or
do I maintain myself in Los Angeles
which would in enable me to speed up
what it is I need to continue to
do
neither you know why no because you're
asking me and not making the decision
yourself I know I know you know which
feels more
correct now one moment one
moment for the purpose of this
conversation I will not hold you to
whatever you say so if you say Los
Angeles oh no that's not what I meant
that doesn't mean you're stuck with it
if you say San Francisco I will not say
well you said San Francisco now you
can't choose Los
Angeles I will never say you cannot
change your mind sometimes you will find
if this will help you that once you make
a decision any decision it then becomes
obvious and the obvious thing may be the
opposite of what you chose but at least
it's obvious now so what do you care
okay now which feels more correct and
why Los Angeles
why because it would be a decision that
would allow me to Center myself and make
decisions for myself as an adult
why why will that in your estimation not
happen in your city of San
Francisco or why would it not be as
likely in that
area because the influence of my family
is still very great up in that area
ah you want me to go on no now let me
not saying this is what you should do
let me just throw another idea into this
nice little machine that you are
creating here and see what it does to
the gears sometimes I am not saying this is
gears sometimes I am not saying this is
necessarily the case
now many individuals know what I'm going
to
say sometimes doing the thing that you
fear the most is the way to accelerate
and take full responsibility
because if you find you have a
trepidation that trepidation may be your
sign that that's actually where you
ought to be for the most accelerated
growth for what you actually want to do
whereas sometimes staying away from that
may be playing it safe and may actually
therefore take longer than doing it the
other way you understand what I'm saying
no no ah
interesting in other words the so-called
influence of your family as you said yes
yes it's your choice to be influenced is
it not yes so if you can coexist with
someone and if you can allow yourself to
understand that their simple presence
doesn't have to how do you say push your
button yes then you have taken strides
because then you're operating with them
as an equal you are loving them
unconditionally you are allowing them to
be who they are and that's what allows
you to be anything you want to be
sometimes if you stay away from that
many times again not saying this is
necessarily the case now but many times
staying away from that is actually an
avoidance of an issue that really does
need resolving and the resolving of that
issue is actually what would allow you
to really stand on your own two feet so
many times facing it being in the place
you feel the least comfortable is
actually what is representative if
you're honest with yourself of the thing
that excites you the most because to
resolve that discomfort is really the
exciting thing to know that you could
coexist with them as an equal and not be
influenced by choice would be having
grown up understand yes does that help
you at all yes and we thank you now The
Choice is still up to you of course so
enjoy whatever you do remember no matter
what you choose neither choice is
wrong correct correct thank you very
much thank you sir oh Sir W you're
welcome sir
shoting hi Bashar and good day to you
I'm so excited to be here tonight I'm
glad you're back back I haven't gone
anywhere well I know you haven't gone
anywhere but we haven't all been
together for a while I see says who in
this in this form a all right all right
um in this game in this story all right
um in my work that I do with people I'm
a psychotherapist psychotherapist speak
up can you all hear the psychotherapist
okay louder they say in my practice I
have recently attracted a wonderful
child 7-year-old boy all right and I
think some new things are going to start
happening for me in my work with people
well they must have already started
otherwise you probably wouldn't be
saying that well perhaps that's true all
right um I'm just really realizing it
now um this wonderful little boy is a
child who um is having night terrors
night terror that's the moment all right
and in addition one moment yes did you
like that night terror all right wanted
to add the proper weight well that's a
good way of describing It Anyway ah it
is also a clue to what we will talk
about but continue okay he's a child
that his mother told me at Age 2 and
three was recalling past lives yes
although now at 7 um he hasn't brought
any of this up with me yet but he do
have an imaginary friend and says he
goes Soul traveling with him yes me too
and some of his understanding what's
happening is of course filtered through
what he knows so far but I'm so excited
to be working with him and I want to
help him be of service to him and learn
and grow my right then repeat after me
are you ready all right night terror
night terror oh that was very
good one more time night terror how's
that all right now did you notice
something when you did it that way you
almost couldn't help but laugh true true
do you think you could allow him not to
run from the fear but to actually
accentuate it to the point where he
starts playing with it and learns there
is nothing to be afraid
of that would be wonderful yes so all
right what is the child's name Matt Matt
Matt Matt Matt all right
Matt night Terror no no no no no not
night terror come on no self-respecting
night terror would go around saying
night terror I'm a night
terror how do you think a night terror
would say I'm a night
terror well he describes these beings as
as monsters yes of course and he's very
afraid of them yes but you see when an
individual allows themselves to as you
say get into the vibration of what it is
they are afraid of they recognize that
they contain an equal amount of that
energy themselves and therefore I'll put
this very simply they are just as strong
as anything that has been scaring them
and they can scare them right back well
I've been trying to use Excuse me you
have been
walked um I'm considering using a method
that you taught us in the workshop both
last year and I believe considering all
right what is it you were talking about
um the method of visualizing a creature
or whatever yourself manifesting your
own fear in your mind and transforming
that into the dragon who flies off okay
and I would love to be able to first
first play a little bit more of a game
that might be a little bit too powerful
at first play a little bit more of a
game the idea use the vocal clue as we
have been doing make a vocal game out of
it allow him to begin to imagine how the
energy of night terror would sound if he
were a night terror all right you have
these night terrors if you were a night
terror how would you sound I would sound
like this night terror well isn't that
how they sound well yes it is well why
should they choose to sound any other
way otherwise they wouldn't be being
night terorist if they didn't sound like
night teror but you know you can sound
that way too which means you have chosen
to sound that way to play that game all
they're doing is playing that game too
so they have to sound that way but you
can sound that way too you can be just
as much of a night teror and then maybe
you can all go out to some night teror
hangout and have
fun allow him to learn the equality of
the energy that is within him so he
understands that it is simply a
reflection and a projection of something
he is capable of being as well when he
knows it is within him too there is
nothing to fear because then the night
tears become buddy buddy right okay and
then they aren't so terrible any more
and he can recognize them as simply oh
shall we say other mischievous children
okay um I guess related to this is I
have been it has been suggested that um
this child has come to me as a bit of a
gift and a teacher a bit all right and
of course I would assume that that's
true anyway oh right thank you very much
for allowing the obvious to stand out
once again um is there any particular
agreement that he and I have that no
none whatsoever do you believe you could
you no no why not well because I don't
believe anything's an accident oh well
thank you then why did you ask me if
there's an agreement I guess I'm asking
the wrong question oh it's not a wrong
question but it does point out to you
that you know there is an agreement yes
what is the agreement what are you
[Applause]
learning well I feel I'm in an Uncharted
area ah and um you mean where the
ancient maps used to say there be night
terrors here
uhhuh ah
well it's simple when you think of it in
terms of just traditional psychology but
because this child is aware of other
realities for me this is a new
experience I see not really well you
have many times charted uncharted waters
in many different ways he knows that
Captain Navigator he knows that he knows
he's in good hands and you also know
that that individual is extremely
powerful extremely powerful simply has
come to you oh tinkerer oh aligner of
magnetic compass needles has come to you
to get a little bit of realignment when
that child is aligned watch out what a
terror but you understand what I mean
yes you have formed a coalition you have
been together again and again and again
and again and in a sense it is simply to
have a little bit of ajustment made a
little bit of alignment made okay for
which he has come to you but you are are
both going to learn you to refine your
craft in many meanings of that word mhm
and that individual to understand
navigational direction again what
direction to point who and what he is
who and what he's chosen to be who and
what he was and what he will
be play together play play play play
together okay explore as you explored
before those maps of Uncharted lands you
are simply exploring a new Uncharted
land so what that it is not necessarily
as material as the other ones mhm I've
really gotten excited about the P
working more with children that are
having these experiences then that is
your best Compass heading the excitement
itself set your needle firmly on E okay
thank you
Shing hello Bashar Andrew you good day
um I didn't really have a question
either oh thank you very much do you
wish to make a statement yeah I do um
thank you um just on the synchronicity I
mean everything is synchronicity oh
thank you very much yes it is what is
synchronicity that's a good point oh
thank you very much if you're not going
to ask a question I might as well okay
good what is the answer what is
synchronicity well it all fits in
together I mean every every keep it
simple keep it simple
everything is f sin all right that's one way of
is f sin all right that's one way of
saying it can you be simpler still
everything is synchronicity all right
which means everything
is one all right very good everything is
one thing everything is everything else
it is all one and the same thing
synchronicity is your physiological
manifestation your physiological
recognition in linear terms that
everything is everything
else except that in linear terms you can
only experience events one after another
but they exhibit a type of link up they
exhibit a type of connectedness because
that's the way you interpret different
things actually being one and the same
thing in a segregated physical reality
you don't experience them exactly
simultaneously but you experience them
synchronistically coincidentally as you say so yes
coincidentally as you say so yes
everything is one and synchronicity is
your physiological linear recognition of
that fact how's that that's wonderful
thank you for your recognition for your
cognition and your
precognition thank you I I do have one
question on all right all right so um
it's all the same one thing yes and
manifesting in all the multi-dimensional
ways that it can right and so um and so
the reason that that I could perceive it
more uh closely to me it connected to me
uh is it because it's closer in um I'm
going to use an example each question
that was asked um speak up speak up
speak up each question that was each
question that was asked each question
that was ask um up to this point and as
always um I could it was like a question
for me it helped me understand myself
yes the synchronicity therefore is in
the timing of your participation in this
event Now understand
all those answers all that information
All Those Questions vibrate in many
different ways anyone who is key to a
particular vibration is going to pick up
out of that question out of that answer
what they need and of course therefore
it's going to seem specifically directed
toward them because it is specifically
directed towards everybody you will only
receive the bandwidth that is the
frequency you're operating on and of
course it's going to seem specific all
right it is specific but it is also for
everyone okay and is the idea where you're open
okay and is the idea where you're open
enough that you can you have all of that
understanding uh all the different
vibrations as an understanding you can
you can recognize that there are the
many vibrations you will not necessarily
want to recognize them all otherwise
perhaps you would be sitting around
twiddling your thumbs and not doing much
with a vibration that would help you do
something but yes you can recognize them
in a certain way if you wish you can say
you can recognize it as a background
vibration and from time to time certain
elements of it can rise to the surface
you can see quote unquote more than one
simultaneously it depends upon what the
definition is of who you are at that
moment and why you would need to see it
that way but yes you can see in gals if
you wish okay but then that that's like
something that seems to be happening
with me right now is I don't seem to be
in a lot of action and I do seem to be
receiving um or understanding a lot of
different things and how to relate to
myself it may Simply Be preparation for
you to take an action is there an action
that you want to take that you're not
taking um yeah I would like to be able
to bring uh more of the non-physical
Concepts into the physical in what way
in my channeling uh with writing a all
right so are you doing that yes but not
to the same degree as I would like to ah
well do you remember what we talked
about in terms of creating the future
memory can you use that exercise for
this particular case in point yes
definitely well thank you very much do
that and see what happens all right and
then it will already have been
accomplished okay great thank you very much thank you
okay great thank you very much thank you
Shing ho ho ho can you hear me oh yes
good day Bashar good day to you I um had
a completely different question that I
was going to ask you that I've been
wanting to ask you for such a long time
but all such a long time oh you know way
way back way way all right but all of a
sudden I thought of an article that I
read about a man named Aldo alino I
believe his name is he has a theory that
at the time of the departure and the
destruction of the dinosaurs uh that
there was a mammal that he calls Proto
setti are you familiar with
that we understand the concept to some
degree but
recognize that you are putting this
theory in very shall we say simplistic
terms that's the only way I can because
I don't really completely understand it
I just read the article all right uh
from my limited experience and knowledge
of but what I gleaned from it was that
this mammal at that time slightly
resembling a small horse had a large the
largest brain capacity at that time of
the mammals no no okay what became the
dolphin did that's that's this creature
that I'm speaking of all right this
creature then then that is the
nomenclature that is the nomenclature
that that when the fusion occurred and
when uh the plant life died and when the
dinosaurs and the um the living
creatures on Earth could not survive
that some of the protti went into the
sea to survive the radiation and that is
uh the Forerunner or the antecedence of
what we call the the citations today
basically basically yes there is much
more to it than that but basically yes
where could we find out more about
that in the akashic records
I'll go home and look at them tonight
thank you very much all right and the
Dolphins have some notion about it you
know you could ask them well all right
all right One Moment One Moment
individuals now there are more and more
of you who are willing to place
themselves in situations
synchronistically and circumstances
where they can interact with dolphins
physiologically can in certain states of
meditative what you would call Bliss
meditative dream sharing with the often
reive telepathic images if you ask that
question of those happenings so long ago
because it is a history that is passed
down from generation to generation in
their storytelling so they can transmit images
storytelling so they can transmit images
to you and you can receive now be aware
that you will likely do some translating
into your own terminology what you will
receive will not necessarily always be
absolutely literally what happened but
you will at least get a sense and some
of the images will be accurate so ask
them the question telepathically go into
the relaxed dream state as you float
with them and let them send you images
and see what you get all right is that
uh could we just ask any dolphins or
should we ask dolphins that we interact
with usually it is in the cellular
memory of all of them now now there may
be different capacities in different
Dolphins to relate to what you are
asking to depending upon the
circumstance they are in and the
environment they are used to generally
speaking those that in your terms are
wild will deliver the most potent
storyline okay you understand yes oh
thank you while the um oh
um I lost it very when you were speaking
of dolphins I wanted to ask you that
when I was in Sedona a woman that works
with dolphins extensively and has worked
and been with them for a year or so at
the Dolphin Research Center said that
they [Music]
um I I guess I'm not supposed to ask it
they're taking it out of my head sleep
on it all right thank you very much
thank you at this timing you may all enjoy a
you at this timing you may all enjoy a
short break we will reconnect in
approximately 10 to 15 of your minutes
remember remember remember enjoy how's it how's it
[Applause]
going anybody who wants to order the
tape for having them again tonight like
we used on Thursday night so you can
order your tape tonight for
not quite as exciting maybe efficacious
perhaps yeah all right the idea however
of course is that all tools are valid
whatever methodology you think will be
the most impactful for you by all means
use it but they are all
equal okay what I'm working on are
magnetic healing devices all right speak
up speak up be magnetically resonant
yourself and you will find a little more
identification with the magnetics on
your planet okay B magnetically
resonant you are the prime
electromagnetic field that you will be
working with
anyway I find there's two opposite
energies right spiraling energy yes and
it's my it's my idea that what we need
at this point is primarily negative
ionic spiraling energy patterns it will
depend upon the area it will depend upon
the person there may be some generalized
truth to this but there will be a wide
variety of fluctuations depending upon
circumstance and
persona but do continue well what I'm
trying to get at is with Magnetic
therapy um with the two opposite
polarity energies yes spiraling energies
yes how can we get a feel for which one
to apply it's my feeling that we need
much more of the negative
counterclockwise spiraling energy
directed and then we do the positive
clockwise spir again generally this may
be so but you will find a wide variance
in Persona structure and Persona
structure will determine to some degree
the output of the electrom magnetic
polarity that is being given off
radiated by any particular individual so
in some cases all we are saying to
arbitrarily and automatically apply one
particular polarity to that person just
because you think it was good for the
last person may not necessarily serve
them the idea is to find out what their
resonance is for times will come around
where you may find you will be surprised
that someone is already operating in one
side when you thought they would
naturally be operating in the other
simply take a reading from every
individual so that you will be able to
more specifically apply the
electromagnetic resonance field or
bubble to that individual as an
individual rather than just generally
you understand uh yes but what I'm concerned
understand uh yes but what I'm concerned
with are the other life forms that are
more or less living off of our life form
living off of uh tumors virus bacteria
things of that nature um in a sense they
are not so
much what you might call a life form
living off of your life form they are
encapsulations of your own
Consciousness but they are ENC capsized
yes so how can we the thing I'm
concerned with yes is if I just use a
polarity to
strengthen will I how do I know when I'm
strengthening these other life forms
that are encapsulated within the
physiological body that I'm treating all
right the idea once again goes back to
finding out what the shall we say at
rest frequency is of the whole
individual it may take actually creating
an
environment a condition in which that
individual is at a place of Peace at a
place of rest as best as they can be
finding out what their magnetic
resonance reading is in that state and
then generating a field a very strong
field that mimics that at rest state so
they will then have a cue to identify
with if your field is stronger in output
than the output of the combined mass
energy of their body their body will
have no choice but to align with your
stronger field and in aligning with it
nothing that cannot exist within the
definition of that ATR field will be
able to exist from that point forward it
will be able to
decapsulate dissolve and go back into
the Blended homogeneous magnetic state
that every individual is to begin with
you follow me yes does that help you
would there ever be a case that both
Solari would be needed at the same time
yes in a sense to some degree you may
find that you will need both to begin
with to create what you would call the
generalized idealized balance tuning
fork Ground Zero rest vibration by
creating a general balance vibration to
begin with and seeing how they respond
to it that will give you your first clue
as to what their natural rest position
is as compared to what the general rest
position is for all the background
vibration will allow you to see in them
how their Persona their unique Persona
translates into physical terms their
natural rest position so you're setting
up what you might call a control
frequency with both polarities balanced
how they relate to that control
frequency will determine to some degree
they at rest balance control frequency
and also by
comparison show you how far off they are
from that by observing how far or in
what way they had to go to identify with
that ground state once you know what
their true ground state is you can make
whatever slight alterations are
necessary to account for their
individualized Persona frequency add
that to your overall ground frequency
overlay it slightly and then amp it up
so that they are then being given an
opportunity to see to feel in
electromagnetic terms the frequency that
is the mirror image reflecting back to
them of their idealized background and
Persona balanc signature vibration
follow me so create kind of a neutral
field and allow them kind of follow them
yes follow them because they are the
best guides because they will simply
align with it in whatever way they can
and their fluctuations within it will
tell exactly how far off they are from
it you will read it emotionally you can
read it sometimes physiologically the
amount of resistance that is present in
whatever form it is present will tell
you how far off the alignment they are
some individuals will actually become
extremely physically ill when presented
with a balanced state of electromagnetic
energy ease off let them recoup let them
find their own feet it may sometimes be
a process that takes a few sessions
before they're actually able to stand in
the radiation of the grounded balanced
zero State you understand well it seems
like it' be almost impossible to come
out with a
mass uh a fill that is going to be
accepted by the majority there is a
general background tonality it is true
for every physiological being in your
particular universal dimension it is it
is also true overlaid with many
fluctuations that represent the
individuals uniquely that you are
however basically if you find what allows you to
basically if you find what allows you to
feel most balanced you yourself as your
own initial
control generally speaking if you are in
a frame of mind in which you wish to be
of service while you're finding out what
your balanced tone is then using your
own balanced tone generally will be
representative of the fact that you will
generally attract someone into your
reality that will be able to identify at
least to some degree with your own
balanced tone otherwise they wouldn't
have wound up in your life
anyway follow me yeah does that help it
yeah well thank you very much thank you
surely hi B and you good day first I
want to say I love you very much and we
love you as well thank you very much yes
um speak up what I want to ask you about
yes H One Moment One Moment yes perhaps
this will help as a tool when each and
every one of you come here to interact
in this way and stand up before the
group you are
auditioning you are auditioning to be
yourself so give me the right reading
who are you and speak like it okay thank
you I want to ask you about pain and
suffering that happens on this planet
look's like I go along in life and for
the most part a lot of pain and
suffering doesn't come into my reality
but every now and then I'm going along
yes and something will happen like like
car crash or something like that yes I
you have resistance yeah yes I do and it
makes me angry that I can't snap my
fingers and make it all better I'll make
it yeah I and I One Moment One Moment I
perceive perhaps that you did not quite
understand what I said well say it again
I do not mean you have resistance after
it happens you have resistance and so it
happens all pain and all suffering is
resistance whether conscious or
unconscious resistance to the natural
self and when you resist the natural
self when you go against the grain you
cause the friction the dissimilar
frequency that causes friction which
translates in your body as has pain
suffering and what you would call
Accidents when you flow with your
natural self when you allow yourself to
be in touch with who and what it is the
vibration of your excitement really is
and you flow with it there is no
resistance to the natural self there is
no fear of the natural self where there
is no fear of the natural self there is
no resistance where there is no
resistance there is no
Collision understand yes the resistance
comes first then the pain pain and then
the suffering to let you know that you
are in a state of resistance it is a
barometer now some of you can take a lot
of resistance because you think you have
to many times sometimes because of the
way you have been brought up to believe
because of the definition you have been
taught of the way life is supposed to be
you will use the pain and you will do it
again and again and again and again and
again not that you have to but because
of certain belief systems you may have
bought in to you may use it until you
get so tired of it that you finally give
yourself permission to not have to do it
that way again that's just the way some
of you operate because of what you have
been taught you don't have to do it that
way the key if you wish is to be very
very aware very strongly in communication
aware very strongly in communication
with as much of yourself as you can
without fearing what you will Discover
it is the denial of self any aspect of
the self any degree of an aspect of the
self the denial of that aspect that
causes resistance friction pain
suffering and negative synchronicity
which is what accidents are yes now is
this helping you at all yes for myself
but I'm looking
at I I find it very very upsetting to
observe the pain and suffering ing of
other people all right your compassion
can allow you to desire that they also
know they don't have to suffer that
maybe I'll give you quote unquote the
benefit of the doubt what you mean by
upsetting however if you are judging the
experience you're adding more negative
energy to it because everyone does
create their reality and not that they
have to create suffering but you have to
understand if you wish to truly be of
service to them that they can learn
something positive from it it is the
attitude change in and of itself not the
condonement of it but the acceptance
that they chose it and so can change it
that will allow them to get something
positive out of it that will allow them
to know they are in control enough to be
able to change it we are not condoning
the suffering accepting that you created
it does not condone it it means it puts
you in control and when you're in
control you can change it you cannot
change what you do not own so the idea
is yes have
compassion but if you are upset in a
judgmental way if you are denying the
positive experiences that can even come
out of suffering you in a sense are
actually short Circ your ability and
their ability to actually proceed beyond
the suffering because you're focusing on
the suffering as something that
shouldn't be happening in a negative
connotation rather than saying all right
this is not what we prefer we prefer
this but we do not invalidate what we
don't prefer invalidating what you don't
prefer gives it more strength than you
need to give it and that's what empowers
it you understand yes is this helping
you to lighten up a little bit when you
lighten up a little bit then you radiate
The Compassion side of what you are
experiencing rather than the judgmental
side of what you are experiencing going
on in other individuals if you interact
with them as a loving being of
compassion and offer them offer them by
example by experience different
opportunities they could take they do
not have to take but that they could
take then they will at least be given an
opportunity to see in you a reflection
they might mimic whereas if you are
coming at them with a sour face judging
their experience and shaking your finger
saying this should not be happening this
way and we do not want this to happen
again and we are going to fight against
this with all our might and we are going
to use the very same energy in that way
if you come up them that way all they're
seeing is another echo of what they're
already experiencing they are not seeing
the potential upliftment you understand
they are not seeing the way out because
you're not giving them an example of
what they could be choosing does that
help yes the J remember as we have said
a few times before you do not get Peace
by hating War you get Peace by loving
peace oh yes does that help yes well
thank you for your compassion thank you
for your drive and your willingness to
have an impact remember you have the
strongest impact when you are simply
fully yourself in a loving
way thank you very much well thank you
very much bye sharing audition [Applause]
[Applause]
time um you don't have to talk the M
right there hello B and do you good day
I'm 10 years old yes and my father died
last year all right um I was wondering
if I would ever get to talk to him again
again remember the first place you
usually wind up speaking to individuals
that have died is in your dreams whether
you remember that or not because the
dream is now the type of reality they
are in you see to begin with let's say
you are actually a nonphysical being to
begin with you become physical when you
choose to at different times but you are
primarily a non-physical spirit being to
begin with when an individual dies as
you call it they simply stop being a
physical being and become a non-physical
being they become Spirit without flesh
and so your dream reality where you can
do anything and be anyone that is the
realm of the spirit and when you are
asleep in your body very often you leave
the body and explore the spirit Realm
where individuals exist who have died so
in your dreams very often you actually
do have conversations with individuals
that have died especially individuals
that love you and individuals that you
love so understand you can begin to
remember these conversations if you
simply tell yourself before you go to
sleep that you know you are having these
conversations not necessarily all the
time but if you know you are having
those conversations already
your ability to know that will allow you
to begin to remember the conversations
when you wake up in the morning and you
will know you have spoken to those
individuals who have died do you
understand yes and then bit by bit day
by day here and there you may find as
you go through life living your life
which is what you need to do as everyone
does there might be certain things that
will happen in your life certain
coincidences certain things that grab
your attention
sometimes those things that grab your
attention are actually messages and
Communications from those individuals
now in spirit form because the easiest
way to talk to many of you while you're
still physical is with the physical
objects that already surround you so
they will simply draw your attention to
something able to will be able to
deliver their message for them because
that thing already lives with you in
your physical reality you understand yes
does that help you yes thank you for
your sharing and pleasant dreams to you
thank you [Applause]
[Applause]
sh good evening bash and are you good
day it's wonderful to be with you again
yes is it wonderful to be with all these
individuals too it certainly is let them
know if by speaking up well I am oh all
right h
Good Start
yes I like what you had to say about
what speak his oh okay ah I like what
you had to say about future memory well
thank you because I've noticed that in
my life that happens a lot yes and I see
that it's um the getting in touch with
our future selves actually is what what
what's happening there yes and often
when I've looked back i' I've noticed
that at different points in my life
there's something I've wanted a lot and
I will Vision that yes and then forget
it yes and then later I come to the
point in my life where it manifests yes
and I have this wonderful Deja Vu yes
and I see that those moments are the
same the time between is an illusion
absolutely thank you very much well
thank you for reminding me of that again
well you're very forget thank you for
reminding me to remind
you my pleasure and mine as well I just
wanted to say that I got back from 7
weeks away so to speak s weeks
away I Australia 3 weeks in New Zealand
all right and nine wonderful days in
Hawaii all right and I don't know if I
can explain what this trip was then
don't no I want to no it was an
exploration of myself oh yes and I see that no
of myself oh yes and I see that no
matter it's like someone said no matter
where you are there you are no matter
where you go there you are um I fell in
love with Australia oh all right I fell
in love with New Zealand oh all right
does Australia know that I think they do
no all
right I've certainly been emanating that
vibration and that no matter where I it
doesn't really matter where I am and I
think moment one moment would you say
that again it doesn't really matter
where I
am would you say it again it doesn't
really matter where I am if it doesn't
matter where you are what does it
do I think traveling is just
revisiting all right but did you
understand what I meant no tell me again
all right simp
once again taking an opportunity to make
a play on your
words it doesn't
matter where I am that's good Bashar all
right the idea
being that you are energy you are matter
where you are is what matters all matter
is where you are it is all within you
you matter and that is what creates the
events that matter to
you yes I guess what I was meaning oh I
understand simply playing around with
you as usual you're so good at that well
it's fun it is and what it does then is
allow me to open some more doorways
myself oh thank you um because I
see or actually I I come to realize that
when I'm traveling or when I'm not
traveling that I Encompass I'm asking
encompassing matter space time
everything yes as a spiritual being yes
it is all within you within the idea
that you are there is no
outside this is so
true and I must tell you one more thing
oh all right if you must I had such a
wonderful time swimming with the
dolphins at SeaWorld in Brisbane yes
well you know they had a wonderful time
with you they certainly did they made it
evident and
um I have I do have one question all
right sort of all right get it out the
whole time I was in Australia I looked
for dolphins in the wild yes whenever I
was near the ocean and also in New
Zealand and I didn't see a single fluke
or fin of a wild dolphin all right and I
was thinking of dreamer a lot yes and
Conjuring up before I went to sleep uh
conversations and interactions yes with
those Dolphins yes but the ones that you
were with in what you call your sea
World park in a sense to some degree
were Preparatory emissaries Now
understand we have discussed from time
to time the idea that many of you have a
desire to meet what you would call one
of us an alien an extraterrestrial and
we have discussed the idea that
sometimes when you think you are ready
for that energy not meaning to put
ourselves above you but you know what we
mean about our higher vibration when you
think you are ready for that energy
sometimes when it is offered to you you
shy away because you realize you are not
ready for it understand that the
Dolphins and especially the dreamers
upon your planet are very much like that
and therefore some degree of preparation
through a little bit more familiar
Dolphins a little bit more familiar
surroundings can prep you for what you
will actually encounter when you do
encounter the dreamer dolphins for it
will always be a very profound impact
that they will have on you for they are
very bold remember there is absolutely
no hesitation in their level of
conviction none zero as you say zip
so giv yourself an opportunity to float
around in a little bit more structured
environment with those dolphins in that
area gave you some preparation energy to
be able to take you to the next level
you understand I do understand in fact
that had occurred to me
and my first interaction was with a
captive dolphin and so far those have
been my interactions yes and it occurred
to me that I'm sort of working up to
interaction in the wild yes you are
working up towards making the big jump
you see the dolphins have their own ways
of putting you through hoops as
well thank you for your progression and
your joy and your dream reality sharing
thank you very much Bashar I love you
and we love you
sharing hello Bashar and good day to you
I was hoping you could help me hoping
hoping hoping speak up understand a
concept uh
regarding um prophecy Destiny yes versus
free will very simple very simple
will very simple very simple
particularly when there's group
Consciousness yes very simple now
basically as we have said there are two
types of Free Will so to speak the Free
Will of what you may colloquially call
the higher self or if you wish the group
self and the free will of the individual
Persona that you physically become you
follow me so far yes now the Free Will
of the higher self the group self
determines the general scenario that the
concentrated Persona will physically
play around in it determines what the
playground will generally look like now
to the physicalized self the Free Will
of the higher self can be called fate or
destiny or any number of those ideas
but it is simply a free will expression
that the physicalized self will adhere
to more often than not because it was
made with the distinct choice and
conscious recognition that the general
experience the physical self was
projected into is the
experience that was desired by the total
being the whole soul the whole
self how you go through that General
experience that was chosen by the Free
Will of the higher self is up to the
free will of the physicalized self the
methodology is in your
hands the higher self the whole self may
say this hallway is the hallway you will
walk down as a physical aspect of the
total being but how you walk down the
hallway is up to your free will as a
physical being you can run you can walk
backwards forwards upside down right
side up sideways in the dark in the
light alone with friends swim crawl look
in all the doors walk all the way to the
end that doesn't matter it can be
positive it can be negative that's up to
your free will because you are the
representative you are the
Emissary in the foreign land of physical
reality and it's up to you to decide how
best to blend in with your environment
but the overall mission so to speak in
very general terms more often the not
has been decided by the Free Will of the
higher self now sometimes there are very
specific things that are quote unquote
ordained to be worked out from what you
would call One Life to the next but
those are also choices and those choices
are usually made by the soul self and
very often are not made in what you
would call a fully conscious State all
the time because even in what you would
call the immediate non-physical physical
soul level above physical reality there
is not necessarily a high degree of
conscious awareness of what is going on
so sometimes there are still reactions
that occur coming out of one physical
life going into the soul level and then
projecting yourself back into another
life that represents a continuation of a
certain momentum that may again seem
like Destiny or fate or a pre-ordained
path but all that is is the continuation
of a momentum you chose to begin at some
point perhaps in another life
recognizing that there is not
necessarily a direct binding tie to that
original choice can free you from it if
you are willing to learn the basic
lesson in whatever way you want to
usually the only thing that keeps an
individual in physical reality feeling
tied to a particular karmic wheel or
predestined path is the lack of
recognition that there is more than one
way to go about learning what they need
to learn sometimes it is only
stubbornness or refusal to believe in
your ecstatic selves that forces you to
take the only path left the one of
struggling and climbing the ladder it is
up to you to choose the positive and or
the negative side in that sense does
this help um somewhat all right you were
saying now that your higher
self decides that you're going to walk a
c down a certain hallway generally
speaking it says let me put it this way
all right in my recognition of all that
I am in this particular like the general
scenario I desire to experience perhaps
is the one dealing very strongly with
issues of Love or issues of abundance or
issues of this relationship or that
circumstance in
general then the physical
self is constructed
out of the vibrational patterns of
physical electromagnetic energy that the
higher self feels best represents the
best opportunity for kicking off the
physical aspects momentum in that
direction this is what your astrology is
all about the recognition that certain
patterns of energy are vibrationally
Frozen at the moment of physiological
birth that represent the general
momentum that you chose with the free
will of the higher self but that is
still very variable and the physical
conscious self still has a great deal of
leeway and a great deal to say about
exactly how you fulfill that original
choice understand it is the same you you
made that original choice it's just that
in your Society in the past it has been
that you as a physical being has
forgotten that you are also the higher
self that made the original Choice there
actually is no difference between the
Free Will of the higher self and the
Free Will of the physical you you're one
being but because your Society has
created such a high degree of
segregation because it sees physical
reality as being so distinctly separate
from non- physical reality you have
concocted this scenario of
predetermination and faith and Destiny
because all that is is simply an echo of
remembrance of the original choice you
made not that you necessarily have to
experience in any particular fashion but
you are remembering the original choice
you made with your free will as the
higher self does that make sense uh I
believe so so the the original choice
was a really important powerful choice
that you made everything you choose is
still just as important and just as
powerful the whole idea is that you are
still the original being that made the
original choice and when you recognize
that there is less separation between
you as a physical being and you as a non
physical one and the choices you find
yourself automatically Desiring with
your free will as a physical being more
automatically and effortlessly line up
with the original choices you made as a
non-physical being understand that this
is generally the way we are talking
about this now generally happening in
your civilization because of what your
specific civilization has been this
doesn't necessarily occur in other
civilizations in the same way in
civilizations that do not forget they
are are the same as the higher self
simply a physical manifestation of the
higher self then there is no necessary
need for this dichotomy of conversation
with regard to what is the original
choice what is fate what is Destiny what
is free will they recognize it simply as
the product of the same being they've
always been but they're the same being
in a different state making choices they
want to make in the state they're in now
make sense yes does that help you very
much well thank you for having made the
choice to discover more and more of and
what you already are and thank you for
choosing to co-create this interaction
this day of your time thank you our love
to you at this timing you can't quit now
oh yes I can it's the perfect time we
can always smell the strawberries coming
no check your timing again you'll see
that that I'm on oh you all right
okay Jonathan yes sir very nice
breakthrough very thank you thank you
very much my pleasure we have played
with you that game many times I know
always stopping just before you step up
yes thank you very much for playing
along all these times do proceed my
pleasure thank you old
friend one of my one of my perfect alien
friends very you are one of my perfect
alien friends too I
know want to update you on the
strawberry connection uh past memories
future memories update way the uh
physical strawberries now exist so that
you can have a vibratory uh frequency to
align with so can yeah they now they're
now in place thank you very much for
being willing to truly act out to
physicalize and act out the realities
you desire oh it's on the way it's doing
beautifully thank you how's the patch
unnecessary absolutely luscious
good okay we'll be up there planning
together soon thank you yeah and that'll
be exciting
I can see all of that in my future
memory very nice yes you too right yes
we had a wonderful time I love it have
Hab yes yes yes yes yes and the
restaurant is progressing the strawberry
connection restaurant is is the design
is moving along beautifully with the
crystals right um I've been in full
design of a magnificent theme park all
right which is of the um size and scope
of Disney's Epcot oh right and has in a
main section called creation Central in
which all of the creative abilities of
individuals are uh manifested in an
extremely entertaining way all right and
another section called the universe
showcase oh oh right one of the lands in
the universe showcase by the way is
called density 4 oh so that'll give you
another vibratory uh Anchor Point to
thank you very much but it it really has
been an exciting project a lot of fun
the films are moving nicely the uh
Universe projector moving along and I
just wanted to share with you all again
as we do on many levels just just here
and you know what the joy of it what I
love you I love you too thank you very
much yeah I'll uh look forward to our
carpet flying together and uh all right
and I will look as usual backwards to it
oh
good thank you for your laughter most of
all ah it's a it's a pleasure yes it is it's
ah it's a it's a pleasure yes it is it's
been a pleasure for a long time it will
be a pleasure for a long time to come
forever I could say it is pleasure
always all that kind of stuff you know
there will be to use your typical temps
a
day believe it or
not when every single individual on your
planet will be laughing all at the same
time loveely love that yes it is thanks
again good friend we thank you very much
and now at this timing correct we shall
extend our appreciation once again to
each and every one of you for playing
along and for allowing us to enjoy the
playground that is your
Consciousness thank you for sharing the
same dream reality a fond and
unconditionally exciting and loving good
day [Applause] [Applause]
h
[Applause]