How was it, anyone?
[Applause] I
didn't just read books, I also tried using the
various meditation methods and other
techniques that were written in the books.
Before this channeling started, I had a
very strong
technique that I used, and I did it automatically. I started doing tarot readings
tarot readings
myself. I found some
found some
tarot cards in a drawer in my desk where I was working, and
no one around me knew who they belonged to or who had put them there. So I read the
instructions and learned what they
were and how to use them.
Then I started using them every day. But I
But I
didn't really do anything special while actually using them. It was just that
when a client came in for work, they
saw them and asked me if I could do something for them.
I started doing them because, unlike before when I had just been playing around, I
had a reason to do it for them, and I felt like I was concentrating a lot more than usual. I didn't
particularly want to write an instruction manual, I
just looked at the cards as I felt.
And so I told the other person about it,
and I kept looking down like this, and I talked, and
then for the first time, I
looked up and looked at him, and he was like this, with his mouth wide open. I
realized that I had hit the nail on the head, and
so I thought, wow, I can do amazing things,
and I've continued to do that. I've done
that with several people for a few years, and
just before I started channeling, I
met someone who was teaching all sorts of psychic things on different levels,
and through his teachings, I learned to balance the
logical part of myself with the emotional part.
I did all that, and
after learning all that from him, I
just gave it to the channeler. When you make
that kind of agreement beforehand,
you naturally learn what you need to do it, and it
naturally learn what you need to do it, and it
happens automatically,
and you trust the information that comes out of that.
And I want you to remember that you're
doing this by choice, and you're
doing it to serve.
And first of all, the channeler  To
experience passing through means
to get in touch with the various aspects of your nature that lie within you.
You are getting in touch with the various aspects of yourself that you have separated in this society. So many
things will
come to you. You have to trust and accept them. Sometimes it
Sometimes it
can be a very emotional experience. It
doesn't have to be an emotional experience, but it often comes out that way.
Another thing I want to say is not to be
too quick to label the information that is coming through you. If what is coming through you is
positive, there is no need to be so quick. By filtering out this being, you start to attach labels to it,
to it,
and you
end up filtering it out a lot. Trust your senses and move forward, but
at the same time, try not to ignore your physical being on this plane.
Any channeling does not come at the
expense of one's personal life,
and if the channeler is satisfied, the
channeling will be satisfactory. There is
something very interesting happening when I enter.
My consciousness is diffused,
and it is more like a dream when I am sleeping.  It's
more like a hum, and you enter into a sort of luster,
and then you go beyond a certain level,
but that point is quite clear.
And after talking to several channels,
it seems that they do go beyond that state, though not all of it.
Channeling is a process of merging with other things, a
process of integration, so at some
point you suddenly come into contact with various aspects of yourself, and
at that time not only the positive aspects but also the negative aspects that you possess
pass through.
When a channeler passes through this, it's the thing that
people who are about to start channeling are most
afraid of at first. It
takes a few seconds to get through this,
but once you get through it, something interesting
happens. You become very sensitive to your environment and
start to feel all sorts of things.
You just feel connected to everything.
When it's positive, you feel very connected and it
feels good, but
when you get past the negative aspects, even the smallest sound or
thing can be irritating.  It
feels like all the
negative emotions that you normally have when you react to what other people are doing come along with it. It
's a very critical part of you. Those feelings come up
inside of you, and you start to
feel them. It's as if
all of your negativity is condensed into these three seconds, and you're
attaching yourself to it for three seconds. It's an experience that's
experience that's
very interesting, and when you go through that, it feels like you
have to look at everything you have again. And
being in a trance
is a very interesting sensation, and I think it
depends on the energy and the things you understand, and you
experience sensations that you don't normally feel. I get to feel how
they feel, how they
feel, how they understand, like, not have. While I'm in a trance state, I can feel what it's like to have
absolutely no doubts. And
gradually, that feeling starts to come into me, and my
real life is gradually
becoming like that too. [Music]
As you know, this time is something you create for yourself,
but how about a deadline for today
? Before I begin, I want you to
remember a few things. [Music]
[Music]
As we're having this exchange today, I
think a lot of new energy will be felt by some of you here. You'll
see new things, feel new things, new
perceptions, new realizations, and if you allow it,
allow it,
it will naturally arise in the space that's most comfortable for you.
When you start to feel any kind of energy, remember that you
have the power to handle it. I
want you to remember that the universe will never
give you anything you can't handle.
Never, never, never. [Music]
So when you feel like there's an energy coming at you that's too strong, you
're using your own definition. The universe's definition is that it's
not coming at you, it's being thrown at you. [Music]
So what we're going to do is let that
energy flow through your body as you breathe. Relax, and
Relax, and
decide to see what you're experiencing in a positive light.
Breathe.  It's
perfectly fine to feel these emotions and changes within yourself.
Just remember, you are choosing to feel these energies now as a product of your
love and service to all.
So, don't be afraid, just feel them with gratitude to the universe. And be grateful that you are choosing to
learn who you are and what kind of being you are through these experiences.
Each and every one of us
is a very unique being with a unique structure.
Your personality doesn't
fundamentally represent who you are. It's
what you are trying to be in that moment, and the
strongest thing you have, that defines you. So, when you change the
thoughts and ideas you have within yourself, you will
completely change as a person. You will
literally change.
So, when you come in here today
and when you leave today, you
will be a completely different person. Think
people, no matter what you look like in the mirror, you will be a completely different person. This appearance
is an illusion. When you begin to change enough within yourself, you will become a completely different person.
When you begin to change fully within yourself, you will
change. For some, this happens naturally and automatically over a
period of time.
Your society is still
very attached to time and space,
so it may
take time for change to actually occur at the physical level. The reason
you keep looking at your face or other external appearances the
same week after week is
because you want to maintain continuity within yourself.
When you start to focus more on your internal perceptions rather than on the outside, you will
no longer be bothered by the changes on the outside from week to week.
And no matter how dramatically you change on the outside from week to week, you will
always be able to maintain your signature vibration, your unique frequency.
No matter how much you change in your personality, your
unique frequency expresses your soul.
At the same time,
even if your outside doesn't change at all, it is very possible that you are
changing inside and your personality is changing.
When you desire change and act on how you have changed, your life will
actually change.
Thank you for having the conviction to change yourself in such a beautiful way.
Thank you. I
want to know about imaginary human relationships. Are
you all ready for the movement?
[Music]
Before I get to the questions, do you have any questions? I want to go through
all the stages first. I want to talk about the
human relationships and other things that are happening all over the planet right now. So,
this is a bit off topic, but I'll take your
questions now. What is it? Yes,
Yes,
on March 1, there were over 300 to 500 cases in Japan. [Music] The
1989-90 period was two years
ago. If you want to do something for society when there is such a
big social upheaval or change,
what kind of action should you take? Of
all change takes place or vast big changes occur for people, those people who want to serve the other, what do they do? The first thing I want you to understand is that all change
can be seen as both positive and negative.
When you think that change has to happen in a destructive way, you have to go through that process.  If you do that, you'll
gradually flow in that direction. [Music] You
can then see these changes in a positive light, as if they're breaking down what was created before and creating something new. This
will then work in a positive direction.
Even if there are big changes, how you personally
experience them is a different matter. Remember, the
Remember, the
vibrations you carry are what you experience. And
when you have those kinds of
vibrations, they
bring fear. But if you have love, service, and joy, those kinds of vibrations, they will
carry you in that direction during times of change. [Music]
Some isolated parts of the Earth may experience these changes
very negatively, emotionally and
in other ways.
Some parts may still have to pass through in what you might call a catastrophic disaster. But
even within those parts, even
within those areas, if individuals
see the positive, they
won't be affected in that negative way.
So,
as these great changes are
coming, what we want to do is to
see them in a positive light. As
we sense your energy and
watch, this is
what will happen between 1990 and 1994. A
very large part of consciousness will
begin to become aware of social unity. There will be a new awareness of expressing
one's individuality very publicly.
At the same time, as there are extraterrestrial planets and so on,
many governments on your Earth are
aware of our existence and
have various pieces of information. This information that the people of 1990 to 1994
have will now be released into the public sphere
and recognized in the public sphere.
As a result, this society
will write a great deal about the universe. But we
don't want you to focus on us when we say this; we
want you to focus on yourself.
Many people are being
asked to take responsibility for their own lives and to tell
others what to do.
Instead of letting everyone else run their lives, you're
now being asked to take responsibility for your own actions. That doesn't
That doesn't
mean you have to listen to everyone. [Applause]
Hey, it doesn't mean you have to become ours.
But here's how change can happen. Governments that have
felt like they've been denied control
can now. [Music] With
all this going on,
change can come much easier if we don't lose our power, but if we take it back.
When we talk about political, economic, and social change, remember that you're part of it.
Taking responsibility means
taking responsibility for your actions and
doing something for your society. [Music]
Your time, from 1990
to 2011, saw a social upsurge. It
's a global story. And many global cultures
intermingle. There
may be a lot of violence in many places,
but in the end, it will all
balance out. Your unconditional love.
Gradually, things will become smoother. [Applause]
Then, in 1997, there will be another big change.
By 2013, this Earth will
be one world.
All of what I have just said
can be said by sensing your energy now.
So, I would
like to talk a little about prophecy here.
From our perspective, there is
no such thing as a prophecy about the future.
When you are feeling the energy like now, you can get a sense of it. No
one can sense the future. You
can sense the energy of the present and sense future possibilities. So,
So,
when you sense something like that, you can say that if the energy state does not
change, this will actually happen. There
is a completion to that energy. If it
continues to be completed, it will
go in this direction. You can sense that. But that does not
mean that it cannot be changed. At
the same time,
even if something like that occurs, it does not mean that
you have to experience it in a certain way. If many people
many people
continue with this energy, it will turn out like this.  If you can
sense that something is going to happen, you
can change that energy. So
So
when prophecies become public and are made known to everyone,
everyone can change it, and so the
prophecy itself often loses its meaning.
Please understand this well. Prophecies
are all reading the energy of the present. So what I've just said is the energy that
we feel within you right now, and I've
only spoken of the energy that I felt would generally change. If
everyone here wants to change that, you
can choose your own energy. Will it be positive or negative? I
can say it this way: if
everyone here
decides to wake up now, there will be no need for someone from outside to
shake them awake later.
Those of you who are born here now have been born into a
very exciting time in this era of change. You have been
given the opportunity to be
born at such a fun time, so make the
most of yourself, as much as you can, and
enjoy it. You
can do this by doing what excites you the most.
So, is that a good enough answer?
And I want to thank you again for your answer.
Thank you very much. Now, let's talk about the second stage of relationships. [Music] [Music]
[Applause]
First, your relationship with yourself. We can
talk about imaginative relationships, but if you're not
imaginative with yourself first, how
can you be imaginative with anyone? Are you ready to be bold and do all sorts of things?
Each and every one of you.
Thank you very much. So, it looks like we're going to have some fun today.
So, please relax and get into a comfortable position.
Close your eyes if you want to.
And take three breaths. [Music]
Please breathe as you relax and
do the following.
Imagine your body relaxing.
See this red, red, and gold light going through your body. [Music]
Imagine each muscle releasing whatever it's holding you back and becoming softer.
[Music]
Start with your feet and slowly let
that relaxation rise up your legs. Gently
Gently
speak to each muscle in your body. [Music]
Allow it to rise up your thighs, into your stomach,
and then down your arms and fingertips.
Relax your shoulders. [Music]
Feel the organs in your stomach relax.
Watch your heart relax and gently send a stream of energy through your body.
Feel your lungs continue to relax. Exhale,
inhale, and exhale.
Energy is rising up your throat.
Relax your body, and the muscles and bones there
relax and rise. [Music]
Feel your jaw muscles relax. Feel it.
Feel the warmth. Feel it. Feel your
nose and the cavity behind your nose.
Behind your eyes. Feel them relaxing.
Through your skull.
Relax all the way to the top of your head
and feel a brilliant red-golden light
shining from your aura throughout your body. Then
see an emerald-green light shining from your heart. Feel
this green light radiating through
and expanding into every cell in your body. [Music] Feel
[Music] Feel
your consciousness merging with your body as you relax.
Feel
yourself connected and vibrating gently with nature. Feel
your sensitivity and your intuition. See
your worries and anxieties
melt away into the green light.
Now from within,
see the blue light at your third eye. Feel an immense joy as your
body and mind relax.
[Music] Feel the
calm, cool air awakening your body. Feel
yourself breathing as a soul. No matter what
your mind tells you, you are free to do whatever it says.
Feel that your soul, consciousness and body are one and
now you have
just prayed and
are in the right state for that prayer to reach out to the other side.
At the same time, you are in the
right state to receive the infinite love that you deserve. [Music]
See the white light filled with oracle bones shining within you.
Feel this light of infinite absolute perfection within you.
You are now in an ocean of infinite love.
Take three big breaths and enjoy it.
Allow yourself to feel like you are floating in a state of relaxation.
You are in a state of complete love and complete acceptance,
accepting yourself and all others. Now
imagine the following: If you are a
woman, the male side of you is
right in front of you, about one meter
away. If you are a man, the
female half of you is right in front of you. It is
not a stranger, it is the gender different from your own gender within you
and in your physical body.
in your physical body.
If you are a man, look at that part right in front of you.
Whatever you think you are.  It's
okay. What would you be like if you were born in reverse
?
So, feel everything you've learned so far in this exercise.
Feel all the love.
Bring it all to your heart.
Bring it to your water hole.
And send it with a brilliant, explosive
light to your other self in front of you. Let that light
express the self in front of you.
Let that light wash over your other self.
Look into the eyes of that other self.
[Music] And now, feel your body coming back to you.
And move closer to that person. Move closer
until you're about 10 cm away. Move
closer too. And allow your other
self to move closer to you.
Then embrace your other self. [Music] It's
okay if a friendly energy comes out. It's
okay if a sexy energy comes out. It's
okay if an emotional energy comes out.
Allow yourself to feel it all. As you
embrace it, the energy inside you will be
transmitted to the other person.
And the other person's energy will be transmitted to you. The
bodies will not be exchanged, but the energy will be transmitted.
Only the two will be swapped.
Forgive all the misunderstandings you have had up until now. Be
happy to accept all the differences you have seen up until now. Feel the
release and the feeling of having found your opposite side.
Look at it now with joy.
And now your energy
is in that other person. If you were the opposite,
how would you feel?
What would your body feel like?
If you were born the other way,
understand that opposite position, that opposite perspective.
Accept it as it is, and
love it. [Music]
Don't try to change it to how you think it should be, just love it as it is.
Recognize the imagination that it has, and
be happy with it.
Then, allow that energy to
return to your original self.
Even when the energy returns, you have
left something
inside the other person, and they have left something inside you. Remember that.
See the light that shines so brightly within you rising upwards. The
other person's light and your own light are
rising upwards, and the two lights become one.
Watch it blend with the rest of you.
Watch your male and female parts spin around in that one light. It's
like watching an eternal ballet. Feel
the infinity within you supporting and sending love to all of the parts of you.
Enjoy the sensation of it. Take three breaths.
As you do this, open your eyes
and come back to reality.
Remember that you are
blending more with yourself. You
are more one with yourself. You are in
love, in love with life, and feeling love for life, and loving life
more.
And what you give, life gives back as love. You are reborn as a whole
new you, whole new and fresh.
Now let yourself look at nature all around you.
Nature shining before your eyes. It is
all part of the infinite imagination, as infinity expresses itself through you.
Relax and enjoy. [Applause]
[Applause]
Infinite beauty and infinite growth.
New things are always being born and
emerging. Enjoy imaginative relationships with that infinite wholeness. The
expression of the infinite imagination through you.
Enjoy, relax,
and for 23 minutes, just simply
feel that new life, that newness,
from for that
mind. Know that from this moment on, you are
connected to the infinite imagination, connected through your body,
through your mind, and through your consciousness.
Not
that you haven't been for all of us before,
but thank you for reminding us of that connection
again.
So, please stand up, stretch a little,
and enjoy the feeling of your new body,
and give yourself a hug, put your
arms around yourself,
you are worth enjoying.
You are worth enjoying. We are
watching you very much, and if you've enjoyed yourself enough, please
sit down. If you haven't, please give yourself a
hug. And once everyone is seated, we'll move on. [Music] We're
[Music] We're
about to move on to the next stage of that imaginative relationship.
But first, the next
time you do this, or if something comes up, I recommend you do the following.
I asked you to physically express who you are, to
do it with your body.
Open your mouth,
tilt your head back, and
look. Take a deep breath, and then exhale in the
following way.
You have become what you have become,
and you have decided to take responsibility for it.
This sigh is a sigh to let go of all the tiring ways that haven't worked for you until now,
and with that, you have to acknowledge the
many ways you have resisted your natural self. You can do as many
fun things as you want,
but one time
is enough. Your laughter will brighten everything.
In English, this
is called enlightenment, which means to brighten up. Brightening up is
very helpful.
What happens when you laugh is that it
releases and brings you
back to the center.
Tears are a way of releasing
and bringing you back to the center,
but laughter is a way of letting go of the negative things that you have done.
And the sigh is the center in the middle. Allow yourself to
be a more balanced individual. [Applause]
[Applause]
So let's add some ideas, some new thoughts.
Remember, like a child,
you have the freedom to play just as a child plays. It's
very important to know how to play when creating imaginative relationships. And at the same time,
balance the energy of your adult self and your child self.
In the second half, we'll talk about how to
attract relationships to yourself and how to
connect with the person you are now, with the person you have. But
before we do that, let's awaken the child within you, so that you
can move with that child. Children are
full of love.
Children have faith in the positive.
[Applause] Children
know that the universe is beautiful and full of wonder.
In your society,
children often have to forget the things I just said. Children are
taught many times in order to forget the things I just said.
And in this society,
after learning these things, we believe that this is human nature. I
think it's normal to walk around blindfolded, to have tunnel vision. We
argue with others, we try so
hard to protect what we have, and
humans don't remember their true, original quality past the age of three. So
let's go back to that child and merge that child with the adult you are now. Now,
close your eyes once more. Take
three loving breaths. [Music] [Music]
Now,
just listen to the beat of your heart. Mmhmm, Mmhmm,
boom, boom,
boom. No
reason? No reason. It's
okay to laugh, because children
laugh a lot. But just be aware of that sound. It
's an imaginary sound, a sound of imagination,
that's what makes you
laugh. Listening to your heart
is listening to your imagination, your imagination. Listening to the magic of love and the music of love.
This is where all reality is actually created, and
that magic comes back to you again.
Remember, the world is
actually full of magic.
You've already learned that miracles do
n't happen often,
but at first, everything around you was full of miracles.
But a miracle is when something happens that doesn't have a specific meaning, or when
something happens that you ca
n't explain. But to a child, that's inexplicable.
Children understand that miracles are
natural things that happen naturally, and they
happen in an instant. You
might think that miracles defy the laws of the universe, but it's the exact
opposite. [Music]
Miracles are what
happen when nature is allowed to function in its most natural way.
They happen in an instant. You
are all miraculous beings, and the
child within you knows that.
[Applause]
Knowing that you are miraculous
doesn't mean you have to be egoic. Knowing
that doesn't make you egoic.  You
can use that miracle within yourself, when balanced with gratitude, in very imaginative ways. Being
humble doesn't mean doing nothing.
When you give back to others, you
can give in ways that are joyful and fulfilling for you. Children love to give back to others.
They love to receive and they love to give. ONE give,
ONE give,
any give.
Children know that the best way to give is to
allow others to give to
you. [Music] So use your imagination and
see something like this: a green hilltop,
and before you, the countryside
stretches out into the distance. Feel the grass
beneath your feet.
And next to you, holding your hand, is
yours—if you're a boy, that's a girl, or
if you're a girl, that
's a boy. That's you, too. The person holding your hand now
is you.
Right now, you're free from all expectations.
This relationship is very free and liberating.  You
two are enjoying this countryside in the most natural way, without
any demands or expectations from the other. You
stand there, holding hands, and you
can hear that young heart beating. You wake up.
This life is full of new discoveries, and you're
excited about them.
The sun shines on you and the rain is
kind to you. The
sun shines on everyone and the rain falls on everyone, but that doesn't
mean you're less important than others. Everyone
Everyone
is equal to you; they're just playmates.
Your heart shines like the sun again.
For all that you've received from nature, you
shine like the sun from within and give
back.
Now you're fresh and new,
and you don't have to think about it; you
can act quickly, empathize, and laugh your way through life.
Now watch yourself run down that hill to
play in the fields. You
'll see yourself gathering in the middle of a group of children.
So dance, sing, and play there.
Merge that energy
with who you are now and become one. The wild is within you. It is never
far from you.
Now take three deep breaths.
See the beauty of the day.
Feel it. When you're done,
open your eyes and come back to this reality.
But you haven't left anything behind.
At the same time, remember that you are a different person now than you were a moment ago.
You are now ready to create and imagine imaginative relationships. This does
n't mean your relationships weren't imaginative, but it
means you can be
positively imaginative from now on. If you've been positively imaginative up until now, you
can be even more so.
If you're fully imaginative and
have fulfilling, joyful relationships, just
play today.
But there's always more to learn. And that
means we can all
keep playing forever. We
don't know about you, but for us, that statement
makes us very happy.
So we're going to take a short break for about 15 minutes, and
enjoy that.
In the second half, we're going to talk about attraction and how to engage with people through imaginative relationships.
[Applause]
So let's continue.
You're all kids now, so imaginative relationships are
child's play. So let's
talk about attraction. When
you're attracted to relationships, when you attract relationships to
yourself,
when you find yourself attracting different situations, let
's talk about some basic things about that.
[Applause] So, I want you to remember again that your
So, I want you to remember again that your
vibrations create your reality.
You've probably been taught in this society that you're
not perfect, that you're half human, that you're half perfect. So
a lot of people walk around outside and they
send out vibrations that they're not perfect, and they look to other people who are perfect,
forgetting that they are really whole beings.
And as we did in the first exercise, no matter who you are, you
have both male and female energy within you.
When you balance those two, you
can have that vibration as your true, complete self.
When you walk around thinking you're imperfect, you tend to
attract people who share that same belief. [Music] They'll
appear before you, drawn to you,
and let you know that you, too,
believe yourself to be imperfect. A
lot of people in this world
see themselves as victims. [Music] They
[Music] They
carry everything other people have on their shoulders, and they
move from relationship to relationship. And they start to believe there must be something wrong with them. And
what happens in these relationships is that they reflect that they're
bad people, that they're somehow flawed.
Relationships reflect those parts of themselves that they believe aren't perfect, and you
you
can actually change them.
[Applause] So when
negative situations arise in your life, it's not like I'm saying, "You're
stuck in this place." I'm
saying, "You're a
rotten person, you can't do anything about it."  I
'm not saying that you're a bad person. It's just a mirror that reflects what you think of yourself right now,
and it's there
to give you an opportunity to change if you don't like it and want to.
By learning various things in society and believing that you are what you
think you are now, you
do the following: By meeting
many people other than yourself and the person you think you are now, you
can finally find who you are.
By excluding others, you allow yourself to finally find yourself.
You look back at your relationships and
think, ``That wasn't me, that wasn't me, so this must be me.'' If you
really love it, and that's what you really want, you
can do that for the rest of your life, and you can
continue doing it in your next reincarnation and the one after
that. Instead, you can see what you
want to be like here and now.
When you create various relationships because you want to see parts of yourself that you're not, what you
're doing is that you've forgotten your true self,
or you're afraid to face your true self.
Your natural self is a
balanced self.
When you're not being your balanced self, the universe creates things to let you know. When you
don't see yourself as perfect,
when you look outside, you don't
bring yourself fulfilling, satisfying relationships,
or relationships that are very difficult. Being a fulfilling, fulfilling self
attracts
relationships that reflect that.
Even when you're doing something that really excites you, you attract people who still have a lot to learn. You don't know,
know,
what is this person trying to show you when you're so excited? But
sometimes you agree to
help others find that excitement.
So there are times when you attract that person and show them what they can
aspire to be, so they can shine in their life.
Or there are times when you attract others and they show you what they can
shine in your life, the
person they want to be.
When such relationships come, if you
look at them negatively, you might think, "You're
not worthy of me," or "I wo
n't give to you," or something like that.
But you only attract vibrations similar to your own,
so you agree. And then you
have to remember that in that moment, you're attracting the best person for you. That
doesn't mean it's just
one specific person.
Sometimes you can
have relationships with more than one person on the same level.
In our world, all relationships are
mutually inclusive. They
work to enlighten everyone, not to exclude others. The
next point is very important.
All relationships are
enlightening when you face them with unity. Even if you have
multiple relationships, if you
hold secrets and don't love honestly, it
becomes an external relationship.
You have to open your heart and
When you communicate openly and honestly, all relationships
move in a direction that leads to more awareness. And when
you approach relationships with an open heart
and honesty, you can
understand why things are the way they
are in various relationships. Sometimes, when you're in two relationships and you
think about it, you might think that people aren't really related after all.
But when you have an emotional connection, when you feel
something emotional, you often feel like you've known someone for a long time, even in a past life, and you've
done many things together.
And when you become a different tribe, you often try to do
something different from before. You can
really only have one person in your life, and that's possible. [Music]
When everyone is in integrity and honesty, change naturally occurs.
That change is a part of the relationship. It
's the
natural course of relationships.
[Music] So the
fear of change
is the fear of losing something.
But everything happens for the best.
If you understand that there are no coincidences, you have nothing to fear losing.
And if you have fear, fear of change, it's
only when the other person changes that you can
change. It's
only when you can't change. Sorry. People
often think they have to
find that one person in their life, that they have to be with just one person. What
this means is that you want to
change, and the other person
doesn't want you to change.
[Music] So you want to change, to move forward, and
So you want to change, to move forward, and
further and further, and
still want to be with that person.
But they don't want you to change, so they do n't change.
But when you change, and you want the
other person to change in order to be with you,
remember this: If the other person
other person
decides to change, after they change, they're
no longer the same person.
Either way, the person they were before
is different from the person they're with now.
So either way, you're still with the same person. [Music]
[Music]
Therefore, there is no need to cling to someone who has the same physical body. The
vibrations you change will
change, and people will be drawn to those vibrations.
Therefore, there is no
need to waste time regretting that you have changed.  It's not that.
Change is natural,
and you just need to
know that you've been true and honest with yourself. [Music] So let
So let
's talk a little bit about this thing called soulmates.
Soulmates do exist,
but they're just a
matter of agreement. The
person who appears before you is someone who reflects what you need most at that moment.
By the fundamental definition of soul,
every individual that you interact with with any particular moment is
your soulmate.
Because in that moment,
in the way that's best for you, in that moment,
in society, it's possible to have a lifelong relationship with one person. You can see
what you want to see in those two people as you grow,
but we don't expect that it has to be that kind of relationship.
And it's only when you're on the
verge of death that you realize you've been with that one person for your entire life.  If that had happened, no
one else would have come. Thinking about it now, I see, we
had a proper one-on-one relationship, and no
one else would have come. Right
now, we live in the present, and we
trust ourselves, so we
don't expect relationships to be a certain way, and we do
n't regret things like, "I did this, I did that, or I shouldn't have done that." So
by always living in the present,
and being true to yourself, you will
attract the right person to you,
and that person will be able to
reward you for the new you you want to become,
and you
can help them become the person they want to be.
That's the purpose of relationships.
Relationships are like looking in a mirror; you
see a different side of yourself. But that doesn't mean you have to look at someone who is doing something completely different and think, "Are they
doing the same thing?"
or "This is really a mirror of me."
But it's an agreement that the two of you made a long time ago. How you
serve each other is
exactly what the other person sees as prosperity.
There are times when you are drawn to someone who is already learning what you need to learn.
In those cases, you will teach that person
what you have already learned out of your love.
All that is needed for that relationship to happen is trust. So
what do you do? I want
you to become and shine like a shining crystal.
When you are a clear, shining crystal,
nothing can make you waver.
You will always shine and be able to radiate to others.
When you are that kind of crystal, a
crystal, all light from other people will
pass through you. The only
exception is if you yourself choose to absorb this light. Everything
else passes through. If there is
negative light being emitted by people around you, but you
choose not to absorb it,
it will just pass through and not
affect you.
Even if someone is sending you negative vibrations,
if you only have positive vibrations,
you will interpret those vibrations as positive. You
will change them into positive ones.
That's what unconditional love can do.
It's literally unconditional love. Remember that.
So, use your heart and all the
power you have to accept it as much as you can and
enjoy your relationships.
So, you can
support them in the following ways: Notice the things that the
people around you want to do that are truly
exciting, that they want to do with unity and excitement, and let them do them.
Support them so that they can do those things.
When they want to do the exciting things they want to do, you
can do all sorts of things to support them.
You can notice things that they enjoy and teach them about them, give them information, and give them
gifts that they enjoy and that make them even more excited. You
You
can support them in how they become.
If the people around you
don't bring fear into their lives, you can
support them a lot.
But that doesn't mean you have to be strong. When you become strong, you can generally become
more independent.  The reason why
this happens so often in society today is because we're
all totally dependent on each other.
But if we become stronger, we
can... But what I want to say here is
But what I want to say here is
that you don't need to lean on anyone. You don't
have to rely on anyone, but
please support others. By supporting others, you
will also be supported,
always.
Total dependence is a
negative way of looking at mutual support. It's the
part where you demand from the other person that you can't live without them, that's the negative part.
Strangely enough, when you truly become independent
and realize that it's okay to be independent on your own,
the two of you will be supporting each other forever.
You can stay connected to each other. When you decide that your relationship has to be a certain way,
then that means you don't trust the true relationship between the two of you.
Something that commonly enjoys together is
together is
one way to truly imagine a relationship.  A
good way to do this is to do
something you both enjoy as a joint project. You
can do this with two people, supporting
each other in the things that excite and make the other person the most happy.
Then those people will make other people happy and
excited, and you
'll create a big, happy family.
All in our world, every individual is
married to every other person, so everything that
everything that
happens on our planet is happening within marriage. [Music]
On a physical level, on a personal level,
there are of course people who are parents to who, but as adults,
we all become one.
When we have that unconditional love and support for everyone, that helps us all connect and connect
telepathically.
When we have imaginative relationships, it always
deepens the telepathic connection.
Telepathy isn't reading what someone is thinking in words. Every
single person has their own unique vibration.
When you start to love someone, you start to identify with that person.
This is what we call a connection of love or a bond of love.
When you begin to align yourself with the other person, your
vibrations and their vibrations and frequency numbers gradually match. They
don't have to be exactly the same, but they become very close. [Music]
When two people's vibrations become very similar, they start to
take in information from the outside in the same way. In
other words, they
become so similar that they start to think alike. [Music]
When there is unconditional love and a very strong connection, they start to think the same things at the exact same time.
So you might think that two people are trying to read each other's minds,
but that's not the case. They're
that's not the case. They're
just starting to think the same things. That's
telepathy. [Music] So
[Music] So
telepathy isn't about
extracting information from the other person and feeling satisfied. It's when
you and the
other person become like mirrors, and a lot of things are happening between you at the same time. [Music]
[Music]
But that doesn't mean you lose your individuality.
In fact, the exact opposite is
happening. You're expressing everything you can within a relationship.
That's when you can have it strongest,
and when you can trust it and go with the flow. [Applause]
Because then you're
fulfilled and you're becoming the person that can satisfy the other person,
so no matter what changes happen between you,
you won't have that fear that you'll be cut off.
And no matter what changes, no matter who you are, no matter
how much you change, the
things you need will come along and you'll always be satisfied. Relationships are
Relationships are
EXPrel, TRUST, and
INSPIRATION. So an imaginative relationship is when you're
So an imaginative relationship is when you're
relaxed and inspired.
Simply put, you're just two people learning how to
play together, and you're both
you're both
learning to love each other unconditionally, as much as you can. So relax,
take three breaths, and close your eyes. Think
back to all the meditations you've done so far. [Music] You've
done a meditation on being yourself and loving yourself. You remember being a child in the person who shows you who you are, and in your first
roommate.
[Music]  You
can play with all kinds of knowledge,
and you can really enjoy yourself in infinity.
Imagine this in your imagination: Imagine
yourself as one facet of a crystal.
Imagine that
[music]. You are
floating in space,
surrounded by stars. A
very strong light is shining from the center of the water form that is you. It
is a beautiful, clear crystal. So you feel that this light is passing through
you and going outward, and being
seen by all the stars around you. And
then,
all of you now see all the stars coming towards you. You understand
understand
those that all
others towards them.
You all know a lot about time and space. As the
stars get closer and closer,
from each star's perspective, it
looks like all the others are heading towards them. The
integration of all of this can be seen in every single one of them, wherever you are.
Just as the stars get closer and closer, you
can see that each star is just one facet of a beautiful crystal, just like you.
Your crystal has many sides and
many cores.
And there's another crystal that's coming up, and it
has a matching side and a matching angle.
Now all those stars are coming towards you, and there's nothing
between them. [Applause] And
you feel such joy as you watch the stars come closer and closer to you. So
open your heart of light, open your heart.
Now you know that completely opening yourself up, surrendering, is not weakness, but eternal, infinite strength.
When you're wide open, you're opening yourself to infinity. When you open yourself to infinity, you're connecting with infinity.
When you connect
with infinity, when you're in contact with infinity,
you're connecting with infinite power. [Music]
[Music]
So now, open your heart, open it up, and open it
to the crystals that are rushing towards you. They're coming, some
coming, some
may be slower than others, but you'll see them match up perfectly
with the sides of your crystals in the order that they come first, and they'll
match up more and more, and as they come
closer and they touch you, they'll all cling to you, they'll cling to
you, they'll
cling to you, they'll match up perfectly.
It gradually grows larger and larger.
All the crystals you imagined, all the crystals,
and those stars gradually come together to
form a large master crystal, a large crystal that
shines with such brilliant light.
[Music] You
are now one aspect of that multidimensional crystal. You will notice one thing: this large
crystal has the same shape as you did at the beginning,
only larger in size. This
includes the completeness of what you had before.
[Applause]
You yourself are this large crystal, just like that crystal. When you
realize that you are this large crystal, you will realize that
you can touch any facet in any order you want. [Music]
[Music]
Now, when you look at it, you will see sharp lights emanating from every facet,
intersecting, and every facet
communicating with every other facet.
Looking from where you are in the center, you will
know which facet you are communicating with. And now your light in the center is shining brighter
and brighter. At the same time,
each facet, every facet there, becomes more and more filled with light.
[Applause]  And
with each breath, with each inhale and exhale, you
feel the energy of that large crystal grow bigger and bigger and bigger.
[Applause] It
gets stronger and stronger,
until you think it can't get any stronger,
and then it gets even stronger. Then it explodes into an infinite number of
countless faces, and
each facet floats off into space again.
But that space won't be empty like it was before, because a
miracle will occur there.
All. Because each and every
crystal that goes flying will become, one by one, a
large crystal just like the one before,
and fill the universe.
And each and every large crystal will
intersect with the surrounding crystals, and
wherever you look, you are within every crystal, and
every crystal around you is
within you.
You are one now, always one,
always together with countless shadows of yourself and countless mirrors that reflect and show you,
forever. Every single
facet supports the whole. The
whole is just one facet of each.
You are supporting, supporting [music]. Everyone here is spinning as a big crystal, spinning
in eternity. [music]
[music]
You are the final crystal of impermanent love.
Take three big breaths and
wake up in a new reality.
Remember, your previous reality and your
new reality are completely
different. You are a refreshed being,
reborn.
Your energy is now lighter and
so powerful.
Your energy is so powerful,
yet so light. It
is an energy that fills those around you,
and you are filled.
You are filled, and
when you are of service to others, you fill those around you.
So, stand up and relax a little. Stretch out and
fill the universe.
Fill yourself with energy.
Fill this physical form of yours with energy now. Be happy and
and
feel joy in this.
Now, please sit down.
Now, if you want to ask a question, please go ahead and do it.
My heart was FAS. My hands and feet went
numb as if they had been touched by electricity. After that,
my IC was Run and my
FEET were so cold to the touch that it
was... That's what happened.
You have now become
super conductive. Your society has now discovered something called a super conductive substance, and that's
no coincidence. What does "
super" mean? It
means that when your consciousness as a collective consciousness is
finalized, it becomes super conductive.
Sometimes the temperature drops from there.
How about that? Please continue. And then,
you were resolving old ideas, old emotions, and all sorts of
things that had been arising. You were
dissolving them. All the
things that you had suppressed during your lifetime are now coming to the surface. You
can think of it
like labor pains.
Imagine that you
are breathing new life into a new you. You
don't need to entrust it to anyone. You are letting the
new you, the child, within you, come out.  Let them
help, and
you will gain another ally.
Once you understand that you are being supported by eternal energy, it
doesn't have to feel like pain. The
new you will emerge physically,
when you actually give birth to the baby, and emotionally, and as various
parts of your energy
emerge, remember that you are connected to eternity. You don't
have to go through pain.
Let your guides help, too. They are a
part of you. They
won't do it for you, but they will remind you of things so that you can do it.
Let the universe play the role of Saba. Then,
labor won't begin.
How's that? Is that okay?
Toward the end of the last thought, it gradually began to appear, and then my
stomach and lower back started to hurt. I was shaking, went away towards the end of the meditation, but then my stomach and lower back were painful. I
just said that. These are labor pains. This
is the time when new life is about to be born. Got it?
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Sumiko is in tears. [Music] It
means you are releasing yourself from negativity,
releasing your old ways, and
and
empathizing with that infinite love.
For balance, tears sometimes
come out as a flow of gratitude.
Release and release always feels
good. I wonder
if that's a good enough answer.
Yes, thank you that still in the places from the and that always.
When I said tears are negative, I didn't mean that you
're still in a negative place when you're crying. I
just meant that
those things are coming out of the negativity
and being released. So, what do you think? Is that clearer now?
clearer now?
Is it kind of clear? Well, okay. What's not clear? [Music]
And it's cleansing. You
can do this from within yourself too. You can say that you're releasing toxins from within yourself. Gratitude
Gratitude
is when you recognize the infinite support you have. The
infinity that connects you to infinite beings.
When you feel connected and realize that your life lives effortlessly,
gratitude is when you recognize and rejoice that you fit perfectly into this imagination. That's great
How are you?
Thank you, willUS
All. When you have empathy, first of all, your
emotions become very even. You
reach a balanced state.
In other words, your
emotions don't go up and down
too much.
So, what's often mistaken in society here is that empathy is
sometimes seen as cold, because some people
feel that way when they can't see that the other person is telling them to be like this and
feel the same way. So, empathy
empathy
can't be achieved unless you first have peace of mind within yourself.
It can be expressed in joyous ways, but it can also be
also be
expressed as an acknowledging
statement. So
when you feel that kind of empathy, you
can express it in a very, very balanced way.  You
can, and you can just know that state, you
know it in a very quiet state, and it can be expressed that way.
So, in other words, empathy
can also be expressed with the word serenity.
People who don't understand this well feel that serenity is a state of separation or isolation from others. True serenity
True serenity
is a state of connection with everyone, where there is nothing negative in it. It
is when you know that everything is worthy of impermanent, unconditional love and is equal.
Most people in this society think that
emotions have to be exaggerated, like in a melodrama. I
think I understand now. Thank you very much for
joining me, and the others
in the back. But
not only that, of course, you yourself should be
your own best guide and hold hands together. Yesterday and
Yesterday and
today we had a workshop, and the dream from the night before came inside.
So today, my hands were wet again, and they were small. Yesterday and today, I attended work, Dream that Fit, meditate, handstarted. shakingJustRememberIedFromABikeletosmallbicleyyetPEReI
guess I found a part of myself that was a child,
and then I
remembered it and I realized
that I could use the negative energy I was carrying and adjust it. I think
that was probably my goal and I think guide to know thatIhandleNEyintoApositiveONEatleastIcanhandleallgoodThat's
very good, after all. I like
dreams, but I
think I feel like I'm feeling outside, and dreams
are TRUST my dreams
GU
Why can't I go and
need And why do you
need my opinion on this? Iiid
Iiid
Why? Try to
define coincidence. You're
adding judgment to your own judgment. I know
now that miracles are very natural,
but of course there are negative coincidences and positive
coincidences, which one do you prefer? Have you
noticed that you create them yourself?
Because there is no
Q. Coincidence is not an accident. It
's not something that happens to you. It's just a reflection of what you already know.
Thank you for giving me this opportunity to convince myself of this. It's ok to take time, so
enjoy it. Do
n't be so hard on yourself.
For those of you who choose negative things, that's
fine, but if you don't like it, change it. If
you're choosing negative things and attacking
yourself for making those choices, it will
take longer to go home. I'm
just suggesting that you do it this way, so
decide for yourself.
Thank you very much. How about time?
Next, yes, that felt good,
but [music]
where are you?
This is called the channeling chakra, so when you
start to interact with a broader consciousness like this, you may feel pain or resistance around here. That
's fine. Then just trust yourself. It won't linger
for too long. In
particular, try not to
think that your vibration is lower than the vibration you're currently accepting. When
there is friction and resistance,
pain will arise, but this friction and
resistance is a sign that you are different from what is happening now, that there
is a difference.
When you define yourself as a wind, you will encounter resistance.
Know your strength well,
and remember that struggling does not make you weak, and
surrendering to it does not make you weak.
Whatever energy or consciousness you are in
contact with or communicating with,
your consciousness will inevitably enter that flow. So just
let it flow gently. In the end, it
is your part. It
just flows by. This
is a common symptom in this society, in your society, at this time. Right now,
energy is rising and falling in your back.
Parts of your spine that have become misaligned due to holding money can
begin to return to their original position when new thoughts arise, causing pain.
Straighten your body and
inhale directly.
Align the hollow within you with this and resonate with it. Make a sound as you breathe. Do
n't just inhale from the front, but inhale so that it comes from the back and goes forward. You
don't need to open the floodgates and cause a flood. Just
play with yourself, and get used to it. [Music]
Feel yourself immersed in a wonderful, beautiful emerald-green light. The
emerald light is a
symbol of change in this time of transformation your world is passing through. With each new energy,
new energy,
plant your feet extra firmly on the ground.
Become a crystal of the water element that extends further out across this planet. When we disconnect ourselves, when we
disconnect from nature,
when new energy comes in, we short out within ourselves.
When we feel that we are only a small part of this whole planet,
or that the whole planet is
merely a reflection of something much larger than ourselves, we can channel
all of the incoming energy
into the whole planet. Then you will
no longer have to do so much yourself,
and you will be able to draw energy from that whole.
Many people feel energy in their groove, in their
chakra, which is connected to their future self.
Use the same technique to
soften and balance your energy. And breathe.
And breathe.
How's that? Did that help? Do you have any questions?
Bashar, you often
tell everyone in your world that they are married,
but have there ever been any cases in your history where there have
been any possessive relationships?
Well, we have been through the same things as
your society. We have been more or less one, and have done various things as one, so it has not become as extreme as in your society.
But I would like to look into that kind of thing in detail later. Why did I
say that just now? When I said I would
find out, that was just a joke.
I was just being possessive and talking.
I have one more question. There was a time in our society when men and women were not even friends. It
's fine now,
but I would like to think that it is okay for some people to be friends with men. There
are still others who are different.
Hey, in your society, how have you dealt with that kind of thing?
How did that change come about?
In our society, there have been possessive things,
but there has never been a time when there was sexual insanity. I understand. That's fine. [Applause]
[Applause]
Or you could think about it like this:
Your society shows this inequality
very clearly.
Remember a time when you saw your masculine and feminine sides in your mind? You were
born with both sides. So you
can treat yourselves equally.
Now, whether you are a man or a woman, there are two sides
within you: a male and a female. When you see these two sides within yourself as friends, you can also be with the
various people around you who look up to you,
whether male or female. What do you think? Is my suggestion okay?
Thank you for being our friend. Sirin: Yes, when the breath comes
in at the time of the bridge, a very powerful
energy comes in, and then the bridge and the
breath come together. Then all of that breath
goes into the body.
Please wait here.
When Power comes in,
this is also a common occurrence. When a lot of
energy comes into the person using this channel, the
people around them also
receive that energy. The
energy that comes in or shines out in this way has a certain frequency.
So, if you are at that frequency,
When you feel like you're trying to match it, or align yourself, you can feel that same warmth within yourself.
Sometimes, people get sleepy trying to align with that energy from a different direction. Some
people feel faint when they try to resist that energy.
But I just want to say
that the energy you're feeling isn't our energy
directly, but your own energy aligned with it.
We're just bringing the frequency of our civilization
here. It's up to you to decide whether to align with it or
not.
But with the energy you have, you're
always aligning with it somewhere. That's why I
always say that our
energy is
n't necessary to raise your energy, because you all have
that energy within you.
So, I just want you to use these exchanges as examples and models and
learn to use your own energy in that way. So,
does that answer your question? I
want to say thank you to everyone here. [Music]
Thank you so much for strengthening this relationship, for the fact that we and you are one. I'm so grateful that
we've both been able to come together like this and be so imaginative.  We would
like to send you our eternal love. A
blessing and a gift. You
are a huge gift to us, and we are
very grateful that you have shared it with us. [
Music] I hope you
have a day filled with love and emotion.
How was today? [
Applause] Thank you
so much for coming today,
and thank you to everyone who came this week. There were many people who helped us
make this happen, and I would
like to thank them as well. [
Applause] And I would
also like to thank you all for making it such a fun time for Erika and me to come to Japan.
Thank you very much.
[Applause] OG