[Music]
I will greet you all this day of your
time as you create time to exist how are
you all this day of your
time we once again thank you for the
co-creation of this interaction which we
will [Music] [Music]
entitle redefining
Dogma now the idea that we have
perceived going on your societ at this
time is that there are the creation of
what you may call many factions of
belief systems with regard to your
relationship to Creation
itself in what you call your typical
format expression of this relationship
you use the word religion to explain and
express your relationship to
Creation now in what you call your new
age awareness
what if we may have a little bit of fun
with the term May rerm the Neo Geo
awareness upon your
planet you are now beginning to
understand different ways different
methodologies of expressing your
relationship to Creation rather than
through what you may term the
ritualistic or dogmatic Expressions
termed religion now first allow us to
underline very importantly we are in no
way shape or form invalidating
anyone chosen methodology of relating to
Creation all tools are valid as we have
said many times and will'll always say
if you find that what you call your
particular religious aspects are what
work for you in expressing your relation
to Creation then by all means utilize
them until you find for yourself in your
own good time that they no longer
suffice but you may also find that in
your desire to
redefine what you are coming out of what
you are used to hearing of in terms of
religious expression in terms of
redefining it in what you may call a
more metaphysical understanding a new
age understanding there may be some
difficulty using the correct terminology
or terminology we shall say that feels
correct to you that feels appropriate
that feels like it has the same impact
to the terminology that you were brought
up to understand so we will endeavor to
be of assistance this day of your time
in creating an example and a suggestion
for how some of the older terminologies
can be transformed and redefined into
newer terminologies that as you say fit
the bill now we will utilize one
particular example simply because it is
probably the most familiar example to
your particular culture at this time in
general in no way shape or form by using
the following example do we mean to call
out any one particular religious
persuasion as being any more correct
than any other we simply use it because
it is a matter of common knowledge to
you all now you will find that because there
all now you will find that because there
is a high degree of redefining going on
in your Society at this time because you
are beginning to look at things in a
different way and new way you will find
that there is a great deal of
polarization taking place between the
individuals on your planet that are
willing to redefine and the individuals
on your planet that want to in your
terms stick to the old terminology so
there is a great degree of focus going
on that sometimes we have observed
create some friction between the
different factions that you create
yourselves to be one group May insist
that another group should be looking at
the idea this way another group should
insist that the former group be looking
at it that way each group thinking they
are correct they are more right than the
other group now the idea more often than
not that we have observed being
expressed in your Society usually deals
with what you call your Christianity
your Christ Consciousness
awareness you will generally find that
the phrase that certain individuals will
more often than not utilize to determine
your particular alignment to Creation
will be the following phrase most of you
have in all likelihood heard the phrase
many times it usually goes as follows
quote do you accept Jesus Christ as your
lord and savior unquote now all well and
good but it leaves wide room for
interpretation in many different ways
before we Supply what to us would be
perceived as a redefinition of that
statement let us first refresh
everyone's memory as to some definitions
about what the elements in that
particular statement me at least from
our point of view we have talked off and
on about the idea of what you have term
the Christ Consciousness as being from
our point of view the collective
consciousness of your entire planet what
could be called the world Soul the world
Spirit In other words the Christ
Consciousness or what some individuals
may call the Buddha nature or any other
name is the
compilation of all the individual
consciousnesses upon your world every
world every Dimension every civilization
has its own group Consciousness which
would be its own world spirit in our
ancient language as we have said we have
called ours shakana you call yours
Christ Consciousness and a variety of
other names now that Christ
Consciousness that world Spirit knows
itself because it is conscious as a
singular individual as a singular entity
knows itself as a single entity but also
knows itself as the combination of of
all the entities you that make it up but
to see to the Christ Consciousness it
always must be both it must be both
polarities it is never an issue of is it
this way or that way which is the real
way that it is is the Christ
Consciousness one entity or is it the
combination of all of us it is both it
always must be both for anything that
you can perceive in the format of a
polarity lets you know right then and
there because you can perceive it as a
polarity that both sides must somewhere
at the center blend and be both equally
true and equally valid so first and
foremost we would shall we say
replace the idea of the term Jesus
Christ with the term World spirit for to
us that is what it is in interacting
with your Society we do find that it is
necessary now I'm going to put this
extremely colloquially it doesn't
necessarily mean that the way I say this
is the way you are used to thinking of
these terms
but our civilization because it comes
from another realm another dimension
actively seeks permission from your
world Spirit to interact with its
individualized components so that we
ensure that we are acting in the most
integrated possible way to assist you in
your true Endeavors your true desires
rather than as you say stepping on any
Toes or spilling any beans or unwrapping
any presents before they need to be
unwrapped so we always as you say double
check with the world Spirit to align
with the pace align with the pulse and
the synchronicity that takes place
within that world Soul before we
interact with the components of that
Civilization therefore we may now
continue with the idea of redefining the
terms Lord and Savior now in your
Society because of the way you have
interacted socially politically for many
thousands of years is the term being
used to represent the Christ
Consciousness Lord in a sense is
accurate however again it has many
connotations which do not
necessarily act as a pure representation
of what the idea of the world spirit is
remember that from our point of view the
idea of the Creator does not really rule
per se in the way you're used to
thinking of that term over its
components it doesn't need to if a
Creator created free will it is a
contradiction in terms who all of a
sudden want to control the idea of the
components that have free will the idea
of being a lord in a sense as far as we
are concerned is simply a representation
of the
magnitude of it's involvement with you
and your involvement with it in other
words it sets down the general themes
the general patterns the general
atmosphere in which you exist as a
society but it does not rule it does not
judge as a lord as a king as a ruler
would in what you call your
physiological political system it simply
presides shall we say observes shall we
say gives birth to the overall patterns
the overall atmosphere in which all the
probable realities you can experience
physically are manifest from it
determines the overall laws of the
vibration reality in which you reside
but it is a benign a rather passive
determination a rather passive structure
the structure is simply placed within
that reality and all the individualized
components make use of that structure in
whatever way shape or form they so
desire with their own individual Free
Will so since each and every individual
within the world spirit is a component
an extension of that world Spirit it can
be said that the world spirit is an
overs soul to the entire world in that
sense therefore you could say that the
term Lord could be replaced with the
idea of the word oversoul which simply
means that you are deriving your pattern
you are deriving your cues for the
smooth operation of your reality from
the oversoul of which you are apart from
which you are
extended savior once again has to do
with the separation you have created
within yourself from your connection to
the infinite it has a lot to do with the
idea that you have created guilt
frustration separation judgment and
invalidation upon yourself so that you
think you need saving from some abysmal
pit into which you have been flung but
the idea now that you are recognizing
this in your new age awareness is that
you have always been in control as we
have said many times it is simply that
you have forgotten that you are an
aspect of the infinite forgotten that
you're always is in control forgotten
that you are the individual creators of
your own reality and the combined
creators of your mass
Consciousness the idea that you need
saving implies that you are not an
aspect of the infinite and do not
contain internal self-empowerment which
you do so you do not really need saving
but perhaps because of the state that
you have created for yourselves now and
then you might need a little guidance
and so instead of the idea of looking to
what you may call the Christ
Consciousness as a savior perhaps you
can look to the Christ Consciousness as
a guide as a mirror as a reflection as
that which gives you the vibration to
key off of to find that you can be
aligned with that vibration and have
everything in your life run smoothly by
synchronizing with that particular
frequency the idea that you so-called
surrender up to the idea of God or the
Christ Consciousness in no way shape or
form means that you are giving up
responsibility for your Creations it
means that you're actually taking full
responsibility it is simply that your
Society is so used to experiencing
control by experiencing resistance that
when you finally actually have true
control with no resistance at all you
don't think you're doing anything you
think you've given it up you think
something else is running your life now
because it is absolutely effortless when
you surrender what you're doing is
taking back full responsibility for your
creation in life for the creation of
your total reality and full
responsibility for being a cocreator as
you were made in the image of God as you
say a co-creator with creation when you
do that and when you align and
synchronize with the flow with the
guidance that is always radiated to you
then your life is effortless and it
doesn't feel in that sense like you're
actually controlling anything but you
are so the idea once again of someone
coming up to you now and saying do you
accept Jesus Christ as your lord and
savior can to some degree be replied in
the following way I accept the world's
Spirit as my over soul and my guide it
is the same thing the idea however of
saying it that way removes the Judgment
removes the invalidation removes the
disconnectedness and the separation that
you have created from the idea of
creation itself and puts it squarely
back on an equal term within you so that
you can go through your life consciously
knowing that the world's spirit in a
sense watches over you but at the same
time you play just as important a part
in sustaining and supporting the
existence of the world Spirit by being
as fully realized a being by being as
fully realized a component as you can be
by Taking Back full responsibility for
your lives and exercising full conscious
and effortless control in the creation
of the reality you prefer use this if
you wish as an example for how to
redefine and transform all of what you
may call The Old World terminology if
that will assist you to see yourself in
a clearer
light simply that is our sharing with
you this day this evening of your time
before we begin interaction allow us to
share with you also one more thing a
little bit of a meditation so you may
all close your eyes and take three deep
breaths this meditation will be for the
purpose of creating a little bit more of
an alignment with the world spirit with
the overso with the gues that all of you
are an aspect of as each and every one
of you now take a leisurely and peaceful
breath allow yourself to remember that
breath bre is life life is breath it is
the fundamental vibration a fundamental
signature vibration anytime any of you
want to know what your signature
vibration is and that means your
signature vibration is your unique
frequency relationship to Creation
anytime any of you want to know what
that is take a deep breath in and let
out a tone let out a
sign that is your particular vibration
it does not even have to last very long
all you have to do is feel it all you
have to do is hear it all you have to do
is find that range wherein you feel most
comfortable and you feel your bodily
form resonating with warmth with
invigoration with life with potential
with promise with probability that's all
you need to do and as soon as you do
that in that instance you are 100%
completely aligned it is that simple now
what you do from that instant forward is
up to you you can become disigned again
if you wish but you do not have to as
soon as you have that signal as soon as
you have that tone you are aligned
anytime you find yourself having created
situation where you are as you say at
odds where you are perhaps frustrated
where you are perhaps a little anxious
take a moment take three deep breaths
and then on the fourth one take a big
deep breaths and let out the tone let
out the sigh of release the sigh of
alignment the tone Of crystallization
and you will be realigned it is that
easy for never never never was it
written anywhere in any text in any
fabric of creation that it should be
deemed in any way shape or form
difficult for you to realize and fully
understand that you are expressions of
the Christ Consciousness too it was
always made to be the simplest of things
to allow you to remember your connection
to the infinite and be because it is
such a simple thing that's why it was
designed the way it was because anytime
you've had enough anytime you've been
struggling too much anytime you've been
trying too hard the only thing you need
to do and the first automatic reaction
you have is to sigh that's how you get
back to center it is the first and most
basic Primal release and centering
mechanism you have use
it we find you for your willingness to
interact at this time you may open your
eyes at your own
pace finding within you that degree and
level of comfort that now expresses who
and what you are as a realized being and
an aspect of the
infinite and at this timing we extend to
each and every one of you once again our
deepest appreciation for the co-creation
of this interaction in the way that your
imagination and our imaginations have
deemed it shall be we thank you for
allowing us to experience the gift of
your Consciousness and in return once
again I ask you now how in what joyous
way for me may I be of service to
you sharing good evening Bashar and good day
sharing good evening Bashar and good day
to you thank you for this
opportunity I hope that my question will
be of service and of help to others
always always always always always it
will it is not something you have to
hope about you understand
thank you oh thank you speak up and be
bold so that all may share your gift I
need some guidance out of the bismal
Abyss that I have flung myself that you
talked about bismal abys yes all right
what is your definition of an abysmal
Abyss um just a little background
information all right 8 years ago I got
married moved to Japan had a very
unhappy marriage but was able to cre a
very wonderful life in Japan for myself
right I moved back to Los Angeles with
my then husband and had the idea of
opening an art gallery all right and my
husband and I separated which was a good
thing but it was very painful all right
I then opened the art gallery on a
shoestring budget which was August of 85 all right
budget which was August of 85 all right
and when I opened the doors I was all
out of money and repeat
that when I opened the door of the
gallery I was all out of money all right
continue okay um so for 3 years now I
have struggled um broken through all sorts of
struggled um broken through all sorts of
fear barriers so the struggle was very
productive I realized and appreciate the
struggle it's built a very strong base
for me it's made me it has helped me to
feel empowered and now you are tired of
struggling how did you
guess um I think I've had this
conversation before yeah
but now I've really had it with the
struggle really had it before you were
just faking all right now you've really had
faking all right now you've really had
may I ask you a personal question yes
are you sure yes all right now how do
you know you're not faking it this time
because I've started to fantasize about
running away from what I've created and
doing something else doing something
else is this something else more
exciting than what you've
created no then why are you running to
it because I don't want to struggle
anymore and the other seems like it's
not a struggle as much and what would
that other thing
be well the fantasy is that
um all right it's something along the
lines of being a um a special events
coordinator at um the LA County Museum
museum for example or for accidental or
some company or entity that I would work
for receive a salary and not be out
there on why do you think you are
attracted by that particular kind of an
expression what do you think you will
learn in that particular type of an
Endeavor well it would be a lot of what
I'm doing now except I would be
receiving a paycheck and I wouldn't have
to struggle but what would you be
learning how to feel supported
I mean about the particular job what
would you be
learning would you be learning anything
different by doing the job that way than
you are learning by having your gallery
no are you sure I I don't I'll give you
a hint I'll give you a suggestion a hint
thank you you would be seeing how other
people do it
successfully thank you understand yes
you would be taking your queue from them
so you can apply it for yourself if
doing the gallery is something that
excites you the most perhaps you would
be doing the thing that you have not
really allowed yourself to do as fully
as you could have which is going to the
individuals that are already doing it
successfully and finding out how they do
it understand yes by letting it rub off
on you by associating with their
mentality with their vibration by
watching their attitude by watching
their actions and mimicking them which
you haven't yet
done understand you're right you have
Role Models All Around you whenever you
want to do something very exciting look
at the individuals that are already
doing it and copy them mimic them in
your own
way then you will have the same results
that they do so what you have now done
as far as we perceive it is cleverly
giving yourself an opportunity to spend
some time being surrounded by them so
that some of them will rub off on your
vibration so that then you will arrive
at a point where you will finally say
aha now I understand what it is I needed
to do my whole attitude was not the
attit ude of being a gallery owner an
excited Gallery owner now I understand
what it is to be that because I've seen
it I've been surrounded by it now I know
that I can be a successful Gallery owner
because I've allowed myself to create a
role model that I can pattern myself
after you understand yes so it is up to
you you can use that as a tool if you
want for now but just remember that if
doing the gallery is what really excites
you the most then what you're actually
doing now is simply doing what you may
call your homework to find out who you
really need to be and in what way you
really need to act to be able to know
beyond a shadow of a doubt that being a
gallery owner is who you really are
which you're not really sure of right
now understand it can get you back on
track if you want to do it that way you
follow me yes I there's another part to
that oh all right what is the other part
okay the other part is is that a year
ago I um mimicked the the other Gallery
owners and I moved to a much bigger
space I really put myself out in the
line I put a business plan together I
got investors I have created a wonderful big
investors I have created a wonderful big
space yeah on North laa and it's and it
has grown and it's successful but but
I'm still struggling ah will you repeat
the first thing you said when you began
the other part I mimicked the other
Gallery owners I got a big space right I
what put myself on the line right why
why do you think that you had to think
that you were at
risk because I was still doing it on a
shoestring then you did not mimic the
other Gallery owners because they do not
go into it with the idea that there is a
risk that they're putting themselves on
the line they do it because that's who
they are they don't give a second
thought to the idea of what you call
risk that does not exist for them in
their mind if you carried with you the
idea into that endeavor that you were
putting yourself out that you were doing
something that was risky then you not
acting like the gallery owner you want
to be you still had a belief system that
what you were doing is not truly who you
are because if you knew you were doing
what you truly are all about risk does
not enter the equation it doesn't even
occur to you you understand right does
that help you no why not well at each
expansion stage okay I I felt like I had
put myself out in a limb and then I grew
into that yes well that's one way to do
it you can do it that way but feeling
that you're doing it that way is what
makes it take so
long understand that you are not at risk
do you not understand that if you are
doing the thing that is truly
representative of who you are then you
Naturally Fit within the support system
of the
universe you understand what we are
saying I understand what you're saying
are you sure you understand what we are
but um but but but but but what it goes
in spurts and starts is what I'm trying
to say I'm supported I feel like I'm
supported to a certain degree and all of
a sudden nothing do you need the
threshold of believability
test what does that mean it means that
if you have a particular image of
yourself as you would really like to be
as compared to who you are now you sit
down in a meditative State and you ask
yourself with absolute honesty absolute
razor sharp laser clear
honesty how long do I really believe
it's going to take to be
that person give yourself the benefit of
the doubt by starting with a time you
know is more than enough time to be that
person do I believe I can be that person
in 20 years no problem that's more than
enough time do I believe I can be that
person in 10 years absolutely do I
believe I can be that person in 5 years
well maybe as soon as you find yourself
hesitating that is how long it will take
to be that person find out why you would
believe it would need to take that long
in your meditation ask yourself what
definitions you have bought into that
would make it take that long then
redefine them if you don't prefer those
definitions as soon as you redefine them
take the test over again ask yourself
now with the new definitions in place do
I now know it would not need to take 5
years absolutely that will be as you say
a piece of cake with the new definitions
in place can I allow it to happen in
four years yes no problem 3 years
absolutely 2 years well maybe start over
again let yourself understand that at
every stage you arrive at you are given
an opportunity to examine more beliefs
that you may be carrying with you in an
unconscious State you can change them
you can redefine them but take advantage
of them and they don't have to take so
very long to allow the next phase to
start up it is only because you allow
yourself to become set back depressed by
the fact that you arrive at another
stage another level and have to go
through that process again that you make
it take longer than it has has to simply
because you are invalidating the process
itself you as individuals as a society
have spent so many thousands upon
thousands of years separating yourself
from creation and creating so many
different points of view and belief
systems that it simply takes a little
bit of time for you to review all the
various hundreds of belief systems
sometimes contradictory belief systems
that you have with within your
Consciousness because of the very fact
that you have created an unconscious
self which doesn't need to exist you
spend time examining and delving through
and exploring that unconscious self But
realize you're still doing all this
exploration in one lifetime even though
you spent many hundreds of lifetimes
creating the separation and the
different belief systems to begin with
so you're actually proceeding quite
rapidly do not invalidate yourself do
not allow yourself to feel tired in that
sense the only reason you would feel
tired is because you're fighting your
own natural self-chosen process let
yourself understand that all you have to
do every time you arrive at that stage
of review is to use it in a meditative
State and not say Oh I thought I was
doing what I needed to do you were doing
what you needed to do do not belittle
yourself do not belittle the process do
not be frustrated and stamp your feet
and have a tantrum the idea is to allow
yourself to say I have arrived at a new
Step oh joy oh joy that means that I am
now about to break through to a new
belief system that I can now go on to a
higher level and I can do this in a very
accelerated way when you approach the
process that way you will have the
support and the abundance you need to
take you through the process are you
following along yes is this being of
assistance to you yes so relax lighten
up all right okay one last part of the
question please okay so in my mind I
gave myself three years I thought it
would take 3 years to build my business
where I would be where I would feel
really confident one moment stop okay
you do not have to set an inv
validational structure in that way in my
mind I gave myself 3 years if I take 3
years in 1 second I'm a failure what you
can say and this is why we talked about
the threshold of
believability allow yourself whatever
the appropriate timing actually is and
if you feel you desire to take time go
through the threshold of believability
and see if you will allow that if you
don't then trust
this the amount of time you find
yourself leveling out at is truly in
every way shape and form right now the
amount of time you really do want it to
take because there are things you're
going to discover in that amount of time
that you don't know about yet that you
are going to need by the time you get to
the time where it will manifest and you
will have appreciated knowing those
things when you get there because if you
get there without knowing those things
you will not be able to handle the thing
you dearly want understand mhm so
relax it doesn't have to take that much
time does that help you mhm are you sure
yeah it helps me yeah thank all right
can I finish the question thank you
sorry takes so long
all right
um I forgot my question
good okay so 3 years in business October
the 8th yes I'm sorry August the 8th
what I said october8 GE I don't know I
don't know okay maybe you were being
honest no no I opened my doors August
the 8th ah 88 88 yeah I opened them
88885 yes okay so so so okay that's 3
years so I'm ready okay and what I'm
ready for is I really want some
financial assistance I want an investor
a big investor oh I see come to my
business all right well have you
advertised for one no why not how do you
advertise for that put it in the paper
yes do you know of the analogy that
occurred with the physical Channel
regarding that very thing no what the
physical channel has in your
terminologies briefed you all on the
project that is of excitement to him yes
right well all the financing was
acquired by putting a little tiny ad in
the paper which
paper your
choice but understand this it is
absolutely representative of what we
have always discussed with you because
you are so busy flurrying around and
what you think you ought to be doing
very often you overlook the obvious
avenues that are already provided
to be able to put out in the world who
you are so that other people know you
exist so they can respond to you
understand mhm so Define very precisely
and very clearly who you are what you
want and let the other individuals that
is the other side of the event find you
so that they can serve you even as you
serve them but if you don't advertise it
who's going to know you
exist understand mhm have fun okay M
what that's it
okay thank you very much fun thank you
Sher hi bashard and to your good day I
say hello to all of your friends from
Las Vegas all of my friends from Las Vegas
Vegas all of my friends from Las Vegas
yes all right they love you very much
you want me to say hello to them no
they're saying hello to you ah thank
you I want to ask you a question about
uh the dolphins all right the Dolphins
yes well not the Dolphins a dolphins
dolphin Al yes okay you told me that she
was a Maui dolphin basically okay and
lately I've been very um drawn to go to
Florida and go and swam with the
dolphins at Dolphin plus and now I'm all
excited about going to Australia all
right have a good time thanks a lot M
you're welome can you tell us anything about
welome can you tell us anything about
monkey
Maya I have a friend of mine that thinks
that it's a feminine
Vortex no Vortex is exclusively f
feminine or masculine in that sense an
individual will pull from The Vortex
whatever process they are going through
most exclusively you understand okay now
the idea that what you call wild
dolphins freely interact with humans in
that area is an indication that it is a
very relaxed State and can put you
squarely in touch with the ability to
blend the masculine and The Feminine
energies to allow you to be more emotive
to be more intuitive to be more
telepathic in that area with them it is
a free zone in that sense that they are
willing to take advantage of to have
interactions with all of you in so you
can go there and interact with them in
that way and allow your wild nature to
be reflected by their wild nature so
that you may discover many more aspects
of yourself then you might otherwise
discover by interacting with dolphins in
what you call captivity you understand
yes does that help you yes but I'd like
some more deep information about what's
going on with the communication because
so many people are becoming interested
now in the dolphin and me and is but you
know what is going on why should I tell
you what you already
know do you wish to share it with
everyone we have discussed this many
times with many individuals about the
overall idea of the sharing and the
blending that is going on so that the
Dolphins can teach you how to
play it is one of the things that your
individual cell and your civilization
needs to remember most importantly how
to play how can we use this information
to share it with with everyone more play
use your imagination and figure out a
way to share it with them in a playful
way where's your imagination gone
perhaps it's already in Monkey
Maya maybe you should catch up to
it that's what it's been feeling like
then go that's what it's been feeling
play play play play play creatively
understand all right thank you thank you
very much have a good time say hello for
us I will sharing
please the next person be ready hiar and
to you good day one moment remember that
when we talk about the ideas of using
your imagination and playing we're not
talking about acting childish but child
like there is a difference and the idea
is not that we are simply discussing
attitudinal changes that have nothing at
all to do with your day-to-day
physiological reality attitude is
everything everything because your
perspective determines the type of
reality you get learning to play and
exercising your childlike Powers will
create the entire Earth to be literally
as a playground in which anything can
occur at any time anywhere any when
continue that's a good topic for me
playing U oh all right let's play then
okay um Bashar I spent I feel like I
spent a lot of My Life um confused and
in a lot of conflict oh all right is
that fun for you uh no it has not been
very much fun what would you rather be
doing uh I would rather not be confused
uh uh I did not ask you what you would
rather not be doing I said what would
you rather be doing I would rather be in
harmony than be in Conflict what is your
definition of harmony do you have a
picture that you can describe that goes
along with the term
Harmony Harmony is that feeling I get
when I just took three deep breaths and
heard my tone that felt like Harmony so
you now know one way one tool that will
allow you to create Harmony Anytime You
Wish yes yes do you have any other tools
that will do it for you um here it comes
once again are you doing in your life
the thing that would excite you the most
I do not believe so Bashar you do not
believe so all right why that one of my
questions why not why not why not
because I'm confused about what what it
is that excites you
yes oh all right but remember that when
we talk about the idea of doing what
excites you you don't necessarily have
to have a career in mind you can simply
do at any given moment with Integrity
the thing that excites you the most at
that moment that you're capable of doing
something about and that will be
sufficient to take it a step at a time
you understand yes I understand that now
my the question I had when I came up
here is that because of some things that
were going on in my life I think that
many times I found myself doing the
thing doing things other than what
excited me the most Fair doing some
things that excited me but that uh did
not have a whole lot of Integrity
associated with them all right Fair up
now is the time to blend the two
together now is the time to blend the
two together my question is I really
don't trust myself
and I don't know whether I'm acting with
Integrity or not sometimes oh all
right do you
believe that there exists either within
you some sort of a mechanism or around
you some sort of a guide that will at
some point even if you've already acted
outside of Integrity give you an
understanding that you have done so and
therefore act as a corrective
mechanism yes but my experience with
that force is really limited because I
spent a lot of time trying to
anesthetize him I see all right do you
understand that you are self-empowered
to create the reality that you desire
yes all
right what specifically is it about
yourself you do not
trust oh One Moment One Moment let me
rephrase that in the way that I would
actually say that
naturally what is it about yourself that
is not preferable that you trust more
than what is preferable because it is
always a matter of trust you are never
not trusting doubt is simply trusting in
something you don't prefer so what is it
about yourself that you don't prefer
that you're willing to trust more than
what it is about yourself you do
prefer boy you've confused me a little
there listen with your energy and you
will understand completely what I am
saying trust is always occurring you are
never not trusting if you stopped
trusting in something you would not have
an experiential reality at all positive
or negative it's always a matter matter
of trust what you call doubt is not an
issue of lack of trust it is a complete
trust in something you don't prefer so
why would you choose to trust in
something you don't prefer as opposed to
using the same trust in something you do
prefer because it is never an issue that
you are not trusting you are never not
trusting in
something understand yes yes I
understand why would you pick something
you don't prefer to trust in as opposed
to something you do prefer that's the
question because I think that I received
a lot of messages for my whole life
about certain things that I was supposed
to achieve or supposed to do all right
but have you heard us talk about the
idea of what a habit
is
no the idea is that generally speaking
by definition a habit is something that
you do that you don't know you're doing
once you know you're doing it you don't
really have the Habit anymore you have
to be Beyond it out of it in order to
know you had it so for you to
say my willingness to choose something I
don't prefer is the product of something
that I was taught a long time ago if you
know that it is the product of something
you were taught a long time ago then the
thing you were taught a long time ago no
longer has any power over what you
choose to do now because you know that's
what it was from the question is who do
you want to be now now that you know who
you don't want to
be understand yes I understand now that
you are willing to admit that perhaps
the things that you used to be taught
gave rise to the things that you don't
want to do what is it you do want to do
knowing knowing the following thing that
now that you know you don't want to do
this knowing what you do want to do is
sufficient to replace what you don't
want to do and if what you don't prefer
happens again you chose to believe for
your own reasons that it
should and if you say that it happens
again because of something you were
taught you yourself are choosing to
believe that that's a natural result
therefore you are using it as an excuse
when you say you don't want to
understand yes I understand so what do
you want to
be you know I have to say I'm not sure
yes you are what do you want to be all
right one moment I'll use the facility
you seem more comfortable with what do
you not want to be maybe we can do this
by process of elimination and see what's
left okay maybe we can maybe we can not
want to be what do you not prefer I'll
tell you I thank you see how easy this
is this is much easier for me all
right um two years ago I went back to
school I went into law school and I'm
about 2/3 of the way through it now I do
not want to be a lawyer
[Music]
all thank you very
much your objection is
sustained what else do you not want to
be or will that suffice as an overall
example wellow that that's that's kind
of example number one now since I'm in
the middle of creating that and and at
the same time realizing that I don't
prefer that all right now I cannot and
will not tell you what to do however I
would strongly suggest that since you
now know beyond the shadow of a doubt
that you don't want to be a lawyer that
you stop trying to be
one and do something else
okay well is there anything else you do
not want to
be uh there's nothing I could really put
my finger on that I do not want to be
well then now that you have labeled and
named the primary symbolic thing you
don't want to be now that you are
perhaps maybe I'm assuming willing to
let that go willing to see yourself
stopping trying being a lawyer what do
you see that could fill the space you
are now spending trying to be a lawyer
be doing okay I see two things that can
fill that space thank you one one is
something that I used to do which is to
create businesses all right do you find
that enjoyable well uh without bringing
in the experiences you have had do you
find the idea exciting yes thank you
what is the second thing the second
thing is writing ah all right now do you
really prefer in any way shape or form
to add to attach qualifications on
either of these things that would make
them appear less desirable than you want
them to be would you run that by me
again all right do you want to find
excuses to not do
them no then don't do not attach any
negative definitions to those particular
Endeavors no matter what experiences you
have had no matter what experiences you
think you have to have do not attach a
definition to what you know excites you
that you don't prefer to
attach understand yes does that help
you yes that helps me and and okay one
short thing is that over this um a lot
of different things have happened to me
over the last few years and
sometimes I change a lot in a very short
period of time all right and I would if
if I knew that I was going to feel the
same consistently for at least some
period of time I would feel much more
comfortable doing what you say all right
well that's easy would you like to know
how to do it yes choose to feel that way
consistently it is a choice how you feel
you know because how you feel is a
reaction to what you
believe yes but
but I for 2 years because I felt the
initial excitement yes for 2 years I
chose to feel very excited about my new
career about going to school you chose
to stop feeling
excited I didn't choose to stop feeling
excited I think I got all of a sudden I
got into situations where I looked at
the situation I said you know I really
don't like this all right but that's a
choice the idea is to understand that
many times you will trct yourself into a
specific Endeavor with excitement but
you don't have to take into that
endeavor the idea that you must take it
to fruition in the way your Society
logically thinks you must many times you
will get out of that what you need to
take the next step even if the next step
is in what appears to be a completely
contradictory direction if the next step
is what excites you as much as the
excitement you had going into the first
Endeavor then it is not contradictory
and the excite is what lets you know
that what you're experiencing is
literally a continuation of the first
step even if on the surface it seems to
be a 180° polarized Endeavor it doesn't
matter it's the excitement that lets you
know you're on track not the surface
apparency you follow me absolutely
follow the excitement that is always
what Rings true for you does that help
that helps a lot thank you thank you
very much for this exciting discussion
Court [Music]
[Music]
sharing hi Bish and to you good
day um by trade I'm aych One Moment One
Moment yes do you wish to read the next
few names do not you do you want to read
the next few names no we're okay all
right continue Thank You by trade I'm a
psychic by trade a psychic all right and
during one of my my sessions I happened
to P your energy one day all right and
scrolling through the park one day one
day I found thear exactly um I shared
that part of myself and you with my
client and very exciting to both of us
all right now remember one thing yes
anytime any of you tap into our energy
you are tapping into the energy of my
mainstream Society okay continue all
right um my question is that I felt I
needed to ask you through Daryl because
I consider him the finest Channel I have
ever seen all right seen many uh whether
or not I should continue in this vein
with you doing this or go on my Mery
way you are
more in every way shape and form
more then shall we say
allowed to tap into our energy stream
anytime you
wish you are more than
welcome to funnel your
aspect of our vibration through you your
version of our vibration through you if
you feel so inclined if that is what
moves you if that is what excites you
you always have our
permission if however you feel that you
are more excited doing it another way
then you have our permission to do that
but you do not need our permission to do
that you are shall we say I'll put it
this way you are rational and cautious
enough to be able to
know that you will take care in making
sure that the information that comes
through you will always be put to the
best benefit in a positive way of this
we have no
qualms so it is up to you
as far as we are concerned we would
always be
honored but it is up to
you understand I do thank you does that
it does very much thank you well thank
you very much by the way by the way back
up back up back
up don't be in such a
hurry there is
also One Moment One
Moment a feminine energy in our societ
that is willing to work more directly
with you and two or three children that
think that they would have some fun as
well working with you all right thank
you very much for thank you very much
sharing a pleasant dreams by the
way yes hi Bashar and you good day I'm
Jeffrey yes hello
Jeffrey I'm studying Alternative Energy
technology yes socaled free energy free energy yes
yes socaled free energy free energy yes
I had a question to to you regarding
gravity oh all right okay uh Galileo
several hundred years ago made a
statement that is the Cornerstone of
physics right now Corner Stone yeah yes
it's off in the corner over there so he
said Falling
by yes I see
it falling B fall falling bodies
accelerate at the same
rate now that's Cornerstone of physics
do do you think that that's accurate or
or inaccurate
or it will depend of course upon the
medium they are in you are talking quote
unquote in a vacuum how about in a
vacuum yeah
okay in what you may call Loosely 97% of
the circumstances in your Universal
reality that would to some degree be so
however there is always a loophole
always a doorway from one dimension to
another in any universe and in certain
cases you will find what you call the
exception that proves the rule in your
particular Universe there can be
manifestations in your Universe where
that is not so there is an underlying
principle that is misunderstood in many
different ways about what you call
gravity is
the idea is not so much a force it is
not so much the
idea of even quote unquote an
effect it is hinged very strongly to the
concept of time in a way that your
scientists have not
understood your scientists have
difficulty in allowing gravity to fit
into what they call their unified field
Theory because they have not completely
understood the full ramifications of
gravity's relationship to time when they
understand gravity's relationship to
time they will understand that there is
a lot of variation and fluctuation
taking place within an event such as two
falling bodies that allows the overall effect
bodies that allows the overall effect
that is perceivable by your senses to
make it appear as if gravity has the
same effect on both of them that they
fall at the same rate but within the
event on what you would term quantum
levels there are a wide range of
fluctuations even fluctuations that are
completely the reversal of what you
would call
gravity in other words seen from one
level what you may call the macroscopic
level it would appear as if they fall at
the same rate but on what you would call
a microscopic level to the extreme they
do not do you think that say a carbon
ball and a lead ball would fall at the
same rate
again it depends upon the level to which
you take the
measurement you will find generally that
in a certain degree of your macroscopic
Universe they will but taken from the
point of view of measuring from certain
other quantized perspectives they will
not so what what would what would be the
Principal Factor determining uh a
different rate of acceleration the
relativity of time the different
reference systems that are occurring
from one perspective to another when you
unlock the understanding that you are
playing a consensus game a consensus
reality that the rules you see are only
rules because you generally agree that
they should be then you will understand
that what you are seeing is not actually
representative of a true structure of
creation but only an arbitrary
manifestation of your consensus reality
relative to time and space they do not
have to fall at the same rate at all but
generally speaking you perceive that
they do because of what you think of
time and space as
being so you're saying is normally if I
took a test and I dropped a lead ball
and a carbon ball for instance just
picking two things from an elevation you
think that they would hit at the same
time that is generally how you would
perceive it yes however if you were
willing to become a little bit well what
your Society calls insane that is not
necessarily how you would perceive it no
well we have made a test from a 2,000t
elevation and and they drop it
significantly different uh rate of
acceleration yes then perhaps you are
getting a little more insane
you see the idea simply is is that what
you are calling the paradigms of science
will change over time even as many of
the things that what you call your
Galileo and your Isaac Newton held to be
true are now considered to be the
sheerest Fantasy by your modern day
scientist you will discover again that
the idea of falling objects has nothing
at all to do with the principles you
think it does has nothing at all to do
with what you typically call falling
objects you do not even understand what
the idea of motion is yet in your
Society once you begin to unlock that
you will understand that if you see two
objects hit the ground at the same time
it is because you are putting that
particular arbitrary consensus upon it
that it should uh what do you think it
is the unifying equation do you think E
equals MC square is is valid in a sense
what do you mean in a sense well in a
sense that it describes one particular
framework it is true that what you call
matter and energy are manifestations of
the same one thing then what does c squ
have to do with it
it implies in your terms of mathematics
the amount of equivalent energy in a
particular particle of matter but the
idea to understand is that the true
unifying principle is consciousness
itself Consciousness how would you
define gravity question
okay if you wish I'll be
brief gravity is an
effect of the intersection of your
Consciousness with a particular frame of
reference you have created the
particular definitions you have created
of space and time it is an effect it
doesn't empirically exist at all it is
an effect a side effect of your
definition of physical
reality it is let's say a timing
sequence effect understand what time is it is the
effect understand what time is it is the
effect of a focused Consciousness
without the focus of Consciousness it
doesn't exist
neither would gravity neither would
space it is in a sense an attraction
that is representative to some degree of
the structure itself as your Einstein
put it the geometry the structure
itself of what you call your particular
Universal reality but
structure structure implies intention
and intention implies Consciousness so
gravity is nothing more than an effect
of the random patterns of Consciousness
that you use to create your Universal
reality understand I understand what you
said I appreciate that well thank you
very much let us put it very simply this
way you have gravity because you desire
to operate within a particular frame of
reference wherein all of your tools
remain in relation to each other gravity
itself is the effect of your desire to
have relationships between different
physiological vibrational
objects thank
you thank you
sh much love to you bash and good day to
you one moment one moment we are
involved right now with the Channel
Through The Format you would call
automatic writing to explain in much
greater detail the workings of gravity
time and space when that work is
completed it will in that sense be
published and if you are aware of the
goings on of the channelings you will be
made aware of when the more detailed
version of that explanation will be
available to you continue thank you I
would like to discuss um speak up so
that all may share be
bold I would like to share the idea or
discuss the idea of communication
communication I would like your
definition of that
please communication yes
communication is a
reflection of a
vibration and an
assessment of a preference to align or
not align with that
vibration to realize the
self in an accelerated
way does that help yes that's what I'm
not really doing all right why not
um will you do me a favor yes say the
word communication communication now
will you do me another favor yes say it
this way
communication communication now this way communication
communication all
right go ah ah no no no
ah ah feel it in here
ah ah oh thank you very much now how did
that feel when you went ah a little more
open yes and how does it feel when you
say communication it feels like it normally
communication it feels like it normally
does that that I am not letting myself
out no all right then say communication
communication
communication all right one more time
communication communication well
well
communication oh all right what is it
you wish to communicate and to whom do
you wish to communicate
it don't know yes what [Applause]
do you have a
fear I figured that must be what is at
the base of communication I can
communicate with people on a superficial
level no all right but when I want to
communicate what I want what I need what
I expect with Integrity yes it takes me
hours or days to get it out oh I can
teach you an idea that will allow you to
get it out in approximately 1 second
would you like to do that yes are you
sure you would like to do that all right
one moment let us make an
adjustment approach the physical
Channel now in no way shape or form do
we mean to imply this in a subservient
way but would you please go down on your
[Music] knees I I'll think it that way all right touch Channel
touch Channel
hand left hand right hand
left touch with
Right Touch with
left touch with right
take your hand put them on your
heart how do you
feel a little lighter a little lighter
yes all right open arms wide wide wide
how do you feel
later bow head down let neck stretch
stretch stretch stretch
slow put head up put head back back back
back slow
fo head right right right right slow far
as you can left left left slow far as
you can deep breath in thigh out out
can deep breath in thigh out out
out deep breath in thigh out out
out deep breath in hold it
f th out out out right right hand pound
1 2 3 likely sorry I didn't see pound 1
2 3 likely on chest pound 1 2 3 pound
pound Pound three yes 1 2 3 I did let me
hear it all
it all
right left hand 1 2
3 open arms wide wide
[Music] wide breathe in through mouth deep
breath breathe out through
nose breathe in through mouth deep
nose one more
[Music] time stand
up twist right keeping your feet planted
firm twist upper half of body right
right right right slowly far as you can
left left left slowly far as you
can back forth back forth let arms
dangle Loosely throw a head back go H
H
ha haa H
ha bend that waist keep feet straight
dangle dangle
down stand
up do you like oh you may go back to
microphone do you like to hug to touch
yes understand that your words your
intention your meaning many times taken
much more quickly by individuals when
you play face a gentle hand on shoulder
a gentle hand on heart a gentle hand on
neck yes understand yes I do
communication flow electromagnetically
more Super conductivity your intention
your meaning will get across you do not
need as many words as you
think understand yes how do you
feel Freer thank you very much pleasant
dreams and thank you for opening the
doorways that you have you'll begin to
accelerate rapidly now I know thank you
so much oh thank you so
much always thank you for applauding
[Applause] [Laughter]
[Laughter]
yourself hello bash and to you good day
uh my name is anik and I'm from
Brussels yesterday tah and Sean helped
me to release uh an entity by the name
of JN who had been speak up speak up so
that all may hear who had been my
husband in many lifetimes all right and
did not want me to come into this life
without him so he may have tried to
strangle me at Birth causing pain in my
in my throat and my neck and my whole
white side that always feel um much
colder than the other side and with less
energy all right I also half in half out
of what you call physical and
non-physical reality you are in a sense
straddling the line between physical
life and non-physical life it is our
suggestion that one thing that can help
you greatly is to understand you will
always remain attached to the level of
non-physical spirituality that you need
to but we would suggest that you do
something very strongly physiological
that you enjoy to ground yourself in
that way and to create an
electromagnetic flow through you that
will not cause what you call the
paralysis the numbing effect of the cold
you follow
me you follow me yes no maybe maybe
maybe all right you are straddling the
line between physical life and physical
reality in other words your focus your
focus is half in physical life and half
in non-physical reality you follow me so
far yes are you sure I think so your
Consciousness in that sense is
split you are in a sense shall we say
now I do not mean this derogatorily
please do not take it that way but you
are dwelling on aspects metaphysically
that you do not necessarily need to
dwell on so heavily you are separating
yourself you are cutting yourself in
half you are allowing your power a
portion of your power to come from a
disassociated place and time the idea of
another time all your power is here now
the only reason it would seem not to be
is that you have chosen to believe that
it is not you are splitting yourself in
half by fixating and focusing on the
idea to some degree a little bit heavily
of the other lifetime it isn't that we
are not saying that other lifetime
recognition does not serve you but
understand those other lifetimes and the
experiences in them do not in any way
shape or form control you you are one
electromagnetic flow let's use the
feeling of coal to create a super
conductivity within you are you willing
to do a little bit of a meditation right
now yes all right close your eyes as you
stand take a deep breath and in your
imagination imagine the following
thing imagine right now that you are
surround Ed your body is surrounded by a
crystallin transparent blue sphere of
brilliant electromagnetic blue white
light do you see it yes all right feel
the vibration of that energy feel that
the sphere is full of energy that it is
interpenetrating every single cell of
your body feel the
coolness the swiftness the flow of
electricity and electrons and
electromagnetism going from head down to
toe and up from toe to head back and
forth up and down feel a white light
pulsing through you up and down up and
down and in counterposition in
conjunction with the coolness in the
sphere feel that the pulse going through
you is more of a white light a white
hotl allow the White Ring the white
sphere that goes through you from head
to toe and back again like a yo-yo to
feel very warm and to warm you up to
Center you and balance you and to
clarify all systems and structures
within your body are you feeling it
going up and down up and
down are you feeling it mhm do you feel
a little bit warm yes do you like the
warmth yes allow yourself to get to the
level of warmth that you feel is
comfortable and then as soon as you find
it is at a comfortable level then
maintain that particular frequency of
the white light going up and down do not
let it go any faster than that just
allow it to pulse at that rate generally
speaking you may find that it is
synchronized to what you would call your
heartbeat do you find that mhm all right
then just sit with that for a moment
just float with that for a moment keep
your eyes closed imagine the blue sphere
around you the white light pulsing
through you from head to toe at the beat
of your heart hear the sound of your
heart as the white light goes up and
down feel it for a
moment now take in one large deep breath
and as you do so imagine the entire
structure collapsing to go within you to
fit you like a second
skin and as you breathe
out understand that that second skin
that energy is now locked to you it is
your thermostatic control it is your
ability to regulate your environment
through your thoughts through your
desires through your preferences it is a
tool it is there use it and allow
yourself to let it Focus you in the
present feel grounded feel your feet on
the ground feel that your spirituality is
ground feel that your spirituality is
intact but also your physicality your
vibrancy your
earthiness you follow me
mhm how do you
feel how do you
feel good do not think about it how do
you
feel do you have an
answer no I just
no I feel
yes how do you
feel warm all
right do you feel like crying no all
right do you feel like laughing yes all
right then do
so One release is as good as
[Music]
another now choosing the laughter
shows that there is nothing negative in
that sense to
release that you knew what you were
doing when you made compacts contracts
and agreements with other individuals
and that the actions of those other
individuals in the past have spurred you
to your present understanding of self
and therefore fulfilled a positive
function Let It Go it has served you you
are standing on your own two feet you're
your own individual there is nothing
blocking you you are clear so laugh and
be merry and be happy you have the
ability to live the life you want
regardless of anything else that has
ever occurred you understand yes does
that help you yes thank you pleasant
dreams to you thank you One Moment One
Moment One
Moment one little suggestion for you
tonight when you are about to go to
sleep imagine imagine imagine
this your feminine side your masculine
side see them blend together into one being
see them blend together into one being
and then see that one being holding in
its arms a baby a child which is also
you rock the child nurture the child
Comfort the child and unconditionally
warmly and happily loves the child and
let the child feel that happiness and
that warmth from you
then go to sleep and see how you feel in
the morning all right all right three
nights in a row 1 2 3 and that will be
sufficient you will have a whole new
childhood all over again all right all
right thank you very much thank
you [Music]
sharing hello bashard to you good day I
i' would like to know if there are any
specific past lives speak up speak up
speak up I would like to know if there's
a specific past life that my daughter
and I had my daughter
Terina that has made this life a Rocky
one and
what way I could make this life more
compatible it is our perception in this
particular case
that there was a life [Applause]
[Applause]
wherein and I will not say who played
what part but one
individual was expected by the other
individual to be able to do a certain
thing and in not being able to do that
certain thing the other individual lost
their life the individual who was expected to
life the individual who was expected to
be able to do the certain
thing truly did not act outside of
Integrity truly could not in any way
shape or form have been expected to save
that other individual
however shall we simply say the belief
systems of the individual that lost
their life were such that they held it
against the first individual not getting
to them in time not reaching them in
time allowing them in that sense to
perish that instilled a type of momentum
a type of lack of
trust however it is
understood that you are inseparable in
that way that you have had many
lifetimes together that particular aspect does not
together that particular aspect does not
necessarily
play as bigger role as you might think
even though it was brought in in our
perception into this life there are some
other aspects most of which are for the
aspects most of which are for the
purpose of allowing you to break
through this particular kind of of a
barrier ceasing to think that you must
be responsible for other people's
Realties you follow me so far yes for
you can only be responsible to other
individuals you cannot be responsible
for them and constantly berating
yourself for feeling that you should be
responsible for what happens to another
individual will only immerse you in the
same Meer in the same Rocky Rapids that
you were immersed in before where the
scenario was played that you ought to
have been responsible for their life
then which you were
not understand yes does this help you
yes it does one moment how do you feel
right
now I feel good because I uh knew this I
felt it and it's just confirmation one
moment may I engage you in a
conversation that is primarily out of
curiosity for moment yes well thank you
very much if you were to use your
imagination right now and you were to
suppose this does not mean it has to be
this way if you were to suppose that you
would have another life after this one
what do you think you would like to
do what do you think he would like to
be use your imagination
um a pilot of a spaceship thank
you that's where I know you
from thank you for fulfilling my
curiosity thank you
Pasar at this timing you may all enjoy a
short break we will resume contact in
approximately 10 to 15 of your minutes
how's it going great
[Applause] I think we forgot to mention that you
I think we forgot to mention that you
need we need quiet when Daryl is going
into the altered state and coming up we
forgot to mention that but thank you for
your cooperation you got it pretty quick
and also again uh later at the end
Refreshments are out here please have a
10 15 minute break when I call you
please come back cuz we can't get
started till everybody's seated and
quiet
right say continue
sh hello bash and good day to you um the
bottom line of my question bottom line
all right is um basically that I have
decided that I just totally wish to
surrender to my higher self and just be
a pure channel in whichever way I am
supposed to be to be of service to
humanity on this planet and you know the
way that is yes um by doing what excites
you the most I I understand that it's I
understand that um one of the things
that has been coming up
is some very strange physiological
changes in my body yes
um number Ness and tingling uh
throughout um my whole the whole of my
arms my fingertips my face sometimes
extending down like into the ovaries and
all right now sometimes sometimes when
you go through energy shifts you may
feel them electromagnetically in that
way as you become more highly conductive
we do always suggest because of the way
your Society exists the way your Society
is structured that if there is anything
happening with your physi logical form
that you are uncertain of that you do
always first Avail yourself of the
belief systems that already exist within
you in other words if you believe in the
idea of doctoring You may wish to find
out first whether or not they can
perceive any reason for what you are
experiencing if you go through this
process feeling that it might or might
not be necessary and then you still find
that there is no explanation in terms of
what your Society can offer you then
usually more often than not it is
representative simply of the energy
changes you are going through because
many times when your civilization
experiences shifts in its energy level
it will still translate them in
physiological terms because you are so
very physiologically oriented and the
difference in energy will pass through
you like electricity through for lack of
a better term a resistor and because
there may still be some resistance
within you due to what you have been
taught to believe about change and the
nature of change then you may find that
that resistance that occurs May manifest
in the way that you call pain or aches
or various physiological phenomena such
as you are describing you follow me so
far yes I follow you um one of the
things the the only thing that medically
I have been tested medically for
everything and the only thing that was
found was um a pituitary and
thyroid uh malfunction a very slight
pituitary and thyroid malfunction one
moment what are they describing as a
malfunction they they say that um um
there's um what is called a
hypothyroid condition um just very
slightly which is created by uh
malfunctioning of the ptary gland which
was created from um too much stress and
fear over the past few years all right
um have you alleviated to some degree
that tension and the stress now uh yes I
have but the
symptoms still continue and one of
things that is happening to me is that
I'm opening up psychically to a point
that um very often I become like a
sponge for other people's pains and
emotions all right all right and um
identification is one of the things that
may strongly begin to occur in
individuals that allow themselves to
become far more sensitized than they
used to be however it is only your
definitions the definitions you are
bringing with you from the old self that
allows you to have to feel the
identification in a painful way you do
not have to necessarily take on the
symptoms in order to identify with them
in a more detached sense what you can
begin to learn is a type of attached
Detachment a kind of compassion an
overriding overall compassion that
allows you to understand what they are
going through without necessarily having
to adopt it personally you follow me yes
I follow you um uh
I'm learning from different people who
are Healers and psychics how they how
they do that will become clear as glass
clear as Crystal transparent to the
point where the energies that other
individuals are emanating can pass
through you leaving the knowledge but
not the symptoms you understand yes
become clear absolutely nonresistant the
only way as we have already said you
would actually pick up upon the
symptomology itself is because you have
resistance within you or fear within you
about what is you're identifying with in
them no fear unconditional love and
compassion will make you transparent
enough to allow those emanations to pass
through you harmlessly you follow me yes
I follow you um is there do you perceive
that that there is any physiological way
that I could heal the the thyroid and
the pituitary condition cuz um I believe
that it it is in link with the The
Awakening of the chakras and the psy
sensitivity yes you can if you wish now
if your imagination desires to change
when we are about to suggest let it
because your imagination always knows
what it is doing best for you we would
suggest that you think in terms of what
we have discussed already this evening
to some degree the idea that the
electromagnetic medium in which you are
all mentally immersed is usually
symbolically represented by Blue Light
imagine cool soothing flowing smoothly blue
cool soothing flowing smoothly blue
light blue gel if you wish a thick blue
gel infusing those areas filling your
cellular structure allowing them to
adjust to be buffered to allow them to
assimilate to the timing in the tempo of
the rest of your body allowing the rest
of your body to assimilate to the timing
and Tempo that is now being given off by
your glandular system understand that it
is your glandular system that controls
the enzymatic and endocrine functions
that biochemically speaking are linked
to psychic functioning to your
connection to higher self the glandular
system is the last sensory physiological
level before non- physicalness alt
together so that is why some of them
have become a little bit activated a
little bit imbalanced rebalance them by
homogenizing your entire system by
filling it with a homogeneous blue gel
of liquid light and allowing all your
cellular structures to blend and balance
in that system by dissolving in that
system until you are just the gel itself
then with your Consciousness
recrystallize your body out of that gel
knowing that at that point every single
component in your body is far more
balanced and perfectly represented and
in synchronized harmony with all other
components of your body do that exercise
as many times as you deem is necessary
but it will not really take very long
because you will find it will create a
super conductivity within you you may
start to feel some other effects you you
may feel a little bit dizzy you may feel
like you're spinning a little bit you
may break out in what you call a cold
sweat or a hot flash but that's all
right these are other symptoms that are
simply representative of throwing off
that energy of letting yourself balance
and assimilate the extra charge you
follow me yes I do um do you perceive
that there would be anything
nutritionally that I can do to help this
physically One Moment One Moment let us
pass through another suggestion and then
there may be an opportunity to perceive
what you have asked we would also
suggests that you can help balance
Yourself by allowing a flow of healing
electromagnetic energy through your
hands towards other individuals by
performing physiological healings and
balancing them allowing them to balance
themselves you may also create a balance
within yourself if you allow yourself
simply to feel the flow again in a
non-resistive way you follow me yes set
up a current that flows so it doesn't
just come to you and stick doesn't just
go to them and stick but a current that
flows you follow me do you mean like a
handson like yes you can do it that way
yes you follow me yes um my parents were
both mediums and channels and healers
all right then perhaps follow their
example in that way now
nutritionally one
moment perhaps to some degree what you
may call vegetables high in water
content would be of assistance in
clearing you out a little bit right now
you follow me um M what you may call the
water CEST you follow me yes one
moment a
few well that will do for now from us
you will receive more information
nutritionally from your own higher self
and your own guide synchronistically you
will run into the information that you
need relatively soon okay we thank you
does that serve you yes thank you very
much thank you
hello Bashar have you good day I'd like
to talk about imagination you go right
ahead I'll
listen um I see a lot of pictures in my
mind of the way I would like or can see
my life going oh all right okay I want
to understand better what the role is of
those images in creating that reality I
see all right now I do not mean this in
a derogatory way but it is evident that
you did not participate in the recent
Workshop that we gave
because the idea is specifically hinged
upon how to use in three steps the idea
of your imagination in determining what
excites you and how to manifested
physiologically I will repeat those
three steps
briefly the idea of what you call the
workshop format is available to you and
you can peruse the details at your
leisure later on you follow me okay step
one identify what it is that does excite
you and create the imaginary scenario as
you have already pointed out see
yourself in that scenario doing the
thing that really excites you the most
step one step two plug all of your
emotions and all of your senses into
that picture in other words feel what it
would be like to be that individual feel
the excitement you would have look at
the attitude you would have see feel
taste smell identify with the scenario
with all of your senses and all of your
emotions plug into it step
three act it out physically act it out
create the props surround yourself with
the symbolic representations set the
stage train yourself train your physical
form into a new bodily habit of dealing
with the props that you know you would
be dealing with in that reality the
closest approximations of the settings
and the props you can create surround
yourself with them and physiologically
physiologically act out anything you can
in that scenario to the best of your
ability to lock it in physiologically
and create the feedback habit patterns
that will attract that reality to you
step one again identify what it is that
excites you step two identify with it
sensorially and emotionally step three
physically acted out that's what the
pictures are for to copy them to use
them as a template all the way down the
line in mental and emotional and thought
pattern format and physiologically to
copy them so that you will get the
result that you are seeing in the
template in the imagination scenario you
follow me yes there are a few more
details than that within the idea of the
recent Workshop that we gave involving
Persona reconstruction excitement and
abundance you may Avail yourself of that
if you wish more details however I will
tell you right now that everything I
have just said is sufficient in order to
create your imagination to manifest
physiologically if you do those three
steps to a full con ition and full
excitement and full involvement it can
be that easy if you don't find that it's
that easy then maybe you need a few more
details but I will leave that up to you
does that answer your question
sufficiently no let me approach this
another way all right go right ahead
um see in my experience sometimes those
images I have end up manifesting almost
exactly the way I see them and sometimes
they don't
correct there will many times be a
difference in your energy regarding any
one of those particular images as well
will there not be how do you mean that
in other words sometimes you simply look
at an image and you know that's who you
are and other times you are more
ambiguous about it okay understand there
are always fluctuations and sometimes
because of the type of mental beings and
analytical beings you have created
yourselves to be not always are you
given a literal interpretation of what
it is that you need to manifest
sometimes the vision that you're seeing
is symbolic but the essence of it can
manifest in another way you follow me
okay it does not always have to be taken
literally take it for its Essence
knowing that whatever it is that does
happen will be the most perfect version
of it that needs to happen at that
moment to give you the opportunity to
examine the things you need to examine
so that you can create more preference
in your life and more Precision in your
life next time you follow me mhm does
that assist you yeah yeah can I ask one
more quick thing what's the symbolic
meaning of the red
cardinal repeat that the meaning of the
red cardinal I've now seen two visions
of a red cardinal ah one
moment how's your love
life is that what that
means to some degree it is a messenger
of physiological and
emotional relationships and
interconnectedness it is delivering
certain symbolic Reflections and
messages from yourself to
yourself they are to some degree like
love letters in that
sense it is not our jurisdiction to go
into this further you already have all
the assistance you need in your dream
state with your own guides okay thank
you very much thank you
sharing good day Bashar and who you good
day um I've read a book the um within
the last couple years that did it take
you two years to read it well I keep
going back to it finding out more all
right um explains to my satisfaction the
change is going on um with the earth oh
all right and our climate yes and I want
to get a comment with from you as to the
accuracy of this Theory um always always
always always our primary opinion with
regard to any of the physiological
changes that may be taking place upon
your planet is the following there are
many probable ways to experience it both
positive and negative whatever vibration
you are will determine the way you go
through the Transformations changes
there will be but they can be
experienced in a positive and or a
negative way the way you experience it
is completely up to the vibration you
choose to be and what you choose to buy
into as being necessary for your
transformation trial by fire some people
will think is the only way they can
change others will understand that
ecstasy is their Birthright and they
will allow the transformation to take
place around them in a way that does not
harm them personally you follow me yes
well this explains it in a cyclic way
that apparently has it is all psychic
cyclic and cyclic it is all cyclic and
psychic yes there are cycles that occur
within your psychic manifestations
within your vibrational shall we say
repetitiveness within the overlaps that
your Society goes through in playing
some scenarios over and over again from
a different perspective there are Cycles
to it but that doesn't really matter you
will experience what whatever you deem
is necessary to be experienced by your
Consciousness but do continue I do not
mean to interrupt you well uh since
we've been taking carbon dioxide
measurements since 1940 in Hawaii near
Hawaii yes um the carbon dioxide level
has skyrocketed from about 4% yes to uh
20 somewhere around 22 to 25 understand
and um this is still not in your terms
irreversible well according to the book
it's approaching
approaching this is still in your terms
not irreversible okay that is our book
okay choose which one you wish to buy
into okay uh what he says is causing
this is the minerals leeching out of the
earth soils and due to the constant
raining in um and that the Earth
basically remineralizes itself through
the process of glaciation approximately
every hundred there are many many
factors being left out it is not so much
that particular idea no that is a small
factor but not a major one so what is
contributing to the carbon dioxide
Builder most of it has to do with the
transformation of certain particles in
what you call your upper atmosphere
transformation of certain particles as
they take place within now the idea of
what you would call vegetation that is
not necessarily allowing them to put out
the abundance of oxygen that they
formerly would have well he says it's
because they don't have minerals to grow
the plant life does not have minerals to
grow the way it should in order to burn
up the carbon dioxide and produce oxygen
it is not so much that they lack the
minerals in the ground there are certain
radiations that are now coming through
your atmosphere that do not allow them
to process the minerals
adequately that is the major
factor okay how can you suggest that we
can turn this around first of all once
again by allowing yourself if you wish
the strongest way to turn it around to
understand that all of the energy that
you need is available in the electromag
IC field of your planet and to cease
using the types of technology that you
use fossil fuels yes
okay understand yeah I do but it just really
understand yeah I do but it just really
made a lot of sense to me that the earth
needs to replenish itself in a sense yes
but it still has to do with what it is
you're doing upon the surface it is
still reversible but it is up to
you so how's that going to coincide with
our phase shifting and um expanding in
Consciousness because the Earth as a
conscious entity just like anything else
is going through the shift with you and
in a sense it is sending ripples of
energy through itself to allow itself to
transform into the type of world that it
really needs to be to function on its
highest level individuals that are
aligned with that will flow with it
individuals that are resistant to that
will create the resistance and the
destruction in their reality whatever
vibration you are will determine the
type of Earth that you experience
understand that when you see the the
Earth change around you it is because
you have changed your vibration and
shall we say colloquially transported
yourself to one of the infinitely
variable Earths that exist that is more
aligned with the vibration you choose to
be understand an infinite number of
earths already exist if you know that
there is a version that you prefer be a
person from that Earth and live that way
and you will start seeing the changes
occur around you but of course that
means you have to do your part as
well but it is still in your terms quote
unquote reversible because you can
simply take yourself to the Earth
wherein those conditions do not
exist Miracles what you call Miracles
remember are not the exception to the
rule they are the natural Order of
Things understand well Moving Mountains
absolutely they are only in your mind
anyway you are sustained
in that sense the physiological
representation of what you call your
planet your planet mass in a sense is
the product of the combination of your
mass Consciousness your physical reality
is utterly the product of what you
believe it to be sweeten it with your
own thoughts and it shall be so sweeten
it with your own direct intentions and
actions and it will change but primarily
what you actually will see is that you
have changed and you will get the Echo
and the reflection of the change within
you reflected in the physiological
environment around
you all right thank you very much well
thank you very much after all it's your planet
planet
Shing hi uh One Moment One Moment In
some other times when there is more time
for what you would call detail we will
discuss not that your world is not
capable of coming up with its own ideas
not that it hasn't we will discuss what
you might call a few more pragmatic ways
in which it could
learn to create devices in which it
could learn to tap into energies that
will allow you to understand you don't
not have to rely upon the technology you
rely upon now but that will be at
another time we have already to some
degree discussed this a few times off
and on but now is not the timing deal
with the idea we have already talked
about in that it comes from your
Consciousness first because all physical
reality stems from there first and then
we will discuss the details later on
after you have allowed a few more ideas
to fall into the proper
niches yes
continue I'd like to talk to you about
excitement in activity oh all right then
let's get excited about talking about
excitement I'm very excited I'm very
excited I'm not sure I understand what
you really mean by being excited I do
not mean that you have to jump up and
down all over the place no I am talking
about the vibration that allows you to
know that you are doing the thing that
is truly you the thing that allows you
to feel most at home at peace the thing
that really moves you the thing that
when you do it is no effort at all the
thing that when you do it gets things
done automatically great that okay let's
say that the things that excite me are
let's say playing yes being childlike
with what frisbee or tennis or swimming
things like that but they don't
necessarily pay the rent why
not why not what limitations in your
belief system says that those things if
they really are the things that really
excite you more than anything else what
is the limitation within your belief
system that says that those things
cannot pay your
rent the fact that they haven't so far
so what what has the past got to do with
who you want to be now
you have had the kind of past you have
had to determine for yourself whether
you prefer that kind of a reality or not
now that you know you don't prefer it
why assume that anything that happen
then has anything to do with who you are
now okay so do you think that yes I I
can um make money by doing the things
that I like to do yes I do but it
doesn't matter what I think it matters
what you think can you give me can you
let's be creative let's use your
imagination can you give me one reason
why you can't make a living doing what
excites you give me a
reason because they give nobody benefits
because I'm not really contributing
energy to society I'm just doing what
feels good for myself so therefore where
did you learn that
definition where did you pick that up on
the way somewhere along the line
somewhere along the way does it have to
be
true no can you
imagine a scenario where you are doing
the thing that excites you the most and
it is being of benefit to someone aside
from yourself can you imagine can you in
any way shape or form concoct such a
scenario yes describe
it paint me a
picture go on okay I'm playing with
other people yes and we're all excited
yes and and
I'm making money do uh doing it why
because I'm helping these people to do
to do the things that they like to do
and to get to help them get
in in Better Health and happier ah so
you are saying that you are capable of
imagining that there are other people in
existence who feel that what you have to
offer will be something worth supporting
in order to get the benefits of it that
they really want that and that you can
can realize that what you have to share
is truly equal to what it is they want
to get out of it that you don't have to
think anything less of it is that what
you're saying yes but along with the
fact that I have some talents that can
help people get healthy yes and that's
but playing and being healthy it's they
sort of hold hands with each other sort
of hold hands in a sense they are one
and the same thing yes and so my talents
are um let me ask you a question may I
um let me ask you a question may I
interrupt you please do are you aware of
even one other person on your planet
that plays and gets paid for
it no I don't you're not aware of any
one person that in a sense plays and
gets paid for it oh MC Jagger I mean uh
all right um anyone
else well you mean the plays the things
that I like to play or in general
in general anything at all in other
words are you aware of anyone who is
doing something they consider play and
getting paid for it yeah um how many
people very a lot of people all the
musicians um
people uh
photographers there's a lot of people
that do things they like to do yes and
get paid for it but it's just that but
but but but but I haven't done the
things that I like to do that I have
gotten paid for so you are saying that
for some reason you believe that the
thing that really motivates you the
thing you're all about somehow doesn't
count doesn't fit in the universe that
you have been supplied by creation with
something that excites you that is of no
benefit to
anyone why would the universe do
something so
pointless well they just haven't paid me
for it that's because you don't believe
you're worthy of getting paid for it do
you you don't believe it's a worthy
calling do you well I do but they
when you say well I do but they it's the
same Echo it's one event if you believe
it's worthy it's worthy it's going to be
worthy to whoever else needs it isn't
it yes isn't it yeah then why do you
care if certain individuals don't find
it worthy if they're not the ones who
need it all the individuals that you
care about are the ones that want it
they're the only ones that have to find
it worthy understand yeah let more of
them into your life
by assuming that there are enough of
them out there by assuming that whatever
it is that motivates you belongs in the
world otherwise it wouldn't exist for
every individual that has a desire to
express a certain thing above and beyond
anything else there is always always
always an audience large enough to
support them otherwise it would be a
pointless creation that is one-sided and
they don't
exist understand yes all you have to do
is allow your audience to find you by
ceasing to downgrade what it is you have
to
offer okay by knowing it can support you
otherwise you wouldn't have the
talent the fact that you have the talent
the fact that it is the most exciting
thing for you is all the signal you need
to know that the audience is there to
support you and remember abundance is
the ability to do what you want to do
when you want to do it it doesn't always
have to be in the form of money it can
be and that is one very valid way but as
long as you have the ability to do what
you want to do when you want to do it on
whatever expanded level you really want
to do it allow abundance to come to you
in whatever way is the path of least
resistance then you will have it all
right understand yes so yes you you once
I listened to a tape of yours of future
memory yes and you suggested painting a
scenario in which you would like to
exist in yes so you suggest that's what
I do as far as me doing what I want to
do and getting paid for it and having
everything do excite you to do it that
way why did you find yourself attracted
to that particular suggestion more than
any other suggestion could your
imagination be telling you
something why is it that you will not
allow the obvious to be
so
H because I trust in my doubts ah
because you trust in the reality you
don't prefer more than the the one you
do why by definition if you prefer
another reality why would you want to
trust in the one you don't prefer in
more it's a good question oh thank
you I'll let you think about it okay
thank you very much thank you very much
have fun
fun
shaning good evening Bashar and to you
good day I'm very very pleased to meet
you why you as well do be bold speak up
in a manner that all can share all right
about 5 months ago yes I purchased a
magnetic Sleep System magnetic Sleep
System yes excited me very much all
right upon bringing it home however
yes I found that my boyfriend whom I
love and respect very much yes had a
very negative attitude toward it no all
right so much so yes that he wouldn't
even discuss it oh all right much less
sleep in the same bed that it was on all
right how exciting it
was I can see that your relationship
never runs out of things to
discuss that is very true about my
relationship yes right and so what do
you want to do about that well I would
like to be able to sleep on it and I
would like him to like that
[Music] too is it something that you must sleep
too is it something that you must sleep
on all the time I'm using it temporarily
right now for meditation all right
however it's best used when it is slept
on all the time oh if you say so and it
gives me a wonderful feeling when I'm on
it oh all right have you initiated a
conversation in any way shape or form as
to why the other individual finds this
so apprehensive yes and he said
because his energy patterns are such yes
that the
magnetism gives him negative feelings
and when I even just have the pillow on
the said yes that when he when in the
few times that we've tried that that he
gets a headache from it oh all right
I'll ask you a question
yes why not make it a project for the
two of you to figure out figure out a
configuration to this magnetic equipment
that would work for both of
you well we could try that right now he
doesn't even want to discuss it oh all
right is he willing to discuss why he
believes it creates a negative effect
within him no well all right I guess
that that means that there's more
conversation that way perhaps anything
an individual refuses to do refuses to
face is usually an indication that
that's exactly what they ought to be
talking about I agree all right but if you
about I agree all right but if you
really love that individual
unconditionally you will allow that
individual their own good timing
understand yes if you are doing what you
are doing out of your own Integrity
you're not just doing it out of spite or
out of St stub berness then it would be
simply our suggestion that you continue
to do so and allow the other individual
to decide for themselves which idea
which reality they prefer more and if
they can allow the reality they prefer
to override the reality that they
don't understand yes I do understand but
I will leave it up to you thank you to
maintain your own Integrity to do what
you know is right for you at the same
time being responsible to that other
individual by being the full individual
you possibly can be and being un
conditionally loving enough to allow
them their own space and their own
timing to come to whatever conclusions
they need to come to all right that's
what I have been doing I was I just
thought I'd check and see if there was
anything else I could do One Moment One
Moment do they have a particular
affinity for any particular type of
flow not any particular particular kind
I can think of perhaps roses ask the
individual if there is any particular
type of what you would call aromatic
aromatic combination of herbs and or
flowers that they particularly like if
not perhaps have them find one if you
take that Aroma perhaps in the form of
what you call a sachche and you feel
what you call a pure cotton
lining Stitch It Up sew it up in a quilt
fashion this sache within a quilt of
pure cotton
or some other natural fiber perhaps in
that sense plant-like not animal
plant-like not
wolf then laying that sachche quilt and
lying on top of that may be able to
filter and rebalance the energy in such
a way that they will find a little bit
more tolerable all right all right thank you
tolerable all right all right thank you
thank you very much the aroma in and of
itself may also be suff ient even if it
is not sewn into a quilt it may help
balance them out it may put them into a
state of mind where they are more
willing to discuss the ideas they're not
willing to discuss
now thank you thank you
sharing hi bash you good day my name is
sunny sunny all right and I like to talk
about the end of our Century
1999 1999 yes yes because there have been
1999 yes yes because there have been
many prediction made that we're going to
have hard time were you paying attention
when we were talking about that a moment
ago no proba that all right we talked
about the idea that yes there are many
changes taking place upon your planet
the way you experience them the way your
vibration is will determine whether you
experience them smoothly or
catastrophically there are opportunities
to experience it either way when those
predictions were made the predictors at
that time because of the patterns and
the habits that your Society had created
itself to be could imagine no other way
for such transformational changes to
occur except by occurring through
disastrous and cataclysmic way they
couldn't imagine a new world being built
unless the old one completely destroyed
itself that is why those predictions
were voiced in the manner they were
voiced in now you are a little more
mature as a society as a species and you
now understand that you are beginning to
control your reality you know that it is
your creation so now you can take those
predictions with what you call a grain
or a pound of salt if you want to and
you can understand that they are simply
an offering an opportunity to decide for
yourself whether you wish to buy into
the fear that goes along with
transformation or whether you wish to
buy into the joy that goes along with it
no matter what occurs on your planet if
you are of a vibration that knows you do
not need to shake yourself awake and if
you are willing to wake up now then you
will not be in any way shape or form in
any location that experiences the
transformation negatively you understand
yeah yes does that help you does help it
helps but could I be a little more
specific yes
okay um said ah yes yes yes yes yes well
um said ah yes yes yes yes yes well
Edgar Cas to SCI yes yes yes yes okay he
said 1999 7 months yes yes yes the king yes
1999 7 months yes yes yes the king yes
yes yes yes yes yes going to come upon
us stop stop stop once again understand
understand all you are doing is forming
an
interpretation of the energy of the
shift the very same way that the
individual you are saying made the
prediction formed an interpretation let
me tell you something about prediction
there is no such thing as a prediction
of the future there are sensings of the
energy that exists at the time the
prediction is made all predictions are
predictions of sensings of the energy in
the present when the prediction is made
if that energy doesn't change the
prediction comes to pass if it does the
prediction is
obsolete if you hear a prediction and
you don't particularly prefer the way
the prediction has been interpreted then
your lack of willingness to accept the
interpretation will in and of itself
have a profound effect on changing the
way that the shift itself will be felt
the prediction takes advantage the
prediction in that sense sens
that a shift will probably occur in all
likelihood that shift will occur because
there is a great deal of momentum and a
great deal of timing within it and it is
unlikely that you will not experience a
profound and impactful shift even as you
are starting to now upon your planet
however always always always the
methodologies by which you experience
such profound transformation can be
positive or negative when the original
predictions were made back in what you
call nostradamus's time Edgar casy's
time the mindset of the world was very
negative it isn't as negative now as it
used to be so your energy the
willingness to know to believe that the
transformation can be experienced in a
positive way rather than a negative way
that willingness to know that has
already made a difference and it will
not necessarily need to be experienced
as negatively as it would have been had
it been experienced 50 or 100 of your
years ago you understand yes is this
making some difference within you yes I
tell you what uh why I was a little
concerned so to speak I'm astrologer so
I open up my eir for 1999 he said 7
months so takes us into August month 8
they're going to be solar eclipse very
extreme yes so um I have written an
article about uh examining United States
chart Soviet unions and China yes and
everything is extremely Afflicted but I
ended my article exactly what she's
saying that if we raise our
Consciousness and and ra raising our
Collective Consciousness we can avoid
that so I just wanted your confirmation
absolutely remember the reading you are
doing regardless of the method you use
use astrology or any other tool the
reading you are doing is being made
now you are not making a reading in 1999
you are making a reading now and the
energy of now will always color the idea
of the probable future if you change the
energy in the present you will get
another reading you will interpret it in
a different way it will all of a sudden
make itself obvious to you quote unquote
how you missed this inflection before
how you interpreted that other idea
differently before you will see it in a
new way and remember many times the
things that you call afflictions in your
present state of awareness are not
necessarily going to ultimately be
called an Affliction later on down the
line after the change has been
made understand understand does that
help you it helps me I still wanted to
make little explanation all right little
explanation okay D said that yes the
king of king of fire now the solar
eclipse going to be in Leo that's a
kingly size sign yes and fire is fire
element all right and so so I I can see
it how centuries back yes he was seeing
this eclipse and he was predicting
according to society that he was living
in yes but also the feeling to some
degree is accurate because the fire that
is also being mentioned is the cleansing
fire of your own Inner Light good it
will burn the world to life understand
understand thank you very much thank you
very much
sharing greetings precious entity I
greet you and c and to you as well
lovely
Consciousness my question is yes yes I'm
in need of an aid in which I can
harmonize my bodies a
bandaid a lemon
Aid what kind if it be so if it be so
all right what kind uh a way of being
able to harmonize when my vibration
speeds up or slows down
harmonize well I think one way that we
gave you was at the very very beginning
of this interaction
what did you feel when you allowed
yourself to
sigh did you feel a little more balanced
yes did that work yes is it sufficient
no why not I need more why I have much
more energy much more energy than
what then I feel that I can balance at
times why do you believe
that why do you believe you are given
something something that is more than
you are capable of handling at any given
moment why would you believe that the
universe is that shall we say cockey no
I can I I don't believe that I was given
something that I can't handle but I do
believe I've forgotten how ah what has
your imagination already come up with as
a methodology for handling
it asking you
anything else did it come up with no
other idea yes it did and what was that
idea I know that inner
peace and all the steps that I need to
find that are also the same things that
will balance and harmonize all right
that's all well and good but I have a
suggestion for you now in your last
statement just open the doorway for us
please well thank you very much
what do you think of the
ocean did you understand me yes I'm
trying to think of all of the things it
means to me oh I'll ask you a favor yes
I would ask that you do not think about
it so much I would ask that you give me
more of a gut physical reaction vast
nurturing I see do you like to swim yes
do you like standing in the ocean water
yes up to your neck yes then do
so and perhaps that will be one of the
things that balances you out very nicely
that type of physiological grounding
rather than being quite so
professorial about the idea of balancing
energy might I simply suggest that you
get yourself a little bit more
dirty that you roll around in the ground
a little bit that you Splash into the
ocean and grab great clumps of Earth and
sand in your hands and fling them around
all right and see if that does something
to balance the energy it does very much
at every opportunity I do that if I
don't have that opportunity is there
some way or imagining when do you not
have that opportunity driving on the
Ventura freeway at
R is there another activity that would
occupy you
physiologically that you can do
in what way do you mean many activities
I'll start you off any
physical the suggestion I make will not
necessarily be something that you have
to do but me making this suggestion may
allow you to discover another idea
simply perhaps because you will not
necessarily like the suggestion I make
and so you will immediately come up with
something else to avoid doing the thing
that I'm talking about try me take a
nice big thick piece of wood and a big
strong sturdy nail and a big heavy
hammer and pound that nail all the way
through the
wood most pleas physical very
pleasurable yes all right you can do
that all right it will have certain
benefits for grounding you you can do it
as long as you
wish or as little as you wish
but know that while you're doing it with
every Hammer stroke with every
centimeter that the nail goes into the
wood and with every resonant vibration
that the wood gives you you are truly
building a stable Foundation understand
yes does not help you yes entity it does
I thank you much thank
you happy sojourning sharing
sojourning sharing
hi Bashar I'm know you
goodday uh Good
Start um precise and to the point I I
have a problem oh all right uh I've had
a fear for my whole lifetime of my
parents dying oh and because of that I
haven't been able to to move far away
until this year I was 26 and still
living at home all right and I just was
wondering wondering whether or not that
had to do with a past life it has to do
with abandonment yes and I was wondering
if you could help me with that because I
still fear it very much and I'm afraid
on one hand that when they die I'm not
going to be able to function and on the
other hand something tells me that I
won't be able to function until they die
so I'm very confused all right I will
consolidate this conversation to some
degree by doing something that we rarely
do and this is a recommendation for an
actual reading material upon your planet
it is our
suggestion that you Avail yourself of a
particular book that exists in your
Society it is called we don't
die and then see what you
think all right okay
now do you
know that individuals always exist yeah
I mean I've I have such a fear of this
and this is going to sound very funny
but um my parents you know before I left
I told them look you know if you die or
if I die yes uh let's meet someplace if
we can and so my father said fine I'll
meet you out by the garbage can and my
mother said she'll meet me in the garden
they have great sense of humor yes um so
that's somewhat consoling to me but part
of me must not believe it all the way or
I wouldn't still be fearing this why
don't you believe that they still exist
I think I'm just going to miss their
physicalness I'm going to miss their
smiles and their bodies and um and I
know that they will exist on the
spiritual plane and but not on a I have
I miss physical things very badly stop
do you have a pet yes and I had to leave
her back in Connecticut and I miss her
terribly what is the pet a dog her name
is
Parker why had to leave
for my career what career I sing for a
living why Parker not
included because I knew she'd be happier
there because there's a lot more room
for her to run around and they live in
where there are not a lot of people and
not a lot of cars and I knew she'd be
happier there ah reverse situation
Parker is you you are your
parents they knew upon death that if you
remained that is simply where you would
be
happier you in a sense have died as far
as Parker is concerned do you not know
that Parker would be happier
there no why
not are you being
stubborn I think I I I don't think I
understood what you just said all right
the analogy let us pretend that Parker
is now you and that you are your parents
you have left Parker for all Parker
knows you're dead I know that really
bothers me but you know Parker is happy
or there yes I don't know that for sure
all right all right that is what you
said I know she would be she'd be
happier with the space that she has but
I know she misses me and I miss her oh
you know Parker misses you yet I'm going
to tell you a secret I lied to you she
doesn't miss me she knows you're not
dead I know she does and therefore why
should she miss
you she misses me physically
why because if the animal Consciousness
knows that physical reality is not a
boundary and Parker knows that Parker is
still in touch with you why should
Parker miss you if Parker really
believes that Parker is still in touch
with you because you are still in
Parker's reality why should Parker miss
you if you're still in Parker's
reality I see what you're saying mhm
well how does it make you
feel well makes me feel better but but
what but you don't want to feel better
no I do want to feel better I think I'm
yes uh I understand what you're saying
it's a really good point oh oh thank you
very much but I do think I really do feel she
much but I do think I really do feel she
misses me and and maybe that's
egotistical or something but I I I feel
very is yourself I'm missing myself and
all you're doing is seeing a reflection
from the dog whose job it is to be a guy
to reflect the things that are actually
going on within you the let's say play
that the dog misses you or act that the
dog misses you for the dog is truly
nothing but an act it is only a
reflection of what you're going through
because that's what animals are
reflective guides the dog knows beyond a
shadow of a doubt that you are always
going to be in its reality
but it will act like it misses you to
show you that you are the one that feels
like something is
missing okay understand yeah I think I
understand now now how do you feel
now ridiculous oh congratulations
congratulations
congratulations expand your definition
of life nothing
ever exists outside of
you and there there's your
answer thank you straight from the dog's
mouth we thank you at this timing we
will extend once again to each and every
one of you you get your answers at all
levels our
appreciation for your co-creation of
this energetic interaction this day of
your time this moment of your creation
as you created to be we thank you for
rec recognizing the now moment that you
are and for creating the next now moment
to be the you you prefer to be our
unconditional love our joy and our
ecstasy and above and beyond everything
our absolute unconditional trust and
faith in you we thank you we B you a
fond and a loving good day and good play [Music] [Applause]
how' it go great
thank you all very much for being here
tonight