Sir, are you all this evening of your
time as you create time to exist?
Are you all alive? Thank you. Allow us
to lay down some foundations for this
interaction this evening of your time.
And if I may say so now, I will be a
little bit more long- winded than
usual. The idea is simply that there are
a couple of ideas that we wish to
discuss. The first
one shall be a very important point for
many individuals and something that we
will further a discussion of at other
times as well. But for now it may simply
be entitled overcoming
inertia. Now we are referring in our
analogy to not only what you may call
the physiological form, the scientific
definition of inertia, but also the
sociological form. The idea of
overcoming what seems to be a
sluggishness or an impedance to you
moving at the rate you prefer to move
within the endeavors you say you want to
be involved within.
There is a similar definition for both.
This definition with a very slight
change can be applied not only to the
scientific idea of inertia, the
physiological the physics idea but also
the sociological one.
Now the idea as your society understands
it to put it on a very simple level is
that inertia usually as you say
represents the tendency of an object to
remain in the condition or the state
that it is in unless acted upon by an
outside force that moves it in another
way. The idea however to us from our
point of view is that inertia is the
effect an effect that is
created by the relative interaction
between dissimilar frequencies of
matter. To put it on the sociological level and
To put it on the sociological level and
perhaps to underline the physiological
definition, social
inertia, that sluggishness, that slow
moving, that idea of having to overcome
what seems to be obstacles is the
result of the effect that is created by
the relative
interaction between dissimilar
frequencies or states of being.
In other words, anytime you'll have in a
physiological object object
nonhomogeneous, disassociated,
disconnected objects, each of those will
have a different frequency, a different
idea, different definition of itself
relative to everything
else. And to define this analogy more
clearly, let us take the notion of many
of your technological vehicles, your
spacecraft, your automobiles and so
forth. When you deal with inertia in the
When you deal with inertia in the
physiological realm that you live in, it
is usually defined by the following
analogy. Let's say you have a vehicle.
Let's say for now it is simply a box, a
hollow box and there are passengers
within it. Little objects that you put
in the box and now you take that box and
you fling it with all your might against
a wall. Well, now you know what happens
to the objects inside and sometimes even
to the box itself. The idea is that as
you say the inertia of the objects at
rest remained at rest and when they
impacted the wall. Their motion was
abruptly changed and they simply as the
motion kept going rest relative to the
box they were still moving relative to
the earth. They kept going and smashed
up against the front of the box. Now all
of you understand this example in
physical terminology. However, many of
you have realized and recognized that
within our spacecraft, we seem to
exhibit properties that would indicate
that we are inertia free. That these
craft can move at what you say many
thousands of miles per hour and can stop
abruptly or execute very sharp angular
turns at seemingly no harm to the
occupants. The reason for this goes back
to the definition we have given of
inertia that it is an effect created by
the relative interaction between
dissimilar frequencies of matter. So
what we have done in our technology is
to create a type of field a type of
energy. We have created the craft's
substance and the occupants substance
and the air within the craft its
substance to all operate on the same
frequency. So it all becomes ethereal
matter. Thus the spacecraft, the air
within it and all of the occupants and
any other loose artifacts all function
as one homogeneous substance. It is more
analogous to the idea of having a solid
block rather than an empty box full of
separate particles. Or it is perhaps
more analogous to the idea of taking
that hollow box with all of the separate
occupants and filling it with a
substance that immobilizes everyone so
that it does act like a solid object.
And so when you throw it against the
wall, because they are immobilized, all
the objects within the box simply cannot
move because they are held within a type
of pressure field. Now this does not
mean we cannot move around within the
craft. It simply is however that the
atmosphere within the craft and I do not
necessarily just mean the breathable
substance but the entire energy
atmosphere of the craft its entire
energy reality is of one vibratory
frequency. Therefore the entire craft
functions as if it were a solid object.
So it can stop abruptly. It can make
right angle turns and the occupants do
not even know they are moving because
relative to the craft they are
immobilized within that energy
reality. Sociological inertia can be
similar. The only reason there is
resistance and friction in your lives is
because you may not be of the same
frequency as the idea, the event, the
vehicle you say you want to be a part
of. Therefore, if you are traveling at
one rate because of your definition of
yourself and the idea is traveling at
another rate because of your definition
of it, then if it all of a sudden stops
or takes a right angle turn, you are
usually turned into emotional jelly. The
idea therefore is to begin to understand
that the way you overcome that inertia
is to as we have said many times in many
different ways accelerate and uplift
your vibratory frequency to match that
of the event in your life you say you
desire. be in other words equal to the
idea and do not consider yourself nor
invalidate yourself to be anything less
than that idea then your frequency will
not be dissimilar. You will not
experience the idea of resistance and
friction in your sociological
interactions. And you will move in an
accelerated manner smoothly as one with
the event itself traveling so to speak
through the changes in that event at the
speed of thought in a very smooth way, a
very homogeneous way. because you and
the event will be one shall we say solid
idea not made of various components that
can become jumbled up and detached but
one interconnected homogeneous idea.
So the way we have discussed many times
to do this is of course in accelerating
your energy it is doing the thing in
your life that excites you the most and
knowing that when something does excite
you it is who you are and feeling equal
to that idea and not thinking oh no
that's too big for me I can never handle
that I don't deserve that that's going
to be difficult I have to overcome this
and this and this in order to do that
I'll never be good enough and many other
ideas that keep your frequency lower or
at least different than the idea you say
could be so exciting. Be at one with
your vehicle and it will carry you
anywhere as fast and far as you want to
go smoothly, effortlessly, and with
absolutely no inertia to overcome
because you'll be on the same track in
the same frequency. Everything will be
in your terms, no longer quote unquote
differently relative. It will all be
from the one point of view that you
desire to be. And your vehicle will then
be seen to be an extension of you. Even
as we understand that even though we use
the format you call spacecraft, we know
they are literally an extension of us.
Even as any physiological object is your
own rocket ships, your own automobiles,
your own airplanes, your own boats, any
vehicle, any idea, your own bodies. They
are an extension of the idea that you
are. They are a representation of the
idea that you are. And they are
absolutely representative of the
frequency you operate on and the
acceleration that you believe is
possible in your life.
Second idea to add some more wind into the
conversation. There will be and have
been for a while many ideas now coming
up regarding the issue of
spirit versus
will. All right. There are many many
many areas of information that are now
coming into your society regarding the
notions of spirit and will. And for a
long time your world has denied the idea in
time your world has denied the idea in
many ways and in many forms of what you
call your physical consciousness when
you deal with spiritual matters. The
idea we have outlined many times is
simply that you cannot really quote
unquote become more overall spiritual by
denying one level of spirituality, one
level of reality, the physical reality.
Physical consciousness is just as
important and just as powerful as the
idea of spiritual awareness. And they
must be blended 50/50 as you say or if
you wish 100 100 fully validated and
equal ideas coexisting as partners doing
the work they need to do together in
order for any individual to realize
themsel as a complete being. Many
individuals now because the idea of the
will has been so suppressed, the idea of
conscious desire so suppressed in your
society now when they deal with
spiritual matters and regain a bit of
awareness of who and what they are will
tend to focus on that spirituality at
the sake of the physiological
consciousness at the sake of the
conscious decision making capability.
You cannot forsake either one. For to go
into the idea of pure spirit and not
allow the idea after having chosen to be
physiologically present, not allowing
the idea of your physiological will to
exercise itself in a
sense will allow you to be a
physiological puppet. The idea of
allowing the will, absolute free reign
without the spirit blended into it will
allow for what you call negative
ego. Both must be present in order to be
a balanced being. Otherwise, you are a
hollow shell denying your physical
existence or you are a physiological
demon running in rampage of negativity
through your physical world with no
connection to higher realms.
Now the idea for why this disconnection
has occurred is due in great part to the
one particular attribute called
denial. The idea of self-invalidation on
many levels. There is a long, shall we
say, history in your society of the many
different ways that this denial has come
about. And right now is not necessarily
the time and place to outline every
single one of those steps. That
information to some degree already does
exist in many works of literature upon
your planet and is always there for the
finding. But the idea to put it on a
simple level for now is that spirit that
upliftment that energization of spirit
and will the conscious decision-making
commandment of your physical
reality are both blended very simply and
very easily within the crucible of
unconditional love. That is all it
takes. That fire of desire of
unconditional love is all it takes for
both spirit and physiological will to
blend to merge to marry and to become
one homogeneous representation as the
being that you are so that you are
connected to both heaven and earth as
you say in equal measures perfectly
balanced in that balanced state then all
worlds all understandings and all
connections are possible.
But not at the sake of one or the other.
They are equal partners. As you express
yourself within the polarity of physical
reality and have created the notion of
spirit and will, they must be equal
partners, fully
blended. We thank you for allowing us to
share in this way at this time. We thank
you for co-creating with us at this time
these interactions so that your world
and our worlds respectively may grow
together in their own ways and yet also
within each other to share the dreams
that we can become to share the dream
reality that we can create wherein
anything is
possible. We thank you for functioning
as ambassadors of your society at this
time and allowing me to function as a
representation of our respective
society. You are a gift to us as we have
shared with you many
times and we are overjoyed and ecstatic
at any
opportunity to perceive within you an
awakening to your own
self-empowerment. Anytime any of you is
willing to shine, the universe is made
that much brighter. And we thank you for
your willingness to discover who and
what you are and for allowing us to
reflect back to you who you already know
yourselves to
be. In return for this
gift, I ask you now, how and in what way
may I be of service to you?
Good evening, Bashar. And to you, good
day. We had a talk
We had a talk
uh a month or so ago. Oh, about a uh
interaction that I had with an
individual that was a physical
interaction, an altercation. Altercation
and
uh it's ties so well with the idea of
inertia, spirit will
um thank you for the synchronicity
really.
Um, we seem to be at a stalemate as far
as any kind of communication. There's a
lot of rage and uh, agents and ideas
like that. And how are you at the
communication within yourself? Then
um, are you communicating clearly to
yourself the ideas that you are working
through? Are you in your terminology, in
your reality resolving the issues within
yourself? Yes, very much and very
actively. All right. Are you then
comfortable with the reality that the
interaction has allowed you to design
for yourself? Uh, it wouldn't be my
preference to choose this way again. All
right. You don't have to. But also
remember, no matter how any individual
chooses to interact with you, you will
only get out of the interaction whatever
reality you are the vibrational
frequency of. You don't want to have to
buy into someone else's approach. You
understand? Yes.
So you can use the interaction to simply
understand what their reality is as
compared to what reality you prefer to
be. And you can thus allow that
interaction to boost your reality, to
solidify your reality, so that you can
give them back a reflection of what that
interaction has created you to be. so
that if they choose to, they can key off
of you what you have solidified yourself
to be to determine whether or not they
wish to change. As long as you believe
honestly with honest communication
within yourself that you are functioning
to the best of your ability within all
the integrity you can muster, then no
matter how they choose to interact with
you, you cannot be responsible for that.
All you can do is give them back
unconditional love based on the being
you chose to create yourself to be out
of that interaction. You follow me? Yes.
In terms of what you call a
stalemate, the idea is simply that you
do not have to take responsibility for
their choosing or not choosing to change
even though you might have. You
understand? Yes. You can simply get on
with your life being the person you have
chosen to be and knowing that whatever
interactions you automatically attract
yourself into with that individual, you
will simply still learn whatever it is
you need to learn about being yourself.
And at the same time, you can be of
assistance to them. You can offer that
opportunity. They do not have to take
it. But it also does not have to be at
the expense of who you choose to be.
Understand? Yes. Is this helping?
Definitely. Anything else?
I'd like to go over u the idea of
co-creation. Co-creation. Yes. Right. I
asked this individual to be here so that
we could ask one or both of us about
these ideas. Uh and again, I'm the only
one here.
Uh is every interaction no matter what
level emotional, mental, physical, a
complete equal co-creation and the equal
responsibility of each individual? Yes,
it is an equal co-creation and equal
responsibility. However, there will be
relative degrees of what it is you are
getting out of it as opposed to what
they are getting out of it. It can be
completely different lessons, completely
different ideas that are being observed
and integrated or not integrated. In
other words, just because you may
attract an individual that acts a
certain way doesn't necessarily mean
that their particular attitude is
exactly a one for one mirror reflection
of the things you specifically need to
work on. The idea, however, is that it
is an absolute co-creation so that it
serves both of you to work on whatever
it is you need to work on that you get
out of the interaction. Sometimes it
will simply be that if you do not
necessarily have that particular area to
deal with and they do, you will be
willing enough to attract them so they
can see your type of reaction so that
from your reaction they can learn that
perhaps there are other ways they also
could act in life. It may be more of a
teaching for them. Maybe not as much of
one in the same way for you, but that
doesn't mean you still can't get
something out of having been of service
to them. You understand? Mhm. And vice
versa. And vice versa. Absolutely. Be
open and honest and vulnerable and
receiving to anything you could get out
of any interaction and always be willing
to serve them unconditionally but not at
the expense of being the person you
desire to be. But it is always an
absolute cocreation and yet of course
paradoxically at the same time you are
always in a sense only interacting with
another aspect of
yourself. Understand? Mhm. So yes, it is
100% on both sides. Not even the notion
50/50. It is
100% on both sides, but you will get
different ideas out of
it. Where does the idea of compromise
come in within that resolution? Thank
you. What you typically call
compromise does not again necessarily
have to be at the expense of anyone's
reality. The notion on the positive side
of what you may call an agreement or a
compromise that is amiable to both
parties is to trust going in that there
is some reality that you can attract
that represents what you both desire to
be and that that reality fits and that
you both fit into it and that you can
attract it. You can find it. you can
create it in your life and that you will
be able to find all the factors
necessary automatically coming in that
serve you both in exactly the ways you
need to be served. The only way that
someone would not feel that is happening
is if perhaps they have certain negative
expectations about what they think they
ought to get out of it and aren't
necessarily being honest about what they
really need to get out of it. You
understand? Does that help you? Yes. So
actually whenever there's an interaction
such as this or any interaction there is
a perfect point where each of where
there's a common ground. Where always,
always, always between any polarity
expression of two sides, there is always
a third alternative that serves both.
Because you being the polarity on one
side and the other individual being the
polarity on the other side automatically
by definition indicates that you are on
different sides of something in the
center. that your existence as
polarities is given birth by that common
idea that exists in the center and all
you need to do so to speak is work your
way backwards to that common center and
find out what common center gave rise to
the polarities you experience yourselves
to be to begin with understand yes does
that help you yeah any insight as to
what that point is you will find it you
will feel it always will come from trust
and unconditional love you'll know when
you have it okay relax enjoy
Thank you. Thank you. Sharing.
Hello, Bashar. And good day to you. Good
day to you, too.
Um, I'm Last week on my way over here,
um, I got into a car accident. Well, how
exciting. Yes. Was I trying to, um, raise my
Yes. Was I trying to, um, raise my
vibratory frequency rate?
you are at least making an attempt to
show yourself
something. Now many individuals can
allow their vibratory rate to be
accelerated by that kind of an impact of
information but it will depend upon the
individual. What do you feel that that
particular circumstance got you to look
at about yourself? What kinds of things
have you been examining about yourself
since that
time? What have you looked at that you
may not have looked at had you not
experienced that idea? We're not
necessarily saying you had to do it that
way. But since you did it that way, what
have you looked at that you may not have
looked at had you not had that
experience? Being here now. Being here
now. All right. Many individuals will
place themselves squarely on the line.
Place themselves in a situation that may
seem dire physically. So they will force
themselves to live absolutely in the
present. That is one way. Do you think
that that is a sufficient
idea? Can that be the entire lesson? Do
you feel that that completes the
understanding of why you would have had
to create that kind of awakening?
Possibly. Maybe. All right. Anything
else? What else have you been examining?
I'm not sure that I'm examining anything
more now than I normally do. I
um I've been examining
May I ask you a personal question? Yes.
Thank you.
Were you, to put it simply, paying
attention to your driving?
No. Why not? Where were you?
I wasn't here now, that's for sure. All
right. I was floating somewhere. All
right. Then the idea can simply be
Then the idea can simply be
representative that as you
accelerate, keep your feet on the
ground. Mhm.
Stay connected. This once again is the
whole idea of not allowing your
explorations of spirit to take you out
of physical will. To remain focused, to
be grounded as you say, to be balanced
as you say with all your explorations.
And whatever you are doing at any given
moment is the most spiritual thing you
need to be doing. Remember that even
driving one of your automobiles, though
I know many of you may not think so, is
a very spiritual act if you do it in the
moment. Mhm. Really. And so it can teach
you how to extend your senses in
physical reality as well as extending
your senses into the non-physical realm.
The creation of dream time. The creation
of your physical reality to become less
solid. The creation of your dream
reality to become a little more solid
seeming to you does not have to take you
out of sync with the reality around you.
Why would one um float like that? Is it
isn't it an escape? It can be, isn't it?
Fear from
from fear of oneself or coming close to
can also simply be that now that you
have discovered that idea, it simply
felt so good you forgot where you were.
Mhm. Can be both ways. Can be both
sides. It's up to you to determine which
is true for you and deal with that. Mhm.
Can be either. But the idea did bring
you back to focus at the center.
Definitely. All right. Then simply
remember the idea of connection of your
senses to your physical realm is just as
important as the connection of your
senses to the non-physical realm. Yes.
And that you can be in synchronous
harmony with all of it. Yes. Understand?
Absolutely. There are also a few other
issues that may be coming up for you
regarding the notion or the definition
of your vehicle, your mode of
expression. What gets you from here as
you say to there? Mhm. These issues may
also be coming up and many of them as we
perceive your energy will be probably
processed in your dream reality. Mhm.
But again, the idea is to keep your feet
on the ground and to understand also
that no matter how fast you start to go,
you can still remain in synchronous
harmony with the physical reality you
are changing in. You do not have to
assume that acceleration or going at a
different pace than everyone around you
must mean that you must interact with
them in a negative way. There is room
for all and everything fits and one
individual can be going this way and
another individual can be going that way
and you can pass right through each
other without
harm. But the way to do that most
strongly is to remain fly focused where
you are not where you are going where
you are and all your immediate
surrounding understand. Yes. Um can you
give me a suggestion? Um because so many
times I thought I just did even beyond a
more pragmatic suggestion keeping myself
grounded. Define pragmatic
when um I catch myself floating. Yes.
Um in in what way can can I help myself
to be in in life's
experience?
Now what do you experience when you
float? What kind of a feeling? What kind of
What kind of a feeling? What kind of
information comes to you?
Um, it's infinite. All right. Do you
understand that the physiological
reality is a part of that infinity? Yes.
All right. I I also understand that I've
been avoiding that. Why?
What is it about the definition you have
of physical reality that makes it
something you want to avoid?
I'm I'm not sure. Come.
Come give it a name, give it a face,
give it some form of
identity. Use that imagination like I
know you all can for now. It's all
right. Use it in a negative way. Figure
out by giving some life to that idea,
the negative notions, the negative
definitions within you, what it is you
believe physiological reality offers you
that is so fearinducing. Self-denial.
Selfdenial do you mean that as long as
you are attached to the notion of a
physiological reality you feel
impoverished? Yes.
Yes.
Why are there not in physiological
reality rich is enough for all? Oh
absolutely. Then why not rich is enough
for you? Mhm. I think that it's
connected to old beliefs. All right. Old
beliefs. Fair enough. Do you want those
old beliefs? No. All right. Do you have
to know what they are in order to
understand that you simply prefer new
beliefs? No. Can you design some new
beliefs? Yes. All right. Design them and
implement them. Know that once they are
designed and once you have approved and
placed your signature on the blueprint
of a new belief that it is now being
carried into effect and constructed into
your reality. In a sense that might
ground you. I will give you one other
pragmatic suggestion.
When you design those new
beliefs, take what you would call a
piece of wood, a nice heavy thick piece
of wood, a nice heavy strong nail and a
good solid hammer and pound that nail
into the wood as a meditation. Okay?
That will orient you toward the physical
and allow you to feel that you are
constructively involved. Right? You
understand? Yes. Absolutely. That can
ground you. I
All right. I'm going to do that. Thank
you very much. Have wonderful time. I
will. Thank you, Bashar. Sharing. Yo. Hello.
Yo. Hello.
How are you? Perfect. And you? Right.
No, it's great. You know, it's great.
All right. Yes. Yes. All right.
Um, are we continuing where we left off?
Yeah. Good. All right. I'm ready. You
are. All right. So, give me a fresh new
point of view. Oh. All right. Do you
remember the last one we gave? No, that
was a question. That was not a point of
view. Or it was a point of view.
Question can be a point of view. Yeah.
Okay. But I'll put it in more of a
statement form if you wish. Okay, thank
you. If you are now ready to place both
feet firmly on the deck of your ship and
acknowledge completely that the energy
you know you are connected to can come
through and not remove you from the
physiological reality in which you
exist. You can own that power, own that
energy in a loving and an enlightening
way. And that will be more than
sufficient to blend and balance the
energy that your son is reflecting to
you about the polarities that you each
represent in terms of your original
societies that you stem
from. Understand?
Uh yeah, you're talking about
origin, you know,
uh your son is more connected and in no
way, shape or form is what we are
saying. meaning that they necessarily
will exhibit this energy in the
classical sense in this life but there
is a very strong connection as you
already understand to the ancient Orion
energy. The idea is that you have a
different connection in a very different
way and that all that to some degree is
being shown to you by the notion of the
will of the son and the notion of the
spirit of the mother is that you both
need as we have already outlined spirit
and will in combinations that recognize
and acknowledge what your energy is. So
you have a reflection from the son of
the will without the connection of the
will without the connection of the
spirit completely and you have a
recognition of you of spirit without the
idea of bringing that down to earth as
will and conscious commandment. So you
are being offered an opportunity to own
the will even as you are offering him an
opportunity to own the spirit so that
both of you can be blended and balanced
but in your own way. Not that it will
make you alike per se, but both of you
will acknowledge each other as
representatives of the energy you are
connected to and both feet in both cases
will be firmly on the deck of your
respective vehicles. Understand? I understand.
vehicles. Understand? I understand.
Okay. Um, a point of view about why just
that specific individual
because it hits you where you live. It's
your son.
Yeah. And the idea is that now many of
the children are teaching the adults and
he will be the one and the only one you
would listen to. The only one that can
really affect you that way. The only one
that can really push your
button. That's why. I got it. Does that
help? Well, not right now. Now, now, but
you know, I'll let you know when it
does. Oh, all right. May I ask you a
question? Go.
Go.
If for a moment you take an opportunity
to
feel yourself standing on the deck,
are you comfortable with that? Mhm.
In what way?
Well, in the way that I feel everything
within and I there's no need out there,
you know, it's only complete and it's
comfortable and all
right. Now, that completion, that degree
of comfort,
is there some specific way that you
really do desire to funnel that through
into your physiological reality that
you're not
doing? Or do you wish to simply be an
observer? Do you feel like only an
observer on that level? No. All right.
How do you feel you are quote unquote
using that energy to participate in the
physiological reality in which you exist
aside from the interactions with your
son? Oh, I use that energy to uh you
know create as it comes and just create
what? Anything. Anything and everything.
Anything specific? No. Why not? Well,
just because. Because
what? Because um
because I'll wait.
Well, there's nothing specific. Uh well,
if you want specificity,
uh yes,
just uh uh
Yes, yes, yes. I forgot my microscope.
Jeez. Living in the moment, it's all well and
Living in the moment, it's all well and
good. Well, that's that's what I mean.
Creating just creating just Yes. Yes.
Yes. Living in the moment is all well
and good. Okay. Well, that's however
once again we are back to the notion of
direction that is given to you by your
conscious commandment. Direction. Your son has an
commandment. Direction. Your son has an
amazing amount of direction.
Mhm. So much so that it cuts like a
knife. Yeah. And is very abrasive in
many ways. Mhm.
Now you are because of your energy a
slightly more shall we say ethereal
being. Ethereal. Ethereal. Not
necessarily wishing to be in your
terminology dragged down into such a
dense reality.
Yeah. I like this dense reality.
Enjoying it on one level. Yes.
Yeah. You know, I like to experience it.
I like to learn to be around it and
totally be happy in all these, you know,
all these limitations. And I'm enjoying
more and more to just be happy like
that. Even though everybody says they're
unhappy, I think I'm happy. All right.
May I ask you something else? Go for it.
Would you be Oh, thank you very much.
Would you be
Would you be as happy if if You
You
were occupying the physiological chair
now occupied by the channel.
No. Why not?
Well, I don't know what it feels like
really and I don't have
like right now any excitement as sitting
in that chair or whatsoever. All right.
What does doing that represent to you?
Well, I guess there's something else to
do, to learn, and to experience. But
right now, I don't feel like
experiencing that. I'm all right. We are
not necessarily saying that you have to.
No, I got that.
Well, thank you. However,
okay, because of the energy present at
this time Mhm. because of the state of
the interaction right now and because of
the process that it may not be much detail
process that it may not be much detail
that we can go further into. However, it
is our sense for whatever you wish it to
be worth that there is something about
that scenario and about that analogy and
about that type of connection to other
individuals and about that type of
interaction to a grand scale of
individuals. That is somehow the crux or
the heart of the issue of your interaction
heart of the issue of your interaction
with us at this time.
Well, my heart is pounding. Yes.
When I say you are bigger than you
think, how does that make you feel?
Well, let me think about it. 2 minutes.
Why 2 minutes? Bigger than I think. Yes,
you are bigger than you think you are.
Okay. I'm bigger than I think I am. How does
I'm bigger than I think I am. How does
it make you feel? Well, deep down it
says, "Well, I knew that."
And in a way, um,
okay, fear, you know, of what?
Um
boom explosions, you know. All right.
But too big. Too big. All right. For
right now. It's like using a little by
little letting it out instead of opening
the valve, you know. I'll ask you one
more question if I may and that may
suffice. Okay. Are you afraid of being
held in awe?
That's good.
That's really good. Thank you. Right to
the core. Thank you. Okay, I'll let you
ponder that if you want. Yeah, thank you
very much. Thank you. Happy travel.
Thanks. Sharing.
Yo, Mr. Representative and Ambassador.
Greetings and salutations. I'm to you as
well. Thank you.
Um, I believe you've
defined abundance as being able to do
what you need to do when you need to do
it. Is that correct? The ability to do
it. Didn't I say being able to? Yes.
Okay. Same thing. I think um it doesn't
say anything about being able to do what
you want to do when you want to do it.
How do you reconcile those? Now, before
you answer, guys.
See, I want to It's kind of a rhetorical
question cuz I want to answer it before
you have a chance to open Thank you.
before you have a chance to open Daryl's
[Music]
mouth. You got me,
Bashar. What can I say? Bush. Well, I
think it has something to do with what
you've been referring to as conscious
commandments. Very good. keep going.
And I've been exploring this and
I've for um a couple years now or so
I've been I I have maintained a very
positive attitude and trust and belief
that if I act on my excitement, think
positively, a lot of other things which
I could enumerate but which I won't that
things will really actually accelerate
and work out very very well. I'm in a
period where I where I'm not
experiencing that and I'm I'm
questioning the beliefs and questioning
the attitudes that I've all right had
toward that. All right. And it comes
down to I believe that I have applied a
conscious commandment in order to get
what I want when I want it.
But yet apparently what I'm getting is
just what I need when I need it. And I
don't like just that. I want more. Ah,
now you are standing on the crossroads
and in a sense we were wondering when
someone was going to catch the idea of
the definitions between need and want as
you are now have done. Yes, it is all
absolutely centered on defining that
idea and aligning the idea of wants and
needs and operating on a level where
they are in many ways the same thing.
Okay, it can be handled in many
directions. It can be consolidated down
to the idea of simply enjoying
everything that comes along because if
it is there, it is worth enjoying.
That's one level. Mhm. And at the same
time, by going through that doorway, it
can be having exactly what you want,
exactly when you want it, exactly the
way you want it, because there really is
no reason why you can't have it that
way. As long as that comes from absolute
unconditional love and not from the idea
of the negative ego. Once that has all
been cleared out, there really is
nothing that stops it. And you now
arriving at the point of recognition
that there does not have to be a
difference between what you call a need
and a want. In that sense that can
propel you very strongly towards your
recognition that you really have the
ability to as you say miraculously and
magically manifest what you want when
you want to. You have now truly opened
that door by recognizing first of all
that those two terms can be
interchangeable which many individuals
have not up to this point. Right. Well,
let's explore this further because
although I do see the concept of the
interchangeability somehow
I I also have the concept
that perhaps our needs are defined at a
level let's say higher than the um
outerware conscious physical conscious
level whereas our wants that I'm using
term is defined at the outerware
conscious
So because you have also just now
illustrated something very important
about your society's definitions of the
two terms wants and needs. Needs are
usually defined by your society as
something below your wants. Wants are
usually defined as something above your
needs. Okay. Yeah, that's true. All right. Keep
Okay. Yeah, that's true. All right. Keep
going. You're homing in nicely. All
right.
Well, if one's needs are defined at a
high level and we have not accessed that
level, let's say for instance, our needs
are to really experience I'll say
deprivation. You and I have touched on
that with me before. And we go well I
don't want to feel deprived. I don't
want to experience deprivation. But at a
higher level consciousness is saying
you're going to experience deprivation.
You can create no no you will experience
the notion and the lessons and the
information of the idea the concept you
call deprivation. Isn't that the same
thing as experiencing it? Not
necessarily physiologically. Remember
the library analogy. Okay fine. If in
experiencing physiological deprivation
as we have said you can understand why
you would have chosen to show yourself
that experience physically you can then
determine to experience that energy that
information and receive that knowledge
in another type of experience.
Yes, experience in many ways is
necessary for knowledge, especially in
physiological reality. But it does not
necessarily have to be always the
absolute actual experience of the
negative in order to have an experience
that gives you the information that you
could get out of having the negative
experience. In other words, if you can
get the information out of imagining it,
that's all that that suffices. Very
good. And now you have hit another nail
squarely on the head. What this actually
involves is the
multi-dimensionality you allow your
imagination to be. This is fundamental
to the creation of dream time. And I do
not mean while you are asleep. I am now
talking when I use the term dream time
as something that represents in many
ways being awake but being in the dream
living that dream and allowing physical
and non-physical reality to blend as one
idea. So this idea of blending and
elevating the vibration of your
needs to be aligned with the idea of the
lofty wants is found within the imagination
wants is found within the imagination
and to whatever degree the imagination
can be
allowed. Its true dominion will
determine your availability of alignment
between needs and wants and allow them
to be one thing and not two separate
ideas. two separate issues. So you have
hit the nail on the head. It does
concern imagination directly, but what
it more precisely concerns is your
ability to really allow that imagination
true multi-dimensionality.
How do you apply this then? How does how
do how would I apply that?
It does to some degree come down once
again to definitions and shall we say
cleansing the definitions you no longer
prefer out of the imagination so that
the only ones that will remain in effect
are the ones that give you a positive
manifestation yet at the same time that
you have the positive manifestation it
allows you the negative recognition you
could have gotten by having the negative
experience. I will sum it up in one
word. develop an
overwhelming sense of connection to
nature, connection to the infinite
through the facility that is called
gratitude. Understand?
Understand?
Yeah. With absolute gratitude,
you will have nothing barred from you.
Nothing. Nothing. Gratitude to whom? Of
what? Gratitude.
Can you define that a little better? All
right. It is in some senses, in some
religions in your society called being
in a state of grace. In other words,
some individuals say it is being humble
yet expansive. It is feeling the
universe in your heart. It is knowing
that all things are contained with you.
It is relating to all of nature. It is
in your terminology being grateful for
the opportunity of all the experience
you have. It is being grateful for the
consciousness of reality in whatever
form it takes to give you the
information you need by being whatever
form it is. A pane of glass, a stone, an
animal, a person, the sky, the clouds,
the trees, the stars.
Gratitude for all of it. Infinite
gratitude opens you up. It is in a sense
vulnerability in trust in strength in a
positive way.
Gratitude. You might find some excellent
examples in what you call your Native
American culture. The way they speak of
gratitude in many ways is what we are
talking about now. It is an
acknowledgment and a recognition of all
of the mirrors you are given in reality.
So that you can be so reflective and so
clear because of that gratitude that all
images can be reflected from you. All
states can be reflected back from you
and you can be whatever you want when
you want to be. That idea at any moment
absolute gratitude in a sense it is the
ultimate centering. Sometimes your
society calls it surrender. We simply do
not necessarily choose that term because
in many ways it actually implies that
you are losing your identity and that
you are no longer in control. It simply
means you become so transparent and so
effortless in your creation that you're
actually exercising the control you are
as an aspect of the infinite. So it
seems like you're not doing anything.
Gratitude. Gratitude. Love.
Unconditional gratitude. The joy of
being given the gift that you have been
given in that way will allow you to
experience it in any way you want to.
And at the same time, by experiencing it
that way, you will still appreciate all
other ways unconditionally that you
could have experienced it. Let me put it
this way. An individual in your
terminology is physiologically very
abundant comes up in a situation where
they meet face to face with an
individual that in your terms is
physiologically impoverished. An
overwhelming sense of love and gratitude
at being who they are is what that truly
centered person feels. And they can be
of service in many ways to the
individual who in your terms may be
impoverished and may desire to change
but may not be able to understand the
alignment of needs and wants. Whereas
the abundant person in that way can
experience through the other person's
life through the other person's eyes the
idea the lessons the knowledge the
understanding of why they would have
chosen that sees the strength within
them understands it and integrates it
and absorbs it within themsel and gives
gratitude radiates light and gratitude
at being able to see that lesson to
receive that lesson and at the same time
be whoever they want to be when they
want to be that person and still receive
all the lessons all the information all
the gratitude
all the
support. In a sense, it is an attached
detachment, an ultimate attachment to
everything and yet
knowing that everything passes through
you and allows you to remain whatever
you wish to be at that moment. Some of
this may seem esoteric, but it is
completely couched in a language of
emotionality. And in a sense, it must
be. There are not too many terminologies
that exist upon your planet in your
language that we could use that are
quote unquote logical in a way that can
unquote logical in a way that can
express the
emotionality. These are things that must
be felt. It is the feeling of that
connection that allows you to be what
you want to be when you want to be it
rather than the idea of the analytical
understanding of that condition. It is a
state of grace, a state of gratitude, a
state of love.
Is this making any sense? I'm
understanding you, but I only have a
partial understanding of one thing. Yes.
Uh I seem to have a
monopolar concept of gratitude as though
in order to understand gratitude, I need
to understand the polar opposite of that
to compare it to. In other words, how
would I feel if I didn't feel there is
the crux, there is the crux. Thank you.
Thank you. My pleasure. When you're
talking about something like gratitude,
unconditional love, you are talking
about the center of all things, the only
polarity that exists at the center of
all things is the outward expression of
everything. Which means in order to
experience the polarity of the center,
you have to experience all the details
and take a long time doing it. We've
done that.
So the idea is that if you wish to
happen quickly, then simply feel it at
the center. You don't necessarily have
to experience the polarity. You can
But experiencing the polarity of the
center means experiencing all the things
that surround the center. The entire
sphere of physiological reality. How
does one do that? In the way you have
gone about it, analyzing and going
through many different lives, having
many different experiences of things
that you may need but don't want. Well,
what I'm saying is how does one
experience the core, the center? Feel
it. Love it. feel the gratitude at
having been created by it and give that
love back. It is an unlimited well. Well,
back. It is an unlimited well. Well,
there is no other polarity that exists
except all the detail of creation
itself. I can I understand that. All right.
Um I lost what I was going to say. Very
good. Good start. um auspicious
um auspicious
beginning. Fall into
it. Relax into it. Let it nurture you
and at the same time understand it is
not taking away your identity.
No, I don't have that concept at all. On
one level, you do. Okay. I'd like to
access that level. How would I go about
accessing fall into it?
Um, how how how do you fall into it? How
do you do that? I'm interested in doing
it, but I I don't have, you know, just
hearing the words fall into it doesn't
necessarily trigger an understanding of
a practical application. All right. I
only can give you a suggestion for there
can be many, many, many techniques. I'll
give you a suggestion. Sure. I do not
necessarily know that this will work
precisely for you. Perhaps your
imagination will take over and alter in
a way to be fit you.
Stand on the edge of some sort of ledge
over a body of water. Okay? While
standing on the edge of the ledge, feel
all your anger. Feel all the idea of the
radiance and the power of your
will. Feel the conscious
commandment. Feel your
deservability. Own it.
Demand it of yourself. The universe
already gives it to you. Demand it of
yourself. Then at the height of your
intense desire for that conscious
commandment and directability and
deliberateness in your life, fall into
the water and cool
off and float in the serene plunge of
support and infinite
beauty that is the answer to what you
have asked for. and see what that
exercise does for the blending of your
will and your spirit. That's
interesting.
Thank you. Will this um will this tie
into the elevation of the needs to the
level of wants? Is that I mean is that
by tying in the blending of the spirit
and the will? Mhm. We thank you.
Fascinating. Thank you, Captain Bashar.
Shim.
Hello, Bashar. And to you, good day.
Welcome to our world. Oh, we thank you.
Speak up. Be bold so that all may share.
Okay, Dr. Pollen, here I come. Um, when
I met Daryl in San
Diego, I felt not that I was just
meeting Daryl. I felt an overwhelming
sense of love. All right. Was there
someone else there with him? Have I met
you before?
There have been passages through our
energy in dream encounter in dream
reality. But also you were sensing
crossovers between channel and yourself
and sensing crossovers with many aspects
of your own future self that are somehow
analogous to what we represent to you.
Did you understand that? Yes. You are
meeting aspects of your own future self,
recognizing aspects of your own higher
self that in some way operate on similar
frequencies to what we represent to you.
Okay? So in other words, the recognition
to put it simply was you recognizing
other aspects of yourself even though
there is to some degree some familiarity
with our energy in different dream
levels. Okay. Um my I have two
daughters. All right. One, two.
Donna is 20 and Deborah is seven. All
right. When Donna was very very small,
she told me that she had chosen me. Yes.
As her mother, she chose to be Everyone
does. And uh she when she said it, she
was really not in command of the English
language. She was not old enough to be
speaking in a solid sentence at that
time. If you say so. Uh well, obviously
she did. Thank you. Uh
babies babies usually she had only had
been limited at that point to just one
word or two. All right. When she said
it. Perhaps she didn't have anything
else to say. Right.
During her childhood guys, she kept
asking uh my husband and I for a baby
sister. All right. And she was very
angry at us that we were not complying.
And then when 13 years later when I uh
had Deborah Yes. Uh the
number a little late mother. All right.
But uh my youngest daughter Deborah, she
says she chose. Yes. But she's was not
she wanted to be closer to Donna. She
wanted to experience the physical
reality. I would guess you would say.
Yes. And are were they kindred sisters
uh before Donna left her and came down
first? Sometimes they have also been lovers
Sometimes they have also been lovers
many times.
Oh, interesting. All
All
right. The reason I say that is that my
daughter is experiencing uh a lot of
negativity towards the males in our
world. All right. And she feels that she could
All right. And she feels that she could
go through life completely without them.
And she is but she is worried that she
is not following what she intended when
she started when you may simply suggest
that she relax. First of all, it does
not necessarily allow an individual to
understand who they are to begin by
chipping away at themselves through
invalidation. If they do not leave
enough of themselves to observe, they
will not discover who it is they are.
Mhm. So the idea first of all is to
relax, not be so hard on the self, not
so hard. The idea can happen as has been
outlined that individual may not
necessarily have to interact with in the
way you are describing it males of your
species. Although we perceive that that
is not really going to be the case. The
idea primarily is that she simply needs
to come to terms with the idea of her
own masculine aspects. Blending those
polarities within herself will allow her
to breathe more easily and not so much
feel that she is being taken away from a
connection that she truly desires
something she had with her sister. Mhm.
Understand? Yes, I do. I do. I do
understand that. Thank you. One moment.
One moment. One moment.
that it is an ancient friend that if she
is willing to allow it can be of much
help in her dream state. For she has
interacted with that individual as a
male before and that friend in spirit
state can remind her much of the joy of
finding the blending of the polarity of
the male and the female within each and
every individual and that can allow her
perhaps more outward expression of that
idea in your physiological reality. You
may simply suggest that that friend is
there and will in a very gentle and
loving way, not forcing, not pushing
anything at all, simply have dialogue
with her and dream reality to allow her
to come to terms with her own
masculinity and her own femininity.
Understand? Yes. Thank you very much.
Well, thank you. Does that serve you?
Oh, yes, it it does. It answers a lot
more questions. All right. Thank you.
Then suggest to them both pleasant
dreams. Okay. Thank you. Thank you. Show
him.
Hi, Bashar. And good night. How you
doing? Perfect. And you? Uh, pretty
good. Pretty good. Pretty good. Pretty
good. Oh, yeah. Uh, before my question,
just cuz it it seems to keep coming up,
I read an article and it said that
ultimately the contacties do seem to
wind up with their feet firmly planted
just somewhere above the ground.
Perhaps simply on the soil of the new
fourth density Earth. Oh, okay. There
you go. That makes sense. Uh my question
is the the Dao universe and the beings.
I've been having some exchanges of
energy with them and I thought maybe you
could elaborate on them. They're quite
different than what I've experienced.
Yes. We cannot necessarily go much into
other universal realities at this time.
However, let us say they function as an
automatic on andoff switch to regulate
some of the functions taking place in
terms of exchange of energy in your
physiological universe. They are more
like a monitoring energy. Yeah, I do I I
do notice that when they show up, the
Plleadenss who were pretty headstrong
quiet up real fast. No need to look at
it that way. You are putting it back
into a melodramatic framework. That is
an earth interpretation of what is going
on in terms of the exchange of energy
and is not necessarily literally
representative of what is actually
taking place. Okay. Yeah, I understand
that. Also, I mean, are they physical
like us or they I mean I know they can
they can represent themselves that way.
Yeah. But ultimately not really. I mean
they're like this gaseous energy cloud.
Well, in a sense energy being. Yes. You
might interpret the idea as gaseous in
your reality, but that also would only
be an interpretation.
It might be more easily understood as
etheric. Etheric. Yes. Okay. Getting
into etheric. Can I mean is the
athetheric fragile? Can it be broken in
parts? Well, in a sense, we quote
unquote break it all the time in order
to interact with you because in many
ways we are also etheric. Mhm. But it
refyses it in our reality according to
our thoughts and our beliefs. Yes. Okay.
So getting back to the doubts I mean
they're just totally from another
reality another dimensional plane
altogether that is to some degree 90° of
a vector to those realities those
dimensional planes that you and I would
call physiologically real. Mhm. They are
a vector universe. How do they get here?
through the idea of phase shifting just
as we come into your universe. The idea
of changing your vibratory frequency to
match that of the universe in question
of visitation and to project a portion
of their consciousness in whatever way
seems to be most necessary to represent
their presence. Mhm. Their presence as
you perceive it is not even the totality
of the being. Right. Right. It is in a
sense but a finger to use an analogy. Do
they have ships? Not as you understand
it. No. But they do have cohesive
electromagnetic consciousness that
sometimes you may perceive as ships or
more often than not would choose to
perceive as simply spheres of light in
your reality. Right? Is are those
spheres I mean is that one being in
there or it's a mass consciousness? It
is a collective and at the same time it
is one male female or that polarity does
not really exist for them. So they just
they understand it as a necessary
representational face in your reality
and sometimes can put that face on. But
that is not to say that even if it
represents itself as a male or a female
that it actually sees itself that way.
Do they have physical technology like we
have or it's total uh you know mental
freedom? Not as you understand it except
in one dimension they would call their
dim past. Uh-huh. Can they one now at
this time would be sufficient to allow other
time would be sufficient to allow other
individuals to interact.
Oh, okay.
Sleep well. Okay. Thanks. Thank
you, Shim.
Hi, Bashar. And to you, good day. Good
day to you.
Um I feel fortunate in that um I
discovered I think pretty early on what
excites me. Oh all right. And uh that is
music. And yes and as time passed I
found out more specifically that um
songwriting in particular excited me.
All right. Uh I've experienced a lot of
inertia on my way to my goal and um I've
often found that I'm on a u not the same
frequency. All right. But uh that's not
really the what I came to address here.
All right, be direct. Uh about a year
and a half ago, I uh I had a problem
with my hearing. Actually, I'm still
experiencing this problem. And
um what it is is um I've volumes. I'm
very sensitive to any kind of volume at
all, especially in my left ear. And it
is uh as I said, very sensitive. that uh
I experiences a dampening and deadening
of sound at times and uh sounds like
I've got um broken eggshells in there.
And it's improved somewhat in a year and
a half and I I've seen a number of
doctors and uh uh they haven't helped me
at all but it as I said it's gotten
better. I wondering at this point if uh
I should interpret this problem with my
hearing as a uh uh how I should
interpret it. Is it a a sign that I'm
there's uh you are to some degree
breaking out of a shell h which has to
some degree muffled the sounds of the
reality you are breaking into. You are
to some degree still immersed in what
might be called embriionic fluid and
that also muffles the sound. Now this is
the metaphysical idea. Some of this idea
of your hearing can be assisted and
accelerated by what might be termed some
efficacious compounds, herbal compounds
that you may ingest to invigorate your
nervous system and those pathways that
your brain uses electrochemically
speaking to create the stimulation of
sonic perception. These you may find in some
perception. These you may find in some
of your literature if you simply allow
yourself to be attracted through
synchronicity to the ideas that you
need. The idea of quiet listening to
yourself in that way can improve that
ability. But mostly it is that you are
now passing through a membrane and this
membrane to some degree has been acting
as a buffer because you have come out of
a life wherein you believe that in this
life you needed some degree of
protection. You came into this life with
some degree of belief that you were
somehow extra sensitive and that coming
back into the physiological reality
would be too abrasive for you. to have
surrounded yourself with this embryionic
fluid out of which now you are just
recently beginning to emerge. You
understand? Yes. And uh that makes me
optimistic. Thank you. Uh so I I
shouldn't should I uh interpret this as
uh uh on a certain level that it's a
nerve damage that uh I've experienced.
Perhaps not a damage but simply shall we
say a resistance. A nerve resistance. Uh
one suggestion. Yes. One suggestion.
Yes, both to assist
your audio acuity and also to form an
analogy for your emergence from a
particular type of shell would be in
what you may call your countryside or
whatever it is that is peaceful to you
and quiet, pay close attention to the
sounds that your birds make. Listen to
that music and listen to the clarity of
the tone. There are sounds and patterns
and information within that that can
train your nerves to hear in specific
ways. Understand? Yeah. Yeah. And by
analogy will also assist you to spread
your wings and fly in that particular
sonic endeavor and to create your own
song in a perfect reflection of their song in
in a perfect reflection of their song in
a very natural way. So it all will be
pure of tone.
Well, that sounds like fun. I I would
enjoy doing that. All right. So, uh I I
don't have to interpret this as a a sign
that perhaps there's another area uh
that I could, as we said, there may be
some herbal compounds you can attract
yourself to that will assist you and
accelerate you in that
direction. The idea also to some degree
of applying some warmth or what you may
call heat to this area may also assist
you. Okay. Well, thanks for your help.
We thank you very much.
Good night.
Shoot him.
Hello, Bashar. Good day, Chakana.
Um, Altar has been coming up for me a
lot lately and I've gotten some
information about the civilization. I
want to clarify a couple of things for
you. All right. One of the things that I
felt is that there are underground
environments and they might be
considered to be zoos or almost like
biological labs that they take
representatives from other worlds and
bring them to their own planet and that
visitors can come and visit those
environments. You are looking at
something that is more of a holographic
representation. It does contain essence
of the actual individual's energy, but
it is not something that is actually
physiological. It is more of a
holographic projector that does in fact
contain true essence of an individual's
energy so that it seems as if they are
in your terms really physically there
but they are not really physically
there. It is an etheric projector so to
speak. Okay. system that allows them to
tap into the essence of the
understanding of any particular
individual but not in your terminology
at the expense of the individual's
physicality. Okay. But there are environments so to
Okay. But there are environments so to
speak, yes, of other worlds, energy
atmospheres created in that way for
examination, for understanding since
they in many ways function as a gate and
are doing their own research and
exploration of the many different
conduits and expressions of reality and
civilization that exist within the many
galactic realms as well as other
civilizations do. That is their way.
They bring the issue to them with their
atheric projectors. Okay, that's what I
thought. And do they have visitors that
come and to these environments now and
then? Mhm. So they don't physically uh
travel. They travel through not so much.
No. Through consciousness. One. Now this
is not going to necessarily make a lot
of sense to you. One aspect of their
consciousness does physically travel. One
travel. One
moment. The analogy. The analogy. The
analogy would be
similar, not identical, but similar to
the idea that if you were busy involved
in a project and one aspect of your
personality were out flying around
somewhere in a spacecraft observing
other things, but it would only be one
aspect that you would consider to be an
aspect of your personality, not
something that you would necessarily
consider to be a being on its own. You
would perceive that from them to be a
being on its own. But that being on its
own physiologically represented to you
as traveling in a ship is only one
aspect of their personality while they
are busy focusing on something else. It
is more like a probe of consciousness
that manifests to you as a physiological
being in a ship. Understand? Basically.
All right. Will that move?
Uh not really. No. Oh yeah. One other
thing about that. Um would they be
considered like recordke keepers? All
right. Yes, you can consider the idea of
those atheric projectors and all the
holographic matrices that they have
created to observe these ideas as a type
of holographic storage memory in a
sense. In that sense, yes. Let's put it
this way. You can say they have found a
way on some level to somewhat in
ethereal matter solidify the aashic
records. Understand? Yes. Yes. Very
much. Does that help you? Yes, it does.
And okay, one other thing about that um
are they is their civilization part of
the positive negative split off from
LRA? Is that their or No, not directly.
No, they have a completely different
idea of connection in that linear sense.
Okay. Thank you. Thank you very
Thank you.
Sh. Hello Bashar. And to you. Good day.
Hello Bashar. And to you. Good day.
Always a pleasure to be with you. And
you as well.
Um, this is a really silly problem and I
realize that's very selfish. Oh, but I'm
going to share it. I need I need some
advice. Before you continue, may I
remind you of something? Please do.
Thank you. Your original root word for
silly in what you may call your old
English is sailing, which means happy,
prosperous, and abundant. Oh, great. I
needed to hear that. I really did. So,
by all means, be silly.
Okay. Well, I find myself um in the last
year, I've moved about five times. Oh,
how active. Very active. And uh I
finally found the place of my dreams. I
visualized the place of my dreams. So, I
thought one detail I forgot to ask for
was a landlord that would allow me to
have overnight male guests.
So, I find myself a rock and roller in
Hancock Park playing out this modesty
play and having to defend my morality,
but I don't know what to do. Oh, yes,
you do. I do defend. No, not defend. Oh,
state. State. Not defend. But I've tried
that. I beg your pardon. I have done
that. Oh, yes. I've told him how I feel.
I know how he feels. And it's auspicious
as you mentioned earlier that you would
have a discussion on inertia because I
know there's a third point of view that
it just seems like I'm up against a
wall. I'm stop.
You like to fight. I do. I call myself
the warrior against presumption. All
right. Then remember you have been
literally physically a warrior many
times. Many times. Now you are a warrior
of peace.
Well, I want that. I don't want to
defend this thing. I don't want to. So,
what do I do? Just do what I want to do.
State be. Do you believe you're in
integrity? Totally. Then state and be.
Stand your ground. Well, what if he
throws me out? I don't own the place in
Hancock Park. I'm just We'll find the
next location. I know. I don't want to
move again. I haven't even unpacked yet.
May I remind you of something? Yes,
please. A warrior never stands still. Ah
A warrior is never where you expect her
to be.
A warrior moves with a wind.
I feel that way. I know. I just want to
relax a minute. Just take three months
to write some songs. The motion. Relax
into the waves you are creating in your
life. Relax into the ocean of your
energy. So, you think I should just back
off and try to find another place? Back
off. Be who you are, but do not make
such a contest out of it. And just
challenge it silently.
No, no, no, no,
no. What are all these words? Challenge.
Defend. Bees. Does the ocean have to explain or
Bees. Does the ocean have to explain or
defend itself? No. Do you understand?
Sort of. Sort of. What do I do? All
right. All right. But what do I do?
Sharpen your sword and put it away.
Do you understand?
Sharpen your sword and encase it in
velvet and love that.
and love that.
of your love guide you. Well, I was
sending him unconditional love last
night when he was talking to me, but it
wasn't getting through. I really don't
think it was. That's all right.
Again, the point is is that obviously
you attracted to yourself an opportunity
to simply state who you are without
getting involved in the feeling that it
has to be a conflict of points of view. Maybe Maybe
one moment.
One moment. One moment. I'm sorry. Oh,
you don't have to be sorry. Just one
moment. Okay, you got
it. Take a breath
in. Hold
it. Keep holding
it. Keep holding it.
Keep holding
it. Don't let it
out. Don't let it out.
Did you let a little out? I did. I'm so
I'm sorry. I did. You're what? I did. I
couldn't help it. Oh, you can't. Why
not? No, because you're so hysterical
sometimes. I had to laugh. But that's not the real
I had to laugh. But that's not the real
reason you couldn't hold it. Why
couldn't you hold it?
Um I don't know because it's natural to
breathe. That's
That's
why and it is unnatural to hold it like
that within you. Let it out. Okay. Let
yourself breathe into these
circumstances and these situations. You
have been told an analogy many times in
what you may call different types of
body technique to breathe into the pain
and that in many cases dissipates it.
Well, same idea with the circumstances
in your life. If you feel that they're
painful, if you feel they present
themselves to you in a painful way,
breathe into it. Breathe through it.
State who you are and breathe as the
ocean breathes. Dance within yourself the joy
breathes. Dance within yourself the joy
of life. Dance. Breathe in the idea.
Believe me, I'm I'm just happy to have
found someone I even want to be with cuz
it's not talking about settling for
less. We are talking about truly having as we
We are talking about truly having as we
did before what you want. But the idea
is that if you have attracted this kind
of circumstance, do not see it as a
conflict. You are simply jumping the gun
in the same way that you used to as a
warrior. And a challenge is fine if you
wish to call it that. But the idea does
not have to be seen even on that level.
The idea is that it is a gift. It is a
sharing. It is a learning. It is an
opportunity to see more and more of who
you are. An opportunity to allow you to
state more and more of who you are, to
state your integrity, and to allow the
circumstance to move you in that way.
You yourself already know that the
physiological circumstance isn't even
necessarily ideally representative of
where you want to be. No, I should have
asked for that house in Hancock Park.
All right. I should have asked for that
can be a part of the issue of your
expansiveness and your willingness to
really state who you are without having
to feel that you have to defend that as
if you are once again in this life like
before holding off the attackers from
the fort. Yeah. Well, the only thing
that I could I could um come up with
from my meditation on it was that
perhaps it sort of kept me from relaxing
again because I have a tendency to do
that with my career and I know I I have
the tools now to really push it and I
was ready to become the homemaker from
hell. You know, I was happy there and I
might have just sort of hung out and not
shot my tape. And so maybe that's what
it's for. Just to just to make me
realize that I don't have all the
freedom that I want and that I deserve.
All right. Very good. So maybe that's
it. But it still pisses me off. Why?
Because I can't. I I just can't handle
it immediately. Oh, yes you can. It's
just that you do not want to because you
like to fight. Oh,
I really don't. I swear I don't. I just
want to relax and have a good time. I
swear. I swear. Sure. Sure.
Sure. Sure.
All right. I believe you.
You're such a comedian. I love you.
Bring it out with me.
So, yeah. So, I'm going to get signed
and have channeling sessions at my home
in Hancock Park. All right.
And remember, you have done your share
of
defending. You can take a
break. It's all
right. You're not an indentured warrior
anymore. It's so funny you should say that. I've
It's so funny you should say that. I've
felt that about myself. I feel like I've
dressed for war every every time I
dress. I swear I do. I know. Feel that. I
I swear I do. I know. Feel that. I
know you weak of it. That's why we're
able to perceive
it. It is a nice energy. Very strong and
a very vital energy. Make no mistake
about that. But you are not in the heat of
that. But you are not in the heat of
battle anymore. I know. Your blood needs
to be I I want to be in the heat of
passion. Oh, thank
you. Now you understand what it means to
sharpen your sword and put it in a
velvet sheath. Heat of
passion. Oo, feel it. All right, I do.
Let that fire carry you. Let that fire
be your new sword.
All right. Thank you so much. Thank you.
Can I ask you about this new guy in my
life? No. Oh,
No. Oh,
that's all right. I like the package.
I'll unwrap it myself.
Thank you, Bashar. You will find I can
share this with you. You will find that
there may be some similar issues that
will come up that you will be able to
reflect and teach to that individual.
Yeah. And vice versa.
Oh, definitely vice versa. All right.
Thank you. Thank you, Bashar. Sh.
Hello, Bashar. Very good day to you. I
had two questions and I've gone back and
forth, back and forth. So, here it goes.
Um, you know how it is and and people
talk about a certain subject and you've
mentioned transformation many times. I
think transformation, okay, I know what
that is. I know what that is and it's
fine. And then all of a sudden one day I
go, I'm not sure what transformation is.
Oh, all right. And um as I understand
it, you have mentioned that
transformation is when you go from third
dimension to fourth dimension. Well,
that is one way going from one state to
another state. That's all. Okay. The
reason I'm asking is the question came
up. I've heard people who are talking
about a loved one who has passed away or
died in our reality. Yes. And they talk
about that as transformation. Oh yes.
And that is a form of transformation.
Absolutely. Okay. That's man mainly what
I wanted to know. Um in my dreams there
has been one symbol that has reoccurred
se several times over the last year. Oh
douche. And uh it is some form of a
slide. Uh like like in child's play in
the park the slide. Yes. And sometimes
it's been just me sliding down a hill.
All right. And I'm not sure what this is
to symbolize. How does it feel?
Well, it it feels good. It feels I I can
actually feel the acceleration, the air
in my hair
going down and out. Acceleration and
Okay. Do you feel that it shoots you in
the direction you prefer?
Well, I I hadn't really thought of it
that way. When you arrive at the bottom
of the slide, are you eager to get back
up and slide again? All always, always,
always. All right. All right. Yes. So
acceleration is something you enjoy.
Yes. Yes, it is. That's very
transforming. Oh, I see. Especially if
you do it as you have symbolized to us
in the manner of a child through
play through allowing your life to be
play in a childlike manner. Not
childish. Childlike.
Childlike. Yes. Childlike.
Well, I guess that that answers the
question then. Are you sure?
Um, well, I I don't know. You mentioned
about is it pointing me in the direction
I want to go and I
would say that I've been rather in a fog
is direction I really want to take with
my life. And what excites you the most?
I've heard this question over and over.
And someday it finally clicks.
I I I that's what I've been hoping for,
that the day would come. I feel like,
you know, here I am in my 40s and it
still hasn't clicked and I'm beginning
to wonder, well, when is it going to
click? I'll tell you when. When you take
the slide and point it in the direction
you prefer to and do not just leave it
up to chance,
point the slide and you do not just let
it deposit you where it will. Where it
will. It brings back into the idea
conscious commandment. Discover your
commandment. Discover your
preferences, state them, and move in
that direction as if you deserve them
unquestionably because you do simply
because you have been able to conceive
of them. you deserve them. Point your
slide in that direction, in whatever
direction you prefer to. The idea is
that it does come to you, but it doesn't
come to you until you send it.
Remember that everything that comes to
you in your life is an echo of a sound
you send out first.
So, use the slide as a tool. Oh,
absolutely. I see. Absolutely. Decide
what excites you.
decide and then act in that direction.
Understand? I will. Yes. Oh, I'm not
telling you you have to. It's not an
order. No, it's it's a conscious. All
right. Talk to myself. Thank you very
much. Okay. Does that serve you? Yes, it
does. All right. Thank you. So, you at
this tiring, you may all enjoy a short
break. We'll resume contact in
approximately 10 to 15 of your minutes. [Music]
How's it going?
There's refreshments in the other room.
Please remember what uh 10 to 15 minutes
when I call you, please come back. Could
we get it?
A continue. Hello, Bashar. And to you,
good day. Well, Henry and I had a great
trip in the American West. Oh, what? And
we went through Sedona and Zion and
Jackson, Wyoming. Oh, what? and uh had
some wonderful conversations with some
davas and energies. All right. And um I
just wanted to share with you that uh
while we were in Sedona, we had one
night and we didn't know where the
vortexes were. So we found a
metaphysical bookstore and I saw this
one book on the shelf that said Sedona
vortexes, right? And it was about And
you found them all in the book? Well,
the book fell off the shelf which was
above my head and into my hand when I
asked Henry, "Do you think we should buy
the book?" Right. So, I saw this in a
Shirley Mlan movie a while ago, and I
thought, "This thing, this really
doesn't happen." But it does happen. I
um and we went to because you are a
vortex as well and draw all things to
you that you need. Are we all vortexes
though in that sense? Yes. Okay. Uh so
Henry and I in one day went to three out
of the four vortexes and he had some
wonderful little uh energy experiences
and I had a pleasant day hiking. And um
I was just wondering how our
electromagnetic field is coming along.
Coming along. Uhhuh.
Um if you had any insights or sharing.
Nice little electromagnetic field. Come
along now.
Don't lag behind.
Well, you know, I thought I'd
experienced something great in Sedona,
and all I had were some Indian dreams
where I recreated a few past lives here
and there. That was all.
Who are you? So, um I was just curious
as to anything you might want to share
on um the vortexes, which I I'm not
going to let you get away with this now.
Your electromagnetic field is far too
strong for this.
All right. Um,
Um,
how do the dreams allow you to
feel? What statements can you make about
yourself now that you did not make before your
now that you did not make before your
trip?
It allowed me to see that whatever I ask
for, I can create. All right. And when I
was in Sedona, I asked to
uh see the life I had as an Indian chief
because I felt very strong and I got it.
All right. And it was so powerful that
by 3:00 or 4 in the morning, I asked it
to please stop so I could sleep. All
right. So, I really see that whatever I
choose to want to
create, it it can be created. You mean
you get what you want when you want it?
Yes. And so you better be careful what
you ask for
because does that mean you don't trust
yourself? Uh means. Well, now you're
making a joke.
Always a joke. All right, I'm laughing.
Okay.
I just learned how powerful I really am.
Oh, thank you very much. What could I
possibly add to that? Absolutely
nothing. Thank you. I love you very
much. I love to you. Thank
you. Ah, okay. Ah, okay.
Sh.
Hello, Bashar. And to you, good day. My
name is Sasha Vasque and I was here
exactly a year ago. All right. And uh
thanks to you, a lot of things has been
happening in my life. Thanks to you as
well. Obviously, it's your life. That's
true. Uh one of them was which
uh at the time seemed like impossible
and it happened. I did go back to my
roots back to Russia and it happened
exactly in a precisely in the time frame
which you gave me and it was uh that was
s sensational. Thank you for co-creating
the timing with us. Uh I have a
question. All right. Uh when you say um
to create um to see the life or the the
professional lifestyle you want to live.
Yes. Um I'm having troubles being a
comedian. Um beginning I'm having
trouble seeing myself in a lifestyle
which um uh successful one would leave
at that time doing Vegas doing big time
comedy shows because I do not know. I'm
not uh I'm not familiar with the I can't
see myself in it. Yeah. Is that what you
really want to do? Uh being a comedian?
Yes. All right. How much does it excite
you? A lot. Does it tickle you? Oh, boy.
Does it make you laugh? Yes. All right,
then. Can you not take the feeling and
translate that feeling into some sort of
imagery? Can you not take the feeling as
if you already were on that stage, wrap
yourself in that atmosphere, let the
feeling unfold as the audience before
you and see yourself and feel yourself
transferring that feeling to them. It
does not have to be
orthodox at all. Remember that what may
prevent you from seeing the idea is that
you may have an expectation of exactly
how you think you have to go about it in
order to be
successful. Don't think in orthodox
ways. You're not orthodox at
all. Catch me so far? Yes, sir. Sir.
Oh, sorry. The last question is uh now I
want to go back to Russia as a comedian
and producer. Do you see do you see that
happening? As soon as you understand
that it's all right for you to be
unorthodox in that setting.
All right. So all I have to see the
audience laughing and uh that would be
enough. It can help you to discover your
methodology of expression. Simply all we
are saying is that what prevents you
from seeing it now may be because you
still have some expectations about
exactly how you think you have to do it
in order to get through to them. Let
yourself relax your definitions of what
you think the idea of that type of
sharing is and let yourself be the
unique and unorthodox you you actually
are. Of course you can do it if you
relax the definitions you think they
expect you to
be. How about a little spontaneity
and a time? That's all right. Thank you
very much. We thank you very much. By
the way, we're all laughing a lot. Good
at what you have to share with us.
Laughter of joy. All you need to do is
realize that what you're doing is
performing a service by allowing them to
lighten up.
That's great. Thank you. We thank you
very much.
shedding. Hello, Bashar. Hello to you. Good day.
Hello, Bashar. Hello to you. Good day.
So, I have an idea. I wanted All right.
I love to play and I wanted to play a
game with you. Oh, all right. I wanted
to create One moment. One moment. I am
telling everyone else that is crowding
in now to back off a little bit.
Everyone got very excited about that
idea, about that offer.
So, that is more than just myself
willing to play. Do continue.
Good. Because it's an interdimensional
game. Oh, yes. Yes. Yes. I want to
create a matrix. All right. And the
invitation is to get inside the matrix.
I'm in it. And spin. I'm spinning. Wait,
I haven't created the matrix yet. Oh,
but you did. Oh, you got all of them.
Ready? Okay. Andromeda as a as a
facilitator for all stellar
uh consciousness in this quadrant. Yes.
Crystal sarcophagus, Hawaii, crystal
skull, angelic, my neck, phase shifting,
and tetrahedrrons. Oh, okay. Nice. Okay.
And get
inside. Spin. Yes. And tell me what you
see. [Music]
[Music]
And then I have a question.
Do you wish to repeat each one and hear
the answer? Yes, very much. Okay.
Andromeda, conviction,
crystal sarcophagus,
eternity, Hawaii, love, light, and laughter.
Hawaii, love, light, and laughter.
Crystal skull, interdimensional
selves, and associations with past
relations. Angelic, Angelic,
an expansive
compassion for all that is my neck.
Delving deep within the channels of high
electromagnetic activity,
phase shifting,
turning around and being surprised by
the unexpected at every given moment
that you create to exist.
and tetrahedrrons
giving birth to another reality.
And one more. Yes. Dolphins. Dolphins as
a global consciousness
wrapped in a blanket of love.
It's beautiful. And peeking out from
beneath the blanket and
laughing and inviting you in.
So I I
I know most of the what you saw already.
Yes. Is there something some way that
you can expand that matrix to key me?
I'm number 13 on this list. Yes. Yes.
Yes. Yes. The transformational number.
Yes. Of course. Be the matrix itself
because you do in fact contain it all.
Yes. Remember yourself as holographic. I
just had that experience. Yes. You know
that. Yes. Okay.
Wait, one question. Yes. About
tetrahedrrons. Yes. Um the last time I
asked you these questions, the tape
blanked out. Blank. Blank. Yes. Blank.
Blank. And um the technical questions
keep coming up for Well, the question is
how do I measure
the accuracy? You said they need to be
extremely precise and accurate. How in
terms of rendering them into crystal
formations perhaps? Yes. Depends upon
what you want to do with them. Well, I
want to do a very big one and be in, you
know, do things inside of it. Do things.
All right. 33 ft. Okay. Yes. All right.
Okay. So, you said that the precision is
really important. How do I know how
precise? The ratio. The ratio.
Equilateral. That's all. That's all.
Yes. And how do I measure the effect?
in the acceleration that takes place
within your synchronous reality. So I
can uh just go on my own intuitive are
the strongest barometer. You are the
strongest electromagnetic needle. So I
can I can just make this thing just and
then just you do you know what I mean?
what I'm saying
sort of kind of
and and it'll be exactly the way I
imagine it to be. Yes. Because it is the
tetrahedral structure, the basic
building block of your dimensional
reality. And when you create it to be
equilateral in all directions, then you
will be creating a symbolic
template and you yourself will be that
actual template. you will carry that
imagery with you and you will be able to
use it in whatever way, shape or form
you want to. So every time I come up
against this uh technical blank, I can
just make it up and trust that within my
own intuitiveness that yes, it will
either work for you that way or it will
lead you into the formation that will or
lead me to people that will fill in
those blanks. Of course, because now you
see, because of your recognition that
you are holographic, the whole idea is
to truly begin to use all the resources
you already have at your disposal all
around you, all of you. And and related
to that is the mathematics. Yes. Um is
it true that when you've in your
vibration into post language, let's say, yes, what
into post language, let's say, yes, what
h has happened to the mathematics? They
are also intuitive and instinctive. They
are seen now mostly as the idea of ratio
relationships between different
dimensional states.
So that's where I can create it. Yes. In
other words, let me put it this way. The
tetrahedral structure now to us is the
only mathematical framework we need. It
is all the equations we have ever
written rendered into one geometric
understanding. So, so by actually being involved in
So, so by actually being involved in
this, it's taking it to that level. Yes,
you can extrapolate as you say
backwards, unfold from a tetrahedral
structure every single equation you have
ever written in your physics and your
mathematics. It is all infolded within
that shape. But I don't have to get
there through the language. I can just
go right there. Absolutely. Okay. And
one last question is in this in this
whole polarity blending that we're
doing. Yes.
As we ex let's just take night and day.
Night and day. In your blendingness, how
do you experience the blend of that
polarity? Let's say on your planet where
you do you experience night and day and
well yes we are still physiological
beings and being in the surface world of
our environmental reality we can still
experience the idea you call night and
day. However, also there is the
experience of what you would call dream
time, which is more like the astral
state where its neutral formation is
more like a gray fog. Got it. Got it.
That's great. Thank you. Thank you very
much. It is, shall we say, the soup out
of which anything can materialize.
Got it. Thank you very much. Lots of
love. Thanks. All the love to you.
Shedding. Good evening, Bashar. And to you, good
Good evening, Bashar. And to you, good
day. I had a question regarding phase
shifts. Shifts. Phase shift. Yes. I am
experimenting with a technique that that
takes me through phase shifts in this
life. Back to moments in time. Forward
in moments in time. Takes me to other
other dimensions. Yes. Takes me to the
past wave distant past. And I'm finding
these shifts very uncomfortable.
Why? Well, because I I have always uh led
Well, because I I have always uh led
with my mind and they they uh I'm having
a hard time explaining them to myself. I
see. May I ask you a question? Yes. Are
you enjoying interacting with me? Yes.
What do you think you're doing but phase
shifting right now? Because I am in
another dimensional state. Yes. Well,
well, all these other people are doing
it too, so it feels better. If I do it
by myself, it doesn't feel so good.
I beg your pardon, as you say. But even
though all these other people are doing
it, too. You're still the only one. And
that's true for every single individual.
It's always both. Remember, remember,
remember, it is always both. It doesn't
have to be this or that. It's this and
that. Understand?
In other words, an individual upon your
planet share with us one time a very
exciting way to look at a particular
word and to pronounce that particular
word and the particular word could be
pronounced alone or all
one which means you are never alone and
yet at the same time you are all one and
so there is only one
I follow that depends on how you look at
it therefore and that's the whole point
of phase shifting it's how you look at
it phase shifting is only a point of
view because remember you don't actually
go anywhere. Nobody really moves. Not
fundamentally. All motion is your
illusion of
continuity. Everything manifests from
you within you. You don't actually ever
really go anywhere. right where you are
right now. If you were to remove all the
ideas of every dimensional reality you
could conceive of, you would find that
you are right now where you have always
been forever and where you will always be
forever and where you will always be
forever. It's just that all the
realities you experience in a sense
orbit around you, move through you so to
speak and even that in a sense is an
illusion real while you're in it. We are
not discounting it as a reality because
that's what reality is point of view.
But you don't actually go anywhere. When
you phase shift, it is simply the same
idea as being able to take a step. You
have to phase shift in order to have the
illusion of moving through a room on
your planet because those are discrete
moments of creation. Discreet now. Now
it is here. Now it is here. Now it is
here. Now it is here. That is a phase
shift. Understand? It's that simple. All
you're talking about is a matter of
degree. You do it all the time. Yes,
that's true. What I would like to leave
behind is this this this the feelings
that go with it. Well, remember that
feelings are reactions to what you
believe. So, what are your definitions
that would cause such negative feelings?
Uh, redefine it in a positive way and
you cannot have a negative emotional
reaction to it. Maybe maybe it's that I
think that I should just be one place
one time. No. All right. In a sense, you
are the one place you have always been,
which is every place, which is every
place. So, you are at one of the same time
So, you are at one of the same time
everywhere and specifically precisely
where you perceive you are in that
particular reality in which you exist.
So, if I played with that belief, it
would feel better. Yes. Play with it by
all means. Let it talk to you. You can
talk to your beliefs. You know, you can
talk to your definitions. They'll talk
to you. personalize them and let them
talk to you.
There's one one of these spaceships that
I would like some help with. There's an
eagle head that keeps coming out of the
top of my head. All right. Could you
give me any information on that? Well,
obviously to some degree it is a
connection to the idea of your ability
to soar. It is an astral representation.
To some degree it is a symbol of the
next phase, a step up, learning to fly.
In that sense, it is the whole issue of
the phase shifting in and of itself
because if you see with the eyes of the
eagle symbolically, you are really
seeing quite piercingly into other
dimensional realities. You
understand? The idea is to let yourself
fly. Let yourself phase into that
reality because you have experienced
that reality in what you may call Native
American associations in many ways. Let
yourself be that symbol. Let yourself
identify with that symbol and at the
same time allow yourself to remain
grounded. Understand? Yes. Remember this. When the
Understand? Yes. Remember this. When the
eagle animal detaches itself quote
unquote from the branch of a tree or an
overhanging cliff and takes to the air,
it knows it is not disconnected from the
earth. Understand? Mhm. Mhm. So allow
yourself to realize that the only
unsettling notion may be that your phase
shift may make your ego feel like it has
no footing. Mhm. But it does. It's
always connected. Always. Understand?
Yes. Does that help you? Yes. I think it
will when I when it settles in. Settles
in another phase shift. All right. Okay.
Thank you very much. Thank you very
much. Shedding.
Good evening Bashar and do you a good
day. Could you tell me what is the origin of
Could you tell me what is the origin of
the Catholic Church? Origin of Catholic
Church only in some aspects. All right.
idea that particular
[Music] religion derived from very ancient
religion derived from very ancient
Druidic
practices remnant of Atalantean
civilization, hierarchy,
priesthood, handed down misunderstood
notions in many ways of the idea
of hierarchy over
congregation. also immersed some in
ancient druidic rituals of connection to
earth. any what you may call ancient
quote unquote pagan rituals now embodied
in what you may call Catholic ritual and
redefined to
fit notions that were created by many
different councils, many different
leaders, many different members of what
it ought to be sociologically,
economically, politically.
Mostly it is one of the offshoots as is
many of the other religions on your
planet of ancient Atlantean priesthoods
but went through a phase redefinition
through druidic practices and
emerged in areas upon your planet that
would
support the definitions of intermingling
of not only the ancient druidic
practices but also some of the
interminglings that took place. a few of
your thousand years ago with many, shall
we say, Orion
incarnations in certain
levels, especially where rules,
regulations are
concerned, especially where structure is
concerned, especially where what you may
call very deep and heavy energy is
concerned, was to some degree reaction
to some of the negativity spawned in the
sinking and the destruction of Atlantis.
the idea of placing a very stronghold
upon certain aspects of the
will so that through that belief it
would be believed that you would regain
connection to the
infinite through suppression through
order through
domination. Understand? Yes, I do. Does
this assist you? Yes, it does.
Is that sufficient? Yeah, that's all
right. Are you sure?
Are you sure?
No, I'm not. All right. What else would
you like to explore?
Well, it's pretty popular belief that
there's a certain person in history who
instituted that commonly known as uh
Jesus. Oh, no, no, no,
no. The
individuals around that
individual have instituted it to some
degree. not that individual. That was
never the intention of that
individual. But you see the idea is at
that point the individuals which you may
call disciples and
apostles were
also full of the knowledge of some of
the ancient druidic practices at that
time. And simply their interpretation of
what you call the Jesus, the
association, the Christ consciousness
was dispensing was interpreted according
to some of those ancient practices,
those ancient understandings and
interpreted through that flow line into
the basic structure you now
have. That was that understanding at the
time of the arrival, the projection, the
intersection of the Christ consciousness
through that particular manifestation.
It was not the intention of the Christ
consciousness to establish that
particular type of structure. It was the
intention of the individual surrounding
that individual because that was their
understanding at the time based on what
they already had learned of some of
these ancient practices and they were
simply to some degree in their own
understanding continuing the lineage but
there was much
misinterpretation or shall we simply say
interpretation of the
times understand? Yes. Does that help
you? Yeah, it does. Um, if this
individual Jesus had uh manifested
himself on say a different location on
the planet, it did not specifically what
you may call the Jesus, but the Christ
consciousness has manifested on your
world many times physiologically. It is
also known as Buddha nature and many
other names. Native American
woka. Many many manifestations have
taken place including what you call your
physiological Mary, the female polarity
of the Christ
consciousness.
Yes. All right. Um,
yeah, you answered my question before I
asked it. Thank you.
[Music]
Hello, Bashar. And good day to you. Good
day to you. I want to thank you for this
last year and for the many interactions
that you brought. Oh, there's many more.
The last one,
especially tonight. Oh, all right. I
feel and have been um experiencing such
high levels of excitement that I
sometimes feel like I'm going to
explode. Oh, me too. And I do.
It's fun, huh? Yes.
I would like to share with you. All
right. Oh, an idea. Oh. All right. And perhaps
Oh, an idea. Oh. All right. And perhaps
participate in a co-creation with you.
Perhaps. Perhaps. One of the things that
I find infinitely exciting is the
creation and the planning and the design
of environments and facilities and
events that bring about growth. Well,
thank you for for people specifically
for children. All right. And I'm sure
they appreciate it infinitely. I think I
appreciate it the most though. All
right. Uh my question
is realizing that we are absorbed in
third density and are you are quasi
third fourth now
and wanting
to find the bridge to assist bridge
bridge bridge bridge bridge implies
there is a gap I sense
that well the gap that I sense is that
which is between what is actually
happening now let's say specifically for
children. Yes. And that which is the
ideal. Can you define the so-called
ideal? Um, and before you answer, can
you on your own level in your own way
perform the ideal
whether anyone else is or not. Yes.
That's where the excitement has has been
triggered is those times when those
moments are just so special and so real
and validating for all of us times right
it's more and more of the time it's
there is no gap per se not for you
doesn't have to be and the more you do
it the more you make it possible for
everyone else to do if they want to
because you will be a living and shining
example could you share what uh the reality for
could you share what uh the reality for
children is on Essani.
Oh, the idea is that by what you term
the three years of physical age that
have been reached, they will be in your
terms relatively independent. They will
interact with whatever individuals they
choose to interact with to learn, as you
say, on the job whatever they wish to
know. That does not necessarily mean
that they will take up the physiological
manifestation exactly in the same way
that what you might call an adult would
be doing it. But they will go and
attract themselves to the teachers and
the sharers and the learners that they
need to attract themselves to. We are
all telepathically connected. We know
where they are. No one is ever out of
sight in that sense. And since the
adults are the parents of all and since
the children are the children of all,
everyone is always within the family.
But by what you call the third year of
age, they are off and learning as you
say, absorbing whatever they wish to
absorb to be the person they have chosen
to be within our societies. Very
ecstatic, very nurturing and very loving
in that way. You might say asani is one
big playground.
Does that help? Yes, that helps. I am I
guess curious. Yes. All right. Well,
your curiosity is what drives you. Yes.
Yes, definitely. Um,
is there is there a way that from my own
self and the experiences that I'm
experiencing with children and the
opportunities that I have to share that
which are becoming very broad that some
of those fourth density realities can be
brought into reality for our children
here. The more you allow them to
experience with all their senses, the
more you allow them to interact, the
more you create environments in which
they can in fact interact and experience
many different dimensional levels of
reality, the more they will be able to
absorb, the faster they can, in your
terms, grow, and the more they will know
it is all right to experience a
diversity of things. You understand?
Yes. Yes. In other words, give them
validation too. Oh, absolutely.
Absolutely. And provide for
them anything your imagination believes
would create
inspiration and love of self,
absolute self validation.
Understand? Yes. Teach them that they
are in fact as powerful as they need to
be to create whatever they want without
having to hurt anyone else or themselves
in order to create it. Yes. Yes. Yes,
and that will do the job. Thank you. And
remember that of course they are
teaching all of you many things
constantly. Constantly. We thank you.
Thank you. Good night. One [Music]
[Music]
moment. All right.
Okay. You are wave upon wave of radiant
energy. Be at the center of
Be at the center of
yourself. Know you are the
center, the eye of
creation through which
creation learns to see itself in all the
ways that are possible to see.
You, us, all beings in creation are all
the ways it is possible to
see. Be the waves that beat upon the
shore of your own reality. Changing with
love, changing with
touch, changing with
involvement, changing with time and
space. All the ideas you have ever been, all
All the ideas you have ever been, all
that you
require is to find that place of power.
All that you require is to feel that
place of power. All that you are is that
place of power. Be the imaginations that
you were designed to be. For do remember
an imagination is not something that you
have. of an imagination is what you
are. You are a dimension unto
itself. We radiate our love. We radiate
our pulse. Feel the pulse. Feel the
heart. The universal beat that
synchronizes all beings in love and
light. Feel the pulse.
We wash through you as you wash through
us. We bid
you the stars. [Music]
At this time, allow us to extend to you
our deepest
gratitude and our experience of you. And
we thank you for your
cocreation of our experience of
ourselves. Our love to you all and a
fond good day. [Applause] [Music] Hey, thank
How'd it go?
Was that the galactic at the end, Darl?
Yes. Uh Bashar announced
um Christmas the week before Christmas
Eve that there would be energy
representative of the collective
consciousness of the entire association
which he labeled galactic and that's
what you heard there at the end
representative of the 360 planetary
civilizations of which we are becoming
members of.
Thank you all very much for being here
tonight.
Come on, you deserve it. Thank you all.
If you want a copy of tonight's tape,
please see Pamela around the corner. And
anything else, I'll be at the desk at
the front. We'll be here next Thursday
and the next Thursday and the next
Thursday.