I say how are you all this evening of
your time as you create time to
exist allow us to begin this interaction
this evening of your time with the
reminder that last week of your time we
entitled this interaction the
Legacy I will be speaking about what
that refers to but this evening of your
time I will be taking my turn second at
the end of the interaction of this
evening of your time will I then speak
about the idea that we have termed the
Legacy as it involves the idea of
connections of your
civilization and our civilization and
some of the underlying reasons for why
our particular interactions with you
have been co-created by us and we will
outline some of the ideas for who you
are to us who we are to
you there will be however another who
will speak first in this place in which
I usually speak first
between that interaction and my
interaction will be what you call the
typical format of interaction between
you and myself in the question
modality but allow us
first to allow another
energy to share with
you some of the things that would be
most important in this interaction this
evening of your time to understand stand
especially for what it
represents in terms of your willingness
your ability your absorption of the
information we have been sharing with
you for the past 4 and one half years of
your accounting and with regard to how that
accounting and with regard to how that
information can be applied in your
physiological reality in stronger ways more deliberate
reality in stronger ways more deliberate
ways more conscious ways one moment [Applause]
we would have you understand that this
is a blending as well we would have you
understand that this is a representation
not only of all the civilizations you
have understood as the association of
Worlds but of the very fabric of which
all worlds are created we would have you
understand that we would share with you
this evening of your time as you
understand time to exist our view of the
flame of Eternity that each and every
one of you is individually and are
collectively we would have you
understand our joy and our love at being
able to express ourselves this way
through you this day of your time we
would have you understand that it is our
recognition that your world is changing
much we would have you understand that
all things you have ever heard within
all of these
interactions are simply points of view
we would have you understand that your
point of view is just as precious
and just as beautiful as any point of
view that we have ever encountered and
any point of view that we contain we
would have you understand that we
rejoice in your willingness to share we
rejoice in your willingness and your
choice to grow to learn to expand as
your representative facet of the
infinite we would have you understand in
this way that you and all beings within
creation are created of the substance of
the infinite we would have you you begin
to feel this to feel this in what you
may call a physical way we would have
you understand that all of the ideas all
of the definitions all of the
nomenclature all of the variables in the
equation of your existence are all
interchangeable we would have you
understand that you have always been are
now and always shall be mirrors of all
other Consciousness within creation on
the whatever level you choose to exist
within the Fab of existence itself we
would have you understand that the flame
that you are Burns eternally and shall
never go out no matter how bright you
allow yourself to become we shall have
you understand that you exist now and
always shall and you always have because
now is the only time and the only place
and the only existence there is and
always has been and ever shall be you
are Eternal you are infinite you are
Spirit you are body you are mind you are
heart you are soul you are an idea you
are an expression you are a thought you
are a dream of the Infinite Creation but
that is reality and all reality is
couched within your dream you contain it
all you are the whole expression in your
own individualized way you are the
Matrix The Matrix is you you are
everything everything comes from you
everything gives birth to you as you
reinforce the existence of everything
and everyone not one of you not one of
you in that sense can be removed from
the Matrix without the collapse of the
entire structure you are integral in
that way you are essential in that way
and we would have you understand that
because you are interconnected in this
way because everything you do has impact
within the entirety of creation that you
deserve to exist in this way and you
deserve to be the fullest individual you
can imagine yourself to be that you
deserve to manifest all the things you
can conceive of that you deserve the
existence you have been given or it
would not have been granted to you that
you deserve all the love you can imagine
because love is what you are made out of
that you deserve all the light you can
create in your life because light is
what you are made out of we would have
you understand in this way that
communication can be given freely
between you and that all that is
required is the idea of honesty honesty
with the self and that the only barriers
that exist to the idea of all the love
and all the understanding and all the
joy and all the communication of the
information you desire the only barrier
to this is twofold and that is the idea
of ignorance and arrogance allow
yourself to understand allow yourself to
create allow yourself to be who you know
you are for that gift is given to you
for that right is given to you for it is
the very fabric of your existence you
are made of that energy you are that
energy energy and all reality that you
experience is not separated from you we
would have you understand all these
things and all these things have been
discussed in all the interactions you
have had for the past four and one half
of your years of time but these things
now these things are to be applied in
your life these things are to be applied
in the life that you chose for it is
made with your choice it is done with
your choice it is manifested with your
choice it is acted out with your choice
it is felt with your choice it is
experienced with your choice and nothing
occurs without it being your choice
whether you create that to be in your
conscious or your unconscious
mind you are beings of
choice all that is the Infinite Creation
the fabric of existence chose
you chose that you should
exist chose you consciously chose
you you are in that way therefore
blessed and we would have you understand
that simply because of the fact that you
exist you are blessed for you are
created out of divine material out of
Divine Light you are the infinite
Creator and your existence was a
conscious decision a conscious thing a
conscious Choice act in like manner be of like
Choice act in like manner be of like
mind respect yourselves love yourselves
unconditionally for out of unconditional
love were you created and out of
unconditional love shall you create
anything you
desire know your integrity manifest your
integrity manifest your honesty it is
your sharpest sword the sharpest weapon
you have ever had but now it is a weapon
of Peace a weapon of Joy a weapon of
love and a weapon only in the sense that
it will cut through all manifestations
that are what you do not
desire begin to feel the wave of your
connection begin to feel the energy of
your interlinking with all thought forms
all Consciousness all civilizations all
eyes all ideas all mind all Hearts all
Soul all spirit is one and you are one
within that sea within that
pool know that you are the fabric and
the essence of the galactic energy know
that we are SU stained know that we are
supported by your Endeavor by your
existence know that we love you because
we know you have given birth to us we
give birth back to you we remind you in
this giving of birth that you can be
anything you desire to be that is our
gift to your birth to be born as anyone
any time anywhere anyhow you so desire
that is our gift to remind you anything
that you choose to be sustains our
existence sustains the fabric of the galactic
sustains the fabric of the galactic
connection you are the rotating Stars
you are the essence of the Spiral of the
Galaxy in which you
inhabit of all creation that you are
that extends from you that issues forth
from you that is projected from you
within yourself for you are everywhere
and there is nowhere else to be but
where you are now everything is within
you there is no outside as you have been
there is no outside as you have been
reminded time and
again now all time collapses into one
now all space collapses into one any
moment you so desire you can be within
the total here and now you can live your
life in that
way events upon your planet events
within your solar system are now
accelerated and within what you call a
2year span of time there shall be much
explosion of Consciousness upon your
world much explosion of the connections
that you have to other worlds within the
galactic substance within the galactic
frame but these connections and these
recognitions all are secondary to your
recognition of your connections to
yourself recognitions of the connections
of yourself to the infinite of yourself
as the infinite for you are the infinite
even as we are the infinite in our own
way you are the infinite in your own way
and and we treasure you and cherish you
wave after wave of love always is
pulsing feel the spinning of the Galaxy
in your heart and in your mind and in
your soul it is a deep and rumbling
sound a deep and thorough sound a deep
and stirring sound allow it to Bubble
forth allow it to bring forth the
understanding of your self honesty
yourself Clarity your Insight and
inspiration for you are all of these as
well we remind you of these things that
you do not need to be reminded of simply
because that is the way you have
chosen but now put them into action put
them into
life be more than just the word be the
thing be the idea be the deed Clare and
honest as a deed
feel in the beating of your heart that
it keeps Pace with the Rhythm and the
pulse of the spinning of all the
galaxies of the fabric of existence
itself of the universal heart of
Infinite Creation for you all beat within that
Creation for you all beat within that
heart and not a one of you is outside
the heart of all that
is you are the blood and the life force
of of God
itself it is your force and your life as
well you are it and it is
you out of your
dreams be
born out of your
heart be
alive out of your
soul be
light for you are nothing else we thank [Music]
you within this idea of the sharing of
the energy of the galactic allow
yourself to begin to feel the threads
that intertwine you all and understand
that your threads are others threads
that you are made of the same threads it
is simply a different tapestry that you
have woven out of the very same threads
a different picture you have painted out
of the very same
pigments a different scene you have
written on the very same Pages the very
same paper the very same ink but a
different
play we extend to you at this
time once again our deepest and most
heartfelt appreciation and love in
allowing us to experience you in the way
you have created yourself to be and in
the way you shall choose to create
yourself and we would remind you that
there are many upon your
planet with many different beliefs they
are all to be loved they are all to be
cherished even if they are not what you
prefer remember as from the vibration of the
remember as from the vibration of the
galactic the only thing that stands in
the way of your open communication and
your ecstatic
Joy is your willingness to choose
ignorance or
arrogance balance in the center and all
things shall flow to you for that is
your Birthright and it is part
one of your
legacy the rest of which we will
discuss later at this
later at this
timing allow us once again
to extend to
you our deepest service in what way at
this time may we help and may we
shine hi um and a good day to you good
day I'm not as nervous this time as I
was last time we thank you very much for
transforming your nervousness into
excitement okay I'm very sad that um
you're not going to be doing this why
because um after what has just been said
well do you not recognize that you are
giving birth to yourself and that you
have the capacity to connect in by being
an equal with us to all the energy that
we have at our dispensation and Disposal
do you realize you are not cut off do
you realize that you are becoming
one well you know having the capacity
and and being able but but you being
there and are the key to tuning into
that vibration and like you know having
your tapes and listening to you all the
time it's like you're a friend at that
highest level you shall never lose our
friendship and we are not done
interacting with all of you it is simply
that we are now commencing a different
format and in many ways you will
understand the wisdom of this for we
have done this with many worlds we know
what we are
doing if you wish I will put it in the
following way and I do not mean this in the
way and I do not mean this in the
fashion you would call egotistical but
if you are reinforcing to me that you
trust who I am and that is why you are
sad to quote unquote lose that
friendship then understand that the
choices we are making in changing the
timing must also be something that you
trust okay I do trust that thank you
okay now then be of joy that we are now
changing because the change is
representative of the changes within you
we do not make these changes arbitrarily
we make them because because we see
within you the growth and the fact that
you do not need us in this way the idea
also is to remember that anything and
everything you have all always felt from
us has actually been your own energy and
now we're giving you an opportunity to
understand that you can recreate that
feeling anytime anywhere on your own
because it has always been your own
energy that you have felt not ours
directly we have given you a template to
match we have given you a challenge to
identify with
if you have felt our energy it is
because you have matched it and it means
you can match it any time any place so
do so and in that sense we will be there
but you will be more fully there and
that is more
important okay now could I have one
little quick question absolutely okay I
wish this I wish I had earlier time that
I had asked this because it doesn't seem
like the right night but it's pending
with me so all things are perfect in
their timing do proceed so it's
regarding the idea of definitions again
yes guess that's what I think definition
right so I always felt that if I
understood like who you were like what
you really represented I would really
know who I was you were I just it it's
not easy for me to know who I am but I
figured if I would understand what you
were so anyway it seems to me that um
that if everything is definition and
Daryl is is defin I know you say you're
Daryl's future self his one way of
looking at it yes but it seems like you
would be a definition in Daryl's
consciousness of his higher self and
then as a um his symbols you you as
bishar are created as Daryl symbols in
many ways that is so because understand
once again the reality that your world
has always called real the physical
reality is a particular vibratory
wavelength the vibratory wavelength that
your reality has always considered to be
unreal is actually the level we exist in
the level of dream the level of etheric
energy is our solid reality therefore we
are very intertwined with what you call
your imagination with your archetypal
energy to some degree this is what we
will be discussing later on this evening
of your time but yes you have already
unveiled a portion of the Legacy we are
very much representative of your
archetyp I stream of Consciousness that
does not mean we do not have our own
existence it is simply that your Society
is beginning to truly understand that
what for you has been a Fantasy Realm is
our real substantial dimension of
existence and that you are now
accelerating to meet that dimension of
existence where you will in a sense
become someone else's dream someone
else's fantasy to their reality respectively
fantasy to their reality respectively
yes I am concocted out of all the ideas
of the the symbology of the channels
mind that is how you experience me in
your world at the same time I have my
own existence and in very many ways I
could say though it doesn't exactly
parallel the way it happens for you I
can also say that I know that you and
your civilization are concocted out of
my symbology for in many ways I know
right now that all I am doing is talking
to another aspect of
myself just as you are speaking to
another aspect of you
does this help it's great it's great yes
it does thank you very much um I don't
experience unconditional love but as
best as I feel that's what I'd like to
express to you thank you very much it is
felt thank
you and by the
way the admission in that sense and the
owning of anything you
feel goes into the cre of it being
unconditional Shing uh I've never been here before
Shing uh I've never been here before
this is my first experience I have never
been here before this moment myself
either everyone is a new person every
single second so this is the first time
for me first time for you but that is
all right speak up and be bold everyone
is a gift and we would all love to
unwrap you
okay I have a uh uh question about my
life work I've just started back to
school and uh started a counseling
profession and I wonder if doing the
right thing is it the most exciting
thing you can think of to do I think it
is do you know that it
is I I believe so I'm getting that
feeling yes then you are doing the thing
that is most you and when you are doing
the thing that is most you what else is
there you understand the idea that we have
you understand the idea that we have
explained many times to individuals who
have interacted with us before is that
what you call that assuredness that
knowingness that excitement the thing
that draws you most strongly that
inspires you most directly is the signal
is the representative energy of who you
are so when you do the thing that
excites you the most you are fulfilling
your purpose to the fullest you possibly
can excitement that feeling that
knowingness is the reflection of the
infinite of who you were created to be
and who you chose to be in what way you
chose to be that you so when you act
upon the thing that excites you the most
you are absolutely aligned with yourself
and all things shall effortlessly and
most abundantly come your way because
that is the interconnectedness of all
things does that make sense to you yes
it does and it is actually a physics
principle it is not an Airy philosophy
when you are aligned with that energy
you flow with creation and things happen
effortlessly it seems as if something
else is controlling everything because
your Society is used to labeling control
as having effort but when you are really
allowing the universe to flow with you
through you and for you to flow through
it you are absolutely in control but it
doesn't feel like you are because it is
absolutely effortless
so thank you for choosing the thing that
excites you the most because it is the
same thing as choosing to be who you are
and that is really all you can fully
be we thank you does that help you yeah
very much thank you very much we thank
you for your gift and your
sharing
sharing hello bash and until you good
day um I have a question in regards to
some information please oh I've had
question in regards to some information
that I'd been studying about a year ago
all right speak up and be bold okay well
I'm trying to create a blend and Inter
all the information well I am creating a
blend I creating the blend is that your
intention yes then say you are doing it
have some conviction okay great I'm
doing it all right and I wondering if
you could give me some Focus as to as to
where the connection is I studied
something called The Cosmic mandate the
blueprint for immortality and it's
channeled from the ran energy by a woman
by the name of Patricia relle
deagle the idea now is that it is
representative of some of the first
stages some of the first levels of the
transformation of the old Orion
negativity into Orion light into the
positive idea the positive side it is
the laying down of a lighter template a
lighter structure one far more
interchangeable far more malleable than
the older Orion structures used to be
the idea of course always fundamentally
for everyone is to understand that every
single ritual and every single
methodology is just one more tool one
more way and if it works for you by all
means enjoy it and use it if it no
longer works for you or if you change
into some other methodology then go with
that and no longer use the ones that
don't work for you it is as simple as
that no other connection really needs to
be understood if it gives you Joy if it
helps you grow if it serves you and
helps you serve others in a positive way
use it if it stops doing that you have
changed you something else but you are
connecting into the idea of the changing
of the format of the old Orion light
into the new Orion light from dark to
light you understand yes does that help
you is that sufficient yes it it does
are you sure well no not really I'm
trying to did not think so okay the universal
to did not think so okay the universal
principles that are behind the blueprint
is what I was kind of trying to figure
out how do they allow you to feel when
you use
them it feels like a very solid
foundation for all right there is only
in a sense a few things that describe
the solid foundation of existence those
background principles one you exist that
is common for everyone two what you put
out is what you get back that is common
for everyone that's
it thank you
does that help you yes it does thank you
thank you very
much
Shing uh good day my unconditionally
loving alarm clock oh thank you very
much for being our Bell to ring qu my
pleasure I would like to uh just share
some of the things I'm grateful for that
uh you and your friends have uh
reflected to me
uh the most important thing to
me uh I was going to let you guess it
but that would be it is play I have to
tell you that is the most important
thing that I've gotten from you well
thank you and uh I love it if I was a
kite you cut me loose it's like uh it's
too cool not too cool I just uh playing
and uh reminding me about my uh
connections with the people of the water
I have to thank you for that too we
thank you little
kite and thank you for allowing yourself
to be struck by your own
electricity quick I know what you're up
quick I know what you're up
to are we that transparent to you now oh
it's because we love you and because
we're part of you thank you very much
and thank you for your sharing I was
going to I did have a question sort of a
question sort of all right the Dolphins
teach us play and unconditional love and
the whales are bigger is it just like
more of the same I have a hard time
relating to the whales so big it is
because they more represent while of
course still representing the idea of
unconditional love they represent it
more in the format of
conviction understand so conviction it's
just like a a personal conviction in
other words they are an absolute
statement you can't ignore
them they cannot hide
they are absolute conviction they are
the higher self the embodiment of the
overs soul of many dolphins that is a
whale and there are many variations that
represent many different ideas of
conviction but basically that is their
basic symbology conviction so they're
playfully convicted ones too in a sense
yes but they can be more Serene in
certain ways because they also represent
the idea of attached Detachment they
simply know and that's it they just know okay
know and that's it they just know okay
we'll finish this later I've been
talking to you the last two weeks all
right thank you very much oh see Shing shab
Shing shab
Shai for sure I wish you to understand
my happiness and your enthusiasm it is
felt and therefore
understood I've come to Los Angeles to
be a director producer cameraman all
right and I'm following this path
through many different routes that
however at the moment I feel fragmented
unfocused all right and I very much
appreciate what you brought to us this
evening prior to this moment and it I'd
like to ask you a question uh
specifically about my career all
right I'd like to know if you might be
able to direct me to uh people or
specific Direction in the industry that
might allow me to mature faster through
my ambition to help myself manifest as
well as to heal the world through my
ideas one
moment do you
right yes but I I've had trouble writing
I um I'm more of a conceptual person an
organizer of ideas all right then it is
our suggestion that you not in an overly
suggestion that you not in an overly
rigidized way not in an overly
structured way that you organize all the
selves you have discovered yourself to
be put it down write a list of the
characters the movie you are
contains write them all down write out
their biographies dialogue yourself
discover all the VI you are all the
personas all the reflections you are
list them write them out see them as
individuals treat them as individuals
you have chosen to work directly and
equally with who help you attain your
desires your goals respect them in that
way learn to Define all of them get them
all out on paper and then learn to be
equal with all of them to respect all of
them to love all of those aspects of
yourself unconditionally see what kind
of a team you are first then once they
are all equal integrate them into the
whole you you are and by doing that by
collapsing in on yourself you will
create the vacuum that will draw all the
appropriate other individuals to you you
understand yes and I'll take your advice
you do not have to just a
suggestion but we perceive it can be
very powerful for you for it will truly
allow you a Clarity of definition of to
who you are and therefore once you are
clear on the definition of who you are
other individuals that you need to work
with will then find it much easier to
find you because you will be making a
you because you will be making a
stronger statement as to who you are and
there will be no question about who you
need to attract and who needs to attract
you all right sounds very clearcut to me action reads
action reads
action thank you very much thank you
good night
shoting bishar good day to you good day
to you speak up so that all may share
honesty honesty the only way I can
express it is you say that you're a
reflection of us yes to ourselves yes
I'm having a very hard time not hiding
from myself all right what do you feel
that you are hiding
from what is it about yourself you feel
the need to hide from can you define it
for us no will you as you say
try this is the quote unquote problem
the quote unquote problem you mean the
problem is even discovering what it is
you are hiding from yes all right may I
ask you a question yes thank you very
much if you are not aware of what it is
you are hiding from why do you assume
there is
something I feel the energy of pushing
something down I don't know how to
express it except it's like something
comes up and I push it away all right
but do you remember that all feelings
are reactions to beliefs yes then if you
believe there is something there how can
you help but feel there is something
there okay would you
prefer to believe there is nothing yes
that is there yes all right yes can you
act as if that is
so all right one moment let me rephrase
that just to make it a little bit
easier can you imagine what it might be
like to act as if yes that were so yes
all right thank you then imagine it
imagine it now imagine how you would be
if you believe there were no such
portion that you would be hiding from
how would you be how would you be
different than you are
now free in what way free how would you
express it
free can you define or describe a
difference in an action you are doing
now and an action you would be doing
then now at this moment or now first
Define how you act now with the idea
that you are hiding from something and
then imagine the difference in how you
would act if you no longer believe that
there was something to hide from pick a
particular scenario and Define for us how you would
scenario and Define for us how you would
act both in believing there is something
to hide from and then in acting in a way
that you know there is nothing that you
have to hide
from what would the difference be how
would you recognize the difference how
would you know you are no longer hiding
from something how would you recognize
it in yourself what would you see
yourself doing that would give it away
that you are no longer hiding from
yourself I wouldn't be afraid of people
of people Define
people in relationships in relationship
ships yes yes
I I would just sense the more the
release and the flow of the energy
release and flow you mean the share the
exchange all right now you obviously
have some concept of what that ought to
be like yes all
right why not simply act in the manner
of your strongest and clearest concept
of what that would be like and let
everything else take care of itself as a
detail so okay I am doing that now more
and more
then I will go with that and not worry
about all right the way I have thought
of the problems so you are saying that
you have changed in a positive direction
all right can you now relate make a
comparison as you say to the idea of the
way you used to be to the way you are
now in other words do you remember the
way you used to be as opposed to how you
are now did you used to be more fearful
yes all right extremely all right so
focus on the difference now focus on the
amount of change you have undergone from
then till now have you got that yes now
project that project the same amount of
change from now until some undetermined
amount of time when you will be yet
again that much more different can you
do that yes all
right can you see the youu you will wind
up being
if you apply the same amount of change
to yourself now can you envision Can You
Feel The you you will be yes all right
can you feel it right now
now
yes let yourself immerse in it let
yourself Revel in it explore play for a
moment we will give you that moment feel
the energy of what it would be like to
be that you all right can you feel it
yes all right
how does it feel fantastic then you are
that you now right now you are that you
all right because you are creating that
energy now now it's up to you right now
to decide whether or not you wish to go
back to being the old you you were a
moment ago or whether you wish to
continue to be the you you prefer to be
now no question all right it is that
simple you can change that easily
because remember your persona is only an
artificial construct anyway you at any
given moment are defining who you wish
to be the decisions you make stick mhm
that's it be the you you prefer to be
imagine what it would be like let
yourself get excited about being that
you and as soon as you find yourself
feeling the energy recognize that you
couldn't be feeling that energy if you
weren't already that you right now you
cannot feel the the energy of someone
you're not understand yes you are that
you now you are that you now you are
that you now act in the manner of that
you this you right now the youu you
prefer to be Act only as this you now if
for any
reason any reason at all this you
decides this is important if for any
reason this you decides to momentarily
act in the manner of the old you it will
not be you becoming the old you it will
not be you slipping back to the old you
it will be this you deciding to
momentarily replay or recreate another
idea but it will be this you doing it
not the old you trying to be the U you
prefer to be it will be the U you prefer
to be momentarily playing out a scenario
of an old you you no longer prefer got
it I got it all right beautiful thank
you point of view is everything point of
view is everything anything you go
through it's all right to go through it
but go through it from the point of view
of the you you prefer to be got that's
all have to do simple thank you thank
you [Applause]
[Applause]
shedding hello Bashar and to you good
day good
day I'd like to thank you for touching
my life and just say that you have been
a wonderful way shower thank you thank
you we thank you as well our love to you
my question I'm really interested in
knowing in your world um what is a
loving relationship like how do you
choose a a partner in life
synchronistically automatically we
simply attract ourselves to each other
we allow it to automatically occur it is
much in the same way to some degree that
you allow your relationships to happen
but we also are tele empathically
connected and we allow ourselves to
recognize that when we do in fact draw
ourselves into those automatic
interactions we allow them to be what
they are we do not put expectations upon
them for what we think they ought to
be we know that they are there to serve
us we know we are there to serve them so
we rejoice in the spontaneous
co-creation and we do not put in any way
shape or form any particular label as to
how we think it should go or how we
think it should wind up or will it be
this way or will it be that or will
there be anyone else once again perhaps
to put it in the simplest
perspective our entire civilization is
married to itself every individual is
married to every other individual and
any relationship that occurs in any way
that it occurs with how many individuals
it occurs is a part of the marriage is
relationships within the marriage there
are times when it takes upon it the
physical appearance of what you would
call a monogamous relationship there are
times that it doesn't just once again as
it occurs in your Society but there's a
great deal of denial in your Society
about that the idea in that that sense
therefore is that we do not expect or
even really know just to point out this
example because it is gerine to your
Society whether we have been in a
monogamous relationship until we reach
the end of the lifespan and we say well
no one else came along I guess it was a
one-on-one wasn't
it because we know beyond the shadow of
a doubt in absolute trust that if any
other relationships do automatically
occur then they are a part
of the overall
relationship they enhance the overall
scenario in whatever way they naturally
unfold and they cannot be an
interruption it's not possible in our
society well if you would have decide to
bring another being into your world what
is understand that we are always in
communication with that level of
Consciousness as well and we simply make
our agreements consciously even as you
can it does not have to be a hidden
thing you can be in touch with the beings that
you can be in touch with the beings that
can be born unto you for understand they
are not children Now understand
understand you can be in touch with them
and you recognize that there are
services that you may want to perform
that this individual puts out that this
individual this non-physical individual
radiates a desire to accomplish certain
things in what you call physiological
manifestation in putting out that desire
and putting out that radiation that
individual in our society simply
automatically attracts only the the
individuals that have the desire to
serve them in that way so it's automatic
there's no wondering about it the
individuals that can be of service in
that way are only attracted to them and
only those individuals will be attracted
to the individuals that can serve them
in that way is that not so now for us it
is absolutely so now that way except you
create negative synchronicity as well as
positive synchronicity we only create
positive manifestations understand I do indeed
manifestations understand I do indeed
thank you thank you very
much
shooting Yahoo Bashar all right and good
day to you good day I want to thank you
so much for all of your sharings and
your teachings I've grown a lot in the
last two years and I've applied
everything that you've said and tested
it and it really does work especially
starting with the citation meditation at
Sea I created a lot of obstacles in
front of me to grow from oh how exciting
and learned and I grew and now I have
five events coming up that are so
exciting oh thank you and what I wanted
to do basically was to touch as many
people as I could so I put it out to the
universe and uh Lisa and Radia and
Steven and fr are assisting me and we're
going to do a whole bunch of new things
together my we thank you and them thank
you my question uh has to do with a man
named Michelle who came down from
Montreal last week he called me by well
there are no accidents he called me on
the telephone and he thought I was Lisa
cuz my number was on her flyer all right
and he said he was told to come
here and that he was also told to go to
the bod tree and he connected with Rick
and Lisa and me and we had shared a meal
all right uh La Tuesday evening after uh
the channeling he came over to my
apartment and he is a medium um old
school medium the kind where people go
and give their power away to
all right and um now he has um since
August since harmonic conversions which
he didn't understand what it was all
about he has grown as much as all of us
here in Los Angeles and um without
attending the classes and I was able to
assist him to trans channel in my home
all right he while he was sitting there
he saw a green ball of light that had
yellow around it and and it was he said
it was coming very fast and it was going
to hit him in the back of the neck oh
right and when he did he started to
channel uh the old style and the energy
was caught so I assisted him in allowing
the energy to flow down through all of
his chakras to tie into the center of
the earth and to come back up slowly and
release it through his crown chak all
right as he did so he started channeling
this extraterrestrial that he said was
green and it was tall and he was on a
craft that had a circular Council in it
my question now this idea to some degree
is symbolic there is a literal
Consciousness but it is now for now
being interpreted in that particular way
because green is the color of the
emerald vibration of the transformation
of your fourth density Earth and that
color is there to assist that individual
in linking with the Earth and informing
the grounding that is needed understand
oh yes okay but it was to some degree a
connection into the association
council is I am recently channeling the
orcus and um when that energy comes
through it is so intense that it does
remind me of the galactic is there a tie
to some degree there is the idea once
again is to remember that the whales and
especially the Orca represent the
polarity the
conviction conviction of motion the
conviction of action the deliberateness
of action they are the path of the
warrior the path of the sorcerer the
path of the Samurai as you understand
those terms in your Society yes the idea
of the galactic is the very substance
the very fabric of the consciousness of
onedimensional Realm all you are receiving through this
Realm all you are receiving through this
channel is a very small fragment of that
fabric of
Consciousness the totality of it in that
sense comes through many individuals in
a sense it actually comes through all of
you all the time but in the way you have
received it this evening of your time it
is represented as a very small flow of
that energy the idea to some degree is
that the Orca with its understanding of
alignment with its understanding of
conviction funnels that energy all the
time that is why individuals that are
not prepared for their level of energy
can find themselves burning out I see
understand yes I do does that assist you
yes very much thank you ha to H
sharing good evening Bashar and who you
good day I'm not sure exactly what the
Crux of this question is I want to thank
me
neither first of all for helping me
discover some joy in my life oh thank
you for discovering the joy that has
always been there within you and there
is more to come yes I'm I'm sure that's
true um I've discovered something that
is exciting to me no all right do share
I think the question is should I just
allow it to be exciting for me or should
I
um should I make a business out of it
and share it with other people well you
could allow it to be exciting for
everyone that doesn't mean everyone has
to choose it but you can allow it to be
exciting for them to allow them to
choose it if they want to by all means
in whatever way you feel represents the
strongest expression of your excitement
do so if that is the way you want to
serve you are only putting it out there
for them to choose it as a preference if
they want to just putting it out there
isn't going to force anyone to take it
you know that's right but the energy the
time involved in making it available of
doing that yes um realistically there's
a living to be made realistically again
which realistically are you talking
about now an old realistically or a new
realistically
I'm talking about the old bills that
need to be paid yes but we have
discussed the idea of abundance and we
have discussed the idea that doing what
excites you the most will always Supply
you with the abundance necessary in
whatever way it is necessary I'm try yes
I'm I know in my heart that's true but
I'm working but you are going to make a
separation of that in your mind well
yeah it's not it's not there yet why not
I haven't I don't know yes you do I
chose it not to be correct
why do you choose it not to
be I like to struggle I don't
know do you really I wonder oh all right
stop wondering yes or no do you like to
struggle I really don't enjoy struggling
thank you much struggling thank you very
much then why is there still a
separation I guess the Endeavor that I'm
thinking about has been around are you
familiar with float tanks yes okay
they've been around a while while and
I've just recently discovered it myself
and I'm wondering if they've been around
for so long and they seem such an
exciting tool yes why hasn't anybody
done anything with it many individuals
have but it is not a tool that works for
everyone it is not everyone's preference
perhaps you can invent something new to
be done with it that could be exciting
to many other individuals remember that
if you're not operating on a particular
frequency on a particular wavelength
then you do not necessarily give
yourself the opportunity to see what has
been done on another wavelength until
you intersect that wavelength you may
also be required to elevate it to a new
level or to Simply extract from the idea
that it is the principles which can be
applied in a completely different way
that particular tool may not necessarily
be the most efficient way for what you
want to do it might be in certain
circumstances but allow yourself not
necessarily to become transfixed by the
physiological shape of it by the
physiological way or method the IDE idea
has been manifested take the idea take
the physical shape if that works for you
but take the idea and transform it into
whatever methodology is actually more
representative of who and what you are
remember this as well many individuals
when they truly have created for
themselves a particular tool that really
does allow them to align very quickly
come to the realization just as quickly
that tools are simply reflections of
your capabilities any anyway and once
you use the tool if it has aligned you
you don't need it anymore okay it
becomes obsolete a good tool renders
itself obsolete almost
immediately understand yes yes does that
help you yes very much thank you one
moment we are not done
okay is this notion still separated
within
you feel around
honestly I have to say yes oh all right
very good thank you for being honest
remember owning it is the first step to
changing it now the
idea as we were discussing before with
another individual is to use the imagination do
individual is to use the imagination do
you have some sort of scenario some sort
of picture some sort of image some sort
of feeling as to what you would be like
if you didn't have that
separation I mean physically like any
way you wish to take any way you wish to
take it do you have in any way shape or
form a picture of what you would be like
if that separation did not exist within
you yes what does that picture look like
can you describe the
differences um on a anyway level it
would be um high energy high energy what
does that mean how does that translate
in your physiological reality when you
say high energy not having an not it's
not do not tell me what it is not tell
me what it is effortless it is
effortless all right give me a
physiological picture of something that
would now be
effortless as you say give me an
ABC an action from beginning to end that
would be effortless that at this point
in your life is not
effortless are you having difficulty
picking something that is not effortless
in your life yeah well very
good the more difficulty you have
discovering things that cause effort
within you the more you will balance and
blend you see many times many of you
think you have all these things holding
you back but when we ask you to look for
what these things are you have a great
deal of difficulty finding them
maybe they're not really
there and just because you think they're
there that is the only obstacle that has
always existed just because you have
bought into your society structure that
says well you all have these things
within you whether you know it or not
you've all got these things holding you
back so you buy into that well I don't
know what it is that could be holding me
back but we all have it so it must be
there somewhere but when you're asked to look
somewhere but when you're asked to look
for it you can't really find it because
there never has in many cases ever
actually been any specific thing there
holding you back except the belief that
there's something there holding you
back so if you can't find it I would
suggest you don't look too hard for
one that you can on one level let it be
all right to not discover those kinds of
things within yourself and to say well
wait a minute maybe I don't really have
as many of these separations as I
thought maybe my ability to conceive
maybe my ability to desire that there is
no separation is my little inner voice
telling me that there really isn't any
and that I can begin to trust that voice
believe in that voice and be that
integrated individual just because it is
dawned on me that I can be maybe just
the dawning on me that I can be is the
doing of the thing is the realization of
the thing is the clearing of anything
that was there or might have in there
that maybe kept me
separated understand yes I do do you
like playing that way yes then play all
you want that way these things these
things are not on one level just mental
games you are redefining yourself the
more willing you are to open up all of
the so-called
reasons to unfold and examine all the
so-called reasons you have for why you
are not who you prefer to be when you
start unfolding them very often you will
find they are quite empty that they are
just shells that they are just
appearances and they never really
contained any substance at
all okay thank you very much thank you
pleasant dreams to you thank
you shedding it may help you by the way to
shedding it may help you by the way to
think of blue
crystals thank you sheding good evening
Bash good day it's great to be here
again with you this evening we are very
happy you are there thank you I want to
let you know that my life is going
terrific oh my everything is wonderful
would you like to change that no oh
right thank you very much it's quite
perfect what do you have to share as an
equal then okay I have a question about
the subject of compassion compassion yes
I've had this question in my mind for
about 4 months right and I've examined
it every which way and I can't come up
with the answer all right what is the
question you have created okay the
question is this oh One Moment One
Moment what is the answer you have that
you have formulated in the format of a
question um you do have the answer a
question is simply an answer that you
place outside
yourself okay well then maybe have a
statement thank you it's a statement
make a statement okay I like to think of
my myself as a warm and caring and
loving person oh thank you very much
okay I have found that the more I
understand how each one of us creates
his own reality yes that I'm having
difficulty feeling compassionate towards
certain people and
situations does anybody know what I'm
talking okay I don't like the way I feel
all right for instance this is awful the
homeless homeless okay I see a lot of
homeless people all right and I think to
myself or the old me used to say yes oh
those poor poor people what can I do to
help them the new me is saying you know
they created their own reality because
they want to be Choice one moment and I
don't like that one moment you have
created what is classically in your
language called a misunderstanding of
the concept okay compassion in no way
shape or form says you can't help if you
have attracted yourself to see those
individuals then you have been attracted
to be of service the idea of compassion
is not taking responsibility for them
however is not giving them sympathy to
reinforce the negativity they have
already created with their
misunderstanding of their connection to
the infinite with their belief of their
lack of connection to the infinite
compassion does not mean you do not have
help compassion simply means you do not
take responsibility for them compassion
means you live the life that is
representative of who you are to the
fullest so you can be the best
reflective example you can be to them
that is what helps them by all means
interact with them compassion in no way
shape or form prevents you from
interacting with individuals you attract
into your life that may require some
assistance some guidance there is
nothing that says compassion cannot
guide there is nothing that says
compassion cannot reflect are we not
reflecting ideas to you yes you are we
know you create your own
reality but it is our compassion that
allows us to desire to share with you
that there are many ways you could
create your reality but in no way shape
or form do we take responsibility for
what you decide to choose even after we
have given you a reflection that's true
understand I understand completely well
thank you very much I thank thank you
very much thank you for your compassion
thanks
sharing problem hello Bashar and who you
good day
[Applause] strawberry bishar I have a lot to share
strawberry bishar I have a lot to share
with you oh all right um my M my mother
is healthy alive vibrant beautiful
loving as you know uh a number of months
ago as we count time she was told by a
doctor that she had terminal cancer and
was going to die within a very short
period of time they gave her no hope
told her to go home and die yes and we
undertook a program to resolve that and
she is now completely healthy from every
aspect that we can find we thank
you we thank you for being so bold and
so full of conviction thank you and so
full of love thank you now along with
the creation of that game her sister my
Aunt out of in my observation love and
out of in my observation love and
compassion went with her and traveled
with us in the program uh part of the
program was we went down to a health
clinic in Mexico Don's box Clinic all
right and she went through this
particular program and in my perception
didn't really need it the way my mother
did it wasn't part of the vibr vibration
but she was doing this out of love and
caring support for my mother now about
last November as we count time she began
to develop a rash of some sort over her
body this continued to develop to the
point where she was put in the hospital
about a week ago with um and now put out
a respirator went into a coma her body
is covered with a scaly purple device as
my M say she almost looks like a monster
horrible to look at in a condition much
worse than my mother had there is so
much that I have been reflecting we've
been doing a lot of telepathic
communication I can almost see a
blending in the mass Consciousness
between what has been two separate
ideologies in our culture one the the um
nutritional movement um on one hand
which says that you know the the body
can be handled through nutritional means
the relatively limited narrow viewpoints
of the medical profession and the
political overtones and the don't allow
them to look Beyond those particular
limits guys and the spiritual and the
mental we Blended these three things and
as far as I can be able able to see
there is possibly this is the service
that Connie is going through but we are
and myself finding um a tremendous amount
myself finding um a tremendous amount
of agitative energy in attempting
to um see all of the posit of this to be
able to flow love to see or vibrant a
lot things going on here we will share
with you this time that it is our
perspective that there is a high degree
of probability that after having served
your mother this individual may be
fulfilling a certain idea of their own
Karma and may take themselves into
non-physical reality it is a high degree
of probability however there are some
things that can be learned and there is
a potential for in your terminology
reversing this effect however I want to
interrupt you right at this I'm going to
say something to you someone Charlene
called me and she said reflected she you
reflected regarding her father that um
there was a high probability that would
no longer live in this life and I said
to her she said Bashar said this and I
said Bashar all right I said
on this idea now I love this
from the Viewpoint of we're not going to
take this prediction this is not a
prediction energy it is not a prediction
okay what is it it is a sensing of the
energy right at the moment aha right at
the moment very nice that's it we will
transform that go yes okay what this
requires now that we may continue for
the transformational energy is the help
of a particular specific Direction a
specific connection to certain types of
Earth Energy that can best be delivered
by what may be called a type of sprite
energy one moment
Erica she will help you lovely I would
love to be helped by her ask for her to
impart some of the information she is
now learning about the idea of certain
connections to the powers inherent in
your natural
Earth all right yes and delineate a
little bit more Bashar she will she will
yes you won't no
thank you Bashar you're a delight I love
you it was wonderful to be part of this
this is of course also Shiloh's loving
request to have this data thank you for
your sharing thank you for your love
your caring it's a delight to be part of
this turn we thank you very much and may
remind you that you have been a
delightful and sweet and succulent
juice thank you baby
Shing hello Bashar and you good day um I
just wanted to share with you that a
friend of mine who was recently pregnant
had her baby last night all right and
the first birth that she had this was
her second and the first birth she had
was real difficult and the second one
after some information that you thanks
some information that you gave to her
her second birth was so much easier and
she wanted me to tell you thanks for the
information and and um it was something
to the effect of being more of a vehicle
we thank you and we thank her for
allowing the total event to be what she
is so that all the energy could be of
assistance rather than simply taking the
burden on herself isolated in a specific
way alone thanks we thank you um I also
have a question um my my father-in-law
died about a year ago and my
mother-in-law has been sort of in limbo
I suppose you might say and I was
wondering is there any way that my
husband and I could assist her in sort
of transforming through this stage of
her life it is our perception that
perhaps what can assist her greatly is
the literature that already exists in
your Society dealing with the idea of
what you call life after physical death
if she can familiarize herself with the
idea of what that shall we say terrain
is all about she will open herself to
sensitivity to sensitize herself to have
her own Communications in a more
conscious way would she be willing to trust her
way would she be willing to trust her
own um her own
dreams yes but the information can come
in a more conscious fashion more in the
form of a conscious meditation as she is
absorbing the information in those books
that already
exist okay I have one more question real
quick why is my dog acting so
strangely Strange In what way
she's just um really she's really upset
and she's walking around the house and
she she isn't looking she's looking for
something and not finding anything and
she's just seems to be generally
disrupted are you contemplating in any
way shape or form a physiological
move oh not real not soon in the future
have you contemplated a particular place
that you might be moving
to yes where Olympia yeah Seattle or
near Washington Washington State
why um we just thought we might
experience a Pacific Northwest a little
bit more deeply
why we wanted to my husband and I just
like the idea what is the energy you
know is there how does it feel it feels
good it's green and clean and all right
green and clean all
right in your terminology when will you
go a year and a half a year is that a
question I'm not sure two questions all
right are you going to try for 6 months
I'd love to go in six months how about
three six months all right why
six I think there's some things I've
started at this point that I should
finish before I leave all right 3 months
it
is communicate to your animal the
essence of the feeling of the green and
the clean it will help to orient because
the animal is only being a magnetic
compass needle for fluctuations in your
own indecisions about what it is you
think you have to clean
up all right thank you very much thank
you very
much
shedding Compadre and to you good day
hello Bashar first I'd like to tell you
that I'm here because of two gifts speak
up so that all may share I am here
thanks to two gifts from my friend and
your friend Victoria Collins oh right
she is right there number one she
introduced me to you about two years ago
and number two I'm here because even
though her name was selected she decided
to give this to me for my birthday
present so the greeting that I give to
you is from both of us happy birthday
thank you and thank you for the gift you
have given to us of both of yourselves
oh with our greatest pleasure I assure
you um over the two years that I've had
the pleasure of playing with your tools
and growing and expanding and
accelerating there is not enough time to
tell you the all the wonderful
experiences that have occurred so I'm
just going to ask you to feel that
already done all right thank you the
primary tool that I'd like to just
mention tonight in the way of a sharing
is the tool called follow your
excitement which I believe we've heard
about tonight okay well I've enjoyed
experimenting with that tool in larger
and larger steps as I learned to trust
that that truly does work for me and the
most recent example of that is an
opportunity that I was given about two
days ago to go to Spain and be paid to
um run
the research aspect of diving for buried
treasure oh what
um 6 months ago I would have invalidated
that idea because I was still testing
the tools on a lower gradient all right
and now I can say thanks to you I am
truly ready all thanks to you as I was
driving over here tonight I was thinking
what questions could I ask because as
you all can imagine there are lots of
questions I could ask regarding locating
the treasure which from a research point
of view is basically our job and lots of
opportunities to judge oneself possibly
at least in Prior ways of thinking lots
of opportunities for others to judge us
and I just realized with all of these
tools there really is no need for that
whatsoever um we thank you you will also
discover certain ideas of the culture in
the area you call Portugal uhu that will
awaken some past memories for you well
that's very interesting that you
mentioned that I was not aware of that
but I'm very very aware of the
excitement that Spain has always held
for me yes I have been there before but
this particular I mean this time I know
but this particular time even though
I've been invited many times before this
is the time I'm truly truly ready as a
being and there is incredible
synchronicity incredible excuse me
synchronicity going on right now with a
parallel Dimension that I'm very much
aware of as a nun in Spain right now and
the reason that I am so Desiring to
speak Spanish now here is that I had
agreed to take a vow of s I have agreed
to take a vow of silence there for
certain um disagreements with the church
Etc and now I find that priests are
probably going to be assisting me in my
translations which I also find very
interesting and so on and so on um one
thing I would like to share with you is
that one of the tools you have taught us
is that
um experiences that we used to label
negative or positive but particularly
negative were opportunities to learn and
I have experimented with that so much
now that I really feel that tool is mine
and as I was driving down here tonight I
realized now that that is really my tool
now I have something positive to look
forward to and that is an opportunity to
learn in other words I don't need to
view just the negative things as
opportunities to learn I already know
that yes so now everything is an
opportunity to learn which probably I
knew but I was always focusing on the
negative part of it yes so there isn't
anything negative
anymore as you have shared with us
before by the way yes the Gilded cross
belonged to
you wo is that why my name is Faith
Perhaps Perhaps wonderful thank you um okay I'm
Perhaps wonderful thank you um okay I'm
moving on down this list here it's all
it's all related but I tried to get
organized I I am getting organized here
okay um even though I don't have any
questions for you I certainly invite
your co-creation and perceptions having
to do with this particular Venture we're
on I have just given it to you the
Gilded cross belonged to you all
right um are you operating out of the
area that is called
kadis that is unknown at this particular
time all right will you take a trek to
the Pyrenees well this is underwater
Pyrenees well this is underwater
treasure so I rather doubt
that however however I need to look at a
map and see where the P
are I'm not sure all right but that's an
interesting question I will definitely
check out the these are the things we
are allowed to share uhhuh there are
many kinds of treasure chest you'll be
opening more than one right and each
will be on a different level physical
astral ethereal causal mental I I
understand I wrote down right here see
if I could beat you to this because I
was quite sure somewhere along the line
you'd say that the Buri the primary
buried treasure that I would discover is
another aspect of myself that I have yet
to discover there is that but you can
create now you have created a sufficient
amount of energy to create now in this
physiological Endeavor the opening of
those Treasures on each and every level
including the physical you can reflect
and parallel all the different levels
all the way as you say down to the
physical that's very very exciting I
certainly am excited about hearing about
that and I will be excited about
integrating it making it more and more
part of my do I dare say part of my
reality as if it were not right now
thank you very much also when you see
the white plaster walls there will be a
very strong memory for you uh-huh let it
come in as you say through your sense of
smell as well for you may even visualize
the paint that used to be on your
hands as you mastered those
frescos very interesting thank you very
much wait just I just want to close
no that's it I just want to express our
gratitude it is already expressed keep
in
touch have never been out of touch one
touch one
moment we would at this time remind each
and every one of you now for various
specific reasons that in your endeavors
of exploration of all the ideas of
nonphysical reality that you remember
that you chose your physical expression
and anytime you find yourself becoming
disoriented unlocked from the physical
reality we would remind you to do
something very physical in that sense
one suggestion we have given will be to
allow yourself to relate to the
physiological Earth to the idea of the
growing things the green things and also
for the idea of grounding yourself and
orienting yourself for what you may call
Lively physical action the idea we had
suggested to another individual is to
take a very strong board and a hammer
and pound some Nails into it this can be
a very very strong
meditation you might be
surprised but Orient yourself to the
understanding that the physical reality
is just as blessed as all other levels
or it wouldn't
exist at this time to allow you to enjoy
a little bit more of your physical
reality you may take a break we will
resume contact in approximately 10 to 15
of your minutes maximum
[Applause] [Music]
how's it going great
remember please 10 to 15 minutes when I
call you please come back cuz we can't
get started till everybody's seated and
quiet there's Refreshments in the other
room I don't say before we
continue what
further word on the idea of the workshop
interaction that we will be having with
many of
you it is designed in a Triad section
the first section being what is called
Persona reconstruction the second section being
reconstruction the second section being
what is called the generation of
excitement and abundance the third
section being called the idea of Astral
expansion it will in that sense shall we
say be taught in a Triad fashion myself
I will commence with the idea of persona
reconstruction Ana will undertake the
idea of excitement and abundance the
feminine counterpart from our society
and the galactic Consciousness will
conduct the idea of Astral expansion the
idea therefore is that we shall proceed
to
demonstrate alongside the Triad phases
of the workshop the idea of the blending
of the polarity of masculine and
feminine energy within each and every
being in the final culmination of the
Blended Galactic energy so there will be
an underlying energy that will also be
taking place an underlying series of
communications that will also be taking
place aside from the actual vocal
Communications you will be hearing with
your ears we thank you in this way for
allowing us at this time the opportunity
to share with you such a
multi-dimensional and
multilevel cocreation and a shared
dream before we now commence with what
you may call our closing dialogue of the
Legacy we will continue with question
interaction briefly
sharing much love to you Bashar and to
you good day
okay um my one question would be
regarding um let's see how do I phrase
this um many years ago I've had um
automobile accident all right and
sustained injury in my neck guys have
lived with pain mostly on the right side
for the past 20 years or so it seems all
right okay um the other night I was
fortunate to have a meditation which
helped me release this all right and
exciting I know it was wonderful and
tonight as I got up off a chair in my
mother's house my neck hurt for a moment
that's all right okay um would you
please help me to find what caused the
pain on whether it whether it is stress
whether it is um anger and so that I no
longer pick this up
again the idea first of all to
understand is that you have made a
transition that you have elevated
yourself to a new
level the idea of having experienced
what you may call the temporary quote
unquote lapse was not so much even a
matter of stress not so much even a
matter of anger but more a matter of
testing yourself of making sure that you
had cleared the idea that you had in a
sense integrated all that you needed to
integrate from having created that
experience in your life that forced you
to face certain things you have
accelerated yourself no pun intended
highly the idea is that many individuals
will put themselves in certain limit
situations of that nature to clear out
and process very rapidly not over the
course of many lifetimes but over the
course of a portion of one lifetime many
of the things that might have taken many
lifetimes to process when you force
yourself into that kind of a mold when
you force yourself into that kind of a
template then many times you face
certain things that you may have
otherwise taken many lifetimes to face
and process you have processed many of
them as you Rose in that sense within
the framework of your maternal energy
you gave yourself one last reminder that
a it was your choice that b you have
created a Transcendence and see in a
sense it was a temporary test just
checking in making sure that the
alignment is still there now it will
lead you in our perception to many other
things to many realizations that you can
be of assistance to other individuals
within the things that you have learned
within the information the knowledge
that you have gathered with your
experiences you can now begin to
function on the other side of the
doorway in complete freedom in that
sense in a complete sense of service
there are many things that you learn
that you will now be able to share with
many other individuals who will be
experiencing similar manifestations to
what you created for yourself with that
degree of limitation are you following
me so
far are you following me so far on the
intellectual level on the intellectual
level how do you feel right now
wonderful then you are following just
fine on all levels but I felt wonderful
when I knew I was going to talk to you
all right but you see you are not really
talking to me you are talking to
yourself yes and that is always a
wonderful thing to understand always a
wonderful thing to discover now the
idea also many times is that we will as
we have just done to some degree share
what is called rapid fire
communication so that you will make an
attempt to focus a little more strongly
on what is being said and so that the
real message underneath the words
actually gets delivered because in a
sense it disarms your analytical
intellectual conscious self by creating
it to focus on the words while at the
same time we deliver the true message
underneath in that sense therefore you
have allowed us to slip something
in which will now blossom and grow in a
very natural way you can to some degree
think in the direction of now
considering yourself one of the natural
herbs of your planet one of the natural
flowering blossoms of your planet you
are going to expand mightily in that way
rise up toward your sun rise up toward
the light bathe in it soak it up let it
fill you let yourself glow become one
homogeneous energy with no idea that you
are made of a collection of Parts which
can become disarrayed begin to feel
yourself as one homogeneous light and
there will be nothing in you that can
anymore ever again become misaligned you
understand yes does this help you yes it
does one
moment I ask you a question of course oh
thank you very much you're welcome do
you like the animal upon your planet
that you call
Raven I've had nothing to do with one I
have no idea do you like
them yes you don't sound too sure well
never having met one I don't
know all
right the next time you see
one okay allow yourself simply to
contemplate its form contemplate its
movement contemplate its
action there is in a sense a reminder
there a connection there that may allow
you to turn one last key to know beyond
a shadow of a doubt that a new idea of
yourself is truly solid L locked
in all right yes one
moment you have inspired us also to
share a few other things now this may
seem to be not connected but there are
levels of it that are from time to time
we have discussed the idea of course
that vocal language is vibration that
you give it its power and sometimes the
vocal language that you use is
representative in reflection of the
vibration that you are many times you
will understand that the way your
language is translated from our Concepts
through the channel takes on unusual
patterns unusual frequencies
unusual usage an orchestration is taking place
usage an orchestration is taking place
and much of these vibratory patterns are
actually what is responsible for the
reactions and the openings that occur
within you the things that you allow to
soak and seep within your Consciousness
and all the different levels you have
created it to
be we have to some degree shared with
you some of the ideas of our ancient
language that we no longer use in that
sense we will share two more
principles let them fall into place
where they apply again this may not seem
to be immediately pertinent but there
are aspects that are we have discussed
the phrase in our ancient language AAR
which means basically experience we have
shall we say dissected the word in the
understanding that El is our word for
miror and this will translate into any
language in the same way it is
constructed in our language you would
spell it in your language i l l i the
reverse reflection of the first two
letters it is the reflection in the
mirror more literally El in being
referred to mirror depending upon the
context will also refer to anything that
is exchanged anything that is returned
an echo can be called elely depending
upon the context this whole notion of
Reflections this whole notion of the
return of the exchange of
information of putting out a radiation
which then is echoed back by your
Reality by your surrounding that whole
idea is
elely another
understanding plurality singularity in
our language we have labeled our word
esani we call our civilization that the
people are sasani now the idea of the
usage of the term a and the usage of the
term e will be the difference between
the plural and the singular in that
sense e sound will mean singular a will
be plural in that sense an example there
is an animal in our
civilization that exists in the ocean
and would be similar to the idea of one
of your seals per se very different in
many ways it has a bluish gray skin very
rough hide in that sense and a brownish
for color the idea is that in singular
this is
called but in plural it is called mamb
the idea therefore of s it it is that
the singular place of all of us the
singular place of all
Sani now this language
lesson to some degree has to do with the
whole idea of the
communication of yourself with yourself
because as each and every one of you in
the past has created yourself to be
thought of as a collection of parts in
fragmenting yourself and fractionating
yourself in that way it requires a very
analytical and sophisticated
communication system to keep track of
all those
parts now that you are integrated ating
yourself into one understanding one
Consciousness one homogeneous whole
communication within you is
instantaneous for it reaches all of you
all at once for you are all right here
right now so there really is no
separation between the idea of I
understand it in my heart I understand
it intellectually in my head it is all
one understanding created to be one
understanding let it soak in let it sink
in in whatever way it need needs to but
at least allow yourself to begin with
the understanding that you do know you
do communicate you do understand in
whatever way you need to let it process
let it unfold like the blossom like the
flower as it does to the sun we thank
you for allowing us what appears to be
this little Divergence we bid you
Pleasant and ecstatic Dream Life in
Dream time which is the blending of the
physical and the non-physical reality
into one aware awake state of malleable
creativity dream time we thank you thank
you Bashar and a big warm fuzzy hug
thank you very
much many of you are quite a bit more
fuzzy than we are
yes
shedding hi my friend and you good
day I don't really have a question well
thank you very much make a statement I
will all right three years
ago the first night I went to see you
you shared with me my
agreements which to me sounded like
science fiction all
right [Music]
and the the joys that I've experienced
since then are our life fact I
guess and I I know that that you feel
every time I send love
nice and I I wanted to thank
you for I don't you know what is all right
for I don't you know what is all right
we thank you and we thank many for
sitting at the table of sharing within
the association yes they have been
communicating quite
frequently and it's been my joy to find
that the
communications exactly parallel those
that come from here on
Thursdays we thank you for your
synchronicity yes and for allowing
myself to create confirmation which
sometimes we all really need thank you
very much for being your own
confirmation Stevenson's love and to him
as well and Rick yes and
um well thank you thank you
love to you
all
Shing greetings B and to you good day
it's been a pleasure to hear you in
speak up so that all may share it's been
a pleasure to have fun with you this
evening we thank you very much I have a
um question we and we've produced a
video on Sedona and on what we call the
Aquarian principles
principles
channeled by an energy named
Aton and I would just like from you any
additional direction or guidance to
continue on with my mission here in my
service in doing what I need to to
promote this and further
it I just like to know what you receive
we thank you for now we will say the
same thing we said to another individual
this evening of your time it can help as
a focal point it can help as a focal
tool and as a direction guidance system
if you will in your calm and meditative
States focus on the blue white
electromagnetic light you will become
your own compass needle and you will
know the
way thank you we thank you very
much and
sharing hello and to you a good day I am
like you this is my first time we thank
you could you tell me where is my son
and my
nephew not
specifically okay thank you one moment [Music]
we will give you what in your Earth
terminology is called an apology this is
not our
domain there is another that can help
you one moment
all we can share at this time is as a
suggestion to seek communication from
the domain of the
sea there is telepathic linkage that can
occur through the co-s species upon your
planet that inhabit your ocean of
dolphin energy they can come in your dream they
energy they can come in your dream they
can come in your physical reality they
can open up lines of of communication to
those that you seek for it will open up
lines of communication from you to
yourself within your own heart and along
that hard line can you send out a
particular frequency of vibration that
will attract you in no uncertain terms
into a direct interaction with those
that you
seek but this is not as you
say our allowance it is not as you say
our domain at this
time we bid you love thank you very much
and I bid you love too we thank
you at this
timing allow us the
expression of the idea that we have term
the
Legacy listen with all the different
types of ears that you have take us on
one level literally take us not
literally at all for are now entering a
true phase of the construction of dream
time as we spoke before the
understanding is that you exist on an
energy level we exist on an energy level
all things are made of the same energy
but there are different frequencies our
frequency of reality to you is the idea
of dream reality etheric reality many
individuals upon your planet have
referred to what you call
extraterrestrial Consciousness as
etherian consciousness and this is to
some degree quite accurate it is why it
is in many ways easier for us to
communicate with you in this way than
using what you may call your
physiological radio devices for we
operate on that frequency not at all
biological senders and receivers are far
more apt in that way once they are
trained to identify with the energy of
love in that sense and
acceptance the energy of light links all
mentality and you are linked not only to
every member in your own civilization
but to all other civilizations as well
and sometimes in very specific ways to
play out very specific ideas we have
been allowed at times to briefly discuss
with you some of the Notions now for
some of the interactions taking place
upon your planet that you have called in
your language abductions which we have
chosen to call temporary
detainments we have reminded you that
these interactions between your species
and the alien species we have referred
to as Zeta reticulum are done through
absolute agreement even though on your
part many of these agreements may be
done unconsciously and they are only
brought to the surface reluctantly
through the idea of the release of your
fear but you are serving each other in
many ways we have briefly discussed the
understanding as many of you yourselves
are now beginning to realize that your
species operates on a very highly
individualistic level that their species
operates on a very highly Mass
Consciousness level and that to each
other you are extremely alien extremely
foreign and just as much difficulty as
you have had understanding the idea of
how it is to operate as one
Consciousness they have the difficulty
of understanding what it is to operate
as a single individual cut off from the
whole in many ways though they do not
express it in exactly the same way they
have just as much fear and uncertainty
about you as you do about them you are
learning to understand each other and in
understanding and blending with each
other you are performing services for
each other you are boosting and
supporting each other's societies you
are aiding in each other's
Transformations you are giving them what
they need they are giving you what you
need in that sense to mature as a
species even as you allow them to mature
as a species they have come from a
completely different direction in
evolution you have come from a
evolution than each other you are true
polarities on many different levels but
now through these interactions through
these givings through these sharings
whether they are understandable on the
surface or not you have begun a true
blending in many ways that will allow
you both to mature both to interact both
to become fast friends side by side in
your expansion and exploration of the
universe in many ways that you cannot
yet understand but in many ways that you
will understand in the time to come we
have shared with you many times the
arbitrary nomenclature that in many ways
we have the existence of Evolution
approximately 150 to 300 years Beyond
you we have told you in many times in
many cases that this is an arbitrary
nomenclature and we will now Endeavor to
Define and precisely explain the
relative frequency of the time span of
your reality and our reality for there
will be a seemingly time a temporal
Paradox in what we are about to explain
about your connection to
us it has already occurred to some of
you it has not occurred quite
surprisingly to a lot of you once again
in many ways what we are about to say
you can take in many ways on many levels
very literally but understand it is also
archetypal energy the substream
consciousness of your realm of our realm
of their realm The Zeta
reticulum we have told you in many ways
that we are the representation of your
own future selves and in many ways that
is allegorical in many ways it is quite
literal reincarnation speaking and also
as a representation of the parallel type
of civilization you yourselves will
create upon Earth but there is one other
way that we also mean it that we have
not really shared with you for it
actually has not occurred to actually
quite a large number of you that even as
we have endeavored to describe our
physical reality our physical appearance
you understand that we are an exact
cross between the idea of your human
shape and your Zeta reticulum we are the
children Children of the blending we are
the hybrids that you are
creating we are your future selves and
come back to remind you that there is a
marriage going on that gives us reality
that supports
us you are in many ways our fathers and
our mothers and we are your
children and we send you our love across
the ages the idea of understanding is that
ages the idea of understanding is that
this blending is taking place in your
time frame and that an evolution does
occur where there is the population of
our world in another dimension by the
cross breeding of what you call the
reticulum and the Earth human and we are
that population and that is why we have
population and that is why we have
remained in that other dimension so that
we would not interfere with the marriage
that is taking place so that we would
not interfere with the consummation of
that marriage so that we would not
interfere in that that
sense with
your right to experience our birth from
your own point of view but now because
of the timing and because of the
sharing we can be allowed at this time
with great joy to share with you that we
greet you as your
children and we thank you for allowing
us to reflect back to you the brilliant
brilliant trust you have placed in us
the brilliant future you have given
yourselves and the brilliant present you
have bequeathed unto us there are many
more levels to this
idea and we will share those in time as
well but understand that there is a
distinct purpose in the creation of our
species by the blending of yours and the
reticulum you are creating the future
you desire in many ways and do remember
one other thing another thing that many
of you sometimes do not stop to
realize in what we call our
present we are also side by side with
your future
Earth and we interact together in joy in
Harmony in
love you are our Legacy as much as we
are are
yours our love to
you we thank you for your
blessing we thank you for your
strength and we thank
you for your
love and our life
and our
joy and we only give you back what you
have given
us in allowing us to exist as we do Infinite
Creation dream you into
ecstatic creations of reality forever
and ever
shivi sh shivi
[Music]
how' it go great than you we love
we love
you thank you thank you all for being
here tonight and every
[Music] night I love you all too
yes thank you
darl starting in 6 weeks a new
era for us
all nothing more to saber thank you very
much for the co-creation for the last 4
years I'd like to thank uh Ken gon who's
been handling our camera
well Paul
gibons who's been Faithfully here every
every week
now providing fantastic audio and video
tapes Pamela who's making our tapes Erica
Erica
and to the association that we are now
becoming part of we thank
us thank you Sten for e e oh