questions you can certainly ask him
anything you want to about his own
civilization um what is happening here
is you're
experiencing a type of a telepathic link
up Bashar is not actually here per se
during the dialogue what's happening is
he is in a similar state of repose to
what you will see me go
into on his end wherever he is and our
minds form kind of a linkup now as he's
described this it's based on the
principle that everything in
nature is the result of some sort of a
vibration or a
frequency of the one energy that we're
all made out
of when my
personality softens when I go into the
trance it allows his personality to sort
of Junction with mine and my energy
takes on the vibration of his energy of
his personality so what you're actually
getting is kind of an imprint kind of a
model of his thoughts made out of my
energy I'm literally functioning like a
translation box for him not too
dissimilar from the principle at least
upon which something like a telephone is
based where you know that when you're
listening into a telephone you know
you're not actually hearing the literal
words that the person at the other end
is speaking you're hearing an electronic
translation so basically what their
civilization has discovered and what our
civilization I think is
discovering is that people living people
are already very efficient biological
transmitters and receivers and that
those that allow themselves through
training to become sensitive to those
energies can form this kind of a linkup
with different beings that are already
perhaps a little bit more well-versed in
that type of of interaction so that is
is as I understand it the mechanism of
what is happening here
today now Bashar is not literally his
name in their society they're pretty
much completely telepathic and they
don't use names as such but he chose a
word out of our own Earth languages so
that we would have something a little
bit easier to call him in conversation
other than hey you and um it's a word
that's actually Arabic and which is
partly my background and the word in
Armenian actually simply means messenger
which is why he chose it cuz it's
representative my basic understanding of
most channelings of this nature is that
they are usually the product of an
arrangement or an
agreement that very often is made even
before physical Life
Begins and then your life as it
unfolds contains whatever kinds of
circumstances or or situations it needs
to to give you you not only the skills
to accomplish the agreement that you
made but usually at some point winds up
allowing you to remember that you made
such an agreement and to decide if you
even still want to fulfill
it everyone gets there differently based
on who they are for me the biggest
Turning Point what started it off was
that about 15 years ago when I was with
four friends on one occasion and two
friends on another
occasion we had two
very very within the same week very
close broad daylight physical sightings
of Bashar spacecraft over Los Angeles
now what I didn't understand at the time
aside from having seen what everyone was
calling a UFO and what I understand now
is that those physical sightings were
bashar's way of sort of tapping me in
the subconscious memory to get me
excited enough to start doing research
into metaphysical studies to learn the
things I needed to
learn so as the years went by
approximately 10 of them and I developed
a certain knowledge about metaphysical
ideas eventually I was introduced to
other channels who were practicing at
that time and one of the entities coming
through one of those channels offered to
teach channeling for whoever was
interested I took him up on the offer
even then not necessarily thinking that
I was going to wind up being a channel I
just simply wanted to learn more about
it because there weren't very many books
out on the subject at that time and I
thought if I went into the class I would
see something new
when I was in that class in a receptive
State under the guidance of the other
entity through a series of meditations
that are not necessarily dissimilar from
what you're going to experience today in
that receptive State thear and his
people made the telepathic link with me
and as soon as they did in that instant
the memory of having made the agreement
came back I remembered who they were who
I was to them why the ship sightings had
occurred I
remembered many dream conversations that
I had had with them that I had totally
blocked from my memory up to that point
they all came back at that one moment
when they did the first telepathic
message I received from Bashar was
basically now that you remember meaning
me that I made the agreement do I still
want to fulfill the agreement because it
was a choice it always is a choice it's
never something that's forced on you
after thinking about it for a while to
make sure I wasn't going crazy I decided
that it would be an interesting thing to
do so I started doing it I've been doing
it for the last 5 years and in a
nutshell that's basically how I got
started now the one thing that I really
like to stress especially to
newcomers is that while I have my own
validations and my own experiences to
allow me to function in doing this to
allow me to believe that Bashar is who
he says he
is there is absolutely nothing
nothing about this interaction that in
any way shape or form insists that you
have to believe he is who we say he is
because I can't prove this to you at
this point anyway Bashar has said that
maybe in about 10 or 20 years when
enough changes have taken place on this
world his civilization may be able to
start meeting us with other
civilizations face to face in a much
more blatant manner right now they're
staying in the background communicating
this way for several reasons probably
the most important of which
is as they've observed our society with
regard to receiving messages and
receiving information that can change
lives they've sort of they've noticed
that we've had a tendency in the past to
sort of lock on to the messenger and
throw the message in the garbage Camp
they don't want that to happen they want
the message and the information itself
to be the most important thing in this
interaction not who who they are they
don't want to be feared they don't want
to be idolized they want to be treated
as
equals and they want to act as a
reflection to teach us that what they're
talking about is really something we
already know in many ways they're here
to remind us of what we are not really
to teach us so much anything new
although there may be many principles
and many Concepts that he will discuss
that you may be hearing for the first
time at least in this
life one of the reasons they also stay
in the background is to sure that it's
completely up to
you to believe in whatever portions of
the information you want to believe in
and to take that information and apply
it in your life if you want to and not
to do so just because they say so not to
do so because of who they are or who
they're not to do so because you feel
it's the thing that you want to do this
is completely in your hands the
information that is being shared today
are tools and they're tools that will
work in certain ways when you apply them
in certain ways they've always worked
for me when I've applied them they have
never not worked and the results can be
quite quick and quite impactful but it's
up to you how to apply them everyone
that I know that has applied them has
found that they do work in various ways
so that's up to you the normal sessions
that we do conduct are usually question
and answer sessions and as was pointed
out there will be a little bit of that
at the end of the session today but this
is is the last Workshop session that
we're doing out of Los Angeles outside
of Los Angeles and basically a workshop
is a couple of hours of guided
meditations so Bashar in this case will
do most of the talking until it comes
time for questions and answers and what
he will be doing is
discussing various aspects of our
personalities of our physical lives of
our non-physical lives and talking about
exactly how
all the different concepts that we're
beginning to hear about now in what
people have been calling a new age how
all of these
seemingly let's say
um Airy philosophies that we've been
hearing about can actually be brought
right down to earth be understood in
very pragmatic and practical terms and
applied into your physical day-to-day
reality that I think is the thing that
really is the strength about what Bashar
talks about is that he's he's very
grounded in that sense and while he will
talk a lot about a lot of new age
Concepts that you hear all over the
place he has a very good um approach in
allowing you to understand how to use
that stuff in a very meaningful way so
if you get a tangible result in your
life and you don't just walk around
thinking nice thoughts without getting
any kind of change going on so hopefully
you will be able to find that in this
particular interaction
today um just briefly so that don't hold
the proceedings up too much uh what
Richard pointed out the reason that this
is the last out of town workshop for us
is that um recently I'm basically a
designer by trade and my business
partner and I recently came up with a
proposal for a whole new futuristic
theme park the concept of which is that
it's all enclosed in one structure and
when you're in it it's like you're on a
recreational space station a 100 years
in the future and we've been working on
that now for several years looking for
for financial backing for it and we have
recently just found a company that is
willing to do that to put that together
for us so that's going to occupy me for
the next four or 5 years putting that
all together and uh when that's done
it'll be somewhere in South Nevada and I
hope you'll all get an opportunity to
come out there and play with us when we
do that so that's that's the thing that
really motivates me in life aside from
this and hopefully whatever it is that
you learn today will help you in
whatever it is that excites you in life
and allow you to uh bring it to fruition
much more
quickly so once again I'd like to thank
you very much for being here there will
be a break today about halfway through
um and then like I said the Q&A the
question and answers will take place at
the very end of the session the one
thing I would like to ask you before we
start is that just as by way of
procedure when I'm going into the
altered state and when I'm coming out of the
state and when I'm coming out of the
altered state either at the break or at
the end when he says goodbye he says
take a break I'll just ask you don't
move don't talk give me a few seconds to
pull myself together because it
literally for me is like being lost in a
daydream I know there's an interaction
going on but I'm conscious of it in a
very different kind of a telepathic way
I don't actually hear the words of the
conversation for me it's like waking up
from a dream and it just Fades away but
it gives me I need a few seconds to just
sort of collect myself to literally
remember where I am and who I am so as
soon as I'm back and in Focus I'll let
you know and then you can jump up and
down and scream and run around and do
anything you want to at that point um
and also when I'm going into the altered
state you will notice that there will be
a few bodily adjustments that happen
none of what I'm experiencing is painful
it's energizing it's refreshing and I
only say that because sometimes it looks
like I'm in pain but those are just
automatic reactions to the changes that
are going on to form the link so please
don't worry about me I'm having a
wonderful time
um all of you please have a wonderful
time [Music]
too are there any questions about
procedure at all before we start does
anything anyone need to know anything
else no okay okay
bye-bye for EX [Music]
all right I'll say how are you all this
day of your time as you create time to
exist are you all aive yes how are you
all this day of your time good
we thank you very much and we extend to
you first of all our deepest
appreciation for allowing us to
communicate with you in this way at this
time we thank you for choosing to be
ambassadors and representatives of your
Society we thank you for allowing me to
be a representative of our Collective
civilizations which we term the
association of Worlds we thank you for
your part in the co-creation of this
endeavor for every single event of this
nature makes a difference in your
society and our society throughout the
entirety of what you may call in your
language the
universe we thank you very much for
allowing us to catch what we may call a
glimpse of your Consciousness a gift as
we perceive each and every being in the
universe to be a gift we thank you for
allowing us to unwrap yet further a
little bit more of your Consciousness to
share in its Delights you are a gift to
us we thank you for allowing us at this
time to reflect to you those aspects
those attributes those qualities we know
exist within all beings in creation the
beingness of living Light Within you
within your soul within your spirit
within your heart of hearts your
willingness to discover your connection
to the infinite gives us joy and the
fact that you are willing to allow us to
participate in that Discovery gives us
joy as well let us remind each and every
one of you individually and collectively
that the ideas and the concepts that we
are now discussing with you this day of
your time
are not for the purpose of trying to
change you in no way shape or form do we
have any intention of giving you the
impression that our ideas and our points
of view and our belief systems are in
any way better than yours they are
simply different you may find that our
civilization may have to some degree
some degree a little bit more of an
expanded point of view we may in our own
evolution in our own history have been
able to arrive at a place
where our understanding sees a little
bit more of the idea of the universe
than your past history has allowed you
to see but in no way shape or form does
this make us any better than you nor in
any way shape or form does it make you
any less this is of primary importance
to understand we desire to form a
relationship with you wherein all
individuals are equal for that and only
that relationship can allow us to expand
and grow and learn and share
together so that we may add to the
overall understanding of all that is the
Infinite Creation we in turn also would like to
Creation we in turn also would like to
remind each and every one of you that
the concepts that you may learn today
that we may discuss today are also in no
way shape or form intended for you to
use to try and change anyone else every
single individual
deserves the belief system that they
desire and when it comes time for an
individual or a society to change that
belief system then they will do so but
only in their own good
timing if any individuals in your
Society are going to change the easiest
way for anyone to change the society in
which they live is to be a living
example of that change to Simply Be a
reflection and a mirror of that change
so that other individuals by observing
that attitude and that bright light
shining from within you can then be
given an opportunity to see an example
of what kind of a reality you could have
upon your planet a place where peace and
love and light are what you may call the
norm of the situation rather than the
exception to the rule but only by being
that living example do you give them an
opportunity to understand that there are
other ways to live other than the idea
of the struggling and the striving and
the Warfare and the conflict and the
disease and pain and suffering that your
civilization has experienced for many
thousands of your years you cannot force
the idea of well-being on someone else
for that is contradictory to the idea of
well-being you must cherish and validate
unequivocally and unconditionally every
single being within creation to allow
them to be precisely who and what they
have chosen to be and invalidating them
as an equal and in acting as a
reflection of what they could choose
then you are giving them an opportunity
to know that they are equal to you you
are giving them an opportunity to
exercise their judgment their
discernment their ability to choose what
they wish to choose and you are giving
them the Free Will and the free Power
and the self-empowerment to be able to
do so because they will know that you
are not trying to change them they will
understand that you respect what they
are and in respecting what they are they
will then give you the consideration of
listening to what you have to say as
long as they understand that that you do
not believe that what you have to say is
any more important than what it is they
have to share as well we would simply
remind you of this first and foremost
before we begin for we wish you to
understand deeply that what we are doing
at this time in your Civilization by
interacting with it is not for the
purpose of trying to change it but only
for the purpose of reminding your
civilization and the individuals within
it who and what they have always been
aspects of the infinite and that they
can create any type of reality they so
desire any type of reality whatsoever it
is completely in your control completely
in your hands and it is a very very
simple thing to do this is what we are
here to remind you at this time every
single individual who understands that
you are in charge shall we say of your
own reality that you can create your
reality to be the way you want it to be
every single individual who understands
that has an infinite impact upon the
entirety of not only your own
civilization but of the universe for
each and every individual that
recognizes thems as an aspect as an
extension of the infinite allows the
infinite to operate that much more
smoothly shall we say that much more
positively and accelerate in that
positive direction creating a momentum
creating a flow creating an atmosphere
in which other individuals then will
find it easier to change their reality
to be what they prefer it to be rather
than living a reality that they have
been taught to believe is the only
reality they can live a reality that
they must live a reality that they must
suffer through just because they have
never been taught that there is any
other way well there are an infinite
number of ways if there was not more
than one way there would not be more
than one person in existence look around
you are surrounded by an infinite number
of individuals throughout the Universe
each and every individual is one more
way that the Infinite Creation has of
expressing the self that it is one more
point of view that it has of looking at
itself and understanding itself within
the creation it has created itself to be
all points of view in that sense are
valid as points of view you have the
capacity and always have had and always
shall have the capacity to choose the
reality that you PR preer to live
representative of who it is you know you
are what is in your terms the truth for
you the idea in a sense is to understand
that the so-called the truth is composed
of all
truths all realities are real in that
sense all imagination is somewhere
somehow someone a real reality because
you are not created to be capable of
conceiving of
non-existence anything you imagine
though it may not necessarily be
immediately applicable in your
particular physical Dimension
nonetheless anything you imagine is on
some level in some dimension in some
reality somewhere somewh a real reality
because you cannot imagine non-existence
and anything you can conceive of is
somewhere within the mind of creation
and therefore exists at its own reality
it has its own level of self-awareness
its own experiences its own fulfillment
its own
path this day of your time we will
discuss certain aspects of the path that
your civilization has taken certain
aspects of what you as members of your
Society have created yourself to be we
will explore some of the definitions
that make up your society and we will
explore the range of possible changes
that can occur that you may prefer to
create in your Society so that you can
have the reality you desire to have
without effort without struggle without
strife and without having to hurt anyone
else or yourself in order to create that
reality because that is how powerful you
are we as a civilization believe in you
utterly no matter what you may choose at
any given moment to think of yourselves
we believe in you utterly we know you
are aspects of the creation it is not a
matter of having to believe it it is not
a matter of taking it as you say on
faith we know beyond the shadow of a
doubt that you are capable of creating
any reality you desire we know it for a
fact and it is with that level of
conviction that we discuss these ideas
with you today knowing that if you are
willing to apply the ideas in your own
way and in your own good time you will
have the impact you want and you will
make the changes that you desire it is
as plain and simple as that all the
things that we are discussing are not
simply what you would call philosophies
we are talking mechanics we are talking
physics we are talking action and
reaction cause and effect if you apply
certain ideas in your life the
principles by which you have always
created your reality whether you knew it
or not you will get the result that you
desire one of the key reasons that you
have been able to create a reality one
of the key reasons that you have existed
within a universe that seems to be
separate from you one of the key reason
re you seem to have lives that happen to
you instead of through you is because
you have created the ability to forget
that you are a part of creation you have
created out of your own fears and out of
your own convenience and I do not mean
this derogatorily the concept that you
call an unconscious mind no one really
has an unconscious mind you are one
unbroken homogeneous Consciousness one
single idea the concept that you call an
unconscious mind has become a convenient
compartment into which you can place
things that you have been taught to be
afraid to look at about yourselves but
there is absolutely nothing absolutely
nothing about yourselves that you could
ever discover that cannot be applied in
a positive way if you so say therefore
one of the understandings that you can
now begin to have and perhaps will grow
understand through this interaction
today is that much of the reality that
you experience is the product of what
you believe it to be on an unconscious
level in other words your strongest
fears your strongest emotions your
strongest definitions your strongest
beliefs are what create your physical
experiential reality are what are the
reasons that attract certain situations
and opportunities to you if you are
creating your reality mostly unconscious
then you are out of touch as to why
certain things keep happening in your
life but if you begin to understand that
you can create your reality consciously
if you can be consciously aware of the
definitions you may have been brought up
with that have created the reality
you've gotten so far and you can learn
how to change those definitions in the
way that you prefer to then you can get
the reality you prefer and it is not
difficult at all I promise if you find
that it becomes difficult it is the
result of other belief systems that you
have bought into that say that life must
be difficult for those are belief
systems the idea that any change must be
difficult is not in any way shape or
form a law of the universe it is a
belief system it is a definition and it
is gerine perhaps to your society and a
few other societies that we have
encountered but it is not as you say
chiseled in stone it is
completely completely completely changeable it is
completely completely changeable it is
up to you
one of the things that your Society is
now beginning to understand in this
exploration of Consciousness in your
so-called new age of awareness is that
your Consciousness is far more than many
of you have been taught to believe that
it is you are beginning to understand
that you are truly an expanded being in
a sense to put this colloquially in your
own language you are first and foremost
a non physical total Consciousness the
idea of what you refer to as yourselves
as an isolated physiological being that
physical beingness this personality that
you are this Persona that you are is one
extension of the total being that you
are one isolated experience of the total
awareness that you are it is to use an
analogy but one finger on the hand of
the total soul that you are each and
every life you have
past present future alternate Dimension
no matter what you wish to label it is
but one aspect one facet of a
multi-dimensional crystal that is your
Consciousness this brings us to the
first phase of this particular
interaction which we have entitled
Persona reconstruction now the term Persona
reconstruction now the term Persona
reconstruction in of itself implies a
few things which we will now Endeavor to
at least Supply some definitions for
first of all the term
reconstruction implies that your
personality is a construction to begin
with that what you call your persona
your day-to-day personality the person
that you are is in a sense an artificial
construct of the Soul Now by saying
artificial we do not mean in any way
shape or form to imply that it is not
natural but we use your term artificial
to allow you
understand that it is a construct
nonetheless that it is a face a mask a
facade a
temporary representative of an idea you
have decided to
express each and every time you change
the idea that you wish to express your
persona the person that you are your
personality under go radical shifts and
you find yourself acting like a
completely different being now some of
you may say well but I look the same
more or less although you will find from
time to time and many you may realize
that when you change enough even other
individuals who have recognized you for
a long period of time may walk up to you
and say you know I don't know what it is
I almost didn't recognize you you look a
little different today well I feel
different you may say I feel very
different and so it is really no
surprise that you almost did not
recognize me I must imagine that I look
quite different well understand
something understand something now very
very very critically and very
importantly and you may and I mean it
you may take me absolutely literally in
what I am about to say I am not
concocting an analogy this is not a
metaphor I am being extremely
literal when you change the idea that
you are when you change the Persona that
you are in any way shape or form you are
from from that moment forward until you
make the next change literally literally
literally not the same person you were
before at all at all at all you may seem
I underline that word many times you may
seem to retain traits of the old you
which may allow you to think that you're
still the old you with a few
changes but any illusion of continuity
is your creation anything you carry over
so to speak from the old you has been
recreated in the new one because for
some reason you believe it must be
continued you are an absolutely New
Creation at that moment an absolutely
new artificially constructed personality
a new extension of the Soul no matter
how you think you look whether you think
you look the same or not you are not the
same person generally speaking in your
person generally speaking in your
Society one of the reasons that you tend
to look the same from moment to moment
more often than not and change slowly
over a long period of time is because of
your focus in physical reality because
time itself is the result of Simply your
focus of Consciousness it is only a side
effect time itself does not exist as a
principle it is a side effect of your
focus of your belief systems within
physical Consciousness
expressiveness the idea in and of itself
does not have to remain you can change
as quickly in any way shape or form as
you desire to if the desire and if the
belief is strong enough that is where
what you call Miracles come in but you
see Miracles are not really the
exception to the rule Miracles are the
natural order of things the idea of slow
change of painful change of struggle and
change of difficult change that is
actually counter to the Natural order of
existence because what you call a
miracle is when all the factors that
exist within creation are allowed not
made not forced allowed to be exact ex L
at the right place exactly at the right
time rather than being kept Away by
assumptive definitions that you have
been taught that is why the further you
taught that is why the further you
explore the idea of your Consciousness
the further you explore the idea of your
expansion of consciousness and the
further you recognize your connection to
the infinite the more you will find in
what you call your new age that Miracles
will be as you say the order of the day
and that magic as such per se and fairy
tales as such will be in your
understanding the way reality actually
is and not once again the exception to
the rule you have given yourself over a
long period of time many stories
fantasies imaginations that allow you to imagine
imaginations that allow you to imagine
that things could be done very swiftly
very magically very easily all of these
stories were for the purpose of
reminding yourself from the deepest
portions of the Consciousness the UN
Consciousness that you have created that
that is the actual truth of the way your
reality is the actess of the energy
being that you are that you can really
do those things that you do them all the
time but because you have forgotten you
have allowed yourself for thousands of
years to play the game that you didn't
notice you were creating your own
reality and that you could have changed
it to be anything you wanted it to be at
any given moment but now now after tens
of thousands of your years you have
finally arrived more or less at the end
of the game of forgetfulness because
primarily you have done just about
everything you could possibly do to play
the game of limitation and forgetfulness
you have played almost all the scenarios
out you are almost at the end of
anything you could concoct within this
particular physical Dimension and so
your new age Dawns upon you where you
are remembering who and what you are and
remembering who and what you are and
therefore that is reflected and
represented by your new interest in the
exploration of your Consciousness to
awaken to the fact that you have simply
been asleep for many tens of thousands
of years but now you are waking up and
in so doing you give off a different
vibration a different frequency and it
is that frequency that we have perceived
and accepted as an invitation to begin
interacting with you so that if you
choose to you can take some of the
things that have worked for us and see
if they will work for you as you now
awaken into a new dawn of understanding
about who and what you really
are let us begin now on what you may
call a more pragmatic level with Persona
reconstruction if you're going to
reconstruct your
persona the second thing that is implied
is that you must understand what a
Persona is constructed of it is
constructed of basically three things 1
2 3 very simple very simple
your persona the person that you are is
constructed much like what you call a
glass prism now I will assume that most
of you are familiar with the idea that
when you hold up what you call a
three-sided glass prism in front of
white sunlight you will see a broken
down colored Spectrum being reflected
somewhere beyond as the light passes
through you all familiar with this
yes the idea is to understand that your
personality is much the same idea
you have three sides your persona is
constructed of three things
belief emotion and thought
emotion and thought
pattern or if you wish
attitude these three
ideas past the white unbroken
homogeneous consciousness of light that
you are the total Soul through the
personality prison and based upon how
you have arranged your beliefs your
emotions and your thought patterns that
determines exactly the type of
Diversified broken down segregated
separated spectrum of your physical
reality you
experience you pass that energy through
you and you get the echo of the way the
prism you are is
constructed basically therefore you can
understand that if you don't like the
reality your experence in then there is
something shall we say a Miss in the way
your prism is constructed and there is a
very easy way to construct it in the way
you want it let us understand by further
analogy what the idea of belief emotion
and thoughts really
are let us use the analogy of building a
house let us assume that your physical
reality your life is a
house are you with me so
far now beliefs these are the
definitions that you have been taught to believe
that you have been taught to believe
in they are the blueprints of the house
they determine your beliefs utterly what
shape the house will be how many floors
how many doors how many windows how high
which way it
faces the blueprint is essential to be
as clear and precise as you want it to
be this is the first and most critical
stage if your
blueprint has all sorts of strange
little fingerprints all over it if lines
go off in all sorts of directions at odd
ball angles as you say you cannot expect
to have any other kind of a life other
than what is based upon the blueprint
that you allow to exist the definitions
of what you think life has to be or
ought to be is what determines the type
and style the flavor the themes in
reality that you
experience emotion emotions are the
builders the construction workers the
activation mechanisms that take the
blueprint you have handed them and
construct it and draw you to the
physical materialization of that blueprint they
materialization of that blueprint they
are the activators the builders and what
materials do they have to work with your
thought patterns your attitudes your
approaches these are the materials that
they have to build the house out of if
your attitude is flimsy and shaky you
cannot expect anything but the house you
have built to fall down no matter how
clean the blueprint if your attitude
however is strong and clear if your
convictions are solid if you are clean
and clear and your movements and actions
and intentions then the house that you
have built will stand firm and will
raise radiate and Shine for all to see
as a living example of what you are all
about who and what you are so believe
emotion and shall we say intentions
thought patterns attitudes the building
materials this is what goes into making
up the person that you are the
personality construct any change the slightest
construct any change the slightest
change in any one of those facets
changes you completely from one person
to another a further analogy to describe
how this is so it will be obvious once
you think about it let us say you have a
cube six sides and they're all painted
blue are you with me so far let us say
you decide that you're going to paint
one face red all right fair enough now
you might say well yes it's still the
same blue cube but I have painted one of
the faces red so there has been a small
change one little change in the overall
idea of the same old blue cube you can
say it that way or you can understand
this point of view you can say well wait
a minute wait a
minute if one of the faces is now red
the entire concept of the cube is also
different because a cube with six blue
sides and a cube with five blue sides
and one red one is a completely
different Concept in total from one
another therefore I can say that it is
the same old cube with a small change or
I could just as literally just as
accurately and just as validly say it is
an entirely different Cube and that
implies that a great change has occurred
you can think of yourselves this way as
well anytime you change a thought
anytime you change a feeling anytime you
change a belief you can say I'm still
the same old me I've just changed a
little bit and that will make anything
you want take a long time to happen or
you can understand that if you rewrite
any variable in the equation you are an
entirely new equation with an entirely
new outcome and you can say well wait a
minute that small change means I'm
starting from scratch right now
zero zero all over if I want to in any way I
zero all over if I want to in any way I
want to let the implications of what
this actually means sink
in if you are truly a different person
one moment to the next then only those
things you want to be attached to you
from the past will be attached and
anything else that you no longer believe
needs to apply to whoever it is you have
redefine yourself to be at this given
moment no longer applies and I mean
we'll get into that later in a more
powerful way we will give you a very
precise and what you call practical tool
steps 1 2 and three for using your
imagination to change the beliefs that
you have and to insert the beliefs that
you prefer to have if that is the case
with you and in such a way that you will
know beyond the shadow of a doubt that
they will
stick but we will get to that in in a
moment first and foremost we would like
to take you through a little bit of an
exercise that will loosen you up a
little bit in an abstract way so that
you will get in touch with certain
aspects of what you may call the
unconscious self that you have created
within you so that you will assist us in
assisting you to begin to dissolve the
barriers between your so-called
unconscious and conscious mind so that
you can begin to function as a
completely conscious being so that you
will be able to take ADV Advantage
better advantage of the other tools we
will give you later so for now let us
begin in an abstract Way by performing
The Following meditation you may all
close your eyes if you wish you can keep
them open if you wish it is up to you
there is no right way and no wrong way
to do this we will suggest however that
you become comfortable in whatever way
your imagination says is appropriate and
we will also suggest that you take three
deep breaths right now and as you do so relax
relax
now continue to breathe in whatever way
is most comfortable for you do not
breathe too heavily do not
hyperventilate as you say we do not want
you falling down on the
floor allow yourself simply to release
to relax to have fun for that is as you
say the bottom line to enjoy yourself
for you are worth enjoying and a very
important Point perhaps is to understand
this as well as you now allow yourself
to Center to sink into deep
relaxation only what you prefer will get
in nothing is forced upon you we are not
in your terms hypnotizing you you are
completely aware of everything you are
accepting and completely aware of
everything you do not want to hear right
now but you will receive it all and you
will use it in whatever good time and
good Pace you decide is correct for you
so do not worry either about getting too
much or getting too little you will get
it all and you will use it in whatever
way you want it when you want it and
secondly as you continue to breathe
deeply fully allow yourself now as you sink
fully allow yourself now as you sink
into your place of perfect
peace to take any sound any bodily
feeling any stray
thought and whereas you may have
formerly considered these things to be
distraction no longer label them that
way accept and include everything that
happens because everything happens for a
reason it is a part of you any thought
any feeling any bodily sensation you
would have formerly called a distraction
that you formerly would have assumed
would keep you from being centered Now
understand if it comes up it is there
for a reason invite it in and it will
take you deeper because you will be
integrating it and adding it to yourself
rather than trying to force it away or
get rid of it which diminishes
you add it in all sounds all feelings
all thoughts
all bodily Sensations temperature
everything added in invited in
incorporate and feel it add energy and
mass to you it may make you feel a
little bit heavier but that is all right
it will allow you to sink into that deep
state of repose of relaxation you in
your imagination
now are creating the bubble shall we say
that is representative of your place of
perfect peace wherever and whenever that
is doesn't matter to me it is completely
in your
hands just know beyond the shadow of a
doubt that no matter what your mind may
tell you you are going to be at the perfect
you you are going to be at the perfect
place you need to be to receive
everything you need to
receive just trust that and remember
this as you now allow yourself to relax
more and
more let us discuss briefly the whole
issue of trust
trust
you in order to create the reality that
you desire are required to
desire are required to
have 100%
infinite and absolute
trust now many of you have been taught
to think that this is a very difficult
thing to
have it is the easiest thing in creation
and I will tell you
why because you as a society have
defined doubt as a lack of trust and it
isn't doubt is 100%
absolute infinite trust in a reality you
don't
prefer you are always
trusting always 100% were it not so were you not
always 100% were it not so were you not
100% trusting in something you would
have no reality and no experience to
speak of your trust creates the reality
you experience what you trust in is up
to
you and that is why it is easy to trust
because the only thing you're
doing is not a matter of learning to
trust infinitely the only thing you are doing
infinitely the only thing you are doing
is Shifting your priority of what you
are trusting in from what you don't
prefer to what you do prefer that's all
there is to
it it is the same mechanism it is
infallible it always has work it is
working now and it always will
because it is a part of what you are you
are co-creators with the infinite
Creator you cannot help but create
because you were made in the image of
God and what that literally means is
that you are multi-dimensional infinite
and eternal creators
too that is what it means to be made in
the image of God God being all that is
so relax do not try too hard do not try
at all just know you are doing right now
in whatever way is appropriate for the
you you happen to be it will be perfect
for you right now and in so
understanding beyond the shadow of a
doubt imagine in whatever way shape or
form your imagination deems as
appropriate the following scenario in
whatever way works best for you it does
not matter but imagine generally
this you are a crystal with a point at
either end a shining bright clear
crystal and you are floating bobbing one
point up and one point down in the
middle of an infinite sea of crystallin
blue energy the surface of the sea stretches
energy the surface of the sea stretches
out all around you 36
°
you are in the
middle at the very
center and as you float gently and
serenely calmly as the sea bcts you in the middle
calmly as the sea bcts you in the middle
one half pointing up to the sky one half
pointing down Into the Depths as you Bob
gently upon the waves you realize the
following thing that because the surface
of the sea is truly infinite in all
directions then
anywhere you are is the center it might
as well be because it is infinite and
there is no way to
tell how far you have come no way to
measure yourself as to how far you have
to go because no matter how long you
travel no matter in what
direction you will still be at the
center because will still be infinite in
every single
Direction so there is no
rush there is no desperation
needed there is no need to try to get to
a certain place by a certain time in the
overall sense
sense
relax life is for the
living full living Where You Are are and
when you are there
paradoxically anywhere you wish to be is
more rapidly arrived that by the full
living of where you
are for if you are attempting to get
somewhere you are not because you do not
like where you are then you are
invalidating where you are and you are
removing the here and the now as a
stepping stone if you do not live the
here and the now to the fullest that you
can it extracting from it the things
that can truly serve you then you do not
use it to get you where you want to be
and there is no other way to get to the
future but through the present because
the future is Created from the present
and by the way so is the
past the present is the only time in
which you actually experientially ever
exist right here right now
forever it will change into an infinite
number of varieties of
presents but it will always be the
present always it will always be here
and it will always be
now so as you make these recognitions as
you float in this infinite sea of
energy you feel yourself warming to the
place you are at you feel yourself
beginning to learn to love it for what
it is because it contains all that you
need to enrich yourself to get you
anywhere else in that sea you want to
go and as you warm up to it as you begin
to relax in it as you begin to become
comfortable with who you are where you
are when you are you feel yourself
beginning to dissolve as a
crystal you begin to melt over the
surface of the infinite sea spreading
out in an ever expanding circle like a
thin crystallin film full of rainbow
refractions you spread farther and
farther and farther until impossible as
it may seem you cover the entire surface
of the infinite energy sea all the waves
are now within
you there is nowhere on the surface of
this sea that you are not
no matter where you focus your
Consciousness is now the center they are
all the center every point is the center
when you choose it to be
so you are everywhere and it is all
within you there is no Beyond no Horizon
that stretches or reaches beyond your
perimeter it is all
within and as you contemplate this in a
relaxed State feeling the waves
undulating within you up and down Crest
and trough you begin to contemplate the
trough you begin to contemplate the
heavens above the brightness of the
light from the sky and the deepness of
space and the Stars
beyond for that is infinite
to and as the light from the heavens
strikes the crystallin film that you are
it excites some of your molecules and
speeds them up and you begin to rise a
portion of those molecules begin to rise
like a crystallin
mist and you begin to fill the entire
infinite volume of the
sky until all the stars of Space are
embedded within
you and as you feel the expansiveness
above you
you
feel the creative pressure of all that
energy bearing down on you and you allow
that pressure to
gently push some of the molecules out of
the film that still lie on the surface
until they begin to sink down Into the
Depths the blue violet black
depths of the infinite sea below you
until you also fill that b you and all
of the creatures in the sky and all of
the creatures in the sea now swim and
fly within you and you feel
them you feel them you feel their
electricity you feel their
electromagnetism you feel their living
light as they move through you like so
many electrical impulses of
Consciousness it is all all within you
and you realize
now that
you you each and every one of
you is truly one complete perspective
one complete point of view one complete
way that all that is has of
being you are all all that is all that
is is
you every individual is yet one more way
that all that is has of manifesting
itself in all of the multi-dimensional
simultaneous ways that it
can and
you are one of those ways and yet within
you are all of the other ways as well
all of them you are infinite you are
Eternal being because you are aspects of
being because you are aspects of
creation you exist and therefore you
always have and you always
will always so
relax anything you desire to
create is within your your power to
create because it has been given to you
with your free will to do so choose what
you prefer it is your
Birthright as children of
creation and now imagine yourself this
infinite sphere of blue white
electromagnetic light filling the entire
volume of creation the entire volume of
creation filling you and pick any Center
any point and feel yourself collapsing
down rushing down toward that center
point until you meet at the middle and
explode in bright white light outward
again and the entire volume crystallizes
with that expanding wave of energy into
one infinite multifaceted Crystal that
shines and is C clear and has order and
purpose and is
aware and
alert and
awake feel the Brilliance the
invigoration the energy the pulse the
vibration coursing through you you are
living light itself
literally living
light crystallized at a particular point of
crystallized at a particular point of
focus for a particular purpose your
own know that you are this living
Crystal that is the symbol of the
crystal in your new age of awareness you
are the living Crystal of all that
is and the physical crystals upon your
planet are simply Reflections are simply
the mirrors
of the crystallin Consciousness each and
every one of you
is take three deep breaths and lock this
understanding in you
now and feel the likess coursing through
you and after you have concluded your
breath of three allow yourself slowly
comfortably at whatever pace is correct
for you to open your
eyes familiarize yourself with your new
surroundings for once again I remind
you you are not the same people you were
a moment ago
literally you are not in the same room
you are not in the same city you are not
on the same Planet you are not in the
same solar system you are not the same
universe literally
you are now whatever
universe is truly more vibrationally
representative of the you you prefer to
be you have taken yourselves there you
have created the impact of
change you are different your lives will
be different because you are not the
same people living them
know that for a
fact and now allow yourselves to stand
up and stretch your new
bodies try them on for size as you
say they are not the same bodies you
used to
be in your own good time be seated
understand what we have just said they
are not the same bodies you used to be
notice I did not say they are not the
same bodies you used to have for a body
is not really something you have you do
not literally as you have been taught
inhabit your body as a spirit no matter
what the illusion that is created upon
physical death where it seems you are
leaving your body no matter what the
illusion that is created upon what you
call astral projection where it seems
you are leaving your body you are not a
resident in a body that is your illusion
that has been created by your
definitions of Separation upon your
planet by your belief in linear time and
volumetric space it is the illusion your
Consciousness creates to make sense out
of what it is you are doing which is
simply expanding your point of
view your spirit does not inhabit your
body your body is is is is your spirit
in physical
terminology your Consciousness is not
contained within your body your body is
contained within your
Consciousness understand that concept and it will have
understand that concept and it will have
great impact in what you are capable of
doing in your physical reality because
if you understand that concept then you
will understand that everything
everything you call a physical
object is within and made of literally
made of your
Consciousness it is not an issue of Mind
Over Matter it is understanding that
mind and matter are the same
thing and as you
think so it shall
be this is why it is critical to get in
touch with the strongest definitions
within you to change them into what you prefer
you to change them into what you prefer
them to be you will get the result
guaranteed you cannot not not experience
a reality that you are not the vibration
of
to explain this in a more graphic way we
have used what we call the radio analogy
now you're all familiar with the device
on your planet you call a radio yes yes
you know that you can receive any number
of programs upon that one device yes yes
you know that each program is different
from every other program by virtue of
the fact that they operate on a
different frequency yes yes but when
your dial is tuned to one particular
program if your radio is shall we say
functioning correctly you usually only
get one program now you know that while
you're listening to that one program
that that doesn't mean all the other
programs aren't still there they are but
you do not receive them because you are
not attuned to
them physical creation is that way there
are an infinite number of vibratory
realities an infinite number of earths
an infinite number of any other civiliz
ization an infinite number of ways you
could be experiencing your day-to-day
physical reality an infinite number of
choices and infinite number of
opportunity the ones you wind up
experiencing and the ones you wind up
attracting as opportunities are
completely the reflection of the dial
you are and to what station you are
attuned in other words the thought
patterns the beliefs and the emotions
you buy into the strongest determines
the program you get you want to change
the program change the dial by changing
your frequency changing your frequency
is simply changing the definition you
are of reality getting in touch with
what those definitions are you have been
taught and changing it Reinventing it
redesigning the definition into what you
prefer it to be and then implementing
that in your life and again we will get
into this much more strongly in a little
while step by step in an
easy very
clear and pragmatic way but
way but
first another understanding another
expansion of the definition of what you
are as a personality so that you may be
more clearly in touch with what that
definition is now many of you for a long
period of time have said well all right
we are physical beings and we have
generally speaking five senses our touch
our taste our smell our sight and our
hearing lately although of course this
knowledge has existed in your
civilization forever and some
individuals now and then have recognized
it but lately more large groups of
individuals have begun to play with this
idea that you may have some sort of oh
how do you say mysterious six sense
somewhere all
right in
fact you have seven physical senses and
an eigh transcendental
one what you have been calling the Sixth
Sense is actually the
seventh the six physical
sense could colloquially be called the
sense of
orientation it is what you simply call
spatial and temporal orientation how you
know where and when you
are what you colloquially in animals
call homing Instinct you have it too it
is centered physiologically in your
sinus area and is hinged upon the
substance in your sinus area called
magnetite and it is very sensitive to
shifts in electromagnet magnetic
patterns surrounding your Earth and
throughout the
Universe this is what your animal
Consciousness is used to as you say
navigate you all have it now some of you
seem to use it in a polarity way you say
I never know where I am I'm always lost
always without fail well that is still a
type of sensitivity it is simply that
you are polarizing it but you're still
using the facil
the idea is to understand that the
reason you are usually not familiar with
the sixth and the seventh senses is
because the first five are
electrochemical in nature and much more
easily sensed by you and the sixth and
the seventh are electromagnetic in
nature and a little bit more refined a
little bit more subtle in a sense now
the one that you've been calling the
sixth which is actually the seventh is
vibrational dis
discernment it is the basic
extrapolation of what in your language
you used to say when you said well The
Vibes are good The Vibes are
bad the vibrations are given off by
every individual electromagnetically you
all resonate at a particular pitch that
is your signature
vibration it is a combination of many
vibrational electromagnetic patterns and
each and every one of you are sensitive
to picking them up and interpreting them
relative to your own so you get a sense
of the Integrity or the lack of
Integrity or the intentions of another
individual or a situation now sometimes
of course those intentions can be shall
we say filtered colored interpreted by
your own beliefs but nonetheless you
still receive those vibrations and again
it is generally electromagnetic
it is centered within what you call the
glandular systems of your body
especially the pineal gland of your
brain and it is to some degree assisted
by the fact that every single cell of
your body at the very center has what
you may call a small antenna a small
receiver that is sensitive to those
electromagnetic pulses they travel to some degree along
pulses they travel to some degree along
your neural network but they also are
shall we say pumped up by what you call
your enzymatic Network and your
endocrine system as well they are
assimilated and regulated by the
glandular flow of your body and
translated into an overall feeling that
you have called
Vibes now the eighth transcendental
sense is simply the sense of
knowingness when you don't necessarily
require any of the other senses to
Simply all of a sudden for no apparent
reason reason know that something is so
it is Transcendental because it directly
links your physical self with your
non-physical overall over Soul the total
being that you are the connective place
in your body is within what you call the
Corpus colossum the membrane that
divides your left brain Hemisphere and
your right brain hemisphere at the very
center there is a gate a doorway that is
connected in that sense what many of you
have called the crown chakra of your
body that connects you to all other
levels of your being your transcendental
sense of overall
knowingness above and beyond what you
call space-time orientation because
space and time are your Illusions as
well not that they are not real while
you're in it but they are shall we say
simply side effects of how you interpret
the idea of the dimension you are being
at this time
they are reflections of the fact that
you have segregated yourselves into so
many different
parts if you chop your idea of yourself
up into so many different parts you
create a need for a medium called volume
and time which will allow you to
experience all the pieces you have
rendered yourselves into when you think
of yourselves in a more homogeneous way
as a single Consciousness you do not
need to experience as much time as much
space and that is
why when you are having what you call
fun when you are truly absorbed truly
creating truly living in the moment
that's why you don't experience the idea
of time and space so much you all say
Well when you're having fun time flies
now you know it doesn't really
fly what you're doing is not literally
literally literally not creating as much
time when you are absorbed in the doing of
when you are absorbed in the doing of
who and what you are that really excites
you that you really love to do you don't
create as much of the concept of space
and time because you're right here
focused right now at the very center
you're not scattered and spread out
therefore you don't need as much time
you don't need as much space in which to
experience all that you are you receive
it in large conceptual gulps in whole
bites bigger chunks as you say now here
is something else about
that when you are doing something that
totally immerses you and you feel
experientially that oh let's say 1/ half
of your hours has passed and you look up
and all around you you see that
approximately let's say three of your
hours have passed you say oh my where
did the time go and understand what you
have simply done because you have agreed
to play the basic Time game that your
whole society is playing is you have
reinserted yourself back in the time
track to play catchup with everyone else
so you will still be synchronized with
them when they say it must be 3 hours
later you will agree
however if you
truly experientially have felt that only
about one half of your hours have passed
you have literally only aged 1/ half
hour literally living in the moment is how
literally living in the moment is how
you become ageless
Timeless like a
child because you are in that sense as
every being is a child of creation you
are infinite you are Eternal and you do
not necessarily have to a age in the way
you have used age you can mature you can
grow you can learn but it does not in
any way shape or form ever have to be
debilitating or disease ridden dis ease
all disease all pain mental pain
spiritual pain physical pain emotional
pain all pain all disease is the result
of res existence to the natural
self it is trying to be something and
someone you know you're not based on
beliefs definitions expectations
judgments and validations guilts
frustrations hates rages all the
self-doubting and invalidating Concepts
that you have created with separation in
your Society they are what create the
idea of the age Ing and the diseases in
your Society you do not need them as
symbols you can still have growth you
can still have challenge you can still
discover an infinite number of things in
ecstasy you can it's up to you but I
guarantee you have every right to
experience it that
way now before we get to the 1 two three
now before we get to the 1 two three
practical steps
one more time let us shall we say
explore another abstract aspect of your
energy so that you will be able to fully
utilize what we will give you
later this type of blending that will
occur in this particular meditation is
of the essence because what it will do
is facilitate a blending of the
polarities the dichotomies the paradoxes
within you and
especially it will allow you to get in
touch with what each and every one of
you have within you and what your
Society has insisted on denying for so
long that each and every one of you has
both masculine and feminine energy
within you the blending and the marrying
of these two energies of this
relationship of yourself to yourself is
instrumental in creating balance
blending these does not mean that if you
have chosen to be born as a physical
male you will cease acting as a physical
male it doesn't mean that if you have
chosen to be born as a physical female
you will cease acting as a physical
female what it means is that you will
understand assertiveness and receptivity
within you no matter whether you are
male or female it mean you will cease
fearing your other self it means you
will marry yourself and be at ease and
at peace in an unconditionally loving
relation ship with the total energy you
are because the soul that you are
contains both even if it may Express
itself physiologically one way or
another in any given lifetime it still
contains both energies a blending and a
balancing of those energies will keep
you absolutely at the center of yourself
and at the center of yourself by
definition there can be no such thing as
this is
none therefore one more time but for the
very first time since of course you are
new people close your eyes take three
deep
breaths no to know beyond the shadow of
a doubt that you are creating the place
of perfect peace in which you will
receive everything you
need everything
everything
imagine in whatever way works best for
you at whatever Pace works best for you
taking my words only as a suggestion
knowing that your imagination will alter
it in whatever way is best for
you imagine the following scenario
scenario
approximately 10 ft in front of
you is a replica a mirror image of your
body of you the physical you you believe
yourself to
be just look at
it just look and observe that it is
looking at you
just
looking now in your imagination while
the other you stands perfectly
still walk up to it and walk all around
it observe it from every
angle float above it float below it look
at it from every possible angle you
can just observe for what it is for it
is the idea
you have been
being just take it in absorb it do not
judge it do not analyze it just
it do not analyze it just
look just
feel and when you are
done go back and stand in your original
position facing it about 10 ft away as
you say and then you stand per L
say and then you stand per L
still and allow your duplicate to come
to
you let it walk all around you as you
walked around it let it observe you from
every possible
[Music] angle it knows you are watching but that
angle it knows you are watching but that
is all right it just wants to be
familiar with
you when it has satisfied itself allow
it to go back to its starting point and
just continue to look at each
other taking a deep
breath and let it out as a
side and just relax send energy in your
imagination to that other self and feel
that other self sending energy to
you send love to that other self and if
for any reason you feel the need send
forgiveness even as you allow the other self to send
even as you allow the other self to send
forgiveness to you for anything that you
feel has been an act outside of your
integrity for anything you feel is a
reason that allowed you to do that do
not continue to chastise yourself you do
not need to consider yourself Unworthy
of
love just forgive even as the Infinite
Creation always forgives
you deserve it just
relax if you are now making a decision
to be a different you then understand
that your choice to Simply make that
decision is enough to
balance any other choice you have
made open your arms and your
imagination see the other you opening
its arms and walk toward each other
meeting halfway in the middle and as you
meet
Embrace and just
hold just
support just
nurture just feel the other
you just love it let it love you let it
allow it
it
just allow it and as you feel your
hearts beating against each other's
chests feel the warmth that begins to
allow you to merge you are literally
merging into one body one form beating
with one heart breathing as one
breath you are one being one you have
Blended the conscious and the
unconscious so there is no longer any
need for the in between communication of
subconsciousness you are now awake and
alert as one being ready and willing to
accept all within
you ready and willing to know that
everything you are now going to discover
about yourself can become a part of who
and what you desire to
be there are no
interruptions nothing to oppose
you you are in
you are in
control you have always been in
control even when it seems you have been
out of control you have created that
illusion with your
belief you are a 100% being
always even if there have been times
when you have used 90% of yourself to
make it seem as if you've only used
10% you are a 100%
being no more but never any less and
less and
now in your imagination turn around 180°
and be behold 10 ft away from you once
again is another being another body
however this body is your identical twin
but your sexual
opposite it is what you would have
looked like had you been born sexually
opposite to what you are
now it is the other side the polarity of
you look at it just look let it look at you
look at it just look let it look at you
do not fear
it do not judge
it it will stand perfectly still for you
while you go walk all around
it observe it from every
angle it knows you are watching but it
trusts you
implicitly when you are through go back
to your starting place and allow it to
do the same to you as before to walk
all around you above and below you to
become familiarized with you as you became
familiarized with you as you became
familiarized with
it until it is satisfied and goes back
to its starting position then as
then as
before open your heart and send ways of
Love of bonding love of
unconditional love and if you find it is
necessary send
forgiveness and if you find it is
necessary receive
forgiveness and open your arms in your
imagination even as your opposite opens
its arms and walks towards you as you
walk toward it and you meet in the
middle and
embrace for the first time in a long
time and you just hold and
support and
nurture and love each other for what you
are no longer is there any need to
express what the other ought to
be it is what it is and as it is it is perfect
perfect
feel your hearts beating against each
other's chests you are in
love as you float in the warmth of the
energy cocoon that surrounds you you
feel yourself merging melting blending
as one
being with both energies male and female
female and male you are one homogeneous
balanced light and as you blend your
light increases and you are a vibrant
radiant white light that shines to the
Infinite Space faes around you so that
all may see the living light that you
have chosen to
be balanced clear
enlightened and clean with your
integrity intact and your
intentions razor sharp and Crystal Clear
you are one un being awake and alert conscious truly
conscious truly
conscious for the first time in a long
time and it feels good and it feels
expansive and it feels light and
effortless and joyful and above and
beyond all exatic ecstasy
you will never
find that there will ever
be too much ecstasy for you to
handle ever you never receive at any
moment more than you can handle for the
universe and creation does not do
pointless nor extraneous
things every everything that is is
because it fits because it
belongs where it is as it is everything
that exists deserves to
exist or it wouldn't
exist treat yourself with the same
respect that the infinite treats you
with by having created you to begin with
if it didn't believe you deserve to
exist you wouldn't
so the you you know yourself to be the
complete and total you is worthy of all
you can conceive you deserve it because
you have conceived of it because it is
representative of you and you belong you
fit or you wouldn't
exist three deep breaths and lock it
in and know it
with all your knowingness beyond the
shadow of a
doubt and in your own way in your own
time open your
eyes and greet the new dawn the new day
the new world around you and the new
once again new
you you are not the same I am not the
same this conversation begins now
happy
birthday if you wish once again you may
stand and stretch and get used to the
new you that you are from this moment
forward until you change
again and as you are doing so allow me
to remind
you be seated if you wish change is the
only stable constant in
creation I ask you simply how are you
truly more stable by attempting to be
static and stand on one foot or by
moving left right left right left right
the motion is what gives you
balance the change is what gives you
growth and it is what truly creates
stability attempting to remain in the same spot
attempting to remain in the same spot
creates
stagnation stability is the product of
being willing to change as you say in
your language to go with the flow
because the flow comes from
you life does not happen to you it
happens through you you are The Crucible
you are the Catalyst the
furnace that melts down
all probable
realities into one homogeneous energy
and crystallizes them into the realities
you prefer to
be after your break we will now discuss
some of the more pragmatic tools you can
apply directly now and get the result in
your physical day-to-day existence but
for now you may
enjoy a refreshing short break we will
resume contact in this fashion in
approximately 10 to 15 of your minutes
of
counting as the new
you enjoy
are you just going to call on raised
hands when it comes time for sking
yeah all right don't say allow us to
continue in the following
manner let us discuss now the idea of a
very specific tool of very sharp EDG
tool that has a great deal of impact
into your physiolog logical
reality and your ability to change that
reality in the way you prefer it to
be it is a very straightforward
technique very powerful technique and we
guarantee that if you use it you will
find great changes occurring in all
levels of your reality but of course
only as fast and only in what ways you
prefer them
to it will not run out of control as you
say it is to be used used by you and
applied by you where and when you want
to to get the results you desire we
discussed earlier with you the notion
that the critical ideas of the
situations that happen to you in life
are basically the product of how you
define them to be what your definitions
are of the most likely type of
atmosphere or circumstance that can
occur to you
now sometimes what can be of great
sometimes what can be of great
assistance as we have said is getting in
touch with what the definition is you
already have and then redefining it in
other words you can't say well if I have
a reality I don't
prefer in a meditative State allow
yourself to imagine what kind of a
belief would you have to have in order
to create the reality that you're
getting examine it honestly with
yourself honest communication is
necessary you have to be very clear
about why you're getting what you're
getting and why you're not getting what
you're not getting you have to very
clear about what it is you really think
about these things what it is you really
believe about these issues what would
you believe if you did get it would you
be different in a way you don't want to
be different do you have a belief that
you have to be different in a way you
don't want to be if you got what you say
you want discuss it from every angle
with yourself for many times you will
find the only thing keeping at B what
you desire is simply your assumption of
what it must be if you get it an
example many of you we have discovered
in our conversations with you have a
great deal of issues as you say
regarding what you call
abundance now the idea can be expressed
in many different ways and this whole
section is also involved with excitement
and abundance for a very good reason
because they are intimately connected
intimately connected in fact they are
effects of the same thing one thing they
are not really two different things
excitement abundance both are effects
different sides of the same coin as you
say the same
issue the idea however is that many of
you have created so many separations in
your life so many definitions in your
life about what you think something is
or what you think it ought to be that is
those definitions in themselves
that prevent you from experiencing what
you say you
want abundance abundance abundance many
of you interpreted in one particular way
you talked about monetary richness and
it is a valid way but let's discuss that
now since that's the way most of you are
familiar with many you say I'd love to
be rich but I can't seem to be able to
get rich I see other rich people all the
time they are rich I'm not I'm jealous
I'm envious all right fair enough but
remember jealousy and envy are the result of
jealousy and envy are the result of
judgments judgments in the following way
if you are jealous and envious of
someone else what you are saying is they
contain something I
don't jealousy is when you
recognize that someone else has
something but you don't recognize that
in order to be a able to see it in them
you must contain it too remember you
cannot experience a reality you are not
the vibration of if you see something in
them you must also in order to be able
to see it in them you must be capable of
attaining it as well jealousy comes in
when you judge that they have it and you
don't when you understand that you also
have the same potential when you allow
them to function as an example to you
then you get the opposite of jealousy
inspiration jealousy is when you
discount yourself when you invalidate
them you invalidate yourself and you
feel cut off from what you see
inspiration is when you feel connected
to what you see and use them as a living
example of what you can also be if you
want to
be but if you also have within you
certain definitions let us say once
again about the idea of being rich then
the following scenario happen you may
not even know you have the following
definition but you may say well I want
to be rich you may say this on the
surface all the time but you may
focus on other people around you in a
particular way maybe in the following
way you may have been brought up
unconsciously to
believe that all the individuals around
you that you see that are rich have
terrible terrible habits and manners
oh yes everyone knows rich people are as
you say very snooty and do not care
about anyone else and they are quite
atrocious in their behavior and well to
sum it up in the English language they
are jerks all right many of you have these
jerks all right many of you have these
beliefs within you that in order to be
rich you have to act like a
jerk if you have that kind of a belief
system within you and you don't want to
be a jerk
then you will also as long as you make
the association between that state and
being rich never be rich either because
you are keeping it away by defining that
it will automatically bring you
something else you don't want you don't
have to Define it that way that is why
it is essential many times to get in
touch with what it is you do Define what
your definition of the situation is
because once you realize that you may
have had that kind of a definition you
can say wait a minute I don't have to
believe that I don't have to be that way
just because I'm rich doesn't mean I
have to be a jerk I can be who I want to
be and be rich I can be rich the way I
want to be I don't have to associate one
with the other therefore there is no
longer any stigma no longer any taboo in
allowing myself to be as rich as I can
be because I know I will be that way in
the way I want to be and I don't have to
follow the example of individuals who
have done it outside of their integrity
I can maintain my integrity and be rich
that is changing the
definition once you have changed the
definition then nothing if that
definition is precise and clear and
conviction exists strongly enough
nothing will stop that reality from
flowing in your direction nothing
nothing nothing nothing nothing there is
nothing to stop it anyway except
you nothing to stop it
nothing so the other way another way in
so the other way another way in
conjunction with the idea of finding out
what the belief systems are that you
already have is to find the belief system you do
have is to find the belief system you do
want and this is simply put in the
following way it has to do with excitement
way it has to do with excitement
excitement what is it what is excitement
how many of you really know what
excitement actually is you may know what
it feels like but what is it that you're
feeling when you feel excited about
something well I'll give you our
definition may not be your definition
but it is our definition it may work for
you it may not here it is
excitement St toop as you
say I excitement since you are feeling
some right now is the physical TR are
you paying attention yes oh all the I
was talking to all of you all right
excitement is the physical physical
physical the physical
translation of the vibrational energy
that represents what the path you chose to be
represents what the path you chose to be
in other words whatever it is in life
that excites you more than anything else
excites you because that's who you are
and what you're all all about do
it why hold back I'll tell you why you
hold back you already know why you hold
back if you are holding back because
your Society has taught you many things
that contradict what you know you
actually are your Society say oh well
yes oh this excites you does it more
than anything else well that's all well
and good but here it comes that's no way
to make a
living oh don't be such a child oh grow
up oh that's ridiculous oh that's silly
oh no one takes that seriously oh well
that would make a nice hobby but as a
real job this is the real reality as you
say all those ideas stop you before you
start stop you from realizing that
whatever it is that excites you the most
no matter how fantasy like it may seem
when compared to some of the more quote
unquote realistic ideas is on your
planet is still nonetheless the thing
that excites you the most and as such is
actually your signal and your sign for
what it is in your life that will
actually support you most abundantly
believe it or not it all comes wrapped
in one kit one unbroken kit whatever it
is that excites you the most tells you
three things a as we have said this is
who you are B because it is who you are
it will be one of the easiest things you
could ever
do and see because it is one of the
easiest things you could ever do you
will be supported abundantly in whatever
way you need to be supported to be
allowed to continue to do the thing that
you really are because the universe
supports you when you are what you know
you are it supports you when you're not
but but it also creates resistance
because that is not who you were created
as it supports you negatively it
supports you by giving you the
resistance to let you know who you are
but your Society has created so much
limitation so much segregation and
separation that you spend a great degree
of time
insisting on being who you're not and
that's what tires you out and why you
are as you say Wasted by the end of the
day very often
an individual that does what it is that
is really apropo and true for them what
is really an expression of their unique
creativity is always overjoyed and
energetic all through the day and
actually finds that they need very
little physical
rest that is why what you call many of
your soall Geniuses seem to subsist on
extremely little Sleek because they are
fully involved in being who they
are sometimes you call them
eccentric fair enough but that may
simply be the way they have to play the
game to be who they are and they are
only eccentric when you compare them to
the way your Society judges that they
ought to act who is to say how you ought
to act to be who you are with Integrity
absolutely if you want to maintain who
you are in a positive direction if you
are being who you are without Integrity
then you usually create a type of
resistance that creates all sorts of
what you call problems however it
doesn't prevent you from being negative
you can be negative because you have
free will but being negative creates
more negativity and more separation and
segregation in your life because that is
the way it accelerates in a negative
Direction being a positive and
integrated individual always creates
more unification and acceleration in the
positive direction that is simple
physics there is nothing mysterious
about this at all what you put out is
what you get back plain and simple at
some point one way or another whether it
seems to build up for a time if nothing
is happening right now it will hit
somewhere some when remember you are
infinite and eternal beings one lifetime
does not necessarily give you an
indication of exactly the type of
momentum you are storing up you will
experience it
somewhere however because this now is
your so-called accelerated new age you
will find many of you that many of the
things that it may have previously taken
you many lifetimes to live out can all
be experienced right now in one life so
you will find you so highly accelerated
that now many of the things you do do
will in that sense come to you will
manifest in this life many of the things
that you focus on are achievable in this
life now so the idea to understand first of
now so the idea to understand first of
all is to focus on the idea that excites
you the most with
Integrity that is the first step
identifying above and beyond anything
else the thing in life that really
motivates you now I do not necessarily
mean that you have to come up right now
with the thing that will be the most
exciting thing you will ever
do but right now out of all the things
you are consciously aware of that are
open and available to you of all the
things that are opportunities for you to
act upon of all the things you are
capable of acting upon that's a key
understanding of all the things that you
have the ability to do something about
pick the one at every given moment that
excites you beyond anything else and do
it with Integrity you will always by
doing that always be completely
aligned flawlessly fluidly effortlessly
and abundantly with the path you are
always excitement is the thread it leads
to all other things and circumstances
that will excite you all other growth
and acceleration that will continue to
excite you and give you the abilities
you need to do the next most exciting
thing that will come along automatically
synchronistically in your Society you
say coincidentally there are no accidents
coincidentally there are no accidents
not
one no matter how
small now we are not saying everything
is predetermined everything is Faith no
we are not saying that you create your
own destiny but you are an
orchestration you decide where you will
go what choices you will make and you
get the result of those choices if
anything is predetermination it is
simply that what you choose will give
you a result and you are predestined to
experience the result of your choice but
as soon as that is fulfilled you're at
the crossroads again and you make
another choice you are always capable of
choice you are always capable of
choosing
always and most importantly you are
always capable of
transforming every situation into a
positive one if you desire to because
because because
because all are you paying attention
still oh all situation all situations
are fundamentally
neutral no situation has built in
meaning they are all blank devoid of
meaning they're all
props the meaning you have been taught
to give to them determines the effect
you get out of them it is that simple if
you give a positive meaning to a neutral
situation you will get a positive effect
out of it no matter what you may have
previously been taught to believe the
situation must mean no matter how it
looks on the surface if you give it for
yourself a positive meaning if you know
you will be able to get something
positive out of it even if its original
intention was negative you will only get
a positive effect out of it if however
you give it a negative meaning the only
thing you can get out of it is a
negative effect again this is simple
physics you get out what you put in
plain and simple it is this principle
the only principle that actually exists
for every being in creation it is the
only law it is the structure of existence
law it is the structure of existence
itself
everything else you call laws whether
moral religious political social
economic or
scientific are all based on the one
structural law what you put out is what
you get back it works for
everyone everywhere every
when it is the only law there is
therefore allow yourself to not be
guided by the way things necessarily
look we are not saying to
ignore when you know for a fact through
observation that someone is doing
something intentionally to harm in a
negative way we are not saying that you
look at this and call it positive what
we are saying is that you observe what
is going on and know that it can be
transformed into a positive idea and the
first step in doing so is to see what
positive can come out of it to live as a
living example a shining example of the
fact that it can be transform and that
will allow the other individuals if they
choose to to see a way to turn it
around because every single time an
individual does something outside of
Integrity every time they do something
negative it is mostly because they don't
believe they have any other choice
because they believe they're out of
control because they have been taught to
believe they're out of control and if
they believe they're out of control they
don't believe the control exists within
the only way they believe they can gain
control over their lives is to interact
with what they see outside and that
means they feel that the only way to
have control is to dominate what they
see outside and who they see outside
them but that is a downward spiral which
causes them to feel more desperate more
out of control because the control is
not out there it's in here already and
if they feel that they are out of
control and attempt to dominate their
exterior and create a sinking spiral of
negativity they feel they are going as
you say down the drain they feel alone
cut off they reach and grasp desperately
for whatever they can and they try to
take as many people with them as they
possibly can because they don't want to
be alone that is the reason basically
fundamentally for all of what you would
call your negative behavior and criminal
activity upon your planet it is because
these people have been brought up to
believe they are not in control already
an individual that knows the control is
there that knows they are an aspect of
the infinite has the infinite power to
infinite has the infinite power to
create anything they want without having
to hurt anyone else or themselves in
order to create it because the control
is already there
so First Step at any given moment or as
a career any way you want to identify
what excites you the most above and
beyond anything
else first
step Second
Step not only identify what it is but
identify with it in the following
way you are beings of great
emotionality we have discussed that
emotions are the activation mechanisms
that bring manifestation into physical
materiality emotion
energy motion use it it is the
activation principle the stronger your
desire for something the easier and more
quickly it can manifest your emotional
content and magnitude literally reaches
out and grabs it and pulls it in
literally out of all the possible
realities you could have your emotions
determine the vibrational pitch that
determines what realities are capable of
echoing that pitch of fitting that
mold so identify
so identify
emotionally and physiologically
sensorially with the thing that excites
you in the following way now we already
discussed the idea that you have seven
physical senses and an a transcendental
one so when we say use all your senses
use all your senses not just the
five in the following way now here's
where you're imagination comes in your
imagination is the single most powerful
tool you
have it is
everything everything here's how to use it after
everything here's how to use it after
you have used your imagination to
determine what it is that excites you
more than anything else use your
imagination to concoct a scenario in
your mind's eye a picture visualize if
you will
see yourself in the scenario you want to be
yourself in the scenario you want to be
in as you say in full Living
Color use every sense you have as you
say to get into to become wrapped up in
to be absorbed by that image because if
that image is truly representative of
what you say is the most exciting thing
you can imagine doing you will will be
excited when you see it in your mind you
will lock into it you will plug into it
with all of your heart all of your soul
you will feel it you will taste it you
will hear as if you were that person you
will touch as if you were already that
person smell things in the way that you
would do
it here's a
clue don't continue to see here taste
feel touch smell sense in the way the
old you that you don't prefer to be
would do it in other words do not
continue the habit of the old you look
at the way the new you in that situation
is handling things look at the
difference in attitude because you know
that if you were that you doing that
exciting thing you would be acting
differently than you're acting now would
you not look at the picture watch that
you being ecstatic handling things with
assurance and conviction with finesse
and creativity with Grace and charm and
ecstasy sharing the joy savoring the
richness and the qualities of all the
things that you see that you doing that
you say are the most exciting things you
can think of to do plug into it feel as
that you would
feel that is a very critical
step get used to feeling that Junction
with it feel that
way if there is something going on in
your life some situation you don't know
how to handle as the you you are now the
you you've defined yourself to be so far
take that situation concoct the
imaginary you that you want to be and
hand the situation to that you sit back
in your meditation and watch what that
you does then
does then
tied into the third
step physical activity you are beings of
physical action
action
do physically do what you see that you
doing with the situation you have handed
it and you'll get the same result that's
what your imagination is for it's a
template follow it mimic it mirror it
match it when you have the of the you
you want to be act like that you and
you'll get the lifestyle you see that
you getting in that picture that's the
third step after identifying what
excites you after identifying with the
excitement emotionally
sensorially as you can and I mean
physically physicalize it make the props
borrow the props in that sense that you
feel are the closest representations of
the things you would be dealing with the
people you would be interacting with the
places in which you would be interacting
as closely as you can surround yourself
with the physical symbol pictures the
props or the real objects you would
actually be having in the actual place
or the closest approximation to it you
can concoct literally build a set if you
must and then immerse yourself
physically in it acting as if you are
already that person becoming familiar
with using the props feeling the space
around you that would be the space you
would live in you would work in if you
were being that exciting person doing
that exciting thing create your
environment to mimic as closely as you
can the environment you want to be in
because then you will train yourself
physiologically to react act to those
stimuli you will retrain your physical
body to react to the things you want to
be surrounded with and you don't
necessarily have to do it all day long
you can set aside some play time and you
can concoct a special area in which you
will go and immerse yourself and for
those 10 minutes purely you will be
nothing in that space But that person
you want to be acting in no other way
but the way the person you say you want
to be what act are you following along
yes step
one identify the thing that excites you
the most step two identify with it
emotionally sensorially create the image see it
sensorially create the image see it
taste it feel it step three physicalize
it act it out literally as if you were
an actor on a stage with props as best
as you can do those three steps and you
will be amazed at how quickly the real
reality will start flooding in you will
generally find that when you go at it
with this much
conviction almost no scenario you can
conceive of will take any longer than
between three days to three of your
weeks to manifest some symbol that it is
started to happen in your life it
doesn't need to take any longer than
that it can happen in less time
sometimes it may take more time but
generally speaking that is the average
time span required for almost anything
you could ever conceive of that has to
do with you if not to the full fruition
of what you want at least within that
time span to see a symbol a sign an
indication that things are starting to
move in that direction when you see that
don't stop keep going accelerate let
that excite you all the more give you
that much more conviction to act it out
even further go and be with the type of
people you think you need to be with to
do the thing that excites you the most
talk with them make them your colleagues
now do not wait until the thing starts
be whatever aspect of that thing you can
be now do the things you could be doing
now how to set yourself up because there
are many times many things that you
overlook because you simply are not
looking for the
obvious use all the Avenues that are
open to you with Integrity do the
obvious and the simple things you could
be doing to as you say put yourself out
there to advertise yourself as the
person you want to be to let other
people know that's who you are so you
can attract them to assist you remember
assisting other people and being
assisted by other people is a part of
the sharing that makes it a whole idea
you are still doing it yourself even
when you attract someone else to help
you you don't have to feel like if I
don't do it all by myself every single
step I won't have done it alone
attracting the people who have the
skills to help you that you have not
necessarily been able to acquire is
still doing it yourself because you
attracted them put it out there who you
are let people know who you are so you
can function as the unit you are as a
society stop being an isolated island
put it out there who are you advertise
it act like it be that person do the
things that person would do do not do
the things the person would not do
otherwise all you're doing is
reinforcing who you say you don't want
to be act this way with Integrity I
guarantee 100% you will get the result
no exceptions because it is always work
this way you have always gotten what you
have identified with what you have acted
as all we are doing once again is
reminding you you have a
choice in the things that manifests you
are not a victim you are in control the
only thing that makes life seem to
victimize you is the fact that you have
created and believe in the creation of
your hidden unconscious self you are one
being act like it and you will have a
life that is representative of that
Oneness I can't prove it to you you
however can prove it to yourself easily
effortlessly and deservedly so
the most important factor I can now add
is this for this is the thing that most
of you have the greatest degree of
difficulty with we have outlined already
steps one two and three in a sense there
is a fourth step it is the simplest of
all once again step
one identify what excites you step two
identify with what excites you step
three act it out step four are you ready
it is the most critical one of all are
you sure you're ready are you sure
you're sure yes all
right I'm not oh yes I
am it is that
easy I have in no way shape or form left
anything out it is is that
simple many of you may find from time to
time that what you call your analytical
mind your judgment cell your ego selves
may say oh no it's got to be harder than
that that can't be all the is to it
can't be that easy that's not complex
enough life doesn't work that way I've
always been told if I don't struggle for
something it isn't worth having it's got
to be harder than that can't I
complicate it just a little bit to make
it seem as if I'm doing something more
important well yes you can you can
complicate it all you want however it
doesn't change the fact that it actually
is that easy it's up to you if you allow
it to be that easy it will work that
easily if you want it to be more complex
it will take more
time because of the way many of you have
created yourselves to be sometimes you
will do over and over and over and over
and over and over and over and over the
thing you really don't want to do just
because you find it hard to believe
until you get good and sick and tired of
doing what you don't want to do that it
is actually truly permissible and all
right to do effortlessly what you really
want to do some of you just take a long
time because you don't believe there's
any other way until you reach the bottom
of the barrel and then finally then when
you're at the bottom do you finally
allow yourself to realize every other
choice is better than this everything is
equal everything is up cuz I can't get
any further
down sometimes you force yourself into
the those Corners just so you will be
absolutely sure there's not one more
thing you could do to complicate your
life just to check it all out just to be
sure I don't want to miss anything and
then finally you will
say okay it's that now some of you say I
okay it's that now some of you say I
surrender it is all right to say that
but understand by surrendering we do not
mean that you are giving up
control some of you have a
misunderstanding about that term in your
Society yes you do need to surrender but
when you surrender what you're actually
doing is falling into the control you
already effortlessly
have the only reason it doesn't seem
like you're in control anymore is
because you've always been taught to
measure control through the amount of
resistance you get when there's no more
resistance you think oh it's out of my
hands something else must be doing it
now I've given it up I'm not in control
anymore something else is running my
life well that's fine it's much easier
now but you are not giving up control
you are actually taking back
responsibility full responsibility
because you're finally realizing that
responsibility doesn't have to mean
blame responsibility means I have
freedom to to
choose anything I want and get it and I
always have and I always will that's
responsibility it is
simply having the conviction to make a
choice and to be responsible for the
choice you make if you find sometimes
that you make choices and you don't
prefer them all right if you find that
you have made choices out of Integrity
all right all right get back on track as
you say use it in a positive way because
now you can say well all right now I
know that's what I don't want to do and
so that gives me a much clearer idea of
what I do want to do sometimes many of
you do that as well you keep doing
things over and over and over again that
you really don't want to do and by doing
that you ultimately Define who you
really are by now knowing who you're really
are by now knowing who you're really
not and that's one way too and it's
valid it's just as valid as anything
else but it takes a long
time taking time is valid
too but it's up to
you allow yourselves to understand it is
as simple as you will allow it to be
because once again Miracles are the
natural order of things and after all
what this whole new age is all about on
your planet is learning how not so much
to be normal but to be natural
natural yes there is still a consensus
reality yes there are many similarities
in your world that you will continue to
share with other individuals and agree
must exist in order to play the
game but you have a lot of leeway in
that game a lot more than you
think learn how much leeway you have now
whatever you can conceive of whatever it
is that excites you the most it wouldn't
excite you if you were incapable of
doing it that would be pointless
wouldn't it it the universe does not do
pointless things it would not give you
something that excites you so much that
you desire Beyond everything else and
then say no I'm sorry I was just showing
it to you you can't really have
it for your Society to assume that the
Universe Works that way well that's a
fairy tale as far as I am concerned the
universe does not work that way what
inspires you inspires you because it it
is what you
are it is the sign the excitement itself
is the sign all of you ask for all the
time oh please God oh please universe
Give Me A Sign what is my mission what
is my purpose why am I here who am
I tap tap tap hey look at this exciting
thing over here don't bother me now I'm
looking for my purpose in
life please give me a sign please I beg
you tap tap tap what about this exciting
thing I said leave me alone can't you
see I'm about some very serious business
I'm trying to find out who I am the
excitement is telling you who you are
that's the sign what else could possibly
get your attention so strongly but
something that immerses you so
completely it is the sign go with it act
on it with Integrity you will be denied
nothing nothing nothing
nothing nothing
now here is another little
exercise that can help perhaps we call
it mirror
mirror and this is shall we say not
meaning to put this in a derogatory term
a little bit of a test for you once you
have decided what it is that excites you
look in a mirror look in your eyes
pretend that the image in the mirror is
actually someone else tell that you
about the thing that excites you have
that you ask you questions about it give
that you some answers and while you're
doing that little dialogue with yourself
in the miror look into your eyes and see
if you believe one word of what you're
saying when you can trust that the image
in the mirror absolutely believes every
word it is saying that's when you know
your definition is clear and when you
have the conviction that it takes
because if you doubt it
why should the universe give you
something you say you can't
handle well this is what it would excite
me but well I don't know I doubt I can
handle it I don't really believe I'm
capable or worthy of receiving this the
universe isn't going to give you what
you say you can't
handle so Mirror Mirror see if you look
convincing see if you really believe
what you say you
believe and another another little tool that you
and another another little tool that you
may find very valuable we are just as
you say talk full of
them it is called threshold of
believability it is if we have
preferences at all one of our favorites
because it works so very quickly very
quickly let us say now you have an idea
of what it is that excites you the most
but for some reason there's some
definition some belief within you that
says well I believe that I can be that
me but I believe it's going to take me
10 years all right fair enough here's
how you can reduce the amount of time
very simply threshold of
believability have the image plug into
it see it for all its worth and then ask
yourself a series of questions be honest
once again honesty within your own
dialogue is essential be honest with
yourself there's nothing to fear you
don't have to cheat everything will work
out just fine
ask yourself this all right here's the
image here's the thing this is what I
want to be this is what excites me the
most now beyond a shadow of a doubt and
I mean no hesitation
whatsoever do I believe that in 20 years
I will be able to be that thing by then
will 20 years be more than enough time
for me to be what I say I want to be 20
years no problem not a Shadow of Doubt
that's more than that's a long time no
problem I have more than enough time in
20 years to become what I say I want to
be 10 years no problem that's a lot of
time I'll be what I want to be well
before that oh yeah well how much before
that 5 years no problem 3 years well
well three I don't that's not enough
time 4 years no 5 years well yes yes 5
years is enough time why is 3 years
enough time I don't know find out what
beliefs would you have to have within
you that say it would have to take 5
years and not three go back into your
internal dialogue find out what your
definitions are discover what the
definitions are that make it take five
instead of 3 years change those
definitions into what you prefer them to
be just use your imagination rewrite it
see it in a book The Old definition if
you want stamp it out rip it up tear it
up throw it away get a new page write
the new definition in close the book any
way your imagination feels most excited
doing it whatever way you can as you say
get into it most with all your senses do
it you have to Chisel into the side of a
cliff do that in your imagination but
somehow erase the old definition that
you have discovered and replace it with
the new definition once you have
replaced the new definition take the
test over again 10 years yes that was no
problem before it's still no problem 5
years absolutely 5 years is more than
enough time to be what I want to be 3
years with the new definition I know
that 3 years is more than enough time to
be easily enough time to be what excites
me the most 2 years yes one year no
problem 6 months ah well maybe all right
do the process over and over and over
again every time the second the moment
you find that any level the slightest
hesitation that is the spot that amount
of time at that moment is exactly what
it will take to be what you say excite
you change it however you want to by
redefining it and allowing it to take
less time if you want to once you get it
down to something you feel is truly
comfortable then leave it there and
assume that is the answer that's how
long it will take
absolutely but bring up all the fears
bring up all the definitions bring up
all the doubts process it go through it
don't deny them denial is your single
most critical factor for preventing what
you want denial don't deny anything
don't even deny the
denial do not judge
yourself if you have
judged fine change your mind about doing
it and don't spend time judging yourself
for having judged it only adds more to
the negativity be clear of
negativity be clear of
intention be clear of your own purpose
know that what you are doing you are
doing out of Integrity out of love out
of service for everyone else because as
soon as you allow yourself to be the
fullest possible being you can be doing
what excites you the most which is after
all your purpose in life to be the
fullest being you can
be then you are a fulfilled person that
all other people can Avail themselves of
can be served by and then can serve you
in
turn only when you act in a complete
manner do you connect yourself to
everything and Avail yourself of
everything only when you support the
whole can you be supported by the
whole so use those tools the three steps
of imagination as we discussed the identification and
identification and
emotionality and acting
as the mirror mirror
technique and the threshold of
believability from all these different
angles if you use these tools you will
have a sharp Cutting Edge Clarity and
precision and
awareness and you will be the authors
and the artists consciously of your
reality you already are the authors of
your reality you might as well be
conscious of it and you might as well
have the reality you prefer because
you're going to create one anyway
because you are a Creator because you
were made that way so you might as well
have the one you prefer knowing
knowing that the one you really prefer
is the one that will be of best service
to everyone else because you fit then
it's no accident that you are where you
are when you are
there be a fully realized being in that
moment and you will be a connective link
for everyone
else you all follow
along very simple and very exciting
because it is so simple guaranteed 100%
there are no exceptions not you not you
not you no exemptions as you said the
universe works the same way for everyone
what you put out what you get back it is
completely
unbiased and it gives you what you say
you want
want
now I have one more suggestion as a
meditation on this particular subject of
excitement and
abundance remember that you already
contain everything abundance is not an
issue of getting what you don't have
it's an issue of understanding that you
already contain
it definition another one abundance dot
dot the
ability to do what you want to do when
you want to do it it comes in any number
of forms money is one way in your
Society doesn't exist in ours but it's
valid but it isn't the only way
sometimes someone will trade you
sometimes someone will simply give you
sometimes you will exchange in a various
number of ways for something if you
insist that it must be represented by
money you are closing all the other
doors through which abundance might come
more easily let it take the path of
least resistance by allowing all the
ways it could come to be
equal don't put such a heavy burden on
it having to be one way and you will
allow it to come you in whatever way is
the quickest way because if you can
still do what you want to do when want
to do it you have all the abundance you
need let it be that definition
definition
therefore here is a tool now some of you
may find that you want to use this some
of you may find that you don't it's a
suggestion it has had profound impact
for some individuals some individuals
find it scary but that's all right
examine why you find it scary and you'll
learn a lot about yourself in the
process and here it
is whatever you do not specifically
forbid will
happen see if that works for you some of
you may say all of it everything what if
I forget to forbid
[Music] something assume that you
something assume that you
will choose what you really prefer and
that anything else will simply not be
capable of manifesting in your
reality but everything else
will everything else
will the library
analogy you can go into one of your
libraries and on the shelves there are
many books there are joyful books the
books there are joyful books the
lightful books there are scary books you
can sit there in that Library all all
day all night you can read every book on
the Shelf you can be overjoyed at some
stories and you can scare yourself silly
with other
ones the only stories you will take home
with you is the on you decide to check
out on
purpose all the rest stay on the shelves
just because you have thought about it
doesn't mean it will manifest if you
don't give it the power by assuming it
has the power on its own it will not
develop in your life until you choose it
fearing something above and beyond
anything else is giving it the power
because you are saying by your fear that
you believe that this is the most likely
reality above and beyond all the
realities and that's what draws it in
remember we said the strongest
emotion fear is an
emotion so choose and understand that
your choices stick why because you say
so it's that
simple it's that and
now let us go a little bit beyond the
idea of physiological reality so that
you can incorporate the non-physical
reality as well so that you can blend an
understanding of physical and
non-physical reality into one experience
that we will call Dream time we do not
necessarily refer to the idea when you
are asleep we are talking about
understanding that you are dreaming
right now right now you are dreaming
right now yes right now you are literally
now yes right now you are literally
dreaming right now and all
dreams not always literally sometimes
symbolically but nonetheless all dreams
are real experiences on a real level of
reality sometimes you interpret them
symbolically because that's the best
your conscious mind can do with what it
has to work with in physical language so
your dreams are not always literal but
they are always real real
experiences and you are living a dream
right now the only major difference
between what you call solid physical
reality and ethereal Airy dreams is
because you define this dream as being
more solid than those
there is no difference other than
that that's why you can change physical
reality so quickly because it is only
what you dream it to
be that's the power you
have that's all it takes is the absolute
conviction and the assumption that
something is real and it is
so remember every system of belief
brings with it
its own
self-fulfilling structure to reinforce
its validity so that that system for
that moment seems to be the only valid
one otherwise if that were not so you
couldn't experience it as an isolated
system that's why you have all these
wars upon your planet saying this is the
real belief this is the real truth mine
works that's why I know it's real mine
works that's why I know it's real they
all work they're all real they're all
true when you believe in it it
reinforces its own validity and makes it
seem as if it's the only one around
because that's the nature of
focus but anytime you change your focus
the new reality becomes just as valid
just as solid just as immutable as the
last one they're all real that's the Act
of
Creation but let's look into a few more
realities right now let's dissolve the
barriers a little
bit astral
expansion you know how many breaths to
take three big
ones close your eyes if you
wish and take yourself back to your
place of perfect peace where in all
reality you have never actually left
remember you are always at the center
you just change the way it looks and
looks and
now the way this time your place of
perfect peace will look is as follows
our suggestion imagine yourself on a bright
suggestion imagine yourself on a bright
and beautiful day or night doesn't
matter sitting on a bench a comfortable
bench on the side of a stream on the
side of a street on the side of a path
doesn't matter but across the stream
across the street is a building a
structure of some
sort has many windows there are many
people inside doing interesting curious
fascinating things discovering many
things discovering many
things your curiosity is attracted to
find out what's going on in that
building yet at the same time you are so
comfortable on the bench you don't want
to move
how to solve this ah your imagination
says I have a way and instantly in front
of you
materializes a telescope or a binoculars
or a magnifying glass of some sort so
that when you hold it up to your eyes
low and behold it is as if you are in
that building in any room you want to be
in so close is the image in front of
your eyes that it is if you are truly
there a you say how wonderful how
marvelous how clever I can be on the
bench what I want to be and yet at the
same time I can extend my senses into
that building my vision into that
building through the use of this
magnification glass how
glass how
wonderful and just to be sure you're
still on the bench so real the imag is
in front of you you lower the glass and
yes there's the building over there here
you are on the bench just
checking raising the glass again you
notice anything at all you want to
notice you are looking through the glass
and everything that you want to draw
your attention to is as if it is inches
in front of your eyes any person any
wall you are like a spirit like a
spectre peering over their shoulders
looking at their books looking at their
machines walking through doors going
upstairs downstairs you even discover
that you can go through the walls
through the ceiling through the floor
you can look at anything you
want and your fascination and your curi
I it knows no bounds and you go up and
down and all over around following
people watching them listening to their
conversation you notice that your
hearing is with you as well and your
vision is independent anywhere you want
it to
be and all of a sudden something Dawns
upon you and you decide that you will do a
you and you decide that you will do a
little
experiment and you take your vision and
you turn it 180° around around and look
out the window of the building and yes
lo and behold there you are on the bench
across the stream across the street
holding up the magnifying glass but your
vision is now over here in the building
and you realize with a snap that you are
released from any prior conceptions that
your senses and your body must coexist
in the same Focus you have begun now to
realize that your Consciousness is as a
bubble that expands to any diameter and
as it expands wherever the skin of that
bubble is that's where your
Consciousness is that's the illusion of leaving your
is that's the illusion of leaving your
body it is expanding the bubble of your
Consciousness so that your body is
simply at the
center but anywhere on that skin you can
open an eye open an ear no matter what
the diameter you can be anywhere any
when and with that realization you snap back
and with that realization you snap back
to your body back to your focus and you
take down the
glass and you feel so invigorated so
different so
new and all of a sudden all the scenery
around you under goes a startling
transformation it is as if the building
the trees the day everything around you
except for the bench and except for
yourself begins to Shimmer and waver
like a mirage of heat turning
transparent becoming
illusionary everything becoming
ghostlike wavering
wavering
wavering illusionary and all of a sudden
you begin to see more and more objects
around they are also illusionary
wavering but there are extra trees extra
buildings extra people all walking
through each other they are in different
realities you are looking through the
veil of different probable realities
different Futures different pasts
they're all overlapping here and now
they do not see each other but you see
them all and they do not see you they
are living their own lives with their
own Focus not necessarily knowing they
can expand Beyond to see the other
reality but you have broken through the
veil you see them all going about their
business some of them even walk through
you you are a ghost a spectre to them
but you see them
all and all of a sudden your attention
is caught by something to one side and
something else over there and again over
there and what you do is you focus a
little bit here a little bit there and
all of a sudden you realize what you're
seeing is a person sitting on a bench
like you there and there and there
different people different
gender different types sitting on a
bench solid they seem solid not
ghostlike like all the other people and
you realize why they are solid because
they are all the other versions of you
in all those other lies that is
realizing right now at the same moment
you are in this one that you can see all
the other
reality you are watching yourself watch
yourself watching all that is you are
seeing the Reflections in all the facets
of the multi-dimensional crystal all the
reflections all the versions all the
variations of the vibrational lives you
are living simultaneously right
now and you nod and they acknowledge
with a return nod at the same time and
you realize at that
moment that all of your lives in all
dimensions and all realities right now
in the their own way whatever way makes
the best sense to them are all realizing
that you're all one
being you are all one being manifesting
in all the multi-dimensional
simultaneous ways you can you
are everywhere everyone in all possible
configurations everyone is you you are
everyone every everything is the same
one thing manifesting in all the ways it can
thing manifesting in all the ways it can
right
now with that
realization everything turns into one
blinding white
light and then
disappear and you are floating in space
and you see an infinite number of
sparkling stars and you know each and
every one of those is not so much a star
but a Consciousness a reflection of the
light you are for you are a star as well
an entire universe
glowing one of the many
Multiverse within all that
is take three deep breaths and lock it
in you are infinite you are Eternal you
are made in the image of
God you are it and it is you open your
eyes once again you are new beings at a
new moment the very first
moment every moment
Zero from the
beginning in in any way and every way
you prefer it to
be it is your choice use
it watch your dream realities From This
Moment forward you will find that your physical
forward you will find that your physical
reality and your dream reality will
begin to blend do not fear you are not
losing your identity you are gaining it
let the structure
go the structure exists within you
anyway let it
dissolve you decide the reality that you
are and it is
so it
is always has been and forever shall
be that easy
one
100% at this timing we extend to each
and every one of you the opportunity for
interaction in the format you would call
sharing or question and
answer the first person is Jenny Raven
who put this exciting evening together
for us thank for before you begin
do remember that everything any of you
have to say is a gift so speak up and be
bold and let all share so that all may
glean from what you have to say the
things that are applicable in their own
lives yes greetings and to you good
day when we awaken from this dreamlike
reality thought will we awaken too the
dream you wish to live you will awake
and live the dream you prefer to be it
is all a dream it is all real the idea
of calling it a dream the idea of
calling it a reality are arbitrary and
simplified definitions they are simply
labels it is existence itself you are
life itself live and be the life you
prefer to be it will be what you wish it
to be you understand yes does that help
you yes it does is that sufficient yes
it is well thank you very much sharing
I am very glad that you're here thank
you for sharing with us tonight we are
very happy you are there thank you for
sharing with us
tonight I'm interested in hearing a
little bit about uh how I integrate the
things that institutional religion which
is going to church enjoying that kind of
worship yes um and how those two things
fit together comfortably well they can
very simply do you believe that you
yourself regardless of what ritual you
surrounded with and I do not mean that
derogatorily do you believe that you
yourself are the primary relationship to
the creation then it Blends does it not
creation then it Blends does it not
anything that you do in your
institutionalized religion is simply
whatever tool you feel is necessary to
allow you to be in touch as the aspect
of creation that you are sometimes it
may change sometimes it won't all tools
are valid if you simply arrive at a
moment where you feel that the tool
you've been using no longer serves you
change it it's that easy you understand
yes very does that help you very much
thank you well thank you very much
sharing
hello Bashar and to you good day I would
like to hear a little bit about the
changes that are going on in science now
and how the what they call the shifts in
the Paradigm of science how quickly that
will be integrated into other aspects of
Our Lives or whether it will be oh yes
as we perceive your energy now it will
be within what you would call the next
30 to 50 of your years maximum
completely integrated and the biggest
shift that is now going on in what you
all your physical sciences is the
understanding the recognition that
physiological reality does not really
empirically exist apart from what you
define it to be in other words your
scientists are beginning slowly perhaps
at first but beginning to understand
that each and every one of you actually
do create your own reality you follow me
that will be integrated within what you
call the next 30 to 50 of your Year's
maximum as we perceive your energy now
is that an answer to your question yes
thank you thank you very much
Shing welcome to Colombia why am not in
Colombia but I thank you
anyway uh Bashar um I have a teenage
daughter that I'm very concerned about
oh concern I would like to be able to
I'd like to know what is the best way to
help her I have not been the type of
role model for her that I would like to
have been and any suggestions you have
would well first of all may I ask you a
personal question well thank you very
much do you understand that everyone
chooses to be with whom they are with
yes do you understand that you choose
your children that you choose your
parents yes then do you understand she
chose you yes then do you understand
that as long as you are being who you
truly believe you need to be with all
the Integrity you can muster the best
you can be it that you are being the
person that that individual chose to be
born to yes and do you understand that
the only thing you really need to teach
your children is the following thing
once again we shall repeat it every
individual is already as powerful as he
or she needs to be to create any reality
they desire without having to hurt
anyone else or themselves in order to
create it
we shall repeat it every
individual is already as powerful as he
or she needs to be to create any reality
they desire without having to hurt
anyone else or themselves in order to
create it if your child has that
understanding really the only other
thing you need to say to them is go to
it
kid everything else is your ball game if
you follow that simple understanding
that what you put out is what you get
back there are no other
limitations understand yes so if you can
share that information with
her then you will be fulfilling in a
sense your purpose as an adult as a
parent of that child give that child the
space to understand that they are
already powerful enough to achieve
anything without struggle regardless of
what the mainstream of your Society may
seem to say at this