There of course is different depending
upon the lifestyle they live depending
upon the person that they
are. What happened in my case is that
approximately 14 years ago on two
different occasions within the same
week. Four friends were with me the
first time. Two friends were with me the
second time. We had very close physical
broad daylight sightings of Bashar
spacecraft over Los Angeles. First time
about 150 ft distant. Second time about
70 60 70 ft distant. A roughly
triangular equilateral triangular shape
shift dark gray metallic in color.
Now, what I didn't understand then,
aside from having seen what everyone
called a UFO, and what I have come to
understand since then, is that that
physical sighting was Bashar's way of
tapping me in the subconscious memory to
get me to start learning the things I
needed to learn. Because after the
sighting, I began doing more research
and investigation into UFO phenomenology
and metaphysical
studies. And that eventually led to where someone
And that eventually led to where someone
introduced me to some channels who were
practicing at the time several years
later. One of the entities or
consciousnesses if you want that was
coming through one of those channels
offered to teach channeling for whoever
was interested because several people at
the time were. I took them up on the
offer not so much thinking that it was
something I was going to wind up doing.
I just wanted to learn more about it
because there really wasn't much
material on the subject at the time and
I figured if I went into the class I
would see something new in
action when I was in that class in a
receptive state under the guidance of
the other entity through the other
channel is when Bashar and his people
made the telepathic connection with me
and as soon as they made that connection
the memory of having made the agreement
prior to the physical life came back who
they were who I was to them why the ship
sighting had occurred many dream
conversations that I had had that I had
totally blocked from my conscious memory
all came flooding back at that one
moment and what came with it was their
first real-time telepathic message which
was basically now that you remember that
you made this kind of an agreement to be
of service in this way. Do you still
want to fulfill the agreement? Because
the one thing I'd like to point out is
that it was a choice and it always is a
choice. It's not something that's forced
on anyone. Obviously I agreed to fulfill
it and that was about four and a half
years ago and I've been doing it since
then for the last four and a half years
in this particular format of
channeling. Now channeling
itself fundamentally is simply any kind
of an opening up to a higher expression
of self, a higher source. Doesn't
necessarily have to be typically another
consciousness. It can be another aspect
of your own consciousness, but it's it's
any creative expression, any level of
that energy that you let through
unimpeded. Now and then when people open
themselves up in that way, they do seem
to contact other entities, other beings
that exist in other dimensional
planes. Most channelings that I'm aware
of fall into basically four categories.
Three of which are disembodied. In other
words, have no physical form as we
understand it. The first usually
involves another aspect of our own
consciousness. The second would involve
what is typically called a mediamistic
experience in the sense that somebody
has at one time been physically alive as
we know it and is no longer physically
alive and is somehow connecting and
coming through. The third would
represent levels or dimensions or
whatever you want to call it, realms of
consciousness in which the beings that
live there have never experienced
physical reality at all in any way that
we understand it. And the fourth is
basically what this one is
representative of. It's an
extraterrestrial connection. Now, there
are many levels to that as well, some
physical and
non-physical, but basically a lot of
them do have physicality. Not that
they're like our own, but they do seem
to express themselves in a similar way
to us as a physical world. Bashar is
such a case. He represents himself as a
member of an extraterrestrial
consciousness. And what's going on here
is a telepathic link. I am basically
simply functioning by being in the trans
state as a translation device, a longd
distanceance communication device for
them. My
My
subconscious takes the thoughts that
come through and translates them
automatically into the language that you
hear. He's not speaking English at all.
It's basically literally like a
long-distance telephone hookup. It's
translating his energy back into the
language that makes sense to us. That's
what the trans state allows an
individual to do. Now, one of the
reasons that they're doing it this way
instead of just coming down and landing
blatantly, they have many reasons which
they've explained, and you're certainly
willing, you know, welcome to ask him
any and all of what these ideas are all
about and anything about his
civilization you want to talk to him
about. But one of the main reasons that
they're doing it this way, remaining
behind the scenes right now, as far as
he's explained, is they've sort of
noticed in observing our society that
we've had a tendency in the past to sort
of lock on to the messenger and throw
the message away. So what they want to
make sure of is that in these
interactions, the most important thing
is the information itself, not who's
giving it. So the whole idea to these
interactions is that if you find that
the information works for you, if you
can apply it in your life in a
beneficial way, then please by all means
use it and get the benefit from it. If
you find that the information somehow
just simply doesn't make sense to you,
that it doesn't work for you, don't
worry about it. Don't use it. You'll get
something you need somewhere else. The
one thing that I would like to stress
especially for the new people is that
even though I have my own validational
experiences to help support my
understanding of who Bashari is and
allow me to believe that I think what's
going on is actually happening. There's
absolutely nothing in these interactions
that in any way, shape, or form insists
that you have to believe that he is who
we say he is because I can't prove it to
you now anyway. All I can do is key off
the things that keep seeming to work.
The information does seem to benefit
people. It's benefited me greatly. It's
changed my life a lot by applying it.
And as long as it seems to keep working,
I'll keep doing it. But it's not about
him trying to say that his ideas and his
beliefs are any more important than your
own. They're doing this to remind us
that we have the ability to live the
lives we want to live, that we have that
power within us already. They're just
acting as reflectors for us because they
would like to join our civilization and
vice versa. They would like us to grow
together, but they can't force their
point of view on us. So, he's
functioning as an ambassador in many
ways to give us an idea of what they're
like and to allow us to choose as a
civilization whether we really want to
interact with them or not. And perhaps
more importantly, whether we really want
to interact with ourselves or not,
whether we really want the kind of world
a lot of us have said we want in terms
of peace and harmony. They're here to
help us with that, but not to do it for
us. Now, we have a real nice intimate
group today in the sense that there
should be enough opportunity for many
people to interact and ask questions if
they want to by coming up here um and
talking at the uh microphone.
When Bashar comes through, when I go
into the altered state, he will usually
say something that he feels is
indicative of the collective group and
then he's going to turn it right over to
you. And he's going to do that by
saying, "How may I serve you?" or
sharing. When he does that, that's his
way of saying the ball's in your court,
and it's time to ask questions or talk
about anything you want to talk about.
That's completely up to you. No subject
is off the list. It can be personal. It
can be cosmic. Doesn't matter what it
is. But what I would like to underline
because of that is especially again for
new people, please don't be shy and hold
back because you think that your
question is either mundane or you're
wasting everyone's time or it's too
personal. I mean you can keep it to
yourself if you want. Bashar is not
going to pull it from you. But don't
hold back because you think it's a waste
of time. Everything serves everyone
that's here and the way Bashar will
usually answer the question will somehow
be applicable to most of the individuals
that are involved. even if it's not your
question. The second thing is that
because what's going on is a telepathic
communication, sometimes the information
will come through in a way that doesn't
necessarily immediately make sense,
either because you've never heard the
principle before or because the words
are coming through and being put
together in an unusual way. If that
happens at all and for some reason you
feel like the information is sliding
past you, stop it. Shout out loud, "Wait
a minute, Bashar. I don't get it. Could
you back up? Could you explain it
again?" Don't feel that that's an interruption.
Don't feel that that's an interruption.
He wants to know that you're getting out
of this interaction. Whatever it is you
want to get out of it. This is your
time. So use it to the best of your
ability by interacting with him openly,
directly, and freely. Talk to him
informally. Treat him as a friend. The
more you reflect to him on that level,
the more he will reflect that back to
you because that's basically all he's
doing. Now, just as a subtle point, the
word itself, Bashar, is not literally
his name in their society at this point
in their evolution. They're pretty much
telepathic and do not have names as
such, but he knows that we use them for
convenience. It's a word that he chose
when he first came through. I had no
idea what it meant. It's actually Arabic
because that's partly my background. And
it has several meanings, but the most
appropriate one in Armenian is that the
word Bashar means messenger. And it
basically is simply representative of
who he is, what he is, what he's doing
with us, what he's chosen to do, because
it is a two-way agreement. I've chosen
to do this, and he has chosen to do it.
So, this is what he wants to do, and he
wants to interact with
you. And so, it's up to you. The control
is in your hand in terms of what that
interaction is like and how it goes and
exactly how far you explore whatever it
is you're dealing with. Um, I wasn't in
the room. Vince, did you explain the
whole idea of the questions and answers
and coming up? Yeah, just basically
just, you know, like I said, we've got a
small group pretty much and you can ask
questions, just line up on the side
here, right where the podium is. And
just the idea that after you ask the
first question, if you want to get back
up and ask another question, you're
standing online. You see anyone behind
you who you know hasn't asked their
first question, let them get ahead of
you. Let all first questioners have
priority over anyone's second question.
If you can just try and be aware and try
and run it like that, it'll give
everyone the best opportunity to at
least ask one question. Go ahead. So
when he's finished talking and when he
says, you know, sharing or how may I
serve you? Then whoever has the first
question, you know, please be ready up
here and then whoever subsequently wants
to go behind him um be in line already
so that there's not a gap. And also
speak into the microphone. We are
attempting to record it. be as loud and
clear and distinct as you can so that we
do get everything on the recording and
so that everyone in the room can hear.
Um, the last thing before we start is
what I'd like to ask you is when I am
going into the altered state and when
I'm coming out of the altered state to
please not move around or make any noise
until I'm actually refocused and I'll
speak to you. I'll ask you, you know,
something like how did everything go to
see if you know everything is all right.
When I'm refocused, then you can do
anything you want to do. I'm just asking
you that because it's very disorienting
for me. Nothing about this is tiring.
It's actually very energizing. But it's
like coming out of a very deep dream. I
don't immediately remember not only
where I am, but who I am because I'm not
focused as a persona. So, it just takes
me a second to reorient. If you all
start talking all at once or getting up
and moving around when he says goodbye,
then it's a little bit jarring and it
makes the transition a little bit
rougher. Just give me a second and I'll
let you know when I'm back. When I'm
going into the altered state, sometimes
you will also notice that my body will
go through certain number of positional
shifts. This is only because of an
automatic adjustment to the energy. None
of what I'm experiencing is painful. And
I say that just because some people have
asked me if it is because it looks like
it is. It's not. I'm having a wonderful
time. So please don't worry about me.
Everything I experience is much more of
an energy and an emotional kind of an
interaction. I know there's an
interaction going on, but I don't hear
the words because I cannot think
analytically in the trans state or in
the altered state. So I retain the basic
premises of the information in an
intuitive form. I can't remember the
discussions that he had with you, but
that's not critical for me.
So bottom line to all of this is to
please have a good time because the more
fun you have and the lighter you are,
the lighter he will be with you and the
more fun he will have with you and he'll
respond in exactly the same way. Thank
you all once again very much for coming
today. Have a good time and I'll see you
all later. [Music]
[Music]
All right, I'll say how are you all this
day of your time as you create time to
exist. We thank you for co-creating this
We thank you for co-creating this
interaction this day of your time with
us and as a beginning we shall lay down
a foundation that we would like to
entitle points of view. The idea that we
will now reflect to each and every one
of you is the whole notion of points of
view. Each and every one of you of
course knows yourself to be an
individual. Each and every one of you
has your own point of view about the
idea of life about the idea of your
experiences within life
itself. But the idea has for a long
period of time in your society usually
been looked at in the following way.
that life, physical reality, is somehow
empirically separated from you and that
your point of view, your perceptions are
the perceptions of life. In other words,
perceptions of something that already
exists apart from you without you, in
addition to you, or that you exist in
addition to it. and that it really isn't
in any way, shape, or form connected to
you, nor you connected to it, except by
the idea that you find yourself existing
within the experience of physical life.
Now, however, your society is undergoing
a vast transformation of perspective.
Even your own physicists are beginning
to understand that what you have for so
long called physical reality is actually
nothing more than an extension of your
imagination. An extension of the
definitions you have been taught to
believe that physical reality is. And
that what seems so solid to your
physical senses is only solid because
you also contain a definition within
your belief system that it should be so.
Therefore, with this new understanding,
with this growing awareness in your
society, it can begin to be understood
by you that what you have for so long
called a point of view is not so much
just an observational tool, but is
actually the creative tool itself. In
other words, you begin with a point of
view. You begin with a belief system and
that is what determines the reality you
get. Now the physiological reality you
get may then through your senses allow
you to have experiences that will
reinforce the original belief. But
because that original belief is
sometimes unconscious, you may not be
aware of the fact that you had that
belief to begin with in order to have
created the experience you are having.
The belief must come first. The point of
view is always there first because first
and foremost you are primarily simply a
consciousness a selfaware aspect of
creation. Consciousness being self-aware
can view itself from many points of view
in many ways and an infinite number of
ways. In fact, any one and all of these
infinite number of ways are all equally
valid ways that the self can view itself
or experience itself. No one way is more
true than any other way. They are all
created from perspective. And the
strongest belief, the strongest
definitions of reality, the strongest
perspective you have utterly determines
the type of experiences that you create
in your reality. Those types of
experiences as we have said then work to
reinforce the original belief you had so
as to accelerate it so as to solidify it
crystallize it so that you can gain
momentum so that you can expand that
reality. Every point of view generates
its own self sustaining
self-perpetuating system of belief
system of feedback system of experience.
So that while you are in one point of
view, that seems to be the only point of
view that is real. That is why there is
so much conflict and argument and
dichotomy upon your planet. Because you
have not yet realized that all the
different points of view and all the
different realities that many different
individuals on your planet are
perceiving and insisting on as being the
one true reality are actually all
simultaneously real, all simultaneously
true. and that there is no one truth, no
one reality against which you can
measure other ideas for their relative
validity. There is a common reality, a
common existence to all, but that common
existence is simply that that you simply
all in fact exist. The only shall we say
rule or law governing the fact that you
all exist is as follows. And it covers
everything and infiltrates and
intertwines with everything. And that
law is this. What you put out is what
you get back. That's it. The idea,
therefore, is that every specific
experience that you have ever had is the
result of your existence, your
self-awareness in that existence, and of
radiating a certain frequency, radiating
a certain pitch. In other words, putting
out a certain idea and therefore
receiving as an absolute truly
representative reflection, an echo of
that radiation and that echo is what you
are perceiving as your experiential
physiological reality.
Now what this means is that while you
have for a long time perhaps been
creating those realities by holding
unconscious beliefs not being as you say
in touch with the idea of why you are
getting the type of reality you're
getting when you say you desire
something else and not understanding how
it is you keep getting what you don't
want. The idea simply stems back to the
fact that many of the beliefs that
perpetuated the original reality are
unconscious that you are not in touch
with them that you don't know what the
definition is within you that would
create such a reality. Therefore, the
whole idea in examining your point of
view in being clear about the
definitions you hold within you is that
once you get in touch with what the
definition is that has been creating the
reality you experience, you can change
it. You can rewrite it and make it a
conscious act, not an unconscious act.
And in making it a conscious act, you
yourselves can finally realize that you
are constantly and forever will be
capable of writing the formula for the
reality that you prefer and that you
will get it because the universe has
absolutely no choice but to give you
exactly what you put out. So it is a
matter of being in touch with what it is
you are putting out. What frequency
shall we say you are broadcasting on
because that is the program you get
reflected back.
Therefore whereas in your past it may
have seemed that point of view is simply
a matter of objective observation. It is
now beginning to be understood that
point of view is everything that it is
subjective. There can be an objectified
approach to things, but there really is
no such thing as a truly objective point
of view. Because anything by definition
that is a point of view is subjective
and everything you experience, if you
are experiencing it, must be by
definition also subjective. No matter
the style of your approach. So
everything you experience is a product
of your subjective understanding of
yourself, your beliefs about yourself,
your definitions of yourself, the ones
you have been taught since you were
children to buy into. Many of you now
have arrived at points where you realize
because you are now, shall we say,
thinking on your own that the old belief
structures no longer fit the you you
prefer to be. And so you go through many
ideas of re-examination and
re-evaluation of the old ideas that
perhaps your parents and peers sold to
you in that sense, not meaning to be
derogatory, that you had to buy into in
order to survive under their care. But
now the idea is that some of these ideas
are so ingrained that it may take in
your terms for many of you a long time
before you can change over to the
realities you prefer to the definitions
you prefer to the beliefs you prefer
simply because you have never been
taught that the realities and the
definitions you have to begin with are
already the product of your own making.
You have been taught that this is the
way it is and that these things are
difficult to change and that any kind of
change or any kind of idea that really
would give you joy in life is something
that you have to struggle and strive for
and is a great deal of difficulty to
achieve. These are also only
definitions. They are not rules of the
universe. They are not chiseled in the
fabric of space and time. There is only
one that is so and that is the one we
have already shared with you that what
you put out is what you get back. That
is the actual definition of the
structure of existence and that's all
there is to it. Everything else as you
say is your ball game even if it is an
agreed upon one even if it is a
consensus reality. For even though you
are an individual, you have obviously
made agreements unconsciously
telepathically with everyone else in
order to experience any degree of
similarity between all the individual
realities you are creating for
yourselves. So when two individuals get
together and say there is a chair yes
says the other individual, there is a
chair. You are agreeing to support that
common reality. One individual could
very easily say, what chair? I don't see
a chair. What is a chair? I don't know
what you're talking about. These
individuals, the ones that do not go
along with the majority consensus
reality, are the ones you usually call
insane. It doesn't mean that what they
are perceiving is actually any less real
than what you are perceiving. The things
they say they see are the things that
are there. And they are not just in your
terms hallucinations. To them, they are
solid realities. They are simply not the
massag agreed upon reality. And the main
reason why many of those individuals do
not understand how to integrate their
perceptions into the mass consensus
reality is because once again they have
been taught from a very young age to
believe that if they did not buy into
the consensus reality then they were
somehow cut off. They were somehow not
to be listened to and so the channels of
communication between them and your
society are shut down and they lock
themselves in a self-perpetuating cycle
of that particular world and have no
ability to communicate nor integrate nor
apply what they are perceiving into your
common reality as well. But what they
are perceiving is nonetheless just as
real, just as solid as anything you have
ever called real and solid in your
lives. Now, this notion of point of view and
Now, this notion of point of view and
the definitions you have within you that
create your reality serves as the
foundation for all of our interactions
with your society and your species. The
idea at this time is that your society
is going through many transformations
redefining itself not only as
individuals but as a collective whole.
These redefinitions in our perspective
are taking you in the directions similar
to directions we have explored in our
past. The idea is that you will not do
it the same as we did it. But we can
share with you some of the ideas, some
of the experiences that we have had. We
can share with you what has worked for
us so that if you want to, if you choose
to, you can perhaps adapt in your own
way with your own power and your own
imagination the same experiences in your
life. And you can understand that what
has worked for us can work for you if
you choose that. It is up to you. At no
time are you ever expected in any way,
shape or form to consider our point of
view to be more important than your
point of view. We see you as equals. We
see you as different and we are
different from you. Alien in many ways
even as you are alien to us. But the
idea nonetheless is that we are the same
type of spirit, the same type of
consciousness, and we are all a part of
the infinite creation. We all exist. And
what is true for everyone across the
board is that what you put out is what
you get back. So we give you
unconditional love and room to grow in
your own way. Room to choose for
yourselves and to decide for yourselves
whether you wish to interact with us or
not. And what type of realities you do
want to experience upon your planet is
completely up to you. We cannot
interfere. We can only accept an open
invitation of equality when your world
functions as an equal world in that
sense. However, these interactions do
create a more conducive ability for us
to interact with your world. And bit by
bit and day by day, we are arriving
close to a point where there may be far
more potential for us to, shall we say,
interact face to face in a physiological
manner. But only when you meet us
halfway by co-creating with us the
vibration that is necessary to create a
middle ground in which we can both exist
with our own individual definition so
that one will not overwhelm the
other. However, this is exciting for us
to interact with you in this way and to
us it is a gift to be allowed to
experience the way in which you have
chosen to express yourself. the way in
which you have chosen to represent your
aspect of the
infinite. We thank you for this gift and
in return for this gift I will ask you
now in what way at this timing may I be
of service to you. Hi Bashard. And to
you good day.
I see you're already having a good time.
I just love you coming here and visiting
us. It's It's probably the highlight of
my whole life when you when you come. I
would say that the highlight of your
life is you. Thank you,
Brucey. Okay. I have two questions. All
right. Number one, first is personal and
second is cosmic. All right. And and
this is a big barrier for me to get over
to even discuss anything personal in
public, if you say so. Well, all right.
You're talking about points of view.
Yes. And uh I think for years and years
now, probably around 10 years, I have
prayed for, begged, screamed, cried,
everything you could imagine, treated to
have my conscious mind be able to accept
the food that will shrink my body into
the kind of a form that I want it to be.
And uh it never seemed to manifest no
matter what I tried to do. Oh, right.
And 8 days ago, I had what I'm I'm
already looking at it as a miracle.
Well, although it although I know that I
created it. Yes. And that a miracle law
is actually the natural order of things,
not really the exception to the rule. I
know. All of a sudden, I I don't want to
eat meat. I don't want to eat anything
that is heavy in any way whatsoever.
I wanted you to give me some
understanding of what's actually
happened. I know that finally I've
walked into that. Well, thank you very
much. We do not wish to give the
impression that any particular substance
needs to be looked at as quote unquote
more detrimental than any other. But
simply when you do finally arrive at a
particular level of energy, a particular
frequency of energy, then whatever the
definition of that level is will create
within you urges for certain things and
will also at the same time create a lack
of an urge for things that no longer are
particular to that level of existence.
So when you do begin to act like a
certain person that is representative of
that level and if there is something
that is not representative of that
level, the new you that you have created
yourself to be will simply no longer
contain any such notion of an urge for
something that no longer defines who you
are. So you won't have to worry about
holding it off or having the stamina to
keep it at bay. Because when you really
define yourself in a completely new way
and when you really create yourself to
be a different person than you used to
be, you don't have the same urges, you
don't have the same thought patterns,
you don't have the same emotions because
you don't have the same definitions and
the same beliefs. So then it is easy and
obvious to allow yourself to align with
certain ideas because you don't have to
worry about fighting off something that
isn't a part of who you now are anyway.
You understand? I know the most amazing
part is no struggle. Yes. This is just
all wonderful. Yes, but that's the
natural order of things. No struggle.
You see, the only reason many of you
have struggle upon your planet is
because you are fighting your natural
selves, not because you are fighting to
become your natural selves. It is
because you are going against the flow
of your natural self, resisting that.
When you finally be your natural self in
the fullest capacity you can, there is
absolutely no effort because that is who
you were created to be.
Last night I worried a little that I was
going to backslide. Can you help? All
right. Thank you very much. An
interesting notion that you have in your
society that you can somehow slip from
positivity into negativity. It cannot
happen. It is an interesting definition
but it is in your terminologies a little
bit of a myth. Let me put it this way by
analogy. Suppose that you have two
mountains and in the center is what you
call a valley. All right. Yes. One
mountain is the mountain of positive
choice. The other mountain is the
mountain of negative choice. Both of
them are mountains because both of them
are choices. You understand? Yes. In the
center is simply balance. The blending
between the two. You must choose to go
in one direction or the other. If you
are on the positive mountain, should you
believe that it is possible to slip, you
cannot slip down off the positive
mountain through the valley and up onto
the other mountain. You cannot slip from
positivity to negativity. You must
always arrive back at the center point
first and there you will stay until you
make a choice to go in either direction
again. So, if you're going to slip at
all, the only place you can actually
slip to is the center. So, why worry
about it? Thank you.
My cosmic question is about the peace
clock. Nice. Um, you told us to uh think
about world peace for one minute at
noon. You mentioned something about the
sun. I was speaking to a friend of mine
and she asked if I could ask you the
question about the idea of the sun as
divine substance and ancient
civilizations that used to worship the
sun. She particularly was talking about
an ancient mantra called Gaotari.
Well, the idea of course is that
everything in creation is made out of
divine substance so to speak. But the
idea is that obviously symbolically in
any solar system the idea of the sun the
star that generates the life in that
system is the supportive factor is the
emanating factor for the highest
frequency of the system and is the body
responsible for determining the
frequency of all the energy in the
system since it permeates the entire
system. Therefore, being aligned with it
when it is at its focal point in direct
alignment with you will allow you to tap
into the strongest alignment of the
energy of the frequency of your entire
system to have that much more momentum
behind your meditation. You want to
understand? Yes. Is this why the ancient
civilizations worship the sun? Does
understand that it shall we say devolved
into what you call worship? The original
understanding was simply as we have
already stated. They simply understood
the relative meaning of the vibration of
the central star. It wasn't a matter of
actually worshiping it in the idolizing
sense. It was simply a matter of
recognizing that in your system it
represents the shall we say outlet for
the majority of the energy of the divine
substance out of which your entire
system and all the beings in it are
constructed. You understand? Yes. Thank
you very much Bishan. Well, thank you
very much. Does this serve you? Yes, it
does. Thank you. Thank you for your
sharing. Sharing. Hello, sweetheart.
Good day to you, Strawberry.
I know that uh fundamentally you're just
reflecting our frustration and
irritation whenever it appears sometimes
that you're irritated with us. as I am
always laughing on this side. No matter
what type of a face I present to you, it
is simply that we have determined that
because of the different ways you
communicate in your society, sometimes
even though we are always having a
wonderful time and are always excited
and are always laughing in a sense,
sometimes we need to present a
particular type of stern face so that
you on your side will actually take what
we are saying with some degree of
sincerity or seriousness. Otherwise, if
we simply presented it in the way we
always presented among ourselves, you
probably would not take it seriously
because we would always be laughing
about it because in a sense, in an
overall sense, we do not really take
anything seriously. Actually, the
laughing works a hell of a lot better
than the uh yes, you know, than the
stern face. Oh, yes. But not for some
individuals. Some individuals in your
society would not understand that they
need the quote unquote authority figure.
But you don't in actual fact yourself
get everyone a little frustrated with
our uh misduplication. Thank you. Not at
all. I always delight in every facet
that you have to share with us. Okay.
But sure, I've been having a lot of wins
and a lot of emotion and a lot of
feeling and a lot of sensation examining
here in Las Vegas the concept of winning
and losing. Well,
Frank and um I noticed yesterday and as
we know time to be that uh you seem to
have a strong preference and seemingly a
definite um I hate to word use the word
adversion but apparent aversion to the
idea of games of chance or not so much
that idea not an aversion. No, we were
simply underlining the idea that every
single individual in our society wins
all the time. Mhm. We do not structure
anything in our society to create the
game of somebody winning while it is
apparent that somebody is quote unquote
losing. We simply allow the idea to
exist equally across and it does not
translate in our society into the format
it does in yours. So we do not have the
expression games of chance. There are
things, there are endeavors, there are
activities that may seem to be similar
to certain activities on your planet
that you may call games of chance, but
there is no quote unquote winner and no
quote unquote loser because you are not
postulating or causing the thought that
you're losing in any way no matter what
happens. Correct. Basic concept.
Correct. from a an energy standpoint. Um
I have had some understandings in the
past that certain emotions are created
by differences in energy potential where
you will assign a negative or a positive
uh meaning to a neutral situation and
the potential difference between them
generates the uh matrix that we call an
emotion. So emotions are reactions to
beliefs. Yes. So
um how about um is it necessary to
create these potential differences in
order to experience emotion? Is there
another anatomy to it or is the idea if
I may backtrack for a moment? Go may
seem to be that in a civilization that
arrives at a place where it views
everything as
equal may to some civilizations to
actually seem to be emotionless.
The idea has been expressed in the light
of what you would call cold mentality.
But you see the idea actually is is that
the type of emotional expression, the
variances of emotional expression in
your society are the result of the high
degree of polarity that exists in your
society. We experience the idea of
emotion. It is simply that through the
understanding that all is equal, the
strongest emotion you usually will
perceive in our society is simply one of
even compassion and unconditional love
which may at times make us seem to be
very detached to the quote unquote
plight of other beings. We are not
detached. It is simply that many times
individuals on your planet do not
understand that the detachment is
actually a firm belief that that
individual has the ability to create
their reality in whatever way, shape or
form they want to. It is an absolute
support, total compassion and
unconditional love for that individual
that makes us seem many times removed
from their particular circumstance. In
other words, more often than not, as we
have observed your society, most of you
equate the idea of love with sympathy
and we do not give sympathy because to
us it undermines your ability to believe
in yourself. It supports the negative.
So many times when you do not perceive
when describing certain ideas or issues
that you do to us all of you and you do
not receive the idea of a sympathetic
response many times it may in your eyes
make us seem to be detached emotionless
unable in that sense to identify with
you. But we see above all the things
that you are doing that cause you to
vary and fluctuate from positive down
through negative emotions and up and
down all across the spectrum. The idea
simply is it that when you allow
yourself to know that you can believe in
everyone and know that their potential
is the same to create whatever they
want. Then you see them with the same
light that you yourself see infinite
creation that you know you are a part of
infinite creation not meaning this
throughout. You see everyone in the same
way that you see a child that is
learning something for the first time.
You understand? I understand. with love
in your eyes and love in your heart,
knowing that they will discover what
they need to discover out of the
circumstance they are in, no matter how
distressing it may seem at the moment.
Now, this does not mean we cannot assist
in the alleviation of some of that
distress. But nonetheless, we never give
sympathy. Empathy, yes. Sympathy, no.
You're looking at a a permeation type of
viewpoint where you're permeating
permeating a business rather than a
linear transition between defined
dichotoies. Yes. So let us say for now
to put it on a basic level that we do
have to some degree fluctuations in
emotion and in expression but they are
mostly the idea of contentment, joy,
happiness, ecstasy and that kind of a range. Well
ecstasy and that kind of a range. Well
the kind
of yeah in this planet you know and I'm
also going to get very personal and I
get very personal and very uh broad with
regard to what's going on here in Vegas.
And I think I may stay around a while.
You know, as my father expresses,
everyone is looking for that that big
win, the concept of abundance in terms
of the fundamental um um agreement on
abundance, which is money in this
culture and everyone's looking for that
big shot. Yes, of course, they can
achieve it in other ways, but they're
all going for that. And there is a, you
know, an emotional thrust toward that.
And within it is the concept of winning
and losing and and making it and not
making it and oh my god, And the playing
of that game in and of itself is
actually more exciting to many
individuals than either the winning or
the losing. Yeah. Oh yeah. Well, you get
a tremendous amount of emotions. You
know, the pile goes up and down. It's
real interesting. Um uh remember that
some individuals play to not win so they
can keep playing.
Yes, I do. I do understand that. I do
understand that. But often, you know,
basically, at least from my point of
view, a game
um I'm looking at it as uh this winning
leads to other winning. The winning of
this game leads to another game. That
particular linear type of sequence, you
know, that um the reward of one game is
the ability to play a bigger game or a
more embracive game. Yes. That sort of
thing. Yes. So that the
but an individual always wins when they
allow themselves to understand the
outcome no matter what it is.
Understood. Understood. Yeah. Very much.
Yes. That intensity of defining this is
a loss which which produces absolutely
the dichconomy of emotion. Okay. one I'd
like one reflective I I've already
gotten a lot out of this and basically I
wanted to share a lot of this with
people and broaden the view but I had a
fascinating experience that I' I've
understood a lot about when I first came
here I had a I put bunch of gambling
money in my in an envelope and I stuck
it in my back pocket and um and within
about five or 10 minutes that money was
gone you know a degree of $400 and I had
a chance to observe oh wow how dumb you
could put it in your pocket. You know,
the old definitions of assigning
dumbness. All right. But what did you
learn? Oh, you know, I learned many
things. One, uh, I could play the game
without that money. That was that was I
could still play the game, you know.
Yes. All right. That's one. I learned
that, uh, it didn't have to be a loss.
It didn't have to be considered that.
Other people could have a ball. Oh, look
at this. You know, I found this money.
All right. We are not in any way, shape
or form supporting the lack of integrity
of another individual. But what else?
Oh, no, no, not so much that because
there was a lot of learning. You know, I
had to look at uh if I picked up the
money, what would
I give a chance to examine myself there?
And what else? There is still something
else we are specifically waiting to hear
from you. Oh, you are. Yes, you are.
Well, you got perhaps in a sense the
most obvious idea. Well, you're learning
to focus, I guess. Thank you. How am I
doing? Yeah, you're definitely better than the
Yeah, you're definitely better than the
average alien.
I I know you don't have differences, but
if you ever want to come to down to
third density and experience somebody
better or worse than you, you know,
we have differences. Absolutely, we have
differences. It's just that all our
differences are equal. Okay, let's
Anyway, I'm avoiding or have let's get
this obvious thing that I'm missing here
with regard to this that's so obvious to
you. All right. Your intentionally your
intention in that sense to use the money
to play the game as you say. Yes. Yes.
All right. Now the idea what is the
strongest i.e. the strongest belief
within you. The idea that in all
likelihood that money in your
terminology in your terminology would
probably have changed out of your hand
into someone else's anyway. Well is
there's been a shift that used to be.
And then I also found myself considering
myself a winner more and more and more.
All right. And that flow was occurring
also. I think I was examining more of
the uh you know the inner belief systems
when
Wait, let me finish before you
interrupt. You know,
we have this communication cycle going,
right? You listen and then then I talk.
You know, you're very verbal, you know.
I like to be verbal, too.
Nice reflection.
Okay. All right. Anyway, I'm done. Your
turn. No.
First of all, of course, just the
beginning of the idea. You say you are
already changing the idea of not
necessarily having to go through the
motion of playing the game to still have
the money go away to do it more
efficiently so to speak. Ah yeah I
thought of
that but you don't have to go through
the process in order to get the meaning
out. Yeah but the conscious intention
was not to have it go away fast. second.
I realize that may not have been your
conscious intention, but nonetheless
intention it was for that is what it No,
this is real interesting because you
know I'll go and have something like
that or I'll have a loose come up. I'll
play it on the table and the lose will
go and I get this belief system. Well,
yeah, of course. You know, well, yeah,
of course. you know, and I'll go and
I'll see this belief system and this
feeling that has emotional impact in
some depth and then I'll go whoa change
this thing but it's fleeting it's like
it's something that materialized out of
some loss very good very good and I go
where the hell that come or how do I
shift it you know and by that time of
course the deal is done too little which
brings us back brings us back to the
original idea our interaction yeah That
level of attached detachment
ah not understanding go when the outcome
doesn't matter is when it usually
happens in the positive direction. Yeah
that's why there is in your terminology
such a thing as beginners luck. Of
course because they don't have the
expectation. The idea is to create that
beginner every single moment. Yeah.
Don't you have a kidding cycle going?
Like you really want to win, but you go,
"Oh, hey, I'll get this detached
belief." You can play that game.
Yeah, I've done I've done both. You
know, it's like you're trying to use the
detached viewpoint as a method of
winning, you know? Right.
There are many ways to play tricks on
yourself. Well, you don't want to really
play tricks. I want to play the game
from an exciting winning viewpoint. and
experience the wonderfulness of of the
intensity of losing. Yes. But that
brings us back to the whole issue once
again of why do you need to experience
it in that way and is that particular
game actually representative of what
really excites you the most? Because
again if it's only a means if it's only
a tool to get somewhere else then your
focus is on the tool and not the actual
goal. Because it's all coming back to a
belief that I have to have a certain
amount of income and abundance in order
to pull off what I want. We've been over
this a thousand times. Yes. And also
admire your your ability to not get
frustrated. Oh, never never have a
wonderful time.
Also, if I may, I'm not saying this is
necessarily very much a strong part of
this equation we are working out, but
also perhaps just as a suggestion, you
might begin, if you have not already, to
ask yourself if you had kept that money
and if you had
won, are you really able to handle that?
Just ask. Yes. You don't have to answer
now. No, I I can answer. I don't I don't
have any problems about answering. I was
investigating it and my conscious answer
is yes. All right. Oh, you better
believe it. You know, I can handle that
flow. I create more generosity, more
friend. I buy more meals for my friends.
I'm creating joy with that kind of
income. I love to be generous. I love to
flow. All right. And I would say yes.
But you have an implication or an
apparent implication that maybe you
couldn't have a winning, you know, and
my invitation is to take that and go,
"Oh, yeah, maybe Bashar said that." You
know, Bashar's here and you better take
a look at this and all that sort of
thing, but I don't really feel it's
there. It's not that you're consciously
above your enjoyment and all this stuff.
You're so cool. Just tossing it out.
Oh, that was nice. See whether it comes
up heads or tails. You
love you like to play. You know we have
we have a lot of fun with you. You have
you come in at our coffee shop meetings
you know in which we discuss the the
great transitions between the third and
fourth in you ought to join. Well across
the channels there are join in now and
then we can in your terminology pick up
on leakage at a later time.
Okay. Anyway, where were you going with
that idea? Did Did we finish with that?
No, I just knocked the mic
off. Anyway, you've been disconnected
for sure.
Did we finish with that idea? I am. Are
you? No. All right. Well, I'm going to
plug you back in. Let someone else
handle it, John. Okay. Um, just talk
louder. Yeah. Um,
our strongest inflection, our strongest
perception. Yeah. the one that formed
the foundation for our interaction with
you was the point that Lee already
shared about learning that you do not
necessarily need the intervening process
to arrive at the same point.
Okay, that's good and I will work on
that and I thank you very much for your
your time and loving care and all that
kind of good stuff. Give my regards to
all your family and people. It is. Thank
you. Thank you.
Hello. and do you good there? I had a uh
mind experiment to discuss with you.
Mind experiment? All right. That arises
from taking different points of view of
the same event. D right. Um as a
scientist I had the thought of um how
much energy would be required to make
the entire universe
rotate about myself nice and that's
subject to analysis by calculating all
the energies of rotation of all the
bodies and there are formulas available
to do that. Well yes you can do it that
way everywhere. Yes. And you can
calculate all of them out and you get a
very large number possibly an infinite
number to calculate all the energies of
all the stars and
then you take another view and that is
you sit on a piano stool and you rotate
yourself with very little energy and you
have accomplished the same thing to your
own perception that is rotating the
entire universe around yourself. Yes.
And you get the interesting paradox that
in the first experiment it takes
infinite energy and in the second
experiment it takes very nearly zero
energy. Yes and no. But continue and you
come to the startling conclusion that if
these two energies describe the same
thing then that thing must be an
illusion. All right. Very good. However,
from our point of view we do not mean in
this that we are bandering back and
forth the idea of semantics.
But both take zero and infinite energy.
The idea simply is is that the first one
requires an amount of consciously
realized effort and the second one
doesn't. So you're introducing the notion of
So you're introducing the notion of
consciousness in the energy equation.
Yes. Always consciousness must be a part
of every equation since everything is
made of it. The notion simply is is that
in the first case by performing the
equation seemingly
externally it requires a great deal of
effort in that sense. It seems to
require a great deal of energy. By
performing the same equation internally
it appears as if no energy is required.
It's the same amount of energy. But the
idea simply isn't that by performing the
equation internally you get the same
effect with absolutely zero effort.
an interesting paradox and I am aware of
your your conversations on paradox where
you say that the third density reality
is really the reason why these paradox
exist yes why they seem to be apparent
as paradox yes yes thank you one moment
is your system working sufficiently yes
it's fine sh greetings
sh greetings
to you a Good day.
I would like to share with you uh two
books which have recently been published
and the reason for doing this is to let
you know that some of the same available
to the society at large. Chan, speaking
of the mic, please. All right. I might
quote just briefly from the first one is
called the Mayan factor and is written
by Jose. Okay.
Jose. Okay.
And what he says simply is first that
human history is shaped in large part by
a galactic beam through which the Earth
and Sun have been passing for the past
5,000 years and that a great moment of
transformation awaits us as we arrive at
the beams in in 2012. Second, that the
activities and world views and cultures
follow the nature of the galactic
seasons, the code of which has been
captured both mathematically and
symbolically by the Maya. And last third
that each person has the power to
connect directly sensuously
uh sensuously electromagnetically with
the energy information of this being
that emanates from the galactic core and
can in this way awaken to tune one's
true mind higher mind deepest mind
I just wanted to share that information
with you and anyone else who's
interested uh it's a terrific book and
I'm really uh really enjoying reading
Well, thank you very much. That date in
your terminology of time approximately
your 2011 to
2013 is the representative date, the
timing frame that we have discussed many
times wherein we perceive that by that
timing your society will be in
accordance with alignment with the
unification of the association of
worlds. Very good. Thank you very much. You're
Very good. Thank you very much. You're
welcome. The second book I'm proud of
because I had a hand in it. The book
written by just one.
Well, actually there was two books, but
this is the this is the one I think
just one hand.
Yes, one hand.
Uh, you remember 7747?
Absolutely. All right. This book is
called UFO Crash and Aztec and it tells
the complete story of that investigation
and what was found complete with
illustrations, photographs, uh some of
the original text from magazines and
some information released under the
Freedom of Information Act. Yes. And if
anyone is interested in that story and
that phenomena because I feel an
injustice was done to those entities
being brought down in the manner they
were the dissections and the things that
followed. All right. So, I'm glad the
truth is finally coming out about this
is a part of the leakage of information
now that has been suppressed for some
time. All right. There's one part of it in the
All right. There's one part of it in the
back that I found a little disturbing.
All right. There were some writings by
Paul Benowitz who says that
in in the state of New Mexico, the
government has given over certain lands
to alien beings who were responsible for
cattle mutilations and the abduction of
women and things of that sort. And that
was a little bit upsetting because I
don't fully understand all the
ramifications. We understand what you
are saying. For now, we will say there
is some exaggeration to that idea, but
we are not allowed to comment at our
time. And I do not mean to seem
mysterious about that. It is simply not
allowed. All we can suggest is that the
idea serves your population in a
beneficial way and is not exactly as it
has been described.
I understand. Some other other
information has uh come up to a to a
writer by the name of uh George who said
that it was channeled to him by entities
from ProI that they were engaged in a
ongoing conflict with beings from Riel
and Sirius was also involved and this
had been going on for some time. This is
not a conflict as you understand such
terminology but simply the idea of the
creative pressure of intersecting
dimensional reality. It is something
that does not translate very well in
your physiological terminology. So
there's no no war conflict. Not as you
understand it. No. All right. Well, that
uh that helps it out. Thank you very
much. Thank you very much. Shammy.
Hello, Bashar. And to you, good day.
Thank you. And thank you for sharing.
And you as well. I'd like to discuss
time. All right. Go right ahead. I'll
pay wrapped attention. Oh, no. I'd like
you to discuss it. Oh, I find time very
frustrating. Oh, I I find Well, I find
that I can operate on a extremely
accelerated pace. Yes. in all other areas except
pace. Yes. in all other areas except
this one. All other areas except time
and all other dimensions except the
physical area where time is concerned.
Ah, all right. Time is your creation.
What is in your terms the difficulty?
The difficulty is that I can visualize
myself somewhere instantaneously. Yes, I
can visualize
uh a job being completed
instantaneously. Yes. Yet I find it
frustrating that we have to go
through the time
element to complete a job or to get from
A to B.
And um I find that it takes me it seems
to take me longer more and more to
accomplish a task. Yes. Then um than I
estimate or uh Yes, of course. This is
no surprise. You know why? Why? Because
you're focusing all the time.
The less you focus on it, the less time
it will take because the less you will
create because you have singled out that
notion as something that impedes you.
Your focus on it creates it to be more
weighty. Anytime you invalidate any segment of
Anytime you invalidate any segment of
creation, you call that segment into
full realization in your experiential
reality because you are giving it more
attention than it needs. All right.
You've said many times in the past, yes,
that uh when you're having fun, Yes.
time stands still and when it isn't
created, it isn't created. Yes. Well,
I'm very fortunate because I'm in a
position to have fun with my profession
and I do then why are you experiencing
so much time? Because I don't experience
the time but even though I may feel like
an hour has gone by in actuality three
or four have actually taken place we
have deadlines and I beg your society we
have I beg your pardon
who has dead lines.
Well, we we call them deadlines. I
understand what you are saying, but that
is not why I'm questioning you this way.
Why are you accepting that notion into
your reality? The acceptance of the
notion that you have very little time
may make all the time you have seem that
much more pressured and increase your
focus on the amount you have, which may
make it seem longer.
Why are you focused on the whole issue
of deadlines? Do you not believe in your
perfect timing?
Why not focus on the timing instead of
the time? Why not trust the timing that
you innately are that everything will
fit exactly when and where it needs to
instead of focusing on attracting
circumstances and situations that
require you to focus or buy into the
focus called a deadline.
When you speak of the idea that it
exists in your society, that is all well
and good. We recognize that many notions
exist in your society. Do you buy into
all of them just because they exist in
your society? Very few. Well, then why
buy into one you no longer prefer? Well,
because I'm in a profession that
requires certain This is another excuse.
It's an excuse. How do I How do I get
others to agree with
me? That if a project isn't completed when
That if a project isn't completed when
it's supposed to be, who says it won't
be? You see all the assumptions you are
You see all the assumptions you are
making?
You are making assumptions that if you
don't do it in such and such a manner
and if everyone else doesn't agree that
it should be done in such and such a
manner that it won't get done. Who said
you said why say that way? Why not
assume that it will by being fully who
you are? And it isn't a matter of
getting everyone to agree with you. It
is being who you are and finding the
niche, finding the circumstances and
allowing yourself to attract the
relationships that work with you in the
same way, that already understand the
same type of approach. You don't have to
stay with individuals that don't
understand it. You will attract yourself
into a circumstance that will allow you
to express yourself in the way that you
are most comfortable. for if you quote
unquote remain in the same circumstance
and if all the other individuals are
willing to go with that flow then they
will seem to change. They haven't
changed you have and in a sense they are
actually not the same individuals you
were dealing with before even though
they may look the same. Is any of this
making sense to you? Some of it. All
right. All right. You said at one point
that when we are excited about what
we're doing Yes. really involved in in
the excitement. Yes. That when we step
out of that particular circumstance into
an hour or into the the physical Yes.
time element that society has accepted.
Yes. That we've only aged whatever you
have experientially felt. All right.
What happens when we step into a second
and in one second experience
uh a million seconds or a million years
in that one split second. You are
becoming highly accelerated in the sense
that you recognize you exist everywhere
at once and your way of interpreting the
fact that you exist everywhere at once
is to see all of that overlapping within
a very small amount of time. Once again,
the idea we are talking about is the
amount of physiological time you have
experienced, not the amount of
conceptual time. You understand? Mhm. So
you can have a notion of infinity that
can pass in a second, but that in your
terminology is conceptual time. The idea
is simply what you physically feel you
have experienced by your quote unquote
biological clock. That is what allows you to not
clock. That is what allows you to not
experience the physiological aging.
I see. Understand? Yes, I do. Because in
a sense when you experience the idea of
millions of years in a second, well, in
one sense, you are millions of years
old. You understand? But you don't have
to physiologically represent that.
Make sense? Yes, of course it does. Um,
how can we blend these
two so that we are experiencing
everything at once and yet or you don't
always want to, you know, you don't
always want to have that conscious
recognition because then you would not
necessarily be able to get the job done
in your physiological
reality. The idea is to gain from that
experience when you allow it to happen
in that way. that type of gestalt
recognition to gain from that what you
need to be able to apply it in your
physiological realm to then create the
acceleration of physiological
biochemical time as
well. That's by doing in the moment once
again and not stepping out of that.
So by living in the moment from moment
to moment, not worrying about quote
unquote deadlines, Yes. we can still go
from A to Z. Oh, absolutely. For
possibly at an accillerated Yes. pace.
Yes. Also understand time will become
very malleable and there may even be
things that allow themselves to happen,
shall we say, for now backwards.
There are individuals in your society
now that are experiencing the following
phenomena by living in the moment and
finding out that time is truly their
creation and doesn't necessarily have a
particular direction when you defocus
from the physiological timeline. And the
idea is as follows expressed in this one
particular way. It happens in many ways
but this is one example. An individual
in your terminology will awaken perhaps
from sleep and recognize that they have
10 minutes to get somewhere that it
always takes them 20 minutes to get to
physically and that there is absolutely
no way they could possibly get there in
anything less than 20 minutes. Yet they
get up, they focus in the moment, they
go, they arrive, and they get there in
10 minutes. They don't know how. They
don't care how they made it. The point
of the matter is is they allowed time to
retrogress the amount of time necessary
to get them there at the appropriate
timing. You understand? Of course. And
you just picked up my thoughts because I
visually was um was um envisioning
uh getting from one point AC from one
end of town to the other end of town in
10 minutes when it should have taken 20.
And I've done this many many times. But
how can I control that? By living in the
moment and not caring when you
experience it. You will always get it
when you need it if you live in the
moment. Do you guarantee that?
Absolutely. Because you see the idea is
that it makes it seem difficult to get
that again when you start focusing on
needing that as a tool. It's only a
tool. Focus on the idea you are doing
and the tool if you need it will be
there to serve you automatically and
you'll experience it again when you need
to. By saying, "Oh, now I just want to
experience the idea of the tool." If you
don't have a need to, you don't have
that experience. Do you understand the
need creates the tool and by focusing on
what you are by being in the moment in
that way and simply being focused on the
idea of where you are going all the
tools that you require to get you there
automatically come into play. When you
focus on the tool you become
shortsighted and you cut yourself off
from where it is you are going and make
it take more time because you're
focusing on the tool that it takes to
get you there. The more focus you place
on the details of the trip, the more
time you need in which to examine all
those details. Simply focus on the idea
of the goal of the trip and you will get
there instantaneously because all the
tools will fall into place automatically
by themselves. You understand? Focus on
the end result. Yes. Is that what you're
saying? Yes. Okay. Thank you, Bashar.
Well, thank you very much. Also also one
other notion we have discussed sometimes
about how you can use time as it relates
to the idea of disease and health. If
you have within you the notion that you
have a
disease that you think must by what your
society says take such and such amount
of time to
heal. All right. If you find that you
believe in that so strongly that you
cannot circumvent it in the normal way
then you can also I'm not saying this
will necessarily work for everyone
because it will depend on who you are
and what you need but you can also
understand that if you really believe
that it will take let's say 3 months to
heal what you have then you can play
with time in the following matter you
can say I began to heal three months ago
therefore I have spent the intervening 3
months healing and Now poof, as you say,
the disease is gone instantly because
you have spent 3 months healing because
your belief system would not allow you
to believe that it would take any less
time. So you can work it retroactively
if that is the obstacle that you find
exists within you. Understand? I
understand. I'd like to do that with
drafting. In what sense? I draft a great deal of
In what sense? I draft a great deal of
the time. And so do you enjoy this? Not
not particularly. All right. Why not
hire someone else to do it? Often times
it's not feasible. Who says?
When you are really being who you want
to be, then you will attract all the
individuals and circumstances that can
help you and assist you in that way and
you will have whatever you need to
interact with them. If you do not
attract it, then there is something
about the experience that you may be
denying you actually need to learn from.
Okay? So, open up to that possibility. See
So, open up to that possibility. See
what happens. But remember, as soon as
you start to discount anything you are
having, regardless of whether you're
going to change it or not, as soon as
you begin to discount and invalidate
what you are experiencing, you create
the so-called block. Understand? Because
you are not living in the moment, right?
Does this help? Yes, it does. Thank you,
Basher. Well, thank you very much,
Sherry. Hi, Bish. And do you good there?
I'm wondering um
sometimes I'm wondering if you can help
me with this.
Sometimes I really feel that I know that
something's going to turn out a certain
way. Yes. And it does. Yes. Yes. And
other times I feel that same feeling of
certainty. Yes. That I know something's
going to turn out a certain way and it
doesn't. Yes. I'm wondering why is it
accurate sometimes and not other it is
always accurate but you are simply
forgetting that no matter what you may
know at a certain time there may be many
factors you are simply not paying
attention to that change what you used
to know. Remember that there is no such
thing as a prediction of the future. All
sensings in that sense can be very
accurate. But if factors come in to
change those things, then in the very
next moment it no longer applies. You
understand? You may have sensed what was
there at one time, but 2 minutes from
then it may no longer be the reality
that you are focused in. Sometimes even
because of your very awareness of it to
begin with. That in and of itself may
change the factors and render your
original sensing obsolete. The idea
therefore is to simply get in touch if
you need to which you may not with what
factors would have come into play to
change the outcome perhaps if I'm just
saying if this might be the case it may
not. If you find that the factors you
are certain of that come to pass are
factors that it is all right for you to
allow to come to pass, then that may
determine why they can. If you find that
other factors you are certain of that
don't come to pass are not all right
with you for them to allow to be come to
pass then that may be why it is not
because your choice and your preference
may play a large part in what you allow
to manifest even though you are certain
that it is there and certain it has
exactly the same potential as anything
else to manifest when you first sense
it. Do you understand? Yes. So like if I
if I know if I feel really certain that
something's going to turn out a certain
way and it's something that I want. It's
I consider it a positive thing. Yeah.
And it doesn't come out that way then
what I haven't looked at is what
happened in the intervening time.
Perhaps you may have changed or clouded
your definitions or you may have placed
certain expectations that have limited
the idea and restricted it. There can be
many different factors. The idea is to
be very clear about the reasons, the
original reasons for why you say you
want what you say you want.
Okay, understand? Mhm. Does this help
you? Yes. Thank you very much. Also, it
is not necessarily a matter for strong
concentration. Once again, what may be
of broader assistance to you is that
sense of attached detachment. Yes. Yes.
To allow yourself to see in that limbo
state all the factors that are involved
in every single event that unravels
itself in your life. Yes. Thank you.
Thank you very much. Shooting or one
moment. There will be some dream
assistance for you if you wish. Thank
you. Continue
and good day to you. First of all, I'd
like to thank you for some advice you
gave me in October when I told you that
I didn't want to go to the health club
anymore. And I talked to you about just
uh imaging my body the way I wanted it
to be. I've been doing that and it's
been working fantastic. I have lifted my
arms and exercised.
Now, now I have a question about aging.
Yes. Um we have to some degree already
discussed this, but continue. Right. Um,
I'm 42 and I want to look and feel like
I'm 33 for the rest of my life. But I
don't I keep I find when people say,
"How old are you?" I'm saying that I'm
33. All right. I don't want to
invalidate what I'm doing by not saying
my actual physical age here is 42. I
understand. So, can you help me with how
to do that? Well, once again, living in
the moment, the issue can become in your
terms irrelevant for you. And the idea
it can become a matter of integrity to
truly say you are in fact 33 for 33 can
be representative of your state of mind
if you wish. So I can say that without
invalidating myself as long as you know
you are saying it with absolute
integrity of what you mean by the idea.
You may wish to explain the notion to
other individuals but I don't have to.
As long as I understand what I'm saying
basically correct. Okay. Okay. I am in
your terminology
approximately 160. However, in your terminology, I
160. However, in your terminology, I
would appear to you to be approximately
40. Oh, okay. Maybe I'll just say it
that way then.
Not the 160. I
don't think the other way.
But perhaps you have also hit upon an
interesting approach
because if you simply wish that
comparative idea, if you did now, you
can let them know that on one level you
are kidding around with them. But in a
sense, you can also understand you are
not. For if you do in fact say just on
the spur of the moment to someone when
they ask your age that you are in fact
160, they will say, "Well, you look
marvelous for your age."
And that can be the response that might
help trigger the other comparison you
are talking about even though you might
let them in on the quote unquote joke.
Right. Okay. That's great. Okay. My
second question is about insurance. Uh
I'm having one
problem how to deal with this. I've just
canceled some disability insurance and
career protection insurance and I'm
trying to not I'm trying I am thinking
very positive that I won't get in an
accident so that I don't need major
medical insurance but I'm a little
apprehensive in cancelling my major
medical insurance because I'm just
apprehensive about the fact that maybe
there might be someone out there and if
there's an accident just waiting for you
with your
Is that what you are saying? No, I don't
want to think that, but you know, we
have to have car insurance and we have
to have homeowners insurance. We are not
in any way, shape, or form telling you
to violate what you have agreed to be
your law. But the idea simply is is that
if you do have apprehension about it,
then that in and of itself may be the
strongest indication of whether you
really believe you need it or not. The
apprehension may say that you do. So, I
would advise you to keep it until there
really is no apprehension. In the same
way we discussed before that when you
really change the individual you are,
you have no urge for a certain thing
that you had before. When you change the
individual you are that really contains
a belief that that is not necessary, it
will not be an issue of apprehension.
You will simply not have it. Okay. So as
soon as I don't have one little bit of
apprehension, then I can cancel all my
insurance. It will automatically cancel
itself. Well, well, they miss cancellation
Well, well, they miss cancellation
notices. No
wonder they never pay it. They're trying
to tell me I don't need it. I didn't
even That's great. Oh, good. Okay. Okay.
That's great. Oh, good. Okay. Okay.
Thank you. And one last thing. Uh, could
you take us on a field trip today?
Yes, in a bit. Great. Now the notion is
simply that in a while we will conduct a
that in a while we will conduct a
meditative state in which you will
combine your mentalities and project
your mentalities to what would be termed
one of our mother craft or city ships.
The idea, even though it may seem to be
taking place in what you would call your
mental imagination, will nonetheless on
various levels be an actual
experience. It will be an actual journey
in that sense and an exploration of one
of our craft. Even though many factors
of your ego structure consciousness will
still insist that you have never left
the room you are in, both will overlap.
Both will be true because it will be an
interdimensional merging or an
intersection. We will undertake this in
a little bit of your time. For now,
sharing. Thank you. Thank you.
Hello, Bashar. Um, I have a couple of
personal questions.
Good day to you. Uh 26 years ago, I took
uh my son to the babysitter and three
days later when his father went to pick
him up, the babysitter, the baby bag and
baggage disappeared completely and they
had been missing for that length of
time. At the time, the law did not
consider this kidnapping. It was merely
child stealing.
And uh I won't go into the efforts that
we've gone through to locate the child.
Uh but I'm wondering if he is well, if
he is healthy and these two people that
needed him so badly uh to are taking
good care of him and although he is an
adult now.
One moment. We may not be capable of being
moment. We may not be capable of being
as precise about this as you may wish,
but we will
scan. Name of child
Joseph, pardon me, William Joseph Euan.
EN.
There would seem to be some indication
that this individual is involved in some
method of utilization of radio
frequencies or
broadcasting. We perceive that the
individual is involved in this
endeavor as what you might call an
occupation. We perceive that this individual may at
We perceive that this individual may at
some time be
able in one way, shape or form on some
level to use this occupation to retrace
the information that will allow for what
you may term a
reunion is all we can perceive at this
time. Thank you. I appreciate that.
he in his country. Uh the lady that took
him was from Germany. The only
understanding we have at this time is an
impression of the area on your planet
you would call Italy.
Italy. And it does not necessarily mean the
And it does not necessarily mean the
being is physiologically there, but that
is the impression of the energy that
seems to have the strongest
representational feel of events that
have affected the individual's life.
It may be that the individual is there
but we cannot scan and pinpoint any more
precisely than that.
I appreciate appreciate your efforts and
no effort at all. Hope that something
will there will be a reunion. No need
for hope for that implies doubt but I
understand what you mean. Thank you. Uh
the other thing is my relationship with
my parents. Yes.
And this is all you know kind of tangled
into a
guilt thing for myself because few years
after that my parents just quit
communicating with me to all right and I
sent them letters and phone calls and
there is no need for self invalidation
because of these circumstances no matter
what their belief system all of these
ideas are the acting out of certain
agreements that were made. It does not
necessarily mean that they must continue
in this format, but the addition of
invalidation through the form of guilt
will not necessarily assist matters in a
positive direction. You understand? Yes,
I I can understand it. But
how I don't know how to drop the the
guilt feelings that it's I must be the
terrible person. First of all, I lost my
son and now I've lost my parents. not
lost anybody. They're they're not with
me. Did you do these things
intentionally
in terms of your conscious intention?
No. Oh, no. Not consciously. Then why
allow yourself to berate yourself with
guilt? If you know that was not your
desire, no matter what the result of
your unconscious agreements, if you know
that was not your conscious desire, if
you know that you are doing the best
that you can to maintain the integrity
you believe you possess as an
individual, what reason do you have to
treat yourself with such disrespect?
I none I suppose. Thank you. End of
conversation. Thank you,
Bashar. I appreciate it. Thank you very
much. Well, you are worth it. Remember
that you were created by the infinite
creator. And if you still exist, then
you must still be worthy of existence in
the eyes of the infinite. You do not
need to treat yourself with any less
respect. Thank you. I thank you.
Sh. Hello. And good day to
you. How are you today? Perfect. And
you? Great. Oh, all right. I'd like to
ask you a question about an event that
has occurred recently in our
[Music] time that I've been trying to
time that I've been trying to
understand. I feel like I do understand
it on a deep unconscious level, but I
want to bring it into conscious thinking
and and balance this these polarities
that are involved. There was an event
that was occurred over the Christmas holidays
was occurred over the Christmas holidays
in Russellville, Arkansas, where a
individual uh engineered I say a mass murder of 16
uh engineered I say a mass murder of 16
individuals. All right. Um in seeking to
move to a higher level and understanding
this event, could you give us some
guidelines to sort of in a sense? Yes.
In no way, shape or form do we ever by
what we are about to explain condone the
idea of the actions of an individual
that chooses the course of lack of
integrity. However, at the same time, one must
However, at the same time, one must
understand that both the so-called
perpetrator and the so-called victim do
on some level arrange for that event to
occur. I understand that.
Therefore, in no way, shape or form must
these things play out this way. They do
not have to play out that way. But the
reason that they are so prevalent in
your society is because so many
individuals are taught to believe from
birth that they are not in control of
their lives.
These individuals are filled with a
great deal of isolation and fear and
loneliness because they do instinctively
on some level feel that they ought to be
in control. But they are locked into a
rigidized structural belief system of
their outer conscious mind that keeps
insisting they are not in control.
Thank you. This conflict, this internal
dichotomy can create a breaking point
where the individual may finally arrive
at a place where they feel they are
truly dying, truly sinking, truly fading
out of
existence and it makes them even more
lonely, more desperate for control.
They will attempt when they feel
themselves sinking down into what they
believe to be a bottomless abyss. They
will attempt to reach out and not
wanting to be alone and not knowing any
other way, not having ever been taught
any other way to communicate their
plight will simply seek to dominate and
doineer the exterior reality and force
as many individuals as they can to sink
with them to take them down with them so
they will not be alone.
This idea in a sense therefore is the
basic foundational reason for the
forcing of one's point of view upon
someone else including the act of
murder. You are now finding as a
society that in at least the majority of
the cases of what you call especially
mass murder in almost every case the
individual will have believed themselves
to be absolutely out of control of their
life, unable to create what they desire
and so act or shall we say
react by projecting out onto other
people a resentment for what those
individuals have because they do not
believe they are capable of having it.
It is jealousy and envy instead of
inspiration. For jealousy and envy are
the result of seeing something in someone
result of seeing something in someone
else and not understanding that you
contain it as well and can create the
same thing.
Inspiration is when you see something in
someone else and know that because you
can see it in them, you must contain it
as well and you can ignite it and bring
it to
life. But because of the following
doctrine, you have the idea of both
perpetrators, murderers, and victims
upon your planet. And the following
doctrine is this, that you are not in
control of your life.
If your
society would begin to teach from a very
young age the following
idea, none of this would occur again.
And the following idea is as follows.
Every single individual is as powerful
already as he or she needs to be to
create any reality they desire without
having to hurt anyone else or themselves
in order to create it.
When everyone acknowledges that internal
control and knows that it is an
effortless ease of creation to manifest
what they desire, they will not need to
feel out of control at a loss and cut
off to the point where they seek then to
dominate and force all other individuals
around them to bend to their will just
to gain some sense of the control they
feel they lack.
Is this clarifying the issue to some
degree? Yes, I think so. I realize it's
a very complex issue in a sense. Yes.
And also that same philosophy that you
are not in control of your life is
responsible not only for the creation of
the perpetrator but for the victim as
well because that is a victim mentality.
And individuals that play into that loss
of control on certain levels of
powerlessness may attract into their
lives circumstances and situations that
reinforce their belief in their own
victimhood. Again, this does not excuse
the perpetrator for it is up to that
individual to be strong enough to
understand that their control is within
them as well and not heed the call of
the victim. In a sense, however, because
the rule that generates them both is the
same, then in many circumstances, you
can see that the perpetrator in many
ways is actually the victim's victim.
And the victim is just as much of a
perpetrator as the alleged
perpetrator because they call each other
through their lack of control, their
lack of belief in themselves.
Understand? So it seems like they're playing out
So it seems like they're playing out
drama. Yes. In some sense that is a
reflection of what we're feeling inside
of us. Yes. So that we can fully
understand. And they are playing out the
idea of the strongest belief system in
your society. That's true. That's true.
Okay. Thank you. Thank you very much.
Do you wish a short break?
Seven. Yes. So far this
$29. In your terminology, what is the hour of
In your terminology, what is the hour of
counting?
7 minutes to three. Three. We will in
your terminology simply allow
you your modes of refreshment for
approximately five to 10 of your
minutes. whereupon we will
reconnect and continue and also proceed
towards what you have called the field
trip. You may take a short break and we
will resume momentarily. [Applause] Earl continue.
Hi Bashar. And do you good day? It's
great to have you here today. Oh, we are
very happy you are there. Thank you.
There seems to be a shift in my life
around families. Family. All right. Yes.
I lived with my own family for a while
and now I have a totally different
family environment I live in. All right.
And I'd like you to explain what is
there to explain the relationship I've
had with my father and now with my new
lover and a little bit around that. Well, what
and a little bit around that. Well, what
do you get out of having had those
relationships? That's the basic
explanation for any relationship. what
you learn about yourself by being in the
relationship. So, what have you learned
about yourself? A lot. Then,
do you wish to share any of it? Yes. Um,
it was good I got detached from my
actual father cuz it allowed me to stand
on my own two feet for a while. All
right. You are still connected, but the
idea of your own autonomy is also
something that is important for you to
learn. Yes, it was very important. And
it looks like now I'm learning a lot
about love and all right. Well, these
things are only
obvious. You have with many of the
individuals, all of you that you are
very strongly emotionally intertwined
with now in this life, been in other
lives with before and have played many
parts and many roles for each other to
allow yourselves to learn the things you
need to learn in any particular life.
The same goes for this life. Now
whatever it is in any relationship you
are in that you are learning the
strongest about yourself that is the
reason at least at that moment for the
relationship. Live in it in the present.
Let it be what it is rather than what
perhaps you have been taught to think it
must be and you will then allow it to be
natural and follow its course and unfold
in a natural way. That is the basic
fundamental answer to any such question
of that nature.
That's great. Does that assist you
sufficiently? Yes. I had a question
about channeling. I've been channeling
for a while. All right. And I was
wondering in what manner?
I am somewhat conscious there and the
channel comes through and uses my mind
and one moment. Nolan cler you are the
channel. Okay. Sorry. the entity comes
through and I can sense it and I can I'm
still there sometimes I think for one
moment one moment do not mean to
continue to interrupt no one says you
should be out of the way okay the idea
is to be clear but now an understanding
exists upon your planet that part of the
reason for those kinds of connections is
for you also to be involved not in your
terminology to filter not in your
terminology technology to inhibit the
information. But the idea is to be
involved in a clear way so that you
benefit as well so that eventually you
can become your version of whatever it
is you are connecting to. You
understand? Yes, I do. And is it like
possible for me to connect with other
entities or is it just this one entity?
It is possible. However, remember this.
In every aspect, including the one you
are perceiving now, it is going to
involve aspects of your own
consciousness first. And that is the
main thing you will always be focused
upon is the idea of the blending with
more and more of your own consciousness
regardless of anyone else you connect
into. Understand? Not quite. All right.
In other words, everything goes back to
the basic of understanding just as you
were talking about autonomy before that
you are in control of your life that you
are responsible for your life fully.
Therefore, anything you connect into,
even though you may make connections to
other levels of consciousness, is always
going to be experienced as coming
through one of the levels of your own
consciousness because there is only the
material that exists, the energy that
exists in your reality that is there for
you to create any experience out of. In
other words, you are not receiving or
perceiving my consciousness directly per
se physiologically. You are perceiving a
model of my consciousness made out of
the channel's energy. Do you understand?
Yes. Therefore, anything that you
channel is going to be made of your
consciousness. So, a portion of you in
some way, shape or form, shall we say,
is always going to be responsible and
always going to be involved and always
going to be the portion that interfaces
with the rest of your dimensional
reality. Regardless of anyone else or
anything else you are tapping into, you
can connect into anything and
everything. We would simply always
suggest that you do not necessarily
place too many differentiating labels
upon it. Simply allow yourself to
understand that regardless of who it is
or what it is as long as you know you
are aligned in a positive point of view
and are willing to be of service that it
is all basically representative of one
source no matter what. Understand? Okay.
The information is most important, not
so much the idea of exactly who it's
coming from. As long as you understand
that it is serving in a positive way.
You understand? Yes. Does that assist
you? Yes. Relax the definitions and you
will expand paradoxically and make many
more connections that will allow you to
need less differentiation within those
connections. There may be one or two
that still seem to, shall we say, hang
around and may even be able to identify
themselves as discrete persona, but the
idea nonetheless is that even though
they are connected to you and assisting
you, the idea of their service to you is
to always turn you back to your own
ability to access information in exactly
the same way you imagine they do. Even
as this channel is learning to
understand that he can become his own
version of what he believes me to be.
You understand? Yes. Does this sister?
Yes. Thank you. Well, thank you very
much.
Shimmy Bashar gang. Good day to you.
Good day to you. I was wondering if you
could give me some information on
growing crystals. Growing crystals? Yes.
Such as
such as Well, I've I've got In other
words, in what way do you wish to use
them? Well, for industrial purposes
first and spiritual purposes also.
One moment. One of the easiest ways to
moment. One of the easiest ways to
manifest the idea of the type of crystal
and structure you desire is to begin to
explore an experiment with different
electromagnetic frequencies. When you
create specific electromagnetic bubbles
that contain certain patterns of energy
and grow the crystal in that energy
bubble, then the crystal will take the
pattern, its cue from the pattern, the
template of that energy. To some degree,
this is how some of our spacecraft are
constructed. They are of a metallic
crystallin substance and in a sense they
are grown in an energy field and that is
why many of them are homogeneous and
seamless in that way. We design the
energy template that determines the
specific idea for which the crystal will
be used and then the crystal growing in
that energy field will inherently
incorporate all of the attributes that
the field defines it should have. In
other words, the circuitry is laid
within the crystal in magnetic lines.
You understand? Yes. That can be one
way. Any other way your imagination
wishes to make use of it is up to you.
But do remember that these crystals are
simply triggers and catalysts for the
spontaneous generation of your own
energy. You understand? Yes. They are
representative of energy. They do flow
energy through them in that sense. They
are in a sense very refined crystallized
energy forms. But nonetheless, they
basically function as catalysts or
triggers for the release of your own
inspiration. you're following. Oh, okay.
So, well, I've gone to the university
and I've done research and I've done
kits and things like this and grown my
own crystals and it only goes so far.
No. All right. Many of the natural
crystals that exist upon your planet can
be in your terminology fashion in very
precise modalities and placed together
in very precise arrangement to create a
number of effects upon your planet. And
many of you now will begin to understand
that many of the quote unquote future
devices, future technology that your
planet will exhibit will use less and
less and less dissimilar materials and
more and more and more. The idea of
single crystallin substances
electromagnetically imprinted. Your
tools are becoming as simplified as your
consciousness now is. It is absolutely
no accident that your society is now
discovering the idea of
superconductivity for that involves
crystallin alignment of materials even
as your consciousness becomes more
crystallinally aligned. You follow me?
Yes. So explore and experiment with that
whole notion and you will find that
electromagnetism itself will be the
force that is in your terms tapped by
these crystallin devices without as many
moving parts without as many ideas of
dissimilar substances. And they will
seem in a sense to be magic devices,
miracle objects that will be able to
deliver the capacities of energies that
other devices in the past needed. many
moving parts and many dissimilar
materials to create. You understand?
Yes. Use them in that sense as lenses to
focus the electromagnetic field. We do
not necessarily mean grinding them
optically, but the idea of arrangements
and relationships of crystallin forms
very precisely cut in a certain ratio to
each other will if you explore and
experiment with it give rise to
measurable fields of electromagnetism
that you can then apply in different
ways. You understand? Yes, those
sisters. Yes, just one other thing. And
synchronicity. I am seeming at a seeming
impass on which way to turn as I've dug
up all of the data that is here that I
know of. Will synchronicity supply me
the next step? Always if you find first
of all that you have many options that
appear to be equal, then recognize that
it doesn't really matter which way you
move. And sometimes simply making a
choice will make it obvious as to
whether that was the choice and the
direction you wanted to move in or not.
You understand? Yes. Keep moving is the
key. Continue to take action to take
steps and act at any given moment upon
the thing that excites you the most with
integrity that you are capable of acting
upon. Understand? Yes. Does that assist?
Yes. Very much. Thank you for your own
crystallization and acceleration. Thank
you. You have been a scientist before
many times by the way. Thank you.
Good day. And to you good day. I wish to
thank you for the information on William
Joseph.
I hope in the future uh take it back.
Erase it. Erase. Start a new
point z moment one. Yes.
Go. in the future. Our time. Yes.
Um, do not worry how you speak.
Well, I understand what you are saying.
I do not mean to give you the impression
that I am watching your every word. Feel
free.
Okay. I look forward to that
day when all the necessary agreements
are carried out. which pertain
which pertain
to child in question at the time and in
the now and so they shall be. Yes. But
now and so they shall be. Yes. But
living in the moment is also enjoyable
and that is what will allow that day to
arrive the quickest. Enjoying what is
going on now by understanding that
whatever it is that is happening now
serves a purpose and belongs there.
So looking forward to it is all well and
good but remain focused in the now.
That's how you get there.
Understood. Yes. Does this serve you? Um
greatly. Greatly one short questions and
we can have more time on the solar wind.
Oh. All right. Um are you in your scout
craft or your board? Scout craft.
Thank you very much.
at this time. Oh, no.
[Music] Well spoken. Well spoken.
[Music]
All right, proceed.
Thank you so
much. You you've told us over and over
to do what excites us most. I have
suggested it. Okay. Can you also say
that if it's in our imagination, it can
also become a reality in physical
reality depends upon its applicability
to your dimension, but basically yes.
Can you manifest yourself here on our
physical reality? I have many times. Not
that I have in your terms set foot upon
your ground, but my spacecraft with me
in it has been in your skies
physiologically many times. Okay,
Bashar. For many many years, I have been
to mountain tops and rural areas looking
for UFOs. Why? I would love to have an
encounter. I think why? Why not?
But nonetheless, why? Because it would
be extremely fulfilling to actually have
a physical encounter. You mean more
fulfilling than the life you have? It's
very fulfilling in this life. And it's
fun, but it would be fun to interact
with with other beings on other planets.
Remember that first of all, you are
interacting with us all the time in your
dream realities and this is no less
real. Well, it it seems a little less
real. Then that is the difficulty. Well,
why can't we manifest it in our physical
reality? Because you don't understand
yet the nature of what we call our
physical reality. Our physical reality
is more akin to what you call your dream
dimension. Blend your physical reality with your
Blend your physical reality with your
dream dimension and we will be there
instantaneously because that is the
existence level that we are in. When we
quote unquote manifest in your reality,
we are coming as close as our vibration
will allow us to. When individuals in
your reality are simply sensitive enough
to our frequency, are alike enough to
our frequency, they perceive our craft
which are in your skies all the time. So
is that is that like a lower vibration?
A higher vibration. A higher frequency.
Higher frequency. And how does one
attain that? By living your life to the
fullest in the present. Well, I feel
like I am. Well, all right. Then
understand this. There is also a perfect
timing for everything. And if it hasn't
in your terminology happened yet, it
doesn't serve the timing of the
agreement between us all to the best of
its ability. Relax. I'm relaxed.
If you say,
a little anxious, maybe. All right. And
a little excited because like I say, I I
really know that at some point in my
life, I must have an encounter because
it's it's like a yearning. It's like a
deep desire that I would I would like
that encounter. I understand what you
are saying but what you are sensing what
you are sensing will be the natural
result of you simply continuing to live
your life as you have agreed to. In
other words, you will not miss it
because you have already set it up. So
don't wait for it because you are quote
unquote missing the life you agreed to
live and that actually will slow the
process down.
Understand? Yeah. While I'm out there, I
experience the stars, the universe, the
peace. Many adjustments are made while
you are in that state. Many
identifications and communications do
occur between you and other levels of
consciousness. When they need to
manifest to serve you, it will. Nothing
will stop it. When the state is correct
for that manifestation, however, I am
not necessarily saying this is
absolutely the case with you. But we
have discussed this issue with many
individuals many times and they say, "Oh
yes, oh yes, I'm ready for such an
encounter." And then they find
themselves in an isolated region and
begin to actually believe that such an
encounter might be occurring. They run
more often than not because they still
contain the anxiety they do not think
they contain. Because remember, the fear
that comes up when such encounters occur
has nothing to do with fearing us. It
has to do with fearing yourself. Because
when we interface with you, our higher
frequency, not meaning to be derogatory
to any of you, forces in a sense an
acceleration of your frequency. Forcing
an acceleration of your frequency forces
you to face things that you may have
buried within yourself that you may not
be ready to face. And that can cause
psychotic shock in some of you. So we
retain our distance as long as we feel
that that particular distance is of best
service to you. When there is the timing
that is appropriate to the agreement of
who it is you have agreed to be. Nothing
will stop that interaction. For we do
all have a deep desire to interact in
very loving ways with all of you.
Nothing will keep us away when the
conditions are appropriate for our
meeting in a way that serves you
beneficially according to the agreements
that have been made. So get on with your
life and you will accelerate that
process by staying in the moment with
your life. I understand that you may be
excited about this idea. We are very
excited about interacting with you. But
at the same time, or shall I say and at
the same time, the interactions that we
are having with you in this way and in
what you call your dream reality, these
interactions are real to us. The whole
point is that when they become real to
you, we will be able to manifest in what
you call your physiological reality as
well. Understand? I understand. Well,
thank you very much. Thank you very
much.
At this timing,
we would suggest that you all find
comfortable positions and close your
positions and close your
[Music]
eyes. A few
foundations. One moment before we
continue. By the way, the last
interaction, notice the timing of our
initial response to end the interaction
just before that individual
arrived. That is absolutely reflective
of the idea that when you really really
try to grab something, it is not the
timing to experience. It does in fact
move beyond your grasp.
So we were reflecting the same quote
unquote difficulty to communicate that
she says she is experiencing in her life
with extraterrestrials simply because in a
extraterrestrials simply because in a
sense she is trying a little too hard.
Now take three deep
breaths. And as you relax, we would
desire that you understand a few
ideas. Once again, remember this will be
a conjunction of
interdimensional realities. Even though there may be, I
realities. Even though there may be, I
shall say for now, a portion of yourself
that understands you are quote unquote
physiologically in a room on your
planet, you also
simultaneously will, by allowing an
overlap of dimensions to occur, be on
board the city ship that translates in
your language as having the name solar
wind. In your terminology, it is
cylindrical approximately one of your
miles in
length. Allow yourself to simply now
drift in your
imagination. Float and feel comfortable.
And remember this. No matter what you
seem to experience in your imagination,
you will be aboard that ship. No matter
how it translates. Sometimes individuals
will allow themselves to see certain
areas in the ship, but they will
translate the imagery into artifacts
they are familiar
with. It does not matter what it looks
like. It doesn't always necessarily mean
that you are literally seeing something
that literally looks like that on our
ship, but you are on the ship and you
are perceiving something whether it is
being interpreted symbolically by you or
not. Simply let your ego structure know
that no matter whether it seems to make
sense, you are having an experience that
will benefit you and that you will be
absorbing information on all levels of
your conscious
reality. You will process this
information at whatever rate and pace
you need to and in whatever manner
serves you best. Do not try too hard to
see the things you think you ought to
see. For I will tell you, there are many
things you have absolutely no
expectation of that exist upon the ship.
Let it be for you in your terms
completely open-ended and random.
Now continuing to breathe in a relaxed
state, begin by understanding that you
are all connected together in this and
that you are experiencing this not only
as an individual but as a single entity,
as a single event.
Envision in your mind's eye that every
single being, whether individually or
collectively, is now surrounding
themselves in a large, bright,
transparent, crystallin blue shell of
electromagnetic light. And this will be
your craft to elevate you into the city
ship. Imagine now that all that you call
the physiological reality outside the
transparent shell is now fading and
dissolving into a gray foglike limbo,
fading back into the primal medium
energy out of which all reality is
created. See you, all of you floating in this
See you, all of you floating in this
ship, in the shell, floating in the gray
limbo state. And now allow yourself to feel
state. And now allow yourself to feel
that you are rising, rising, rising. And
that you emerge from out of the fog. And
the fog in a sense falls away. And below
you, you see your bright blue sparkling
planet Earth. And all around you, the
stars of space, deep and bright and
penetrating. And as you rise and
continue to rise, you look up and there
above you, opening itself to you with a
bright emanating light from within is
the city ship we have termed the Solar
Wind awaiting you, greeting you with
loving warmth. And as you merge through
the hull, you find yourself in a
whiteness. And in this whiteness, beyond
the shell of your craft, you sense many
entities, many consciousnesses that are
a part of the blended energy. Some of
them may be distinct, some of them may
not, but you perceive that you are
welcome. And you perceive that there is
energy and you perceive that there is
love. And
now feel the connection to each and
every one of yourselves. Feel the link
so that you will always know no matter
what individual goes to what portion of
the ship that you are always connected
and communicating. And
now what individual goes to what portion
of the ship that you are always
connected and communicating. And now
allow the shell around you to dissolve
so that you are within the white light
of the
ship. Allow whatever format of entity or
energy that wishes to communicate with
you to do so. Allow yourselves now the
opportunity to drift and free float,
merging through the hull in your astral
ethereal form, in your mental form to
explore any portion of the idea of the
vastness of the ship. You are being
guided. You are being supported. You are
being loved. and we will allow you a few
moments of freedom of play to explore at
your own leisure and joy. Continue to
breathe and feel the interconnectedness
of all aboard the ship.
And as you
explore whatever you perceive, allow
yourself to feel the energy that
permeates all aboard the ship. The
energy out of which the ship is created.
The crystallin
energy out of which all consciousness
within the ship focuses and crystallizes
itself into manifestational
being. Allow yourself to feel the
energies pulsing through you. Allow
yourself to identify the support and the
love that you are being
given. Absorb.
Absorb in a comfortable and warm and
easy manner all the information you
require. And feel yourself
expanding and feel yourself breathing
and feel yourself contracting and
expanding once again. And feel your
consciousness extend to the full body of
the ship. And feel your consciousness
extend to the stars to which the ship is
always connected. And feel your
consciousness consolidate back into the
center, the core of the ship. And then
be
aware of all the connections that were
made between you and all the individuals
that came with you.
Find yourselves now back within the
original area that you arrived upon the
ship and feel all the individuals that
have supported you and loved you merging
back within the white light becoming
one. One mind, one thought, one heart,
one soul, one
spirit. We embrace you. We love you. And
now form the idea of the blue white
crystallin shell around your beings
again. And know that you will always be
with us and always are. And allow
yourself in a sense to float and sink
through the
hole. And take a moment as you float
outside the solar wind to appreciate as
you look below the bright blue jewel
that is your planet. and feel the true
love. Feel the true energy, the true
power of your choice to exist in that
dimension as that dimension and the
connection that that dimension has to
all other dimensions. You are not
isolated. You are not cut off. You are a
part of the infinite. You are the
infinite. Allow yourself to drift slowly
down to earth.
and feel the warmth that surrounds you
and penetrates you and loves you and
nurtures you. And as you float and
you. And as you float and
float, the stars of space become the
gray mist once
again. And you allow yourself to feel
the connection you have with each and
every one of your beings, each and every
one of your mates.
And you know that you function as a
whole. And you know that you are an
individual. And as you breathe the new
warmth, the new conviction of your
connection to all and know that we are
always with you even as you are always
with us. Breathe life back into the reality
us. Breathe life back into the reality
from which you came. And know beyond the
shadow of a doubt, even as you may see
and perceive the room to reform out of
the gray mist around your blue white
shell of light, know beyond a shadow of
a doubt that you have come back to a
different earth, of a different
vibration, of a different frequency, one
that is now far more reflective of the
crystal clarity of your consciousness.
that you have aided in the assistance of
the acceleration of the transformation
of your world by your identification
with all that you can be and all that
you are.
Dissolve the idea of the crystallin
shell and reinstate yourselves into your
reality, the new reality as new beings.
As in that sense, belonging of your
society, but also as ambassadors and
emissaries of the universe at
large. to deliver and act in your
actions in your life the message of
harmony and peace that is sung among the
stars and to which you belong.
Three deep breaths. And as you do,
gently awaken and open your eyes to your
surroundings. And truly allow yourself
to be open to the understanding that you
are in a new world, in a new time, for
the first time. The first
time. And remember, with each and every
moment, it is a new world. And whatever
you have retained and whatever you have
brought back from your experience is
your personal gift from us to you. Allow
it to unfold as a flower in your dreams,
in your lives, in your realities by
being the people you have chosen to
be. We remind you it is all in your
point of view.
We extend to you at this time our
unconditional love for sharing the dream
that together we are
forever. Our sweetest and deepest love
to you all and we bid you a fondly good
day.
I'm going Let go. [Applause]