help give all of you at least a little
bit of a background and can help orient
you to what it is that's taking place or
at least what I believe is taking place.
My basic understanding of most
channelings, as they're called nowadays,
is that they are usually the product of
an arrangement or an agreement that is
made on some conscious, unconscious or
subconscious level between the person
that you are and another facet of
yourself or another aspect of another
consciousness somewhere else in time or
space or on a different plane. and that
your life will contain whatever
circumstances it needs to to get you to
remember that you made such an agreement
and to give you whatever tools and
abilities you need to fulfill that
agreement if you still have a mind
to. Everyone will be living a different
lifestyle. Therefore, how they arrive at
that recognition of course will be
different according to the different
person that they are. Some people will
have a long time to realize that such a
thing is possible for them. other
individuals will simply one day be
walking down the street and be hit with
a recognition that something has changed
within their consciousness and that it
is representative of a new direction
that as far as I can put it best
represents a direction that would be
beneficial for them to go in not only to
themselves but perhaps to others as
well. So how everyone gets there of
course is different. How I got there
began about 15 years ago on two
occasions within the same week with four
friends present with me the first time
and two friends present with me the
second time. We had very close physical
broad daylight sightings of Bashar's
spacecraft over Los Angeles. First time
about 150 ft distance, the second time
about 70 ft
distance. On both
occasions, the craft was
approximately an equilateral triangle
about 40 ft on a side, roughly about 8
ft thick of a very dark gray metallic
substance. After we got all excited
about seeing this, we began to double
check our story with each other to make
sure that we had seen what we thought we
had seen. And all of us agreed that it
wasn't a plane. It wasn't a helicopter.
It wasn't something unusual. Especially
since we had about a 30se secondond to
40 second opportunity to view this thing
in, like I said, broad
daylight. What I didn't understand at
that time, aside from having seen what a
lot of people call a UFO. And what I
have come to understand now through
research and through many events that
have happened in my life is that those
sightings were Bashar's way of tapping
me in the subconscious memory to get me
to remember that I made this agreement
and to get me to start learning the
things I needed to learn to fulfill that
agreement with him because a lot of
preparation it turns out was necessary
in terms of my mental patterns, my
thought patterns, my emotional patterns
that needed to change in order to make
some sort of a link possible.
between our respective
mentalities. Bashar does present himself
as a member of an extraterrestrial
community. Many channelings, the ones
that perhaps you have heard of through
the media, are connected to more often
than not what are called disembodied
forms of consciousness. And on that
level, there's probably about three
types that have been classified or at
least the classifications have been
given to. And the first type basically
has to do with your own consciousness.
Channeling, as Bashar has said, is
really only that process of
allowing more than your typical
day-to-day personality to come through
in a free flowing stream of
consciousness in a very creative way.
Any artistic endeavor at all on the
basic fundamental definition of
channeling is a channeling. So all
aspects of channeling, all levels, all
types of channeling always involve a
portion of your own consciousness. At
least you are always involved in the
process since it's coming through you.
So your own consciousness is always
involved. Your own consciousness may be
all that there is to it. But it does
manifest itself in a number of ways that
seems to present other
personalities aside from the one we
normally think ourselves to be. And
therefore other categories have been set
aside to describe these different levels
of channeling. The second level is
basically what is called mediumship or
disembodied spirits. People that have
died that have been physically alive at
one time or another and that now exist
as non-corporeal consciousness and
somehow have the ability to communicate
through mental processes with people
that are still alive. This is probably
the most commonly known or most
familiar. And the other type would be
dealing with levels of consciousness in
other dimensional plains that have never
experienced the physical reality that we
are familiar with at all. And they have
never experienced physical reality to
any degree that we would describe
physical. They are disembodied as their
natural state. The fourth type which is
this type and this is not to imply that
one is more powerful than the other is
what is called the extraterrestrial
connection. And basically what this
simply means is it is a mental
connection that is made a channeling
that is
done with and between another entity who
for lack of a better term is also
discrete as a personality like we are.
Bashar has described that they have
physical beingness. They are not
disembodied spirits. They are a literal
physical race of being. They do have
existence in what he describes another
dimensional plane, a slightly different
frequency from our dimension. And unless
a shift or an adjustment is made in
their frequency, they would be invisible
to us. We would be invisible to them.
However, they do describe that they have
physicality. They are not too dissimilar
from us. And if any and all of you have
questions about their society, he's more
than willing to discuss aspects of that.
I only bring that up to show that in his
communication, for lack of a better
term, he is relatively down to earth,
more so than a lot of what might be
called disembodied spirit because he has
had existence or still has existence in
physical reality. And so he can relate
perhaps a little more strongly to our
physical existence than perhaps a
disembodied consciousness
could. Now the most important thing I want to
Now the most important thing I want to
say about this interaction is what
follows. This to me is the most critical
thing I could say.
I have my own validations for Bashar
being who he says he is because of my
sightings, because of my experiences,
because of unsolicited validation that
has come from many different sources
that reinforce that what I'm
experiencing, at least in my world, is
real. real enough to allow it to
continue to occur because the
information that comes through seems to
be valid at least for many people and
has allowed them to make the types of
changes in their lives that they want to
make. The thing that I want to stress
most importantly is
that there is absolutely nothing about
this interaction that in any way, shape
or form insists that you must believe
that Bashar is who we say he is. I
cannot prove this to you at this time.
Anyway, Bashar has said that within 10
or 20 years when certain types of
social, economic and political changes
have occurred on earth that would make
it conducive. His society and a few
other societies may be able to
physicalize themselves more blatantly
interact with us on a physical level,
but for right now they are remaining in
the background and communicating this
way for a various number of reasons. The
primary reason is that in observing our
society, they have noticed that we have
created a
tendency to when any kind of a messenger
comes along to take the message and throw it
along to take the message and throw it
in the garbage can and focus on the
messenger. They don't want that to
happen. They want to make sure that the
information itself is more important
than who's delivering it. They want to
make sure that if you feel you can use
the information in your life that you
are free to decide on your own valition
that that information has merit for you.
Not because it came from them, not
because they're supposed to be any
greater than we are, not because they
are supposed to be feared or adored.
They want to make sure that the
information in its raw state is what is
most important in your life. And if you
want to use it and you find it works for
you, then by all means apply it. If you
find that it's something that doesn't
work for you, don't worry about it. you
will get what you need somewhere else.
That is one of the reasons. And again,
you can go into more detail with him
about his time schedule and what he
perceives to be our time schedule for us
coming together in a face-toface
encounter. None of this in any way,
shape, or form is impressed upon you to
believe that you must believe that he is
who we say he
is, whether it is a separate being or
not. is not really ultimately what's
is not really ultimately what's
important. The idea is that whatever it
is that's going on here, it represents a
talent that many people that all people
have, an ability to lock into certain
states of consciousness that all people
have and to access information that can
be applied in positive ways in our life.
Like anything, of course, can be applied
in negative ways, too. But that's up to
us. Um before we actually continue and
to keep this brief, I would like to just
state a couple of
things about the actual interchange that
will go on. I allow myself at this point
to go into what most people call a trans
state. This is somewhat of a misnomer.
I'm in an altered state of
consciousness. I know that there is an
interaction going
on, but I go into a type of altered
state where it's very much like a
daydream for me. Very much like an
energetic daydream. I feel the energy. I
feel the emotions. I feel the basic
concepts of the
interaction, but I don't really hear the
words. In the same way that if you're
daydreaming about something that's
really strong, someone might walk in the
room and call your name and you wouldn't
hear them because you're not paying
attention. You're not focused in that
way. For me, the experience is very much more
For me, the experience is very much more
like listening to music than it is
actually listening to a conversation. It
moves me and I know something is being
communicated. And the raw essence of the
idea is instilled within me, but only in
a way that I can apply in my life. I
won't have a recollection of the way he
has discussed the idea with you
specifically because that just passes
right by me because words in this state
are very secondary.
My consciousness as I understand the
process as Bashar has described it
becomes diffused or softened or expanded
if you
will and allows the frequency of his
consciousness to impress itself upon my
energy. When that occurs a telepathic
link is formed between us. I become
susceptible to his frame of reference.
So what is actually happening here is
he's not coming down. He's not
possessing me. He's not inhabiting my
body. As far as I understand, that is
not literally what happens in any
channeling anywhere and never has at any
time. Our definition of that
circumstance makes it seem as if that
is. So what I understand is happening is
that my energy, the energy that I always
have as myself, is being transformed
into a model or a pattern of his energy.
So that what you are getting is a
representative mirror of his personality
of his thoughts made out of the energy
that exists right here and right now
which is my
energy. As such when he begins to speak
to you he is not literally speaking
English. I am programmed for lack of a
better term with English. I am
functioning like a translation box for
him. Whatever concepts he sends with his
thoughts are simply automatically
translated by my subconscious into
whatever language I am comfortable and
familiar with. It's an automatic
process. If there are words or
terminologies that I don't comprehend or
understand, it causes a fuzziness or a
static in the translation going the
other way.
He can discuss most concepts or most
ideas with you but now and then there
may be a confusion in terminology
because of the way he looks at things
and the way we look at things. If for
any reason at any point during the
dialogue between you there is something
that he is saying that you don't
understand. What I would like to ask you
to do is to speak up and say, "Wait a
minute, Bashar." Interrupt the entire
proceeding and say, "I do not get it and
I want to understand it." You know, just
say, "Could you use another word? Could
you rephrase it?" He will. He wants to
make sure that whatever it is he's
talking about with you, if you want to
know what he's saying is understood. So,
don't feel like you're going to
interrupt the proceedings by asking for
a clarification.
As was already pointed out as well,
Bashar does not believe that there
really is any such thing as a stupid or
a silly question. Nothing is too
personal to ask. It's up to you. You
don't have to ask it, but you can ask
anything from personal to cosmic
questions. He doesn't care. He's not
shy. He will respond in whatever way he
feels is of best benefit to you. There
may be some things he will either not be
able to say for one reason or another,
some things he will not know. He is not
an all- knowing being. He is an
individual like you and I with his own
personality in a civilization that in
certain ways may be more advanced than
ours. But he has his own personality.
There will be certain things he will
know. There will be certain things he
won't know. But his point of view is
relatively expanded relative to the way
we usually look at things. And his point
of view therefore sometimes gets us to
think in new ways. And that's the
biggest benefit that he usually has on
people. But feel free to ask anything you want
But feel free to ask anything you want
if you're not embarrassed to ask it in
front of the crowd that's here. Treat
him like a friend. Treat him very
informally, very directly because he's
going to be very direct with you. That's
his style. The last thing I will say
before I actually go into the altered
state is when I allow my personality to expand
is when I allow my personality to expand
and I go into the actual
energy, you will notice that my body
will go through a few reactional
changes. That is only adjustments to the energy.
That is only adjustments to the energy.
Nothing of what I'm experiencing in is
painful in any way, shape, or form. Some
people have said it looks like I'm going
through a lot of pain, but I'm not. So,
don't worry about that. I'm doing just
fine. It will take a few seconds for the
adjustment to happen. When he comes
through, because of the increase in
energy, the voice, my voice will usually
be a bit louder than it normally is. So
if for some reason because of the
microphone it's too loud, just ask him
to tone it down and he will. But that's
usually just representative of the
increase in the energy itself. The
bottom line to all of this, I think the
most important thing is to have as good
a time as you possibly can have. This is
your time. So please have fun.
The more fun you have with him, the more
you treat him like a friend, the easier
the flow will be and the more
information can be discussed. The last
thing I will say is when you are coming
up and asking a question when it's your
turn after the
break, please out of courtesy to
everyone try to keep it to one question
so that as many people as possible get a
chance to get up here and interact.
Sometimes people will go on 2, three,
four, five, and six questions.
This gives you an opportunity to focus
on to what is the most important thing
you want to talk about. It also gives
you an opportunity to listen to every
single other person that comes up here
because very often they will ask a
question you did not get a chance to
ask. So please keep it to one question
because we are limited on time. Once
again I will thank you very much for
coming. Please have a good time and I'll
see you all at the break.
Yes. Um thank you.
When I'm going into the altered state,
when I'm coming out of the altered
state, I will ask you to please be quiet
until he's actually speaking. Or when he
says goodbye, be quiet until I actually
refocus myself. If he says goodbye and you all
myself. If he says goodbye and you all
start talking all at once, I'm in a very
raw and exposed kind of mental state at
that point. And it's like having a
hundred people screaming in your ear
when you're trying to wake up in your
bedroom in the morning. Give me a second
to readjust and pull my personality back
together. I'll let you know when I'm
focused by speaking to you in my normal
fashion. And then you can jump up and
down and scream and do anything you want
to do. But give me those few moments to
readjust in silence and then everything
after that is
okay. Have a good
time. All right. Hey, I greet you all
this day of your time as you know time
to exist. And before we begin our
interaction, I would like to lay down a
few foundations between us so that there
will be some commonality, some common
ground for this interaction in terms of
who we are to you and who you are to us.
So before we begin, allow me to say the
following thing. Our perception of
thing. Our perception of
existence is as follows.
We perceive generally that all things
that you would call material things will
be made as you already know of energy
vibrating at different frequency
rates. The idea is that these frequency
rates will determine whether you
perceive something as material or not.
Many of you already understand this on a
fundamental level within your own
dimension of experience. But from our
perception, the different dimensions
themselves are the product of variation
in frequency in pitch if you will of the
primal energy of existence itself.
The idea therefore is that different
beings, different
consciousnesses will exist at various
frequency levels, various planes,
various dimensions as you call them of
existence. And that all of these dimensions, all of
And that all of these dimensions, all of
these planes, all of these levels of
reality will coexist simultaneously with
each other. In a sense, shall we say,
over overlapping,
overlapping,
interpenetrating each other, but from
one dimension to the other. Usually they
will be imperceptible to one another
because of the variation in frequency.
An analogy that we have used to explain
this idea many times on your planet is
what we have called the radio analogy.
You have on your planet a device you
call radio. You know that you can perceive
radio. You know that you can perceive
many different programs coming through
the radio at any given moment. But you
also know that you only perceive the
program at any given moment that your
dial is tuned to. Now this does not mean
that all the other programs are not
there. You know that all the other
programs that are being broadcast as you
say to your radio are all there
simultaneously. But because they are on
different frequencies you only perceive
one at a time. That is if your device is
functioning properly shall we say. The
idea therefore is that realities and
dimensional planes follows this analogy
in certain ways and that you can
perceive different reality, different
consciousnesses, different
existences, different realms, different
dimensions if you change your frequency
so that your senses, your perception
will be more aligned, more harmoniously
linked with those other frequencies.
then you can perceive them instead of
perceiving the one that you have been
taught for so long is the only reality
in which you exist. Each and every
reality shall we say has its own
barriers, its own limitations, its own
definitions of what that reality is. And
by definition each and every frequency
is going to be
selfreinforcing. What that means is as
follows. any reality will contain within that
any reality will contain within that
reality a system of reflective laws,
shall we say, to reinforce the validity
of that prime reality as opposed to all
other realities. If that were not so,
there would be in your terminology too
much bleed through from one reality to
another and you would not as
physiological beings be able to make
sense out of any one particular reality
at any one given moment. So each and
every dimension is self-reinforcing and
seems by definition to exclude all other
dimensions of reality.
There is, shall we say, a place, a
state, an attitude, however, that
bridges them all. A central limbo state
in which your consciousness can be aware
of the fact that there are an infinite
number of realities, all overlapping in
one particular type of here and
now. That particular state is achievable
by any being in any plane, in any
dimension of experience at any given
moment. But achieving that state, the
ability to perceive other dimensions,
other planes, other consciousnesses is
usually a matter of attitude, of
perspective, of belief system, of
emotion and thought pattern. Because it
is your belief systems, your emotions
and your thought patterns that you have
to explore your reality with. And
through those filters do you perceive
the reality that you have for so long
believed to be the only solid reality.
Do remember that your senses, which by
the way you have seven of, not five.
We'll get back to that in a moment. Your
senses are not so much the windows to
the world that you have always been
taught. They are. They are filters that
keep out a majority of the realities
around you and allow you to perceive
only the reality you think you ought to
be perceiving or need to be perceiving
at any given moment. to allow you to
function as concentrated
consciousnesses, as physiological
beings. Were it not for those filters,
as we have said, you would be
experiencing so much bleed through that
you would not be able to function in any
one particular reality
smoothly. Now, your world is changing in
many ways. This all of you know. One of
the ways your world is changing in its
conscious evolution is to be able to
begin to realize that there may just be
more than the one reality that you have
always been taught is the only reality.
That there may just be other
civilizations, other dimensions of
consciousness, other planes of reality.
And because you are now beginning to
consider that that may be possible, your
belief systems, your emotions, and your
thought patterns are opening up, are
allowing a little bit more of these
other realities to, shall we say, leak
in. But these realities will only leak
in at a rate that is comfortable for
each and every one of you to make the
best sense out of. For many of you, of
course, will have to, shall we say,
compare and weigh the reality you have
always been taught is real against the
new energies, the new perceptions that
you are receiving before you will decide
whether or not you want to incorporate
those new sensings into the reality you
have always taught to believe was real.
It is all right if you take your time.
That is up to each and every individual,
up to each and every civilization. Your
pace is your own and whatever pace that
is is absolutely perfect for you. There
is no rush. You are eternal beings.
You're going to be around forever. You
can take your time. It is up to you. The
idea, however, is that when a
civilization begins to open up to the
possibility that there may be other
realms of consciousness, you begin to
interact with those other realms of
consciousness. Your willingness
itself to believe that there might just
be a possibility to interact with other
beings and other dimensional planes is a
type of invitation to those other
beings. That invitation is answered but
answered at least by us and the
civilizations we are familiar with in a
very delicate
way. We respect the idea that each and
every civilization is discreet. We do
not wish to interfere in the evolution
that that civilization has laid down for
itself. Therefore, when we receive that
invitation, when we perceive that a
civilization might be on the verge of
being willing to recognize that it can
communicate with other beings, we
approach cautiously. We, shall we say,
to use your terminology, test the waters
to see what degree of receptivity
actually exists in that civilization.
For there have been times in what you
would call the past where civilizations
were approached, shall we say, too
quickly and the result was quite
detrimental not only for that
civilization but also for the
civilization that approached.
Therefore, we are always very cautious
about these interactions to make sure
absolutely make sure as best as we can
that our existence, our ideas, our
perceptions, our perspectives are never
something that are forced upon you. That
you understand that you are in every
way, shape, and form equal to us in our
eyes. and that we simply present you
with a different point of view that you
can decide whether or not to incorporate
in your reality. It is up to you. We do
this because it serves us as well. For
the more civilizations that we are able
to harmoniously interact with, the more
creation is expanded for us and the more
we learn as well. We learn many things.
First of all, in you, we get to see how
many more ways infinite creation has
manifested itself. And this teaches us
of all the probable ways that creation
could manifest itself. So we are always
learning by these interactions. To us,
these interactions are a gift. And
therefore, for that gift, we thank you.
And in return for that gift, we share
with you our thoughts, our ideas, our
perspectives, so that you can decide for
yourselves what you want your lives to
be. And so that you can choose if you
want to to interact with us in all the
ways that it will be possible to
interact in short order, as you say.
Now the idea of your senses, the idea of
your filters, more often than not, you
are taught that you have five
physiological senses. The idea is that you call them
senses. The idea is that you call them
your sight, your sound, your hearing,
your taste, and your
touch. You have two more physiological
senses that you are only beginning to
understand. The reason that it has taken
this amount of time for a majority of
your civilization to recognize this is
simply because the first, shall we say,
five senses are generally speaking in
your terminology electrochemical in
nature and are immediately apparent
within your physiological form. The
other two have
electrochemical shall we
say side effects to them but they are
also electromagnetic in
nature. The sixth would be called
orientation and it is connected to the
idea of your orientation in space and
time. Many of you understand, many of
you have phrases in your language that
say you simply know where you are going.
You have a sense of direction. You are
oriented in space and time. Spacetime as
you call it. This is in a sense a sixth
physical sense. And it is located to
some degree within your sinus cavities
within what you call also to some degree
your inner ear. It is hinged upon the
idea of the substance magnetite that
exists in your sinus cavity and it is
what many of you and also the animal
species upon your planet use to orient
and navigate themselves through physical
spaceime. The seventh sense is in a
sense what you would call discernment,
vibrational discernment. This has been
classically categorized by you as
picking up upon another individual's
vibratory aura. The idea is also
electromagnetic in nature, but is
cellular in scope and interpenetrates
every single cell and every single
atomic structure in your body.
The shall we say all-encompassing eighth
sense of knowingness is transcendental
and does not really
have shall we say an absolute fix in
physical reality. It is to some
degree connected to what you may call
the pineal
gland the idea of what you have
colloally termed other glands in your
system. But it is also transcendental in
your non-physical consciousness as well
since first and foremost at least from
our point of view you are non-physical
consciousness to begin with and you
project in a sense a portion of yourself
as a physical
being. This is before we continue the
last thing I would like to talk about.
The idea of your notion of yourselves as
physical beings that contain a soul or
contain a spirit. From your point of
view, this is accurate. From the way you
have defined physical reality, this is
accurate. And in no way, shape or form
am I invalidating your
understanding. Our point of view,
however, is as follows.
You do not have a physical body in which
is deposited a soul or a spirit. Your
physical body does not contain a spirit
like some sort of a vessel. From our
perspective, your physical body is your
spirit manifesting itself in
physiological terminology presenting a
face in the physical definition of the
reality in which you abide that you
yourselves have created with your very
definitions with your belief systems.
As such, the idea of changing your
beliefs, changing your emotions,
changing your thought patterns does not
bring changes in your physical reality
down to an issue of mind over matter. It
brings it down to an understanding that
matter and mind are the same thing. That
spirit and matter are the same thing.
that all of these so-called
differentiations you have discussed for
thousands of years of your time upon
your planet are really discussions about
the same thing. The primal energy of
existence manifesting itself in all the
multi-dimensional multitudinous
simultaneous ways that it possibly can
by creating itself to be discrete and
differentiated frequencies that you
perceive as discrete and different
plains of existence or discrete and
different material objects.
The foundation of all the things we will
be discussing this day of your time will
hinge upon this principle that the
reality you perceive around you is
actually created from you. That it is
contained within you. And that when you
change your beliefs about it, your
emotions about it and your thought
patterns about it
sufficiently, when you change the
frequency of the being you are
sufficiently, you do see reflected back
to you in no uncertain terms
physiological manifestations of those
changes because your physical reality is
but the shadow of your soul, the shadow
of your identity, the shadow of your
idea of yourself and that you can create
the realities you desire. If you can in
your terms get a handle as you say upon
changing the belief systems, the
emotional patterns and the thought
patterns within you. You are as you say
in your biblical references made in the
image of God. Now the idea of what you
in your society may call God and what we
may call God may vary here and there in
semantics and terminology but it is
basically the same concept. It is all
that is one infinite creation that
diversifies itself into many
multitudinous transformational
manifestations. If you are made in the
image of a multi-dimensional infinite
being then that means you are
multi-dimensional infinite beings as
well. At least that is what the phrase
means to us. So when you say you are
made in the image of God, understand
what that truly means. You are the
co-creators with the infinite, the
creators of your immediate
reality. And as you design the filters
of your senses to be, so you experience
the reality you believe you are in. This
will be the foundation of all the ideas
we will discuss this day of your time.
At this time, allow me to end and to
allow the interaction to begin. But
first, I will once again thank you for
choosing to function as ambassadors and
representatives of your society. For
that is what you are. Make no mistake
about it, for there are many, many, many
on this end listening in. I thank you
for allowing me to function as an
ambassador of my society and communicate
with you in this way at this time so
that it may serve the best of all
concern. In return for your gift of
sharing, in return for your willingness
to explore this idea, I ask you now in
what way may I be of service to you? So
Bashar nice in as much as this is a many
of the people sitting in this room
attend a class in that considers the
issues around death dying and afterlife
so simply put uh the question that I've
been asked to ask has to do with what
happens at death but before you answer
let me expand it a little bit all right
the question is what happens to us when
we die what happens to our physical what
happens to our psychological what
happens to our spiritual being at death.
The question is asked in the following
context. All right. In our human
religions, we seem to have historically
framed at least two major concepts or
images of what happens to us when we
die. Three. One of those one of those
images is um and then if there's three,
you can add the third. But one one of
those images certainly would be the
eastern image which would be spoken of
generally in terms of transmigration or
reincarnation in which we see that an
individual is recycled in a sense and
that at death doesn't really cease to
exist but then has the opportunity to
choose to come back into this life form
in another life form perhaps but the
same soul or spirit. So the notion of
reincarnation, the notion of recycling.
All right. And then in the west,
Judaism, Christian, Islam, etc., we have
more of a linear concept in which a
human person has one lifetime. And in
that one lifetime, the lessons that are
to be learned must be learned such that
at death there is not a recycling, but
if anything, a continuation on into sort
of following a trajectory that has
already been established in life. Now
could you give some feedback from your
perspective with regard to this question
what happens at death in the context of
these two and I've heard you say three
possibilities. Yes. The third simply
being those that are uncertain about the
other two. The idea at this time from our
two. The idea at this time from our
perspective is as follows.
We perceive the idea of reincarnation to
be a fact as you say, but not
necessarily in the way many of the
religions upon your planet understand
it. For even many of the religions upon
your planet look at reincarnation in a
linear sense, and we do not. To us, all
time is simultaneous. All lives exist
right now.
They are quote unquote as you say
separated by a convenient frequency idea
to prevent it from becoming what you
would call
confusing. The idea again can be drawn
upon an analogy for clarification to
begin with. We have used the analogy we
call your film strip analogy to paint
the picture. You are familiar in your
society with the idea of what you would
call a strip of your motion picture
film. Yes.
The idea is that there are upon that
strip of film many frames, one frame at
a time being necessary to represent a
particular discrete and specific action
that then in your terminology follows to
the next action, the next, the next, and
the next. By creating the illusion of
the continuity of motion by moving that
film through one of your projectors, you
sense that there is a linear time, a
progression, an unfolding of events.
However, to the characters, shall we
say, upon each frame of film, they only
know that particular moment at any given
moment, any given time in space. And
they do not necessarily have knowledge
of what is coming up and perhaps a very
dim knowledge of what has already
passed. They live in that frame and that
frame only. And the characters on the
film are, shall we say, imprisoned on
that frame.
However, the projectionist sees the
entire film all at once, knows that all
the frames exist all at the same time,
and it is up to the projectionist's
discretion to decide whether to run the
film forwards, run it backwards, or look
at any particular frame at any given
moment. And they do not have to be
looked at in any particular order to
what we call the higher self, the
oversoul energy of your consciousness,
the non-physical awareness that you
actually are. This is how physical
reality looks like a strip of film with
discrete moments, discrete frames. It
can be understood by the higher self
that that reality needs to make sense
out of that motion picture by running it
through their projector in one
particular direction one frame after
another. However, the higher self does
not have to look at it that way and
recognizes that all those frames
coexist. Not only that, but that many
films cross and coexist at the same
time. An infinite number of films can be
going on all at the same time from the
perspective of your higher
consciousness. Therefore, first of all,
reincarnation to some degree is a
misnomer. Reincarnation implying that it
is a linear mechanism that you incarnate
and then reincarnate and reincarnate
after that having incarnated before. To
us, it is simply simultaneous
multi-dimensional incarnation. Only from
your physical point of view do you see
it linearly and call it
reincarnation. The reason that that
exists, the reason that there are
multiple lives is as we have said, you
are a multi-dimensional being. You fill
existence. You are a reflection of the
infinite. Some of you exist in one frame
of reference at a time. You can't all
fit there because that's not the
definition of that particular frame of
reference. Therefore, you have
conveniently compartmentalized the total being that
compartmentalized the total being that
you are to play out the various
scenarios you could play out that are
possible to play out within all of
creation. You play all those scenarios
out simultaneously. But to the you in this
simultaneously. But to the you in this
particular scenario, it seems as if
those other scenarios are being played
out in a linear time frame. You follow
me? Yes. Now, in a sense, it is also
true the linear idea of well, there's
the one life and that's it. Because even
though you are a multi-dimensional
incarnational being, the you are now, so
to speak, this life, this you, this
reality has only one life to live. You
have never been this you before. You
will never be this you again.
Therefore, in that sense, this life
really is a beginning, a middle, and an
ending and does not necessarily in a
linear fashion reincarnationally
directly connect into any other life.
You can still even in what you call an
astral realm have a perception that one
life can follow another. But that is
because you are still even though
non-physical closely associated to the
linear time track of physical reality.
Linear time is one of the definitions of
physical reality. It is that definition
that creates what you call physical time
and space. Volume and timing are the
product of the definitions of the
dimension in which you exist. And even
in some of the lower astral dimensions
as well, you have to be of a higher
frequency away from that physical
reality to break free from that linear
time frame.
So even in an astral state after having
died physically as you say you can still
think of the idea of having one life
after the other. However that is not
always so. Some beings in the astral,
the non-physical, what you would call
the spirit state after physical
death can decide that they would like to
have a particular
experience. And they can decide to have
that experience after the life they have
just ended. Even if that physical
experience took place or shall we say
will take place many hundreds of your
years before the life they just died
from. When they inject themselves into
the time stream and have that life from
your perspective as a being in the time
stream, it will conveniently find the
niche it needs to find to make sense out
of the dimensional laws in which you
exist and will appear to have happened
before the life you are living now. But
from the point of view of the spirit
that chose the life, that decision to
choose that life may have actually
happened after the present life. you
following along so far? Now, we do
understand that there is some difficulty
in a dialogue of this nature where all
of our tenses are becoming confused. And
we do understand that a lot of this
dialogue is absolutely pertinent only to
specific frames of reference that you
may or may not exist in at any
particular moment, physical or
non-physical, lower astral, higher
astral. And we also understand that all
of these different levels are also
rather arbitrary because they are all created
arbitrary because they are all created
by your belief systems about what
different frequencies of energy of the
primal creative energy should
represent in a sense. Therefore, all is
one thing but it has been fragmented and
fractionated into a number of different
layers. Each layer
about the flow of time, the direction of
time, the idea of volume, the idea of
self-awareness, the idea of existence.
All of these things when discussing
ideas from one level to another can
become quite confusing. Since the
terminology and the tenses and the
perceptions of one level are not
necessarily, as you say, gerine to
another, we will do the best we can with
the language we have at our disposal to
explain the idea. We will simply ask you
to allow for the confusion in tenses
which may occur in making an attempt to
discuss something of this nature. Has it
been relatively clear so far, as you can
tell? Yes. Let me follow it up with just
a quick question. Have you yourself
experienced death? Yes. The idea as a
soul is that all beings have experienced
the idea you call physical death many
many times. As the discrete persona I am
now. No. In a sense in terms of your
linear time. As the discrete persona I
am now, I have not in your terminology
even been born yet. The idea is that I
am, for lack of a better term, a future
aspect of the physical being sitting
before you. In my civilization, in my
flow of time, my reality has not even
happened yet relative to your
reality. In my civilization, the time
frame you exist in is history to me,
ancient history.
The idea therefore is that my dimension
flows at one particular rate. Your
dimension flows at another particular
rate. What you call non-physical reality
flows at another rate altogether.
That is why certain discrepancies can
occur when communication is attempted
from one level to another and why
somebody may say well this looks like
this might happen then or it did happen
at such and such a time and the time
frame may be completely erroneous
because the time scales are radically
different and are very difficult to
assimilate and synchronize from one
frame to
another. What happens generally when you
physically die is as follows. There will
be specific scenarios that are relative
to specific individuals, but this will
generally happen to all beings that are
inconce in a physical reality. At least
as far as our experience has told us.
What you do is expand the consciousness
that you are. You are not so highly
focused as a physicalized, materialized,
shall we say, crystallized
consciousness. You expand. You in that
sense contain the idea of the previous
physical reality, but it becomes now
simply a fragment of the total being
that you are. Shall we say your focus is
not on it as directly anymore.
Therefore, the materiality begins to
dissolve, what you call decompose or
decay. Your focus no longer holds it
together in the way that it used to. As
you expand your
consciousness, you then can experience
many different things. From our
experience, this will be the most likely
scenario. Whatever in physical reality
you held on to as the strongest belief
about what you think would be your
experience at death will be your
experience at death. because you are now
transforming into, for lack of a better
term, a thought form in a world made of
thought
energy. And instantly as you believe an
idea to be real, that is what you seem
to experience tangibly around you. The
second you change your thought, the
experience around you changes. But on
that level of non-physical reality,
because you're no longer within the
definition of time and space, there is
not the same kind of time lag between
the thought and the manifestation of the
physicalized or apparently physicalized
thing. So the first thing you believe
most strongly would be the thing you
would experience on death is usually
what you experience. If it is in other
words the idea of long lost uncle, long
lost aunt. That is usually the
manifestation that will greet you. Now
it can be literal. It might actually be
the consciousness of that being. But it
doesn't have to be. It might simply be
your concoction, your manifestation out
of the primal energy that you need to
see in order for you to relate as best
as you can to the transition you're
going through. It might actually even be
another consciousness allowing its
energy to be
utilized to represent to you the
longlost uncle, the long lost aunt, to
allow you to feel more comfortable. The
beings that do that are usually referred
to in your society as guides. Many times
they will simply present themselves to
you in whatever way is most pleasing,
most acceptable to your belief system so
that you can make the transition more
easily than you might have had you been
confronted with something completely
unknown. The idea to put it flatly and
most simply is that from that point
forward, from the point forward that you
realize whatever you really think is
what you can experience, then everything
opens up to you. You can really in all
reality, no pun intended, go anywhere
you want, anytime you want and you can
create any type of reality you desire.
There are different levels in which
different kinds of manifestations are
possible. Some are more likely in one
level than another. But once you
recognize that you are an energy being
and that it is simply a matter of
changing your frequency, you can really
do anything you want. You can go on to
other dimensional realms. You can
incarnate in other physicalized
civilizations. You can reincarnate in
your own civilization at any point along
the timeline. It is completely up to
you. Does that answer the question
sufficiently? Yes. Thank you. Thank you
very much,
Bashar. We've been informed that your
life is uh uh in the future according to
our understanding, but it is it is in a
physical plane. Yes. Similar to ours.
Yes. I wonder if you could describe for
us the planet on where you live, how big
it is, how far it is from the central
sun, the time periods for your year and
your day, and uh uh some of the physical
aspects of your life. All right.
Our physiological form is generally as
follows. We are approximately 5 ft of
height in your counting. white whitish
gray skin coloration very wide upturned
eyes. The pupil of our eye encompasses
most of the eye so it would appear as if
our eyes are black. They are actually
not. Most of them tend toward what you
would call gray in coloration but
because of the enlarged pupil they
appear almost all black. The males will
usually have no hair. Females will have
hair usually tending also to be whitish
in color although there are exceptions.
If you wish some type of comparative
analogy between our civilization and the
species of your civilization, you could
use the idea of Mongolian and you would
be close but not exact. We are
relatively slender in that way,
relatively frail as you would understand
that idea. And our civilization is
evolving from physicality to
non-physicality. We no longer eat as we
once did. We absorb energy directly and
our skin is somewhat transparent in that
way. The idea of our planet which in our
ancient language which we no longer
really use is termed essani. Essani in
your language translates out to place of
living life. It is our understanding
that all beings are made of living light
and thus we have called our own world.
It is not too dissimilar to your own
planet. It is a tiny bit smaller. What
you would call our gravitational
component is approximately 85% of your
own. Our day is a slight bit longer than
yours. Approximately what you would call
25 of your hours. However, our year is
much longer being that we are
approximately in your terms 120 million
miles radius from our central star
making in your terminology our year
approximately 454 of your days of
counting. Therefore, in terms of our terminology,
Therefore, in terms of our terminology,
I am approximately what you would call
the idea
100 30 and
approximately six of my years, 100
approximately 70 of your years, allowing
for the variation in our time flow, our
time stream. Our planet is in your
terminology parklike very green. Our central star is
parklike very green. Our central star is
yellowish
green. The idea is that we have no major
structures upon our planet at this time.
The majority of our civilization at any
one moment, which does not number very
much anyway, at least not in terms of
your world, exists in what you would
call city ships or spacecraft. And
therefore, the surface of the planet
itself has been left more to what you
would call recreational purposes at this
time. With a very slight adjustment,
your civilization, your species would
find it most comfortable. Our axis tilt
is not very much, approximately no more
than what you would call 3 to four
degrees. Therefore, we maintain a
relatively constant temperature. We do
not have the wide variation in seasons
that your civilization experiences. It
never varies more than what you would
call 13° around the average temperature
you would call approximately 72 of your
degrees Fahrenheit. The idea is that you would
Fahrenheit. The idea is that you would
find it most comfortable. It would be
perhaps a little bit more rich in oxygen
to some degree. You may be a little
lightaded there for a while, but
adjustments can be made. Our permanent
population is approximately what you
would call between 200 250 million of
your counting. There are many other
species from other civilizations that
will come and go upon our planet at
various times for various reasons. But
as we have said, at any given moment
fully 3/4ers of our population exist in
city ships which range anywhere from
what you would call one of your miles in
length to approximately 10 of your miles
in length and will contain several
hundred,000 individuals at a time for
the purpose of exploring different areas
of the galaxy. interdimensional
penetration and for communication with
various civilizations, those that make
up what we call the association of
worlds approximately numbering 360
worlds and also for exploring and
contacting new civilizations such as
your own new to us that
is has this answered all the ideas
sufficiently or is there something else?
I think that's fine. If I could just add
uh one more thing, could you tell us uh
how far your planet is from us and in
what direction that we would look to see
where you're going to be? Yes. Now, you
will not be able as we have said to see
our star because we are in a different
dimensional plane. While we are in our
dimensional plane, we cannot see your
star either until we make the
dimensional shift. However, if our
dimension and your dimension were over
overlapped, you would find our star
approximately 500 of your light years of
counting in the direction of the
constellation you call Orion.
Will that suffice? Thank you. Thank you
very much, Sharing.
I have several uh small questions. Small
questions. All right. Uh uh Daryl Daryl
can't prove that you are a uh separate
uh physically embodied being uh well not
this time and he holds out the
possibility you are in fact only a
manifestation of his uh his nature.
Correct. But he doesn't think so. The
evidence that he has compiled would seem
to discount it. But again it does not
really matter. In a sense, we are
aspects of the same soul. And it can in
all reality be said we are fragments of
the same consciousness. Both situations
are real to me. I am a discrete entity
to myself. And yet at the same time,
both Daryl and I are aspects of the same
consciousness. Where is your body right now? It is in
Where is your body right now? It is in
what you would call a state of repose
upon my scout craft orbiting my home
world. A long ways away. In your
terminology, yes. But the idea of this
type of telepathic communication does
not involve the need of space-time
volutrics and therefore is
instantaneous. Nothing is being violated
in a physical sense.
Do you use other people than Daryl as as
facilitators? Yes.
Who are they? Some of which we can
mention now. Some of which we are not
allowed to until they progress further
in their own understanding. But of late,
the channel has become aware of several
that now exist in the area you would
call your
Japan. There are now some individuals
who exist within what you call your
United States also that have begun to
tap into our stream of consciousness.
And this does not necessarily involve
only myself. Many members of my
civilization and other civilizations are
also in communication in this form with
many members of your civilization. Those
that are simply receptive to it. Could
you name one or two people who you are
in touch with? Yes. In what you would
call your Los Angeles area, there is
another individual that we have given
expressed permission to channel our flow
of consciousness. The name of this
individual is what you would call Steven
[Music] Huitt. In what you would call the Japan
Huitt. In what you would call the Japan
area, the individual involved is female
and goes by the terminology of
Ayako. Will this do? Great. Thank you
very much. Now, a couple of brief
questions. All right.
Uh, can you give us some uh means of uh
distinguishing between uh genuine and
fraudulent uh uh beings uh who play this
uh role that Daryl plays. We will make
an attempt to do so. However, the
terminology of genuine and fraud tunes
may be quite touchy as you say. We can
however guide you to the idea of what is
positively or negatively oriented one
way or another. Usually you will find
that those in your terminology that are
quote unquote
genuine will usually have a positive
desire behind them. The signs and the
signals to look for are as follows. If
an individual is focused upon
saying you must do this, you must do
that. I have the answer and this is the
only way you are probably not absolutely
probably dealing with what you would
call an ego structure aspect of the
individual present before
you. If however the energy coming
through acknowledges the validity of all
belief systems, is simply sharing
information for the purpose of sharing,
for the purpose of expanding, for the
purpose of learning in a beneficial and
positive way, makes no demands, does not
want to take your power from you and run
your life for you. In all probability,
no matter what it is, it is a positive
and therefore quote unquote genuine
experience, whether it is someone else
or not.
That is the criteria we would suggest
you look for. This does not necessarily
mean that individuals on your own planet
and that your own consciousness cannot
come up with either idea. It does not
prove as you say one way or another that
just because you are hearing something
positive that it actually has to be
another consciousness. However, we would
simply go by that particular framework
that if it is selfmpowering to you, if
it gives you the power to make the
decisions you need to make in your life
to know that you are in control of your
reality, then it is a genuine experience
that can be of benefit to you. If it
seeks to run your life, if it seeks to
drain your power and control the reality
around you, then in that sense, it would
be called quote unquote fraudulent, no
matter what it is. Does that make sense?
Great. Now the hardest question. Oh,
hardest question. All
maybe we find out that Daryl is indeed a
sincere person and indeed he is in touch
with a being many light years away. All
right. Uh named Bashar. Well, that is
not my name. I will explain that in a
moment, but go ahead. Uh that's that's
not relevant either. All right. Uh the
interesting question would be and this
is why it's a hard question. Yes. Uh
from your perspective, what are the
chances that Bashar's motives are not
entirely pure? From my perspective, it
could be 100% that they are not pure. It
could be 100% that they are. It could be
anything in between. This is why we say
there is nothing that I can prove to
you. It is up to you to prove to
yourself whether the information we
share with you works in your life or
not. We always leave it up to you. We
can guarantee the following thing and
this is the only thing we can
guarantee. If what we share with you
works for you in a positive way and you
use it, you will see a change for the
positive in your life. In that sense,
you will be proving quote unquote my
validity to yourself by utilizing the
information in whatever way works best
for you. But that is the only way at
this time that you can prove the idea.
There is absolutely no way, shape or
form that we insist that this
information must be used by you and that
is the only validity and the only proof
we can give you at this time. It is up
to you to decide whether or not what you
are hearing is something you can
assimilate in your life. I could be an
absolutely canankerous and rotten
individual as far as you know. However,
I will leave it up to your sense of
discernment to decide for yourself with
your own abilities what the information
we are sharing can or cannot do in your
life. And that is the best I can do. I
I'll close with two really simple
questions after that tough one. Uh first
of all, uh one moment, one moment. Can
each and every one of you hear this
individual adequately?
Will you speak up so that all may share?
Uh my my last question which you may not
have heard was is there any way to
detect whether uh Bashar is uh uh even
if he exists uh a uh well-meaning uh
purely motivated being. Uh now the easy
questions are are these uh we're all
familiar with new age doctrines. Uh I
wonder if uh in your view any of the
current new age doctrines are seriously
misguided. Yes. Many many
misunderstandings exist. Many
misinterpretations exist. For you see,
much of the what you call new age
doctrine is patterned on old age styles
of approaching things. And therefore,
many of the interpretations are still
old age interpretations even though they
may be, shall we say, dressed in new age
apparel. The idea can be explained
perhaps as follows.
Because your society for thousands of
years has been taught to think in
certain ways along certain lines. Many
new sensings that come in may still be
being passed through the old filters of
the old belief without conscious
understanding that that is being done
and may be being interpreted along
oldfashioned ways of thinking. An
example, an individual may have been
brought up to believe change is
something that can only occur when
trials by fire are present. You have to
really break everything down and tear
everything apart in order for any real
change to occur. You have to really
suffer and you have to really struggle
in order to amount to anything. Now if
that has been something that has been
ingrained in that individual and they
allow themselves at some point in their
life to perceive that a new energy is
taking place in the world that new
recognitions are going on that changes
are occurring all around them they may
say ah well I am sensitive to the fact
that these changes are coming their
unconscious and subconscious minds
however may fill in the picture to say
and the only way those changes can come
is through destruction through fear fear
through trial by fire. Therefore, they
will say this is the way it must happen
because that's the way they have been
taught is the only way it can happen. So
there can be a true sensing going on.
They can be very sensitive to the fact
that certain things are about to happen,
but they may be
interpreting those changes in the
modality they are used to thinking in
without even recognizing they're doing
it. And they take it for gospel as you
say simply because the mechanism of
applying meaning to situations is so
ingrained and so automatic with all
beings within any particular reality
they may not even realize they are
attaching their own interpretation to it
and may simply take it as the way they
receive the information in its raw state
which may not be the case. Does that
help? Did you wish to discuss something
Did you wish to discuss something
specific along this line? That's
specific. Yeah, that's helpful. My my
last question is this. Uh this has all
been very one-sided. You've been telling
us things. Maybe you came here uh in uh
some degree of ignorance and curiosity
is always curious. Is there anything we
can tell
you? Well, all right.
You can tell
me
why individuals because this is
something we truly do not understand
even though we do have some
comprehension of the mechanisms and the
belief systems that created it. Why do
individuals upon your planet truly
insist on not believing that they are
deserving of anything they can
imagine? Well, you do not have to
applaud. And if you do applaud,
understand you are applauding
yourselves, not
me. But this is something in all honesty
that really does puzzle us. Because you
see, in all of the civilizations we have
encountered, of course all civilizations
are unique, but your civilization is one
of the most highly focused in certain
ways we have ever encountered. And one
of the most highly focused ideas we have
seen in your civilization is the idea
the insistence of giving away your
power. The idea that you are very
willing over and over and over again to
believe in a sense what someone else
tells you other than what you know is
true for yourself.
That is why we always always always
always in all of these interactions
outline from the beginning that you are
never expected to believe anything we
say just because we said it. The idea is
that we have noticed a strong tension in
your society to lock on to things and
just the opposite to shy away from
things just because of what you think
you must absorb one way or another.
We really have found it quite
mesmerizing. We really have found it
quite puzzling and it has taken us quite
a long time to even gain the glimmer of
understanding we do have as to what the
mechanism is that creates an absolute
insistence on the part of your species
to keep yourself at the lowest common
denominator you can imagine.
rather than allowing yourself to truly
be inspired by your existence and rise
to full heights as you could. Uh I'll
I'll try and answer to that. Uh my guess
is that it's something like this. Yes.
Uh because of our embodied nature. We
develop habits that tie ourselves very
closely to our physical bodies, give
rise to an illusion that uh my ego is
tied to my body and produce with that
habit a kind of uh sleep sleeping state
which uh blinds me to possibilities that
if I awakened I might uh be aware of.
All right. Will you define habit?
Uh it a habit is a repeated tendency
tied to uh the state of the body uh to
behave in certain ways without the
benefit of awareness. A
tendency you are suggesting therefore a
type of momentum that occurs. Exactly.
Exactly. All right. From our point of view,
All right. From our point of view,
therefore this momentum, this habit as
you call it can only occur when there is
unawareness of the habit.
Exactly. Once there is awareness of the
habit, it should no longer occur. Is
that correct? True. Is this what you
actually see happening upon your planet?
Of course.
All right. We thank you for the
clarification.
That's great. Since I'm filling in for
an anthropologist, I'm going to ask some
anthropological questions. Oh, all
right. You've given a a fascinating
description of the physical
characteristics of your planet. Oh, all
right. etc., etc. Very scientific. Now
as a visiting in in our terms as we
understand them as a visiting
anthropologist say I would like to ask
what the equivalencies are for your
people for things that we have like
uh marriage ceremonies. Oh thank you
very much. Well I'm not done. I have
hold on. Um well you see we have rituals
to mark special occasions. Yes. like
birth and marriage and puberty. Yes. And
we also have myths to explain why we do
the rituals the way we do. What do you
all do for that? Usually whatever we
want like now the idea what Thank you.
The idea is that there will be a type of
ritual that remains in our society that
we perceive you may or may not find
interesting and it takes place usually
at what you call approximately the third
year of life.
This ritual is a recognition that upon
that third year, the individual born in
our society has what they need to begin
absorbing on their own at their own pace
all the other information that is
pertinent to whatever it is they are
going to do in life and can begin to go
out into the world on their own and seek
what they wish to seek, gleaning
information from whomever they wish to
glean it and learn at their own pace
whatever they wish to learn. In this
sense, it can be termed quote unquote a
naming ritual or a recognition of
adulthood at 3 years of age. Even though
the physical form may not be mature as
you understand
it, this ritual takes place in that
three individuals will gather
representing one for each year and they
will surround the child. As you say, the
child will sit in the middle. Each
individual will focus upon an aspect of
what you would call body, mind and
spirit and will flow a sense of energy
to that child. This child will in this
ritual take from each of those three
individuals a blend and a balance of
those ideas that the child makes its own
its own unique formula, its own unique
frequency representing its own idea of
what its combination of body, mind and
spirit ought to be. In other words, it
solidifies or crystallizes its identity
within our society because up to that
point it does not really have a
solidified one. It is fluid and it can
come and go at any time become
non-physical instantaneously if it
wishes to. At that point, if it decides,
as you say, to hang around in our
society after three years in
crystallizing its identity at that
point, it then harmonizes or if you
wish, synchronizes with the tempo of the
mental framework of our society so that
it will fit in and flow in all the
places and to all the places that best
represent the path of least resistance
for that individual to grow in whatever
way evolution needs for that individual
to grow to fit into our society
best. Now we do not take names per se in
our society at this time. We are
teleathic in nature and therefore we are
always interconnected with one another.
We do recognize our biological parents
as it were and the birth process is not
unlike your own. Although there will be
in your terms a seven-month gestation
period rather than a nine. And the
physical sexual act is not so much as
physical anymore as it used to be, but
now encompasses a high degree of energy
exchange since we are in our
evolutionary place moving into
non-physicality. However, there will
still be the idea of the carrying of the
child and birthing in a similar fashion
to what you understand to be physical
birth. However, because we are
telepathically connected, because we are
in touch, as you say, with each other at
any given moment on various levels in
various ways, our entire society truly
feels truly knows itself to be married
to every other member in the society. We
are one marriage. We are one family and
even though a child may recognize its
biological parents, it also feels that
all the adults are the parents of all.
All the adults feel that all the
children are theirs as well. And because
we are telepathically intertwined, no
child is ever out of sight, out of mind
at any time anyway, no matter where they
are in spaceime.
So we have a high degree of trust, a
high degree of love, a high degree of
nurturing, a high degree of support in
allowing that individual to be who they
want to be. Within our society, there
are many, many, many spontaneous
manifestations that you might call
rituals. But none of them are, shall we
say, as heavily bought into as many of
the rituals upon your planet. They are
simply artistic expressions that are
individual in the moment. Sometimes
groups will spontaneously come together
and form a myth, a ritual, but only
because it is one way of expressing an
idea. It is not something that will be,
shall we say,
institutionalized or rigidized in that
fashion in the very next minute or
perhaps several years later. it may
simply dissolve because the society no
longer sustains the need for that
particular format or matrix. Does this
help answer the
question? Is that sufficient? Oh, well,
I have one more Oh, all right. I just
have one more quick question. Yes. For
how long have you been doing things this
way? And
where did you get the idea to do things
in the way that you've described? Thank
you. In your terms of counting, it has
been approximately a period between 300 and
approximately a period between 300 and
500 of your years ago that our society
made an abrupt
transformation. We were always to some
degree because of the nature of our
environment, because of the nature of
our evolution, shall we say, prone to be
a little more cohesive than your
society. There has never been as much
variation in our history as there has
been in yours. Never as much segregation
in our society as there has been in
yours. So to some degree, shall we say,
speaking of evolution, we might have
had, to put it this way, a little bit of
a head start. We were pushed in that
direction by environment to some degree.
However, as you said before, the idea of
a tendency, a momentum developed until
it brought us to a certain point where
the collective mentality of our society
manifested in a particular event. This
particular event is not unlike what you
would call your quote unquote Christ
scenario. In other words, let me
backtrack a moment, lay down a
foundation. If I may, what you call the
Christ consciousness is from our
perspective the combined consciousness
of the totality of all the individuals
upon your planet. It knows itself as a
singular identity, but it also knows
itself as being made up of all the
consciousnesses upon your world.
Every single planet, every single
society, every single dimension of
consciousness has its own version of the
idea you call the Christ consciousness,
the collective soul, the world spirit.
In our ancient language, we called our
shakana. Our
shakana is what occurred, what
manifested in our world, but did not
need, did not require to manifest as a
full physiological lifespan. It existed
in physical form as a physical birth for
approximately what you would call three
days of your counting. Within those
three days, because we were already to
some degree susceptible to intermental
linkup, the added momentum of the
combined consciousness focusing in that
way upon our planet created a surge of
mental linkup throughout the entire
world. And in a sense, we went into a
daydream, a waking dream. And the entire
world woke up three days later with a
new understanding of our ability to
expand beyond what we had understood
before. I do not mean anything
derogatory of by what I am about to say.
In no way, shape or form is this an
invalidation of the way you have done
things. But to put it most simply, when
we were presented with a reflection of
the collective consciousness of our
world spirit, we
listened. That is all there is to it. It
woke us up and everything we have
created from that point forward was
possible because we started to function
as a unit. Functioning as a unit in no
way, shape or form, contrary to what
many of you have been taught to believe,
invalidates individual identity. In
fact, just the opposite. It strengthens
it. Each of us became the strongest
individual we could possibly conceive of
ourselves becoming. And in becoming the
strongest component, the strongest
individual we could become. That
strengthened the whole and allowed us to
function as a unit to be literally in
love with each and every being upon our
planet. and understand that the way to
truly expand our reality was to be in
love with all of creation, including
your civilization. Which is why we are
very eager to communicate with you. When
certain changes take place upon your
planet to make that more conducive, then
nothing nothing will hold us back from
nothing will hold us back from
interacting with you in very blatant
ways. But let me say this, it is not in
any way, shape or form critical that
your society interacts with us. That is
not the end all be all of the idea of
why we are communicating with you. We
are not the most important thing. You
are on your world, your planet is the
most important thing to you. And when
you as a society, at the risk of
sounding preachy, begin to allow
yourselves to truly live up to your full
potential, you will cocreate with us a
vibrational frequency that will create a
middle ground, a meeting space in which
your frequency and our frequency can
come together in a compatible format.
You see, you must meet us halfway. The
dimension in which we exist from your
point of view is rather ethereal in
nature, rather dreamlike in nature. And
that's why it's actually simpler for us
to contact you through the aspect of
your consciousness rather than
physically materializing in your world.
It can be done and it has been done, but
it is actually not as easy to do because
we have to lower our vibration so far.
We have to solidify ourselves so far in
order to materialize in your planet that
it's actually easier to touch you on a
mental level first because that is where
you are closest to the frequency in
which we naturally exist. What to us is
our physical solid material reality. To
you are the stuff dreams are made
of. Does that suffice as an answer? Oh,
thank you very much for your sharing.
Yes.
The idea to put it very simply and
concisely is that once again we are
telepathic. So a number of thoughts are
always being fed a number of
informationational bits shall we say are
always being fed into the minds of all
individuals that are willing to access
that stream of consciousness. There
really is no formal education in that
sense. an individual will attract
themselves to whatever endeavors they
truly are most interested in. So to put
it in your terminology, the majority of
individuals in our society learn by
doing. They learn, as you say, on the
job by simply attracting themselves to
the environment that represents what
they're interested in and allowing the
individuals in that environment to teach
them what they need to know. the
individuals in that environment are
always more than willing to take the
time to share their knowledge with that
individual because they know that
there's no way that individual would
have wound up on their doorstep had it
not been an individual that would become
one of them. So they always want to
instill within that individual whatever
knowledge they need to know. They take
them as you say under their wing and
tutor them until that individual feels
they have received a sufficient amount
of information to satisfy their
curiosity. There really is no formal
structure. Now and then there are
organizations that occur for specific
trainings that may be necessary. One of
those organizations or associations is
responsible specifically for my ability
to be able to communicate with your
civilization at this time. The idea that
we contact many civilizations means
there are many modes of thought and to
some degree some training is necessary
to allow one to become acclimatized so
to speak to the different ways in which
different alien societies do
think. Without that training and without
certain other tools to assist us, I
would be far too alien and you would be
far too alien for us to have a
meaningful communication. One of the
other things that we do that prepares us
to be able to communicate with other
societies, going back to the issue of
reincarnation, is to have at some point
a life in that society so that we can
build up a framework in our own
incarnational history that allows us to
draw upon that framework later on to use
it as a model, a reference point so that
the society we then interact with isn't
so alien because we have had at least
one light in that society to which we
can relate. That is the situation that
is going on here before you for I am as
I have said the channel's future self.
This physical channel before you is the
one past life I have had on your planet
so that I could create a frame of
reference through which I could
communicate with you more easily than
coming in as you say
raw. Understand?
Is that sufficient?
Thank you, Bashar. Perhaps perhaps it
might be good for us to take a break
now. We're all brimming with questions
and the audience hasn't really had a
chance to ask you a question. All right.
So, uh then you may enjoy your break. We
will resume contact in this fashion in
approximately what you would call 15 of
Everybody will remain very quiet.
How's everything going?
Good day. It's nice to see you again for
the first time. Oh, thank you very much.
Um, I am very concerned about the uh
aspect of toxic waste on this planet at
this time and I'd like any advice or
information that you could give us on
what might be appropriate ways that we
could either neutralize or clean up
safely this waste. Thank you. Now many
of you already recognize that certain
forms of energy already exist upon your
planet specifically with regard to the
electromagnetic field of your planet
that can be as you say
tapped in nonpolluting methodologies to
supply all the power you need for every
endeavor that you could possibly
imagine. Since you have already decided
to create certain technologies that have
as you say detrimental
byproducts, there are a few ideas that
can be done to alleviate some of that
concern. One we have discussed before.
You will find that some individuals as
we perceive the energy of your
consciousness now on your planet are
beginning to discover, are beginning to
explore, are beginning to investigate
certain polymer materials, plastic
materials that will actually have the
ability to molecularly bond with the
residue given off by the toxic waste and
will be able to form some sort of
containment, some sort of absorption.
ion containment process so that the
toxicity and we are talking about
radioactivity specifically will no
longer pass beyond that barrier. These
polymers may exist within your society
within what you call the next 15 of your
years as we read the energy now of your
technological evolution. Of course, you
can also create electromagnetic bubbles
around such substances to isolate them.
And certain types of electromagnetic
bubbles can actually change some of the
molecular composition of that material
and render it at least neutral if not
actually usable in your terminology.
However, when the vibrational rate, the
vibrational frequency of each and every
individual upon your planet accelerates
to a higher state, then some of the
substances that you have created at your
lower frequency will also simply no
longer have an effect upon your
corporeal forms, upon your bodies
because they will be of another reality
level, another frequency level, and will
not be able to create an effect in a
physical ical reality that no longer
relates or shall we say is no longer
synchronized with the former reality in
which those substances were created. You
can truly create a separation of
universes so that the old substances
will no longer affect you physically
because you'll be operating on a
different plane entirely. However, you
will no longer, as we have said, need to
create such substances anymore when your
society allows itself to realize that
all the power you need, all the
technology you can invent can be based
upon electromagnetic or gravitic
principles, and that that will be
sufficient for any endeavor you would
wish to create, and then you will no
longer create any toxic byproducts or
radioactive byproducts from that point
forward. Now many individuals have been
experimenting and exploring with this
idea of electromagnetic utilization for
quite some time. But because of the way
you have structured your society's
interests, some of that experimentation
has been suppressed simply because it
does not serve the interests of the
individuals that control your technology
at this time. Once those barriers are
listed, many individuals will come to
understand that certain methodologies do
exist and have existed some for decades
of your time of counting that would
alleviate all of what you would call
your power problems. Does that answer
the question sufficiently? U is there
any way that you could tell us of how to
produce those electromagnetic bubbles
and what frequency it is? You do not
have the technology at this time. The
idea of the polymers we can be perhaps
of a little more assistance with. We can
point you in certain directions but only
point you we cannot give you the entire
idea. A because some of your technology
has not yet been decided on. Therefore,
we cannot predict such a thing with
absolute certainty because your future
is still in flux about what it is you
will discover and B because some of
these things you must be allowed to
discover yourself. We cannot necessarily
remove the process of discovery from you
in that sense. However, it is our
perception that
individuals who are exploring and
experimenting with certain types of molecular
with certain types of molecular
arrangements in
polymers that
simulate certain biochemical
certain biochemical
processes in the body. certain
biochemical arrangements in your human
bodies within what you would call the
DNA and RNA structures will be closest
to the mark. In a sense, what we are
saying is that these polymers, to use
that term very loosely, will be
almost bioorganic in nature and will to some
bioorganic in nature and will to some
degree contain an
affinity, shall we say, an affinity to
certain heavier elements. And in
absorbing those heavier elements into
their structure, we'll set up a matrix,
a certain type of magnetic
matrix. One moment, one
moment. A certain type of magnetic
matrix that will actually create a type
of polarized effect for the particles
that will be absorbed by the polymer. In
other words, the particle will strike
the polymer. Let's say a radioactive
polymer particle will be absorbed on one
side of the barrier. Something will be
released on the other side of the
barrier, but it will be polarized in a
way you have not seen polarization yet.
The new polarized particle will be
harmless to your species, but it will
still exist. In a sense, it will be
pollution of another type, but one that
is not harmful to
you. All we can do at this time is
describe this basic mechanism. At this
time, the knowledge is not available to
us to understand more specifically
exactly how this mechanism will be
created in terms of your
technology. Thank you,
Sharing. Hello, Bashar. And to your good day.
Hello, Bashar. And to your good day.
This question concerns my life and the
nondirection it's taking at the present
time. Nondirection? Well, even that is a
direction. Um, what do you wish it to be?
Um, what do you wish it to be?
Most of my life, life just sort of
happened to me. Ever since I've been on
my so-called spiritual path and growth.
Yes. Ever since that's happened, my life
has slowly gone downhill, it seems, on
the surface. Oh, all right. Sometimes
you go faster that way.
And I've been learning about trying to
learn about intuition and learning to
follow the joy. All right. You mean the
excitement? What excites you the most?
Yes. All right. May I ask you a personal
question? You certainly. Oh, thank you
very much.
What makes it difficult for you to
follow? What excites you? Do you not
trust it? That's part of my question.
Yes. Um, I so want to find a career path. One
Um, I so want to find a career path. One
moment. One moment. When we talk about
the idea of doing what excites you the
most, we do not necessarily mean that
you must have a cognition of the thing
that will be the most exciting thing you
will ever do in your entire life. We are
talking about living in the moment.
Keeping it in the moment, keeping it
present focused at any given moment. If
you do not have an idea of an overriding
career, at any given moment, you can
still be doing at that moment the thing
that excites you the most with all the
integrity you have at your disposal. Do
you understand? Yeah. Doing that step by
step, a step at a time, will always lure
you, always lure you into the
circumstances that represent the next
step you need to take to bring you an
automatic and effortless understanding
of what it is you could be doing. that
represents more and more of who you are.
We are talking physics here. This is not
simply some airy philosophy. When we say
do what excites you the most, we're not
just saying, "Oh, well, yes, have a good
time." We are, but that is not simply
being left on that level. We are talking
mechanics. We are talking physics
because the idea of what excites you the
most if I may digress for the purpose of
the rest of the individuals is that
excitement that knowingness of what
moves you is actually your physical
translation of the vibratory energy that
represents who and what you are. That's
what excitement is. Excitement tells you
what you are best capable of doing. If
something excites you, it excites you
for a reason. Excitement is the sign
many of you ask for. Who am I? What am I
supposed to do in life? What is my
mission in life? Give me a sign. Hey,
look at this exciting thing over here.
You could be doing this. Don't bother me
now. I'm busy looking for my purpose in
life. The thing that excites you the
most at that moment is your purpose in
life or something else would excite you.
There are no extraneous creations. No
accidental interactions. Whatever at any
given moment is the most exciting thing
you could imagine doing with all your
integrity is the path in its most
synchronistically unfolding manner.
Follow it. Do it. Trust it. It will
always lead you where you need to go to
give you the skills and the abilities
and the abundance necessary to do the
next most exciting thing or the next
most exciting step of the thing that
will come along. Also, many times
individuals will say, well, all right,
that's all well and good, but I really
would desire an overall career that
excites me and I just don't know what
that is. Many individuals know very very
very well what that is, but they have
been taught out of believing that what
they know they really want to do is a
valid way to make a living. So you shut
it down and pretend you don't know what
you really could be doing. Let me ask
you another personal question if I may.
May I? Tonight. Thank you very
much. without placing the judgment on
it, without invalidating it in any way,
shape or form, at this particular
moment, is there any one thing, no
matter what it is, no matter how silly
it may seem in the eyes of your society,
that actually would give you the most
joy in doing as a career. Oh, a career.
Oh, well. or if you wish just doing
what would give you the most joy. I
would probably just dance for free but I
know that's one moment. One moment. Let
me repeat
myself without
invalidation without
qualification. What would give you the
most joy? Are you saying dancing? I love
to dance. Well, thank you very much.
Could not have said it better myself. I
love to dance.
Is it the most exciting thing you can
imagine doing above and beyond anything
else? Yes. No. Probably in this moment. That's
Yes. No. Probably in this moment. That's
only the only thing that comes to my
mind. Do not qualify it. Of course, we
are talking about this moment right now.
Is it the most exciting thing you can
conceive of? Yes or no? That's it. Yes.
Yes. That's it. All right. Thank you
very much. Then right at this moment, as
long as you are focused on that idea
right now, you are a dancer. You are the
energy of a dancer. You are the
frequency of a dancer. And if you
continue to act like a dancer from this
moment forward, you will have the
lifestyle of a dancer and attract
automatically, automatically,
synchronistically, synchronistically and
effortlessly, effortlessly all the
circumstances and relationships that are
gerine to the life of a dancer to allow
you to take advantage of them so you can
continue to be the dancer you say right
now you are. Are you willing to act that
way though? That's the real question. Are
though? That's the real question. Are
you willing to act in the manner of what
you say really excites you? Knowing
beyond a shadow of a doubt that by
acting as if that really is the true
you, the universe will support you in
the doing of that thing. Are you willing
to believe that? Or do you doubt
yourself? There's probably a little bit of doubt
There's probably a little bit of doubt
there. No. All right. Let me remind you
of something else if I may. May I? Oh,
of course. Oh, thank you very
much. When we talk about infinite
trust, we are not talking about
something that is difficult to do. When
we say trust it
100%. Many times we hear a collective
psychic groan from many of you. Oh no,
that's real hard.
100% trust. Everyone knows. Everyone
knows how hard that
is. But you see, you have all always
trusted 100% in
100% in
something. What your society calls doubt
is not a lack of trust. It is an
absolute unshakable unswerving 100%
total conviction in a negative
reality. You always use trust 100%. It's
just a matter of whether you trust in
something you don't prefer or trust in
something you do prefer. Now, which do
you prefer to trust in?
What you do prefer or what you don't
prefer? Well, my mind says I would chooseh.
When I am at least for this moment
speaking to you, I am speaking to the
total you. If you now choose to
segregate yourself into a mind and a
conscious and a subconscious, you will
spin a game that will last for years as
many of you already do because you will
think you have to reconcile all these
different fragments of yourself that you
have created yourself to be. But you
have created these levels. I'll let you
in on a little secret which is no secret
at all. May I? Good.
You don't really have, none of you
actually really have an unconscious or a
subconscious mind. You are one
consciousness, one homogeneous idea.
What you call your soul, your spirit,
your higher consciousness, your lower
consciousness, your mind, your
mentality, your physical consciousness,
your subconsciousness, your
unconsciousness. All of these are simply
different convenient ways to avoid
looking at something you fear. That's
all it is. You are one consciousness
unbroken. You have created convenient
compartments into which you can place
things for some reason you have been
taught are dangerous to look
at. Why? It's only a portion of you.
There is absolutely nothing you could
ever discover about yourself that cannot
be applied in a positive way. Oh yes,
you can discover many things and apply
all of them in negative ways. But is
that what you prefer? Yes or no? If it's
no, then why not assume? You have just
as much power to
decide how to apply what you discover
about yourself.
just as much power to decide to do that
in the positive way as you have always
had in the negative way. You can apply
anything you discover in a negative or a
positive way. Why not choose to
understand that you only prefer to apply
it in a positive way and therefore you
will only get a positive result out of
that application. You cannot get cannot
get cannot get a negative result from a
cannot get a negative result from a
positive
application. Understand? You cannot
experience a reality you are not the
vibration of. If you have a reality you
don't prefer, then it's because you are
buying into a belief system that
supports that reality. It's as plain and
simple as that. It is absolute physics.
absolute mechanics. You have a saying
for it. What you put out is what you get
back. What goes in is what comes out.
You cannot get the opposite effect. You
can only get an equal and opposite
reaction. If you put a positive idea
out, positive preferential trust, you
can only get a positive reality back. If
you put a negative idea out, what you
call doubt, you can only get hesitation,
guilt, frustration, and all the other
symbols that your society has created to
represent negative
trust. Is this helping you at all? Yes.
Do you
believe? Are you at least willing to
consider the possibility of believing?
Yes. That if you act in the direction
fully act in the direction of the being
you say you want to be that you yourself
can be responsible for attracting the
things in your life that will support
you as that being and that that spiral
will continue
forever. Are you willing to believe that
that could be possible? Yes. Are you
willing to
believe that nothing is too good to be true?
that nothing is too good to be true?
Yes, I'm willing to believe that. All
right. Then discover what stops you from
believing it. Come to terms with what
that definition is that prevents you
from living that reality and reinvent,
redefine the reality you prefer to have.
You will get that reflection. I
guarantee it
100%. The universe keeps nothing from
you. Nothing. But the universe can only
give you what you say you're ready for.
If you do not believe you're ready to
handle the idea of success because you
are willing to buy into that it's got to
be a struggle or it's got to be a
striving, the universe will only give
you so much because obviously you're
telling the universe, I'm not ready for
it anymore. Please don't give it to me.
I am still creating a trust in a
negative reality. And when I have that
kind of a belief, I do not want these
things because I they will not manifest
in a positive way. Give them to me when
I choose to believe that I deserve a
positive reality. You do. You know, you
deserve anything you can conceive of
just because you have the ability to
conceive of it. You don't have to earn
the right to deserve
happiness. You already have that right
because you exist. Do you understand?
I hear you and I want to believe that.
All right. Why not?
Why don't I believe it presently? Yes.
What belief system would you have to buy
into that would reinforce your lack of
ability to believe that you deserve
everything? Probably just feelings of unworthiness.
Probably just feelings of unworthiness.
All right. May I ask you a question?
Yes. Did you have to do anything special
in order to deserve to exist?
No, not that I know of. All right, then
why not assume that because you do
exist, infinite creation obviously
believes that you deserve it. Otherwise,
you wouldn't. So why not treat yourself
with the same
respect? Understand? Sleep on it. Thank you.
Understand? Sleep on it. Thank you.
Thank you, Bashar. Next sharing.
Greetings and excitement to you, Bashar.
and to you good day.
I've discovered in the past couple of
years that uh my ego was very
ineffective at running my life. I
noticed whenever I turned things over to
it, it was, you know, it didn't
appreciate it and it mucked things up.
Muk mukmuck messed them up. Mukm. Okay.
Not a good job. Um a perfect job of a
negative reality you don't prefer.
However, absolutely not. And it keeps
showing up for me. Keep showing up. Yes.
Uh, what I'm wondering is if you have
any suggestions for a game I can play, a
meditation I can use, or some dance I
can do that will lighten my lighten up
my relationship to my ego or give it
something to do so I can get on with
what I want to be doing. Oh, now one
moment. One moment. It is not something
that you have to shove out of the way,
you know, right? You must function as an
integrated being to get what you prefer.
You cannot dissect yourself and remove
the offending portion of consciousness.
You cannot give it busy work to keep it
occupied. It will eventually discover
that and resent you all the more.
The idea is to truly form an equal
alliance with it and let it do the job
it was constructed to do, which is to
keep you focused in the physical reality
you chose to be focused in and to be the
representative of what you simply call
your conscious decisionmaking
capability. to be clear as a reasoning
being. Allow it to do that job and
understand that it is in your terms a
part of a whole idea. It is not to be
cast aside. You as a whole being function
aside. You as a whole being function
flawlessly. If however you have been
taught to assume that the ego must run
everything, that is what gets you into
trouble. In a sense, the ego was not
designed to run everything. And that is
why in your terminology it fumbles the
ball. It simply is designed to do
certain ideas to bring you to certain
recognitions to give you certain amounts
of focus. Let it do that job. The only
reason that the ego is overburdened with
more than its share is because perhaps
of ideas within you that you fear to
take full responsibility for the
creations in your life. that you fear in
that sense to allow yourself to delve
fully into certain things because you
think there is going to be some sort of
idea some sort of negative reaction by
delving into that by exploring this
particular aspect or that particular
aspect. Are you following me so far?
Absolutely. I'll ask you and all of you keep this in
I'll ask you and all of you keep this in
mind as each and every one of you begins
an interaction with us. Ask yourself
always, are you doing what excites you
the most? Many times all of these
complications and all of these
imbalances of ego structure and feeling
and emotion are simply the product of
not allowing yourself to be who you
really know you are by trying to be
something you're not. By living up to
everyone else's
expectations. Who are you? Who do you
want to
be? And can you allow yourself to
believe that whoever it is you discover
you are can fit in the universe as it
is. Ask yourself, are you doing what
excites you the most? Yes or no? Yes, I
am. And what what what what is that? What I
And what what what what is that? What I
am doing is exchanging information and
learning from people who come into my
home. You know, we're studying spiritual
ideas together. I'm a nurse and I'm
transforming my nursing into spiritual
experiences for people. All right. In
your definitional terms, can you name a
specific way you say your ego structure
gets out of hand? I'm sorry, I'm not
clear on the question. All right. You
have said you feel that from time to
time your ego runs away, creates an
imbalance. Yes. Yes. Can you describe in
a specific instance how that might
occur? I talk too much. I I run, you
know, I talk too much and don't listen
enough. Are you saying that therefore
you believe that you must try very hard
to convince other people of something?
Um, not sure. Just maybe that I think my
ideas are more important than more
important. All right. Do you understand
that if you truly believe that your idea
had power, you wouldn't have to say a
thing? I understand that on a cognitive
level. Cognitive level. You understand
the principle that in a sense, the more
you talk, the more you're simply trying
to convince yourself of what you think
you believe. Yes, I'm clear about that.
All right.
Now, whatever it is you have come to
believe, whatever cognitions you have
made are absolutely valid for you. In
whatever way you share those cognitions
with other individuals, it is an
offering, a
gift. No one needs to take it. I'm sure
you realize that. Yes.
The idea simply is allow yourself to
relax into this recognition, a
recognition of synchronicity. No one, no
one comes into your life before or after
they are ready to. You enter no one
else's life at an inopportune timing.
All timing is flawless, perfect, and
absolutely representative of whoever it
is. all the individuals in that meeting
are at that given moment. So you don't
have to rush through anything. You don't
have to try to convince anyone of
anything. You wouldn't be together if
they didn't have something to learn from
you and if you didn't have something to
learn from them. Allow yourself to stand
back. Here's your meditation. And truly
observe the reflections that are going
back and forth. See what it is you are
doing as a service for each other. What
is it they are learning from you? What
is it they are seeing about themselves
by looking at you that they need to see?
What is it you are seeing about yourself
in them that you need to see to learn
who you want to be? Stand back from the
idea of communication in the way you're
used to looking at it and understand
that the relationship of you and any
other being is not two different
separate ideas but one whole event of
which you and the other people are
reflections. Let yourself see what the
whole event is and let the relationship
be what it is for not what you think it
ought to be. Thank you. Understand? Yes.
Does that help you very much? Also allow
yourself if you have not already done so
to call upon your guides when you are in
meditative state. Let yourself begin to
feel communication. It does not all have
to be cerebral. Let yourself truly feel
the pattern. Feel the orchestration and
the momentum of the relationship you are
in. You will instinctively know what to
do. understand something very critical
in any form of art which is what
communication is all about. It isn't
really so much what you put in. It's
what you leave out that makes the
statement clear. Understand? Yes. Now
that does not mean that you hide things.
But when you deliver a
message, the idea of what is there is
very profoundly affected by the things
that are implied around it. Rather than
bludgeoning the idea to death by
thinking you have to define every single
detail, people will get it. They're very
intelligent, just as intelligent as you
because you have attracted them in your
life. Are they not reflections of your
own understanding?
Yes. It's exciting. Yes. Thank you very
much. Thank you Bashar. Shouting.
Hi Bashar. And good day to you. Can you
tell me I'm asking for my sister who
couldn't make it when the soul actually
enters the body? There are variations to
that theme. There is a portion of what
you would recognize as soul
consciousness from the moment of
conception. However, what you call the
persona, the person aspect of the soul,
actually does not enter until just prior
to physiological birth. And sometimes,
not even does it lock in tightly up till
the idea you call 3 years of physical
age. It can come and go any time within
there. It is a very loose structure up
to that time. It is analogous to the
idea we described earlier in our
civilization of a child locking in its
frequency at age three to that
civilization. But what you would term
the soul personality actually does not
really shall we say align itself to the
physical body until just prior to birth.
For you see it is an aspect in many
cases of that soul to assist and aid the
parent in its own birth. And it can do
that more easily as a non-corporeal
form. You understand? Sure. So any
individual giving birth, by all means,
you do not have to feel like you're
bearing the brunt of that idea upon your
own shoulders alone. Call upon the
assistance of the child you are giving
birth to. Remember that in that state
now as a non-physical being, it isn't a
child yet.
Does that help you? Sure it does. Does
that change? Like can one soul actually
decide to go into to become a baby and
then that different souls interact in
that? I mean what I'm asking
is can it like one soul decides to
interact to go into one mother and then
maybe another soul decides to to go into
that one also? Do you do you see what
I'm saying? Like can there be a change
like one decides to this to be the
mother and then that switch over and it
be somebody else? Yes. You mean in
different lifetimes?
Uh no actually I was thinking before
birth if ah ah ah we understand right it
can occur. Yes it is possible. Okay. All
things happen by agreement and by
arrangement. And if such an arrangement
would fulfill the needs of the
experiences of those souls in physical
reality then it can occur. What was
formerly in your terminology the focus
of the mother consciousness can actually
become its own child. and one was
previously the child can become the
mother. Yes, thank you very much.
Everything is malleable wherein the
dimension of imagination is concerned
and remember the dimension of
imagination is responsible for creating
what you call solid reality. It is all
malleable and flexible. Thank you very
much. Next sharing.
Hello Bashar and to you. Good day. Okay.
I don't know if you can hear me. I guess
um my question has kind of a two-part.
All right, speak up so that all may
share. Be bold. All right, there we go.
Okay, the first part is, what is the
correlation between death and an out-of-
body experience? Very similar, except
once again, you have not completely
removed your focus from the physical
plane in what you would call an astral
projection or out-of body experience.
You are expanding your consciousness,
shall we say, temporarily, into very
much the same realm that you enter when
you quote unquote die.
Okay. My other question is more
personal. I believe I have what is
considered an out-of- body experience. I
have had that. All right. All of you do,
you know. It's just that many of you do
not retain conscious awareness of it.
Yeah. It was um actually very
fascinating for me. It's happened more
than once. Yes. And it has occurred
usually in a situation where I am a a
nurse and I have been dealing with a
person who has been very close to death.
All right. Um, I kind of want to know
one, is there a correlation between
their death experiences and my
experiences? Oh, absolutely. Absolutely.
Let us answer that first. You see, there
are already many beings on what you
would call the other side that assist
individuals in their deaf transition
into the non-physical reality. Your
planet is now learning that it can also
train individuals while still physical
to assist them in going across to the
non-physical reality. And some of the
individuals who will best accomplish aid
in that direction will be those that can
astrally project so they can literally
take the soul by the hand, so to speak,
and say, "Look, this is where you're
going. Everything's just fine. You're
still alive. Have a good time." Yeah.
Well, that's basically what I've done
during those experiences. Um the other
thing that I found interesting and I it
was more of a physical sensation. I
thought maybe you can explain it. All
right. Maybe. Um my instructor Kramer
had talked about there being a pinhole
in the head where your soul is can lead
in a sense. Yes. It is called in a sense
a black hole. A type of gateway. It
resides in the corpus colosum between
the hemispheres of the brain. Okay. I
have experienced a sensation of when I
had this out-of body experience of all
my blood kind of rushing towards the
center of my chest not towards my head.
Understood. I um the sensation was
something I have never could never
really understand and so I thought maybe
you might clarify. Thank you. Even
though the idea of what you call that
pinpoint exists in the corpus colossum
of the brain remember that every single
gate of your body what many of you have
called chakras exist in many portions of
your body and are all intertwined and
interconnected. What you call the chest
region is not only the energy of the
heart, the idea of opening your
emotional self, but in the solar plexus
is what you call the chakra of
intention, the chakra of focus and the
one that leads most directly along a
conduit, shall we say, of energy to your
future self, your self of conviction. So
you may feel a buildup in that area
because the more conviction you have,
the more certainty you have, the more
boldness you exhibit, you will feel the
energy rush in that area. When you align
with that area, when you align all your
chakra gates, you may feel that
pinpoint, that gate at any place in your
body, but the primary one exists in the
center of your brain. Okay? Space and
time do not have that much meaning when
that alignment occurs. The idea that
many of your people have described upon
death or astral projection of the going
through the tunnel with the light at the
end is your physiological analogy of
going through that gate, that pinpoint
structure into a new dimension of
experience. Okay. Thank you. Pleasant dreams to you.
Okay. Thank you. Pleasant dreams to you.
Sharing.
Good evening, Bashar. And to you, good
day. Thank you for being here with us
tonight. Oh, thank you for being there.
Um, some of us at Speak up. Speak up so
that all may share. Be bold. Some of us
at some time or another um experience a
great deal of pain and sorrow. Yes. When
someone is taken from us in death, we
understand. I wonder if you could
enlighten me a bit. In the next life
when our souls go on over, is it
possible for us to identify those that
have gone on? Yes. But there are also
many many circumstances that define
these types of interactions and types of
meaning. Now I will use an analogy.
Understand that it may not be directly
applicable to your situation but you
will take the gist of my meaning. Many
individuals because of the type of
mythology you have been brought up with
believe that when an individual dies
they have nothing better to do than hang
around waiting for you to contact them.
They are very busy. They still have
lives to live, things to learn, places
to go and people to see. As you say,
they are now wrapped up in the job of
learning about their new environment.
They are expanding in different ways. A
portion of their consciousness is always
available to be contacted by you,
whether you are still physical or not.
However, it may not be what you
previously recognized as the actual
persona you used to know in that
particular life that you wind up
contacting. These are very arbitrary
things, very very fuzzy definitions of
one particular manifestation and another
particular manifestation. Where does
this persona begin and another persona
end? Where do they all blend within the
oversoul that any individual is created
from? You can always contact that
particular person if you wish to, but it
may not be in the way you used to know
them that you're actually contacting
them. You may not actually be calling up
exactly what the persona used to be.
Some representation will be there and it
will be just as real as anything, but it
may not necessarily be the same type of
person that you used to know in physical
reality. There may be many changes. Many
individuals in different lives catch up
to each other or make agreements to live
different lives together and orbit
around each other and dance around each
other in many different ways, taking
turns being different things to
different people at different times. All
right. Now, I'll be the father and you
be the daughter. Next time you be the
father and I'll be the daughter. You can
catch up to each other in a variety of
ways. Or you can allow yourself
communication while you are physical,
they are non-physical. But remember, you
operate on very different frequencies
now. And in all reality, there is
actually some degree of difficulty for
someone who is now focused in
non-physical reality to learn to refocus
down to the pinpoint tunnel vision type
of reality that your physical reality
represents. They are so much more
expanded now that it's actually
difficult for them to as you say get a
handle on exactly where you are and who
you are because from that point of view
they see you as more than you see
yourself and they may have communication
going on with many different aspects of
your consciousness that you as the you
are here is unaware of. Is any of this
clarifying the situation or is it
becoming too complex? It's a bit
complex. I um need to know also if we
are at somewhat the same level as they
are at that time and place that we will
be able to identify and perhaps have an
understanding of nature. Remember this
each and every one of you already exists
on every level there is to exist upon.
The idea of going from level to level is
not so much the process of actually
going there but remembering that you
actually are already there. Does that
help? Yes. Thank you. Thank you very
much. Next sharing.
Hi Bashar. And to you. Good day. Is your
planet populated entirely by females?
No, just the brave one. Oh, all right.
Okay. My question is um with all of this
unfound energy that we all have um is is
Oh, one moment. One moment. Do not mean
to interrupt you. I understand what you
mean, but it is not unfound. You are
using all of your energy at every given
moment. Even if you're using 90% of it
to make it seem as if you're only using
10. That's good. That's
good. Okay. Okay. Then with this energy,
my question is, is it true that we have
the power with our energy to heal other
people physically and to give them a
sense of well-being? In a sense, yes.
You can create a type of magnetic
envelope in which another individual may
find it conducive to allow themselves to
go back to their natural state of
health. In a sense, that's what a healer
does. provide an atmosphere, an
electromagnetic environment that makes
it possible, more probable for someone
else to want to align with that
vibration and that vibration is
therefore representative of what their
natural state of health is. You follow
me? Yes, I do. Does that answer the
question sufficiently? Could I ask one
more short one? Yes. Um, is there a very
quick and simple way for us to be able
to initiate that unconditional love? as
much of it as you can muster, as much
sharing as you can do, living the life
that is truly representative of who you
are. It will inevitably rub off where it
needs to. Thank you. That's Thank you
very much. Sharing. Hello, the shark.
And to you, good day. I want to
sincerely thank you for sharing with us
tonight. We thank you for the same. I
have a question concerning preparation
with interaction with other entities.
Yes. I'd like to know uh specifically uh
should we protect ourselves in any way
in saying should I be concerned about
entities that really have harmful
intentions or not good intentions? Thank
you. Now we are not saying that there
are not consciousnesses that exist in
various levels in various plains that do
not have the best of intentions for
there are many degrees of consciousness
both positive and negative. However, let
me describe the paradox of what you are
talking about. When you create yourself to be,
about. When you create yourself to be,
the frequency or the vibration of their
reality is when they are most easily
able to align with you, the negative
side. When you create your vibration to
be of a positive nature, only a positive
vibrational consciousness can align with
you. The paradox is is that when an
individual fears that they need to
protect themsel from something negative,
the fear itself creates the vibration
that attracts the negative
consciousness. You understand? I
understand. Therefore, if you simply say
to yourself with all the conscious
commandment you can
muster, what I am doing, I am choosing
to do for a positive loving reason. I
know this is so because I say this is
so. And all the experiences I will have
in my life are all channeled into
allowing me to know that it is so for a
positive loving reason. When you know
that and you know you're on that
frequency, nothing that is not the
vibration of that reality can possibly
touch you. They cannot even find you.
You are invisible to them. You
understand? I understand. Does that help
you? That's what I thought. I needed to
make sure. Thank you. All right. Are you
sure now? I'm sure. Thank you. Thank you
very much.
Sharing. Yes. There are more than females. Oh,
Yes. There are more than females. Oh,
thank you very
much. Although, of course, everyone has
both sides. I agree. Um, I would like to
briefly respond to your question of the
uh issue of deservability. Yes. uh with
what little information I have gathered
on the the idea um and that is uh one of
um guilt guilt and that everyone
experiences um a guilt uh similar to what's referred
um a guilt uh similar to what's referred
to as the original sin. We understand
the concept the separation from father
or from god uh the the taking um doing
things uh of one's own valition and the
the guilt for doing that we have a
particular definition of guilt may I
share it with all of you please do guilt
not hate is the true opposite of
love hate is a
polarized have a particular Definition
of guilt. May I share it with all of
you? Please do. Guilt, not hate, is the
true opposite of
love. Hate is a polarized expression of
love, but still implies deservability,
even if it's only
self-deservability. Guilt being the lack
of deservability, is truly the opposite
of love, which is absolute validity and
equality of all. Therefore, yes, the
idea, the vibration you call guilt is a
self cutting off from the source of
infinite creation. Now, you're never
really cut off from it. You can't be.
But you can create the illusion, as you
have pointed out, that it is. So, when
an individual learns that unconditional
love of self, of all that is, is the
most positive direction they can flow
in, then they recognize there is no need
for guilt. because guilt is only a
denial of one's own existence.
Thank you. My question is
um of education. What can you suggest uh
that we do in our current situation to
improve the methods with which we
educate our children etc.? Yes.
Imagination is the key. The idea of
allowing individuals to do, to act, to
be, to involve themselves, to use all
the senses rather than being restricted
in that use of imagination and fed a
number of formula which do not
necessarily relate to the world of their
interest. Allow all the things that need
to be learned to be translated in
terminologies that befit the interest of
each and every individual and they will
in your terms gobble the information up
voraciously. Thank you. Thank you very
Thank you. Thank you very
much sharing. Hello Vashar. And to you
good day. Good day to you too. Speak up.
Speak up so that all may share. Thank
you. I was wondering uh you mentioned
your planet. I was wonder I was
wondering if there's a possibility of a
human at this time as humans no time of
visiting your planet and what technique
we would use only in astral form.
And what technique would you suggest to
get there to change our frequency so
that we could be with you? Do you mean
physiologically or astrally?
or astrally?
Astrally. Allow yourself when you are
lying down in your meditative states to
close your
eyes. Think of the vibration you are
feeling now that I represent to you.
When you think of my identity, you will
automatically be keying into the
frequency of our civilization.
An abstract form that can assist you is
also to think of a threesided
tetrahedral structure outlined in
electromagnetic blue white light that
will also align you to our
frequency. Thinking of my identity will
allow you when you simply let yourself
flow to flow in the direction of our
dimensional vibration. It is as simple
as that. Many times, many of you do
visit our dimension in astral form. But
when you wake up in your physiological
reality, you bring back with you the
remnants of a dream that may or may not
have made sense to you because there may
be many aspects of your own
physiological consciousness that may not
be able to relate or need to relate to
some of the things that you did when you
were out of your body. So you may not
necessarily carry a literal memory of
your interaction with us, but you will
carry back a symbolic one at least that
will contain the symbols necessary for
you to be able to apply in your reality
whatever it is you experienced and or
learned and or shared in the other
reality. But that is all you need to do.
Think about us and you automatically
align yourself like a dial on your radio
to our frequency. That's all you need to
do to attract yourself astrally to
anyone. Think about them and the
thinking about them aligns your
vibration to identify with them and
draws you there. That's it. Thank you.
Well, thank you very much for thinking
of us. Sharing. Good evening, Bashar.
And who you good day. You've given us
such a wealth of information tonight. I
think the human mind is overloaded. So,
I've got a simple question for you. All
right. Uh in the very recent past, I was
Uh in the very recent past, I was
involved in what you call channeling.
Yes. With a personage that was a
uh ship commander, such as yourself, a
very small ship. It was in the Earth's
atmosphere. All right. He was known to
me as uh Commander
Jargo. Have you ever had any knowledge
of him or any relationship with him? One
moment. One
moment. Do understand. We do not keep
tabs, as you say, on every single ship
coming and going. I would hope not. I
would hope not.
The terminology you are referring to as
a name is not familiar, but the
vibration we are picking up upon is as
follows. There seems to be a connection
with this level of consciousness you
have referred to to past incarnations of
your own self all the way back to what
you would call Atalantean or Leamuran
times that have now associated
themselves with certain extraterrestrial
levels of consciousness and have now
reintroduced themselves into your earth
plain to allow the rest of its
consciousness to shall we say catch up.
It is to some degree a specific
connection within your energy family,
your soul family. And it has to do with
certain past recognition, certain past
understandings in some ancient
civilizations upon your planet that it
is now time in a sense to catch up to
and exemplify on the surface of your
planet now in your society. In other
words, time to reinvent or rebirth some
of the same principles that were lived
back then. That is what this particular
focus of consciousness you have referred
to is awakening within you at least from
our point of view. So in a sense to put
it simply you are crossing a time stream
of another you but one that is very
strongly associated to past
civilizations and now in making a
connection to extraterrestrial
consciousness seems to be coming to you
from a future idea. But this is only an
echo, only a rebound of where it is
actually originating from. Does this
help you? Well, not really. Uh I do have
uh photographic records of uh Commander
Jargo ship on three three different
occasions. Yes.
Um and he was very real at his one
moment. I did not say he was not. Uhhuh.
I simply gave you an interpretation from
our point of view of where the vibration
of that consciousness originates from.
how it is connected to you. It is
connected associated to your energy
through a past life in what you would
call the ancient civilizations of
Atlantis and
Lamoria more strongly than it is
connected to you right now through any
extraterrestrial connections you might
have because the things that you knew in
those ancient lives are some of the
things you have to remember now. And
therefore that is why the connection is
most strongly resonating through those
past civilizations rather than so
directly as an extraterrestrial idea. It
represents itself extraterrestrially
because it has made that association.
But what it is awakening within you are
certain past memories that can now come
to fruition on the surface of your
planet depending upon what you do with
the memories that you have.
Does this make more sense? Yes. Thank
you. Thank you very much. Good night.
sharing. Good evening, Bashar and to you. Good
Good evening, Bashar and to you. Good
day. Thank you for being here. Thank you
once again for being there. Um, I had an
experience in the beginning of February
where I went away for 3 days on vacation
and my right arm began an involuntary
jerking. All right. And it tingled up
through my arm and sort of tickled.
Um, on the third night when I got home
at about
10:00, my
arm was doing that a lot and I was
giggling with my husband and my daughter
and all of a sudden I left my body in a
spiral. And I was still over my body. I could
And I was still over my body. I could
see my husband screaming out of fear. My
I turn my whole body fell to the ground
and I was completely stiff as if I died.
How exciting. Did you have a good time?
Yeah, I did. Although when I woke up I
was in a in a ambulance and everybody
thought I had died and there was a lot
of fear around. Yes. And therefore it is
not seen as natural yet as normal yet
but it will be right. I
actually took on that fear and
why? I don't know. I Oh, yes, you do.
But to go on with it,
um I moved on. I left LA. I did a whole
bunch of crazy things and changed my
life. And crazy things. All right. Yeah.
And um felt an energy coming in my body
every night at the same time. Yes. The
vibration of the energy was much much
higher than mine. And
therefore I began to study about it and
began to see channels like Mafu and Rama
and and just to take a look if if that's
what it is for me. I feel like it is.
All right. What do you want to do with
it? I don't know. And when I'm in the
energy, it's as if to be in an energy
field and it feels very frightening
because I don't know what to do with it.
It's so big.
All right. All right. May I ask a
question? Yes, please. Thank you very
much. Do you really honestly believe you
could ever attract anything in your life
that's truly more than you could handle
at any given moment? No. Then what are
you afraid of? I don't know. I It's It's
as if Yes. Yes. It's the most foreign
thing I've ever had. Foreign. All right,
let it be foreign. Does it have to be
frightening just because it is foreign?
Okay. This is what I'm frightened of.
Oh, thank you. What I'm frightened of is
is to be pulled out of my body in the
experience I had.
I realized I went through resent me
resentment with that because I was
frightened because I was taken so to
speak without my permission. Although I
know I gave permission, I do realize
that you may not remember that yet. I
understand that is what causes the fear.
I believe that I the sooner one moment.
Yes. The sooner you allow yourself to
begin to know you did create the
permission, the sooner you can relax and
the sooner you will remember having done
so. I believe that strongly and I have
come to do that. It's I believe
sometimes that my deepest fear is to be
in a hospital and people think I'm dying
again. That comes up a lot. Um when the
energy is in my body and moment excuse
me for the constant interruption. No.
When you say your deepest fear is to
wake up in your hospital and all people
are around you afraid you have died, are
you saying you are taking responsibility
for their reactions?
No. I think what I'm scared of is having
needles put in my arm, which they did,
and having cat scans, etc., thinking
that I was dying. All right. Can you now
create a reality now that you know more
of what is going on? Can you now know
that you can create a reality where that
does not need to happen that way
anymore? because you simply have used
that symbol, you've used that tool,
you've used that circumstance and
situation. If you're willing to learn
from it what you need to learn and stop
being afraid of it, you then give
yourself more ability to create the
situation to continue in a manner that
is more pleasing and preferential to
you. You understand? You're not out of
control. I Yes. Um Yes, very much so.
I've I've been working with that and
with myself
how hard Yeah. How hard have you been
working hard? Oh, no. All right. It's
been enjoyable work because Oh, very
good. I'm searching something that's not
known to me. Although I still get such a
sensation in my arm almost every night.
That's all right. It is simply
electromagnetic acclimatization.
Sometimes it wakes me up and I'm I lay
there in and my body is vibrating and I
think to myself, yes, am I making up
that this is fear or is this real or All
right. All right. One moment. One
moment. Remember this if you care to.
Excitement and
anxiety are the same energy. One from a
positive point of view, one from a
negative point of view. So when you feel
that energy, if you say, "Oh joy," it
will take you in a positive direction.
If you say, "Oh no," it will take you in
a negative one. You call the shots. The
energy is neutral.
understand very much so. You are in the
driver's seat. You decide where it will
go. Oh, Joy. Oh, no. It's up to you.
Right. It's just your energy. That's
all. Mhm. I It's been very confronting
for me. Very good. Very wonderful times.
Very fright. I mean, every emotion in
the book. All right. Very good.
Experiencing all those emotions is what
will allow you to blend them all into an
overriding knowingness and calm, relaxed
state of awareness. Okay? You're doing
just fine. Don't worry. You are going
through a process that is quite typical
on your planet at this time. Yes, we
understand not many of you are familiar
with it, but it's been going on for
quite some time. It will continue for a
little while longer. And you are not out
of the ordinary in that sense. I believe
that. Remember that the whole process
you're all going through now is that you
are learning to unlock from being
normal. And finally learning to be
natural. And for many of you being natural is a
And for many of you being natural is a
very unnatural way to be.
So can I ask you if you would know if
there is an entity trying to or spirit
or soul trying to enter me my body and
no one is trying to enter your body. Let
me what they are making an attempt to do
is awaken you to more of yourself. Okay.
Do not resist your natural self. Assume
because you have decided to because you
have the conscious commandment to say so
that what is going on is going on for a
positive reason and know that that is
so. Okay. Then you will awaken in your
positive self clearly and consciously.
Relax. Relax. Enjoy it. All right. All
right. There are other consciousnesses.
Yes. But more importantly, there is also
you. Mhm. Thank you. Thank you. pleasant
dreams to
you and say hello for
us and sharing.
Hello Bashar. And do you good day? A lot
of the people this evening have talked
about fears that seem to be
blocking becoming who they are. Yes. Um
and what I would like to know for myself
and those who have mentioned this Yes.
What are some ways that we
can face those fears so that we can go
beyond them? Oh, thank you very much.
This is what your imagination is best
at. It's why you have an imagination.
Your imagination, first of all, will
tell you any methodology, any ritual,
any exercise that you need to work best
for you in doing anything you want.
That's why you have an imagination. Ask
your imagination first. What would be
the most creative and enjoyable way that
I could possibly create to face this
fear? Let your imagination show you what
would be an enjoyable way for you and
then act it out. That is the key. Act it
out. Physically act it out.
Fear is only being uncertain about
meeting another aspect of your own self.
There really is nothing
inherently fear causing in any
circumstance or situation that exists.
Only your belief that there is fear
creates the fearful situation. Nothing
is built into any circumstance that must
be inherently feared. Only your
definitions say that is so. So play the
imagination game, the definition game.
Ask yourself the following
question. What kind of a belief? What
kind of a definition would I have to
have in order to have this reaction to
this circumstance?
Find out what that definition is. Once
you have found out what that definition
is, ask yourself, what definition would
I prefer to believe with regard to this
circumstance? Then in the most
imaginative way you can using all your
senses and acting it out to the fullest,
find a way, invent a way, create a way
to replace the old
definition with the new
definition and see it, feel it, know you
have made a difference.
Then go on with your life acting as if
you know beyond a shadow of a doubt that
the new definition is in place. The new
reality is in place. And that's all
there is to it.
Remember all circumstances are
fundamentally neutral, blank, empty,
devoid of meaning. No
situation, no circumstance has builtin
meaning. They are neutral. You supply
the meaning based upon what you have
been taught to believe the meaning must
be. You see this and you say that's bad.
You see this and you say that's good.
These are subjective value judgments.
Yes, there is positive integrative and
negative segregative energy, but that
doesn't mean necessarily that the
situation automatically brings one or
the other of those things with it. Every
situation contains the ability to have
both positive or negative
manifestation. Whatever vibration you
are going in is the effect you get out.
Whatever meaning you give to the
situation that is fundamentally neutral
utterly determines the effect you get
out of it. Positive meaning in, positive
effect out, negative meaning in,
negative effect out. Once again, it is
simple physics, simple mechanics. And I
guarantee 100% that whatever you put in, whatever
100% that whatever you put in, whatever
meaning you give to a circumstance, no
matter how it appears or how you have
been taught to believe it appears on the
surface, whatever you give into it is
what you will get out of it. Even
if someone else comes into your life
with a negative intention toward you, if
you go into that relationship only
knowing that the only reality you can
get out of it is a positive one, that is
the only reality you will get out of it
regardless of their original intention.
Understand? Yes. Does that help you?
Yes, it does. Thank you. We thank you
very much at
this timing allow us to extend to each and
timing allow us to extend to each and
every one of you our deepest
appreciation in being allowed to
communicate with you in this way at this
time. We thank you for functioning as
representatives and ambassadors of your
society and allowing me to function as a
representative and an ambassador of
mine. Bit by bit, day by day, such
interactions will co-create a conducive
atmosphere in which we can meet as
equals face to face, in which we can
share, enjoy, and love in the
exploration of the expansiveness of all
that is. We thank you for this
opportunity, our unconditional love to
you all, exciting dream life and life
dream. Remember, you are dreaming right
now. Wake up and live the dream you prefer.
Wake up and live the dream you prefer.
It's your
choice. We thank you and we bid you a
loving and exciting good day. [Music]
How did it go?
[Applause]