Institute, P. Box 1394, Roseville,
California 95678. We also have other tapes
95678. We also have other tapes
available. Send us a self-ress stamped
envelope and we'll send you a list.
Thanks for your consideration.
A little we send greetings to you this
day of your time as you create time to
exist. How are you all this day of your
time? Allow us to begin this interaction with
Allow us to begin this interaction with
the laying of a few foundations between
us to provide some commonality for the
experience we are sharing this day of
your time.
Realize that this interaction is for the
purpose of providing each and every one
of you in your own way at your own pace
with the appropriate type of tools.
Tools that you can apply in your
physiological reality to create the
changes that you desire to occur in your
physiological reality on certain levels.
You as an individual unique being will
always always
always take what we will share with you
and your imagination will transform what
we will share with you into whatever
unique format you find will work best
for you. So the first thing we would
like to have as an understanding between
us is that there is no need to assume in
this interaction in this what you call
workshop that anything we say must be
followed absolutely verbatim as you say.
We will be giving certain suggestive
structures even though they may sound
very specific. We may say think this,
visualize that, but that does not
necessarily mean that your imagination
must absolutely in a rigidized fashion
follow suit. The idea is that your own
imagination is a processing unit and it
is everchanging. It is never static. You
are different beings from moment to
moment to moment and therefore your
imagination will make different
interpretations from moment to moment to
moment about the information that it is
receiving. We are also a non-static source and we
We are also a non-static source and we
are ever changing. Therefore, the
dynamic interaction between yourselves
and ourselves will never be something
that becomes fixed in one particular
focus. Realize therefore that while we
may say certain things and paint certain
pictures, you are not required to follow
them to the letter as you say. Whatever
way your imagination sees fit, whatever
way your feelings see fit, whatever way
your mentality sees fit to alter our
suggestions will be absolutely in accord
with the vibration that you are being at
that particular moment and the way you
interpret it will be exactly correct for
you. You all follow along so far? Amen.
In other words, to say everything I have
just said in a very simple manner, there
is no right way and there is no wrong
way to experience this interaction. Your
way is the best way because you are who
you are. We simply reflect an energy. We
simply radiate a particular frequency
and in a sense we challenge though not
meaning that word in a derogatory way,
not in a conflictive way. We challenge
you to match the frequency that we
radiate. Remember this. We would remind
you very clearly always that if you feel
in this interaction any changes taking
place within an energy field around you.
It is not so much that you are feeling
our energy. You are feeling your own
energy. Yes, you may say why I felt your
energy radiating from you. But pay
attention to the fact that you are your
own universe and therefore anything
everything you feel in your universe is
made out of your energy. You by matching
our frequency, by accepting that
challenge and equalizing with our
frequency will create in your universe
your version of our energy so that you
can operate on an equal level with us.
Which is what our desire is in terms of
our interaction with all of you. That we
function as equals. And this is why we
share the idea of these tools with you
this day of your time. So you can know
that you are always self-empowered to
apply these ideas in your life when you
want to, where you want to, how you want
to, without having to run to anyone
else, especially us, for the ideas or
the abilities to be able to do what you
want to
do. This, as we have said a few times,
is your year of conviction. And we can
think of no more appropriate timing in
which to discuss the idea of having the
conviction to do in your lives what
really excites you with absolute trust
in that direction. You will get the
result, you will get the feedback and
you will get the flow. If you act with
the conviction of the things you desire
to do. Now this particular interaction
for we have had many interactions with
you and have shared many different
perspectives and tools with you. This
particular interaction shall be shall we
say broken into three phases. I myself
as the persona you understand me to be
that which is termed
bashar will conduct the first phase
which we have entitled persona
reconstruction. The second phase will be
undertaken by a female in my society who
uses the name of Anima simply so that
you may have something to call her by.
It is not her name literally for we do
not have literal names. The third phase
shall be conducted by an idea more or
less. Let us explain it this way. It
will go by the name galactic. It is
representative of consciousness itself.
It will be to some degree a blending of
my own consciousness, a blending of
consciousness, so that the male and the
female aspects will be represented in
one whole conscious idea. The galactic
consciousness is actually the
consciousness of the fabric of spaceime
itself. It is self-aware like any
consciousness can be. It also
understands that it is composed of all
of the fragmented realities and
universal perspectives that go into
making up what you may call the
space-time matrix of your physiological
existence. The section that I will cover persona
The section that I will cover persona
reconstruction will be at first what you
may call a bit of a refresher course to
define the idea of persona to allow you
to understand by that definition how it
can be disassembled in any way, shape or
form you choose it to be and reassembled
in any way, shape or form you choose it
to be with the results that you get the
reality you want based on the person
that you have now created yourself to
The second phase conducted by Anima
shall be entitled excitement and
abundance for the two are really one in
the same idea and will explore aspects
within yourself to bring these aspects
to the surface so that you can
experience spontaneity and excitement
and abundance in every single moment of
your life should you choose to apply the
tools that we will share with you or
create your own for that is spontaneity
itself. The third phase which shall be
conducted by the galactic consciousness
shall be entitled astral
expansion. And here we will allow the
idea of segregated physical reality to
begin to blend with what you have called
imagination and dream time to extend
what you may call your senses beyond
what you call your physical definitions,
your physical barriers, if you will.
My segment will begin with this
particular notion but in a different
light. The idea of your physical senses.
If we are going to talk about persona
reconstruction then we must understand
the definition that actually exists that
defines what you are as a physiological
person to begin with. So let us start
there. Step number one, some
Step number one, some
clarification about some of the ideas
you have held about yourselves for quite
some time. You have for quite some time
time. You have for quite some time
talked about your physiological senses,
those ideas with which you see the
world, your physical reality.
Most of you have been taught to think in
one way, shape or form that what you
call your physical senses are your
windows to the world and through these
windows floods the information by which
you perceive the reality around you.
Well, in a sense, yes, this is so it is
one valid way of looking at it. However,
it may not necessarily be precisely a
mechanical definition of what is
happening and sometimes it can actually
be in your terms a bit
misleading. The idea of your physical
senses are windows, but they are not so
much windows as they are filters. And
they actually keep out
99.9% of everything there is to see to
allow you to experience the one focused
idea you say you want to experience as
your physical reality. So your senses do
extend. They do let information in. But
only what you decide they will let in.
They will only see and will only feel
and will only sense what you allow them
to. They are completely under your
dominion in that way.
Now another thing we would like to
illustrate before we continue is that
you have also talked about the fact that
you have five physical senses and you
have hinted at the idea that you may
have this mysterious sixth sense into
which you have lumped all sorts of
phenomena. All right, fair enough.
However, what you are calling the sixth
sense in a sense is actually the seventh
one. You have seven physical senses and
one transcendental one making a total of
eight. Now you're already at least to
some degree most of you familiar with
the idea of five senses being your sight
and your sound and your taste and your
smelling and your
touch. The sixth sense is what you might
simply call orientation.
Now many of you have experienced the
idea that you have a very good or
perhaps in your estimation a very bad
sense of direction in terms of space and
time. You get lost easily or you never
get lost. This on one side or the other
is an interaction with your true sixth
sense of spatial orientation.
It is centered physiologically basically
for the most part in your sinus cavities
and is hinged upon a substance that
exists in your sinus cavities called
magnetite. It is with this substance
that the animals in your world navigate
and have what you call homing instinct.
You also have it and you follow lines of
electromagnetic force if you allow
yourself to be sensitive enough to them
so that certain individuals will realize
that they simply always know what
direction they are facing. always know
how to get back to where they started
from or perhaps again conversely never
know. But one way or another you are
simply using that sense whether
positively or negatively whether through
allowance or denial you are dealing with
that particular faculty within
you. The seventh sense is what you
usually call your sixth sense and
basically put this is simply vibrational
discernment. Vibrational discernment basically means
Vibrational discernment basically means
that everything in physical reality is a
matter of a vibratory frequency of a
prime electromagnetic energy and your
very cellular structure is very
sensitive to vibrations in that
electromagnetic spectrum. Now you have
at various times labeled your ability to
sense the emotional patterns of other
individuals or to sense the layout of a
particular situation by saying well the
vibes feel this way or the vibes feel
that way. Not necessarily understanding
how accurate you are being. You are
truly picking up on waves of vibratory
electromagnetic radiation, ripples, if
you will, in your physical matrix that
represent, just like what you would call
fingerprints, the matrix, the setup, the
manifestation of that particular person
or that particular situation or
circumstance. Everything has a signature
vibration, a signature pattern by which
it is recognized by those that allow
themselves to be sensitized in that
area. And in terms of it connecting into
your physiological form, the glandular
structures of your body, especially what
you would call the pineal glands in the
brain are responsible for allowing you
to extrapolate these electromagnetic
waves into something that makes sense
physiologically as an emotional reaction
or a
feeling regarding any particular person,
place or thing.
Your eighth sense, the transcendental
sense, is one that is beyond physical
reality and to some degree is actually
responsible for all the other senses.
And it is simply the state of
knowingness. Regardless of any
physiological connection, there are
simply times when you simply know
something to be. No, you know the
scenario as one complete picture, one
complete event without segregating it,
without separating it, without breaking
it down to its usual components. You
simply see it as what you call a
gestalt. You know it even though there
has been no direct transfer of
analytical information. You simply know
it. You identify with it. You are that
idea knowingness. So as a physiological
being you have seven senses not five and
the eighth makes up the total octave of
your physical
reality. With this definition we can now
begin a little bit of a refresher
course. Some things that we have talked
about with many of you from time to
time. For those to whom this is new do
not worry you will understand it very
easily or you would not be involved in
this interaction. Allow me also to
remind each and every one of you to
paraphrase what we have already said. If
there seems to be something you do not
necessarily understand on the surface,
do remember that some portion of you
does understand it. Allow yourself to
simply absorb it in a comfortable
manner. And if the analytical side says,
"Huh, allow yourself to understand that
sooner or later it will be told by
another aspect of your consciousness
what it needs to know." So the more you
relax rather than concentrate with
effort on trying to understand, the more
you will actually understand through
that relaxation. Just let it soak in.
You will miss nothing. You are actually
incapable of missing anything. Even if
you play a pretend game that says you
have missed it all,
remember you are a
100% being. Never any less. Never
anymore, but never any less.
100%. And you are always
using 100% of yourself. Even if you're
using 90% to make it seem as if you're
only using 10, that is just your
definition of yourself, but you're
always using the total 100%. So do not
worry, you will miss nothing. I
guarantee it.
Now, the refresher course begins by
understanding once again the idea of
what you are as a person. What is a
persona? What is your personality? Where
does it come from? How does it get
there? Who are you? And all these
questions that many of you have been
asking for thousands upon thousands of
your years. All right. Now, let us begin
by reminding each and every one of you
that what you typically call your
daytoday personality, the person that
you believe yourself to be, is an
arbitrary artificial so to speak
natural. Yes. in one sense, but it is an
arbitrary artificial construct.
Temporary temporary construct to reflect
reflect a particular idea to present a
particular idea at a given moment for a
specific reason. In a sense, let's put it this
reason. In a sense, let's put it this
way.
You are now
interacting in an event that most of you
have called in your language a
channeling. We have discussed many times
the idea that channeling basically is
simply allowing any full creative energy
to come through you. It is doing
anything you love to do so to speak.
Channeling is simply an expression from
one level to another a manifestation. It
does not have to be any more mysterious
than that. Art is channeling. Acting is
channeling. Singing is channeling.
Talking is channeling. Being who you are
in a sense is a channeling because you
exist on more than one level. Therefore,
the persona you are as a physical being
in a sense is being channeled from a
more complete version of you. The higher
self, the whole self, the oversoul does
not matter what you call it. Whatever
the total idea is that you are as a
consciousness in a sense is extending a
fragment of itself into this physical
reality and therefore that extension can
be called a channeling. So these
so-called fixed personalities that many
of you have always thought yourselves to
be are quite temporary extensions. In
other words, you are channeling
yourselves right now. Whatever you
define, whatever you believe yourself to
be will be the filter through which the
channeling takes place and through which
the persona is
constructed. Whatever the strongest
belief, the strongest idea, the
strongest notion, the strongest
experiment is that you are dealing with
will utterly determine from moment to
moment what you are as a persona, as a
person, as a personality. all the same
thing. No difference between them. Now,
persona physically speaking is
constructed of three sides like a prism.
And the analogy goes further than that.
You are all basically familiar with the
idea of a three-sided glass prism. And
you know that when you take white light,
which contains many frequencies, and you
pass the white light through that prism,
it is broken down into the diversified
spectrum of different colors. You have
segregated that white light out. So it
is with your personality construct and
the three sides to that prism are called
belief, emotion and thought pattern.
When you take the homogeneous unbroken
white light of the overall non-physical
being that you are and you pass that
energy through the prism of your belief,
the prism of your emotion and your
thought pattern, you break down those
frequencies into a diversified spectrum,
particular aspects, particular fragments
that create a particular face, a
particular representation of that idea
reflected by that prism. If you change
any of those sides, change the belief,
change the frequency of the emotion,
change the frequency of the thought
pattern, you change the way the white
light, the unbroken you comes through
the prism. You get a different
projection, a different reality. The
prism is you, your physical persona. The
spectrum is your physical reality
reflected back to you. If you want to
see a different physical reality, a
different spectrum, a different ratio in
terms of how the colors are spread out
in your life, all you have to do is
change the ratio of the prism that you
are, the persona that you are. And that
is as simple as changing a belief,
changing an emotion, or changing a
thought pattern. do any of those three
things and you have completely now I
mean completely changed the entire
persona structure that you
are. Let us digress for a
moment. We understand and this is not
the case with every single one of you
but it has been observed by us that
there has been created a particular type
of approach to things in life on your
planet. The scenario we have summed up
as this or that. This or that. Well, if
it's not this, it must be that. If it's
that, it can't be this. Is it this or is
it that? Which is true? Which is more
real? This or that? From our
perspective, it is always this and that.
They are both real. They are both true.
They are simply truth from different
perspectives. If they could not be both
just as real, if they could not be both
just as true, both could not coexist.
You would not see the paradox. You would
not see the polarity. You would not see
the dichotomy. There would be one very
obvious way, and you would never be able
to divert or digress from it. The fact
that there exists more than one way
shows in and of itself by definition
that all of those ways are valid ways
and they all can bring an understanding
and they are all reflective of a
perspective. You can learn in any of
them anything you want in any way you
want to. The idea to understand is the
following thing.
When you
allow your particular
belief, your particular emotions, your
particular thoughts to be redesigned in
the way you prefer them to be, then you
have changed who you are as a persona,
as a physical
representation. Absolutely, utterly,
completely. There is no, oh well, it's
still me with a little bit of a change.
This comes from the this or that, the
segregational aspect. In other words, it
comes from saying, "Well, all right.
Here's a cube. It's got six sides.
They're all blue. I will now paint one
of the sides red. Now, it's the same
blue cube with one red side." Well, no,
it's not. It is a completely different
cube as well. It is this and that. Yes,
you can say it's the same cube with one
red side and not or and you can say it
is a completely different cube and it
is. It depends on how you want to look
at it. If you are willing to allow
yourself to understand that you can look
at it as if it is a completely new cube
rather than saying well is it this or
that. If you're understanding that it is
both, that it is both, and that you can
choose which one you prefer to be
representative of your reality, then
many many more things, many different
things can be done with this perspective
than were capable of being done with the
other perspective that you had. Not that
they are not again both equal. Not that
you cannot necessarily do as many things
on both sides. That is not what we are
saying. But if you are willing to
embrace all that it can be, there are
more things that you are capable of
doing. So let us for a moment remove
ourselves from what can be said to be
the old earth pattern of saying it's the
same old cube. It's just got a facelift
on one side. And instead of saying that,
begin to understand. Well, if one side
is different, it's an entirely new
concept. It is an entirely new cube. It
is not the same cube. Let's go with that
side for a moment because that is the
tool that you can use in your life to
change anything you want in any way you
want to. Go back to the prism of your
persona. You have belief, emotion, and
thought. Change your thought. You do not
have to be the same old person with a
little new thought. an insignificant
little new thought that doesn't do much
to change the person that I am. It's
just a little tiny thought lost in the
sea of the big vast idea that I don't
like to be. All right, fair enough. You
can look at it that way. Or and you can
understand that that one seemingly
infinite decimal change has completely
rewritten the equation of your reality
of your existence
completely. Completely
Completely
completely. There is a saying that
exists upon your
planet. A difference which makes no
difference is no difference. However, if
even the slightest difference is made by
adding a difference, then everything is
different. The whole game is different.
The whole scenario is different and you
start from zero at that moment and you
start completely new.
From our perspective, in our society,
from our experience, this is the way
reality can be. We are not going to say
this is the way reality is because
reality is anything you want it to be.
That's reality. It can be this way, however,
reality. It can be this way, however,
and if you are willing to allow yourself
to play with this particular notion, it
can be very malleable indeed.
So let us start by understanding that
belief, emotion and thought are simply
the building blocks of the persona that
you are. And that the persona that you
are is not chiseled in stone, is not
unchanging. It changes all the time.
Your planet is in the habit, shall we
say, of creating the illusion called
continuity. This illusion called continuity is
This illusion called continuity is
reinforced by your perception of what
you call linear time. And the illusion
of continuity makes it seem as if
changes happen in minute ways. Oh yes,
you can say well there are great changes
sometimes. But the idea generally is
that continuity makes things seem to
stay generally the same while you notice
that changes are going on.
This perspective can be
completely removed. Now how much of that
removed. Now how much of that
perspective you will remove will depend
upon your comfort
zone in allowing your reality to
completely disassemble. For some individuals the
disassemble. For some individuals the
way they have been brought up, the way
they have been taught, allowing a
complete disassembage of their reality
may be a little bit frightening.
their analytical ego structure
consciousness may feel all of a sudden
it hasn't got any ground any stable
foundation to stand upon. It may panic
and it may throw you into a deeper kind
of fear. Well, that is all right. You do
not have to go any faster than you want
to. The tools we are sharing with you
this day of your time will be applied by
you and your imagination at whatever
pace is comfortable for you. All we ask
you is this. That you trust yourselves.
That you will absorb the information
however you need to. And you will never
never never give yourself more than you are
never give yourself more than you are
capable of handling at any given moment
because you never ever have. No matter
how it seemed, you have always had just
enough for what you are capable of
looking at. When you begin to understand
that principle, then you can recognize
that even though there may have been
times when certain things in your life
may have seemed to be overwhelming, you
can now say to yourself, well, wait a
minute. If I really never never attract
anything more than what I am truly
capable of handling and this huge and
powerful change is coming along, then I
must be that powerful, too. It doesn't
have to be overwhelming. If I understand
it's exactly representative of my
frequency, it must be exactly who and
what I am. Therefore, I am more than
capable of handling that because it is
precisely key to me. Beginning that
attitude will shift everything.
Remember, belief, emotion, thought that
can be summed up as attitude. Attitude
is everything. Many individuals when
they hear us talking about these notions
will say oh well nice philosophy Bashar
but what does it have to do with real
life all right but understand from our
perspective we are not talking
philosophy we're not talking airy theory
we are talking physics mechanics
absolute cause and effect and cause what
you put out is what you get back you
cannot not experience a reality. You are
not the vibration of whatever vibration
you are is the only reality you can and
do experience. If you don't prefer the
reality you're getting, change the
vibration you are and you cannot get
anything else but a different reality.
It is simple physics. Some of the
difficulty we know many individuals on
your planet have with this idea is that
it is in their minds too simple. They
think reality is more complicated than
that. Oh yes, there are complexities. Oh
yes, many things are interconnected.
Well, everything is interconnected.
Everything is intertwined. On that
sense, we would agree that reality can
be very complex. But being complex,
being rich doesn't necessarily mean that it
rich doesn't necessarily mean that it
has to be complicated in approach, in
applicability. It is actually a very
simple principle. Existence is there
really are only two things that we have
ever discovered that, shall we say,
govern everything in creation. Number
one, you
exist. All of you exist. Everything that
is self-aware exists. Everything that
exists is number two. What you put out
is what you get back. That's all there
is to it. Everything else, as you say in
your language, is your ball game, is
your agreement, is your choice, is your
belief, is your teaching, is your
learning, is your assumption, is your
perspective, is your point of view.
everything else. The things that seem so
unchangeable, the things that seem so
solid, all of those are solid and
seemingly unchangeable because of your
assumption of continuity, of momentum,
of inertia, and all the other
definitions you have been taught that
your reality is supposed to be. Did all
of you see that? Supposed to be.
There are no supposed
to except what you put out is what you
get back.
Now, you do not have to answer this out
loud, but I will ask this question for
each of you to answer on your own to
yourself. Can you
allow reality to be that simple? Can you
allow yourself to believe that reality
can be that
ecstatic? Can you handle that much
ecstasy? I'll leave that up to you for a
moment.
Now, belief, emotion, and thoughts. All
right. What are they? Definitions. The
ones we will provide anyway. You can
make up your own. Doesn't matter to us.
Here's our perspective.
belief, the
definitions, the
blueprints you create your reality to
be, the patterns that you follow, your
beliefs. Emotions are the engines, the
activators. Emotion, energy, motion are
what activate the blueprints, activate
the beliefs. They are the builders of
the house represented by the
blueprint. Thought patterns are the
materials the builders use, the
structures that they follow, whether it
is your stone or your wood or your steel
or your glass, the thought patterns, the
style of your approach to life, the
materials your emotions have to use to
build the houses of your reality from
the blueprints you believe in. to begin
with. Change the blueprint, you get a
different house. Maybe the same material
if you're still using the same thought
patterns, but you get a different house.
Change the thought patterns, you get a
different material. Change the emotions,
you get different types of
builders, different speeds, different
rates, different attitudes. All these
ideas work hand in hand to create and
build what you perceive to be the
physical reality around you. If you
don't like the blueprint, if you don't
like the layout, if you think this is a
little too cramped or you should have
another story so you can aspire to
greater heights, add it onto the
blueprint. It isn't fixed. It isn't
rigidized. It is not set in stone. It is
absolutely up to you. No matter what you
have been told, there really is no such
thing per se as that's the way it is.
Get used to it. That's life. Face
reality. Oh, grow up. You understand all
those things? Those are now here's the
important point. They are all valid
perspectives. But we will now create
another definition.
All of these attitudes, all of these
teachings, and all of these learnings,
including our own that you have ever
been brought up with, they are all
stories. That is what they are. Stories,
beautiful, creative, wondrous,
imaginative stories. But they are
someone's story of life. There is no
that's the way it is. It's that's their
story. Now you can accept portions of their
Now you can accept portions of their
story. You can adapt ideas from their
story into your story. But you have your
own story. Yes. Yes. Yes. There are
certain things that all of you have
agreed will be relatively common or
similar in the world story called Earth.
But there is a lot of leeway within the
pages of the world story. The only
reason you have a world story is so you
have a background, a foundation upon
which you can write all the other
individual stories in a way that makes
sense to you experientially in your
lives. Eventually you will together
change as you are doing right now the
world's story as well. But it begins by
allowing yourself to live to the fullest
that you can the individual story you
are. Now many of you spend many years
trying to figure out what your story is.
That's all right because that figuring
out is a part of your story too. There
is nothing that is outside of your
story. It is all in your story. It's all
yours right there on the pages of the
book. You are. You don't have to go
searching far and wide to the ends of
the universe to find something that will
make sense out of your story. You got
the front cover, you got the back cover
on all the pages right with you right
now because you are that book. Now, this
does not mean you cannot go looking for
things in different places. You cannot
go exploring. It does not mean that. By
all means, that's a part of your story,
too. All we are implying is that there
is nothing that is beyond your story
that you will encounter. If it doesn't
belong in your story, you'll never
encounter it in this particular life. If
you encounter it, if you're even aware
that it can be encountered, it belongs
in your story and you can create it.
Now, allow yourself therefore when you
hear other people saying, "You can't do
it that way. Do it this way. this is
better than that way when you hear these
things or you hear well that's life
that's the way it is it can't be changed
it can't be helped or sometimes even
when you hear the other idea well this
is all very marvelous and it's marvelous
if you do it like this but not if you do
it like that if you do it like this it's
marvelous but if you do it like that
well less than marvelous when you hear
all of these let yourself begin to get
into a new habit Ah, interesting
story. Fascinating story. Very creative
story. Allow me to commend you on such a
creative story. Allow me to commend you on your
story. Allow me to commend you on your
willingness to be of service to me, to
allow me to decide what pages of your
story fit in my book and what pages do
not. Let me also remind each and every one of
Let me also remind each and every one of
you by the way that we have noticed that
it is one of the strongest things that
many of you do to allow yourself to
figure out what your story is. Sometimes
you will find that for some of you it's
easier to figure that out by finding out
what your story is not then you do it
through the process of
elimination. And sometimes that's why
you put yourself through certain
scenarios and certain circumstances and
you say what am I doing here? It's to
find out what you don't prefer so that
you can be more understanding of what
you do prefer. You don't have to do it
that way. Sometimes that can take a long
time, but that's up to
you. The whole point is is that when you
use every scenario in your book in the
most positive way you can, you will then
allow yourself to learn as quickly as
you can who you are. Even if it's
through the process of finding out who
you are not. The sooner you find out in
that way and allow yourself to
understand who you prefer to be, the
sooner you will have a reality that is
reflective of that preference. Remember,
preference is not judgment. When you say
I prefer this, you're not saying that
stinks. You are saying that doesn't
serve who I am. It is valid as a lesson.
It is valid as a reality. Maybe I used
to believe it. Maybe someone else now
believes it. But if they believe it and
I used to believe it, that doesn't mean
I'm so much better and so much greater
and that they are still stuck in the
muck. It does not mean that. It means
their vibration requires that lesson and
your vibration requires this reality,
that situation, that circumstance, this
lesson to be more and more of who you
want to be. So preference is not
judgment. Invalidate any portion of
reality, you invalidate your ability to
create what you want because you are
connected to the whole. You are a
representation of the whole. validate
any fragment of it and you cut your own
lifeline right
now. That's why if you support the total
whole, validate the whole, bless
everyone's creative story, the universe
will support any story you prefer
because you are supporting the whole and
in return it can do nothing else but
support 100% your story as well. You
understand? So, a beautiful story. Thank you for
So, a beautiful story. Thank you for
sharing it. I will see what portions
overlap the leaves of my story. Should I
choose some of your story and
incorporate it in mine, all well and
good? Should I choose that some of your
story does not match the vibration of
mine, I love your story, no less.
Now, we understand that there are many
conflictive points of view and
perspectives and personas upon your
planet. I am right. No, I am right. You
are wrong. No, over here. I am right.
You're both wrong. All
right. Allow yourself an
opportunity also to
relax. Relaxed from having to defend
your point of view.
Yes. If you have to defend your point of
view, you are not sure you believe it
yourself.
So if you wish some sort of a response
to someone who attacks your
belief without being judgmental, we can
simply suggest a response that is loving
and perhaps a response that will allow
them to think. Not that they necessarily
must change, but simply that you give
them room to change should they decide
they want to. And the response simply is
recognize your philosophy does not allow
for mine, but my philosophy allows for
yours. That simply explains the
definition of expansiveness and
allowance right there. Because that is
what creation is. It allows all
philosophies. It is an absolute
contradiction to say the creation gave
you free will and then wants to control
what you
think. Understand? You have free will
because you are versions of the
infinite. You have in your biblical
literature a saying that says you are
made in the image of God. How many of
you actually understand what that means?
What you call God, we call all that is
infinite dynamic existence,
self-aware, always creating, ever a new,
always existing,
multi-dimensional, infinite, and
eternal. If you're made in the image of
that, that's how powerful you are. For
that are your attributes as well.
Infinite, eternal,
multi-dimensional. You are creative in
your own right. You are given the free
will so that you may continue creation
as cocreational aspects of the infinite.
The idea of creation wants you to
control its creations that it is given
free will to in a sense now I'm going to
put this in colloquial terms and I do
not mean anything derogatory by it nor
is it meant to be judgmental but to
assume that creation would create free
will and then want to dominate those
that have free will is at best throwing
a gift back in the creation's face.
Allow yourselves to be allowing of all
beliefs because all beliefs are faces of
creation. That allowance of all beliefs
is what allows any belief the best
opportunity to change into something
more harmonious with all other beliefs.
And this does not mean you have to share
the same absolute perspective. But all
beliefs can be harmonious when they are
allowed to be reflective and
representative of all of the faces of
the infinite because that is what they
are. All that is is everywhere is
everything. Everything is made out of
all that is. There is no outside not to
all that is nor to you. Everything you
can conceive of you contain or you could
not imagine it.
Allow yourselves therefore to understand
that the personality, the persona that
you are, the person that you are is a
highly transformational extension of the
transformational extension of the
infinite. And with your free will, you
can decide what definitions of reality,
what emotional reactions to reality, and
what thought patterns of reality you
prefer to
experience. And in shifting your
definitions and your emotions and your
thought patterns into what you prefer
them to be, you cannot get a reality
that is anything other than those
representational vibrations. It is not
possible. What you put out is what you
get back. Action reaction that is the
basis of all existence. It is as simple
as that.
Now, here is a meditative tool to begin
to access the power of your
transformational persona. All of you
become comfortable in whatever position
you wish to become comfortable in. Close
your eyes or keep them open. It does not
matter. And take three deep breaths.
All right, three
more. And three more after that. Three *
three. Do not
hyperventilate. Allow yourself to relax.
Easy, long, resonant, deep, creative,
long, resonant, deep, creative,
fulfilling breaths. Easing.
breaths. Easing.
easing into a new state of
awareness, a state of awareness that is
far more representative of the you you
prefer to
be. Because remember this, while you are
relaxing, while you are soaking up the
energy of your own creative
breath, remember
this. You are a different you from
moment to moment.
You are not the same you you were a
moment ago. In the next moment, you will
be another you, not the same as you are
right now. If you allow yourself to be a
now. If you allow yourself to be a
completely different you, you can begin
to understand the following
things. You live in the present. You
exist in the now. It is the only
experiential place in time that you do
exist. What you call the past, what you call
What you call the past, what you call
the future, those labels that are
created from the concept of continuity
are your illusions, are your creations.
They are real while you play in them,
but they are your creation. And they are
only as arbitrary as you define them to
be. There is no fixed future. There is
no fixed past. You create both the
future and the past from the present
which is where you exist here and
now. As you define yourself to be now,
so you create ripples in your past,
ripples all up and down the timeline to
your future. You change the past and you
change the future from the present.
Because if you are a different person
now then different things happened to
create you in the present. You have a
different history and you have therefore a
history and you have therefore a
different future as
well. Anything you no longer prefer as
an
association will no longer exist for the
you you define yourself to be in the
present. Anything in what you call your
past that you believe up to this point
has been holding you back from being who
you prefer to be no longer exists if you
simply define it out of the definitional
equation that is your present
self. Change the equation in the present
and nothing that has been attached to
the old you will have any effect on you
any longer.
Remember, what you call a habit, a
habitual ritual, a pattern, is something
that you do that you don't know you're
doing. Once you know you're doing it,
once you know you have a habit, you
don't have it
anymore. You have to be beyond it in
order to know you had it to begin with.
The only reason it would seem to
continue, the only reason it would seem
to repeat is because your definition
says that that's what a habit
does. Once you know you have it, you are
a different person and you no longer
contain it. Don't act like it will
repeat and it won't. Don't believe that
it must repeat and it can't.
Know that your reality will be what you
want it to be when you want it to be how
you want it to
be. Imagine in any way, shape or form
that works for you. Feel it, see it,
smell it, taste it. It does not
matter at this point. Just know in any
way, shape, or form that you need to
know that you are now relaxing and
sinking down to your place of perfect
peace, to your centered state of
vibrational existence. And if you find
that what you call your analytical mind
is chattering along, that is all right,
too. Do not make an attempt to shut it
up. Let it talk all at once. Because this is
Let it talk all at once. Because this is
a place where you integrate, where you
let everything in. And letting
everything in drives you into a deeper
state of
relaxation. You do not need to keep
things out to get there. You need to let
it all in to get there. The more energy,
the more mass you let in, the deeper you
will sink into the softness at the
center of your
being. Any noise that you would have
formerly called a
distraction, know it is there for a
reason. It is a part of your
orchestration. Let it
in. Acknowledge it. Invite it. Accept
it. Integrate it. Acknowledge, Acknowledge,
invite,
accept, integrate. integrate.
Acknowledge,
invite, accept, integrate. You cannot change
accept, integrate. You cannot change
what you do not
own. Own it. It's your creation. It
doesn't mean you have to prefer it, but
if you don't own it, you can't change it
into what you prefer it to be. If you
deny it, that's not mine. Has nothing to
do with me. If you run away from it, you
have no control over
it. Embrace
it. No matter how you have been taught
to fear it, embrace it, love it, and you
will change it. Accept it for what it
is, and then you can do anything you
want to with it. Because it becomes, as
you say, putty in your hands. More
appropriately, it becomes putty in your
heart because your heart is a furnace, a
crucible in which all solid realities
melt down into the plastic
puddle of golden
light. And you can make anything you
want out of it from that point forward.
Breathe and know regardless of what your
mind tells you, regardless of any other
old beliefs, know at this point beyond a
shadow of a doubt that you are now at
the center of your place of total
receptivity, total acceptance, total
integration. You have the ability to
create or recreate this vibrational
reality anytime, anywhere.
You need no special conditions. You are
a special condition unto yourself. You
are an environment. You are a universe
unto yourself. Anything that now comes up,
yourself. Anything that now comes up,
let it be reflective of a release of old
ideas. Exhale and expel them. Transform
them. You are not denying them. You are
not getting rid of them. There is
nowhere to get rid of anything to. There
is no outside. You are transforming them
and seeing the reactions in your bodily
form, your bodily consciousness.
And now in whatever way works best for
you, imagine simply
imagine simply
imagine that you are a bright shining
crystal and that this
crystal is floating on the surface at
the surface level with the surface of an
infinite energy sea of blue white
undulating ing
light. And you look as you bob up and
down in the waves, this little crystal
that you are in this infinite sea, you
look all around to the horizon in every
direction and you see it is
infinite. The horizon goes to an
infinite sky above you, all the way
above you. Bright bright sky above. And
as you look down, deep, deep sea below,
infinite sea stretching below, deep,
deep blue. The sky above, bright
crystallin blue. The sea surface all
around you, brilliant blue, white,
crystallin, liquid light. And you just
float. And you relax. And you bob up and
down in the
waves. And you enjoy being at the
center of all
creation, being granted the ability, the
opportunity to
view what you may call God's eye
view, the center of all that is. And you
know that stretching to the infinite
horizon is also the awareness of all
that is. And it sees itself from every
point and every place within that
infinite sky, that infinite surface and
that infinite depth. It is all alive and
all aware and every point within it is a
point of
view, a reality unto itself.
You do not have any way to know where
you are under that sky in that sea. You
could be anywhere. It would be infinite
from any point and would be infinite in
all direction. There is no way to tell
if you're
halfway, part of the way, almost all of
the way. There is no way to arrive at
it. Goes on and on.
And you now
understand that it is not a matter of
struggling and striving to reach
something. It is not a matter of it
going on and on and that is an
interminable and infinite and suffering
road forever. It simply means that
anywhere you are you have
arrived. Anywhere you are could be
anywhere else in that sea.
What makes that particular area unique
is not where you are in the sea but what
you are. Who you decide to be at that
point at that place in that infinite
sea. That is what
decides where quote unquote and when
quote unquote you are
you. It is a clean slate. You are at
zero, the center of it all, your
ultimate and infinite resting place, the
place of perfect
peace. And as you make this
realization, you begin to
melt. Your edges
soften. You're not as sharp as a
crystal. You begin to dissolve.
And as you dissolve, you
spread as a radiating circle across the
entire surface of the infinite sea out
and out and out and out until you cover
the entire surface. And every wave and
every motion and every particle on the
surface of the sea is now within
you. And as the shining light from the
sky shines down upon
you, it
lifts like steam the particles that you
are. And you rise and fill the volume of
the infinite sky. And even as you rise
to fill the sky and cover the surface of
the sea, some of the particles
sink until you fill the volume, the
infinite volume to the farthest depths. And then
volume to the farthest depths. And then
you keep going forever and
ever. The sea and the sky are within
you. You fill the volume of your
You fill the volume of your
reality and you are at the center of
your reality.
This is not a selfish idea. For you now
understand that in
supporting in serving the totality of
the volume, you are supported by the
volume, you are supported by the
volume. As you
serve, as you support, you are
supported. As you love, you are loved.
You will never lose your
individuality because there is only the
individual you to fill the universe that
you are becoming homogeneous
with. And every single being and this is
the paradox of it will see it the same
way from the same perspective. All of
this expansion will always be happening
to
you from your unique point of view. And
the same will be going on for all other
points of view. And this is the nature
of multi-dimensional
creator. It is all
real. And
now you allow yourself to
feel the volume of the infinite. You
fill the sky. You fill the surface. You
fill the
depths. You are
expansiveness itself. You are infinity
itself. You are eternity
itself. Know that whether these concepts
are making sense to your analytical mind
or not, you are
understanding. You are feeling. You are
knowing. Now you
Now you
decide how you will experience any level
that you want to turn this volume into.
You are now the sole determiner of how
this volume will crystallize into
whatever matrix into whatever pattern
you desire it to be. From the center
out, see the entire volume crystallized
in a perfect pattern that
represents clarity, perspective, and
clarity, perspective, and
insight, stretching to the ends and
going on forever. There are no
ends. Forever and ever. You are
connected to it all. It is all connected
to you because you are it all. It is all
you. It is neither this or that. It is
this and that. It is not just the
creator or
you. You are the creator. The creator is
you. The creator is
all that
is. And it isn't even
necessarily what you may call a creator
for that term is created within time. It
is a dynamic existence,
self-aware. It is
eternity. It is
infinity. All of time and all of
space is within
it. It is not within anything but
itself. And
And
now as you see the entire volume filled
with this crystallin
understanding, focus on the one facet at
the very center. Wherever you determine
that center is will be the center and
then focus on another facet and that is
now the center.
And whatever you determine that facet is
that is the center and there the center
shall be and another facet and another
facet and another one at a time one
after another or multiple simultaneously
it does not matter they are all at the
center because it is infinite in all
directions. So the center is anywhere
you are. Everywhere you
are. Bring your consciousness back to
the focus of your
individuality. And with three deep
breaths, lock that understanding of all
you have experienced in this meditation
into the facet you choose to be at this
moment in time. And know beyond a shadow
of a doubt that that understanding that
that choice of continuity will be in
every single facet you ever decide to
be. And that your freedom to be any
facet you
want is inherent in the understanding
that you are all facets you possibly
could be and that they are all
you. Again, this is not simply a
philosophy. It is the vibrational state
of dynamic existence
itself. Open your
eyes. Orient yourself in any way, shape
or form you find is comfortable.
But remember
this you, the you I am addressing now is
not the same you you were a moment
ago. You are not the same
individuals. Some of you may think I
look the same.
That is your illusion of continuity to
let you know you are dealing with the
same signature vibration, the same
overall concept. You are not the same. You are
concept. You are not the same. You are
not the same body. You are not the same
mind. Remember your body does not contain your
Remember your body does not contain your
spirit. Your body is your spirit
expressed in physical terminology.
Your body does not contain your
consciousness. Your consciousness
contains your body. Your body is an
idea. Your persona is an idea. It is an
expression. It is a creative act. It is
a
channeling. It is a face. One of the
faces, one of the infinite faces you
have, one of the infinite faces you
are, one of the realities you can be.
All of you now stand
up and stretch your new
body. Begin to allow yourself to
understand that from this moment
forward, as you create time to exist,
every single moment of time will create
a new body. And that moment by moment,
minute by minute, hour by hour, day by
day, week by week, and year by year, at
whatever rate you are comfortable with,
fast or
slow, you
will allow yourself to redefine the
beliefs, the emotions, and the thought
patterns more the direction you prefer
them to be. and that you will be the
person, the persona that is reflective
of the reality you desire. Sit
down. Here is the final point to this
idea. Are all of you ready to pay
attention? Are you sure? All right. Thank you very
Are you sure? All right. Thank you very
much. Looking for conviction is what I
am doing. Remember that that is one of
the things of the new definition that
you say you prefer to be conviction
boldness. Now the whole
Now the whole
idea even though we have been using
colloquial terminology is not
necessarily a matter of becoming who you
prefer to
be because becoming who you prefer to be
still implies it's going to take some
time. Therefore, understand
Therefore, understand
this. All realities exist now. They all
simultaneously coexist. The you you say you want to
coexist. The you you say you want to
become exists right
now. Right now. Oh yes. Right now. It
exists right now.
the stronger you can
identify not with it but as it the
sooner the reality that is reflective of
that you will occur in your life.
Therefore, with your
imagination, with your inventiveness,
with your
creativity, the stronger you can act
out, the stronger you can
construct a version of you that you
believe is representative of who you
want to be. And the more you can act
like that
construct, the sooner you will have the
reality that is reflective of that
person because you will be that
vibration and you can have no other
reality at that point other than the
vibration of who you are being.
We will refresh your memory with the
idea once again of allowing
you to physicalize as much as
possible. Act out stage as you say mock
up as much as possible the scenario you
prefer in your
life. All physical objects are props.
They have no meaning in and of themsel
until you give them a meaning.
So if you feel, if you desire, if you
imagine, if you envision a particular
scenario that you think would be just
the sparkling
reality, the most exciting reality you
can picture, one of the easiest ways to
become that
persona, is to set aside some actual
physical space alone or with
friends and put the closest
representational physical props you can
in that space to actually create the
environment you want as closely as you
can. Then live in that environment for a
while. Play in it. It is your
playground. It is your
template. It is your pallet. It is your
visualization tool. Create it physically
as best as you can. Surround yourself
with the physical things that are
representative of the reality you say
you really want. Don't surround yourself
with the physical things of the reality
you don't
prefer. Reinforce the idea of the
vibration you prefer. Act it through.
Act it out. Play the scenario out
physically as much as you
can. Identify as that person. This is
who I am. If you really are that way,
how would you act that is different from
the way you're acting now? Act in the
different way. Set up the pattern. Set
up the vibration. Turn yourself into
that frequency by acting as that being.
Then you will
see very very
assuredly all of the physical objects
that in your terms are the real props
will begin to attract themselves to your
life to replace the temporary props, the
representational symbolic props you have
created. That is one way. In other
words, your physical reality that you
have for so long thought to be outside
yourself is made of
you. The chairs in the room, the walls
of the room, the floor of the room is
made of you literally.
So if you want to be a particular
reality, if you are a particular idea,
create the representations that are more
representative of the vibration you want
to be. Get that reflective feedback from
your exterior reality of the vibration
that is more what you prefer. And then
you will create a loop, an expanding,
accelerating cycle where you will get
that feedback because you have put it
out there. You will reflect that back to
it. It will reflect more back to you.
You'll reflect more back to it. You will
build up like a reactor until you
explode in ecstatic
manifestation. That is what you can do.
Now, of course, you can do this
negatively too. You know, and from that
I judge that many of you
have. The idea is to simply understand
that it's the same process. Same
process. When you allow yourself to play
victim, you surround yourself with the
things the victim
loves. Oh, poor
me. Oh, look. I'll interpret anything I
see in a miserable
way. I will hope it will get better.
But hope implies doubt. So I'm not
really sure that it
can. Oh me, I'll walk like
this because I will assume that my
reality has turned against me and that
I'm experiencing a negative thing.
Therefore, I'll act the part. I'll look
at all the gloomy stories and I'll nod
my head and agree with them.
I'll look at the gloomy pictures or I
may try to cheer myself up, but I know
it's probably
useless. All right, that's creative,
too. Take nothing away from that. That
is a good
act. Very creative. However, if you
don't prefer it, you don't have to have
that one. You can create whatever you
want. It's up to you. Up to you
completely. Physicalize it as much as
you can. Surround yourself with the
things that are representative of the
reality you say you prefer. Don't do the
reality you say you don't want anymore.
Don't reinforce it.
Now, some of you will say, "Well, all
right, then that means if I feel like I
want to go out and splurge on a $100,000
dinner, I will. Well, I don't have the
money. So, how can I do that? Again,
start with what you
can. Mark it up physically. Lay it out.
If you have a friend that owns a
restaurant, go in after hours if you
wish, or go in while it is open. Play
the scenario out. If what you would
order would not represent your $100,000
dinner, then play
order. Do not order something that is
not representative of what you want.
Order an empty plate and fill it with
your imagination or put some
representation on the plate of what you
believe represents your $100,000 dinner.
Well, maybe for some of you, this is
something you may prefer to do after
hours rather than having everyone in the
restaurant look at you enjoying an empty
plate. That is up to you. The more
creative you can get with it, the more
you can identify with the excitement you
would feel if you knew the situation
were real, because it is, the sooner you
will attract it synchronistically,
coincidentally, spontaneously, and
automatically in your life. Basically
what we are saying is you have many many
many outlets, many scenarios, many
stages upon which you can mock up the
entire idea. Do so because you are
tactile beings. You are physical beings
as well as the idea of spiritual beings.
Use that. Do not deny the value of
physical reality. Use it for
yourselves. Use the physical symbols.
reinforce the physical symbols that are
representative of the physical reality
that would be reflective of the
spiritual expansion you want. Spiritual
expansion cannot take place at the
expense of physical reality. You have
chosen physical reality. The way to
expand is to integrate physical reality
in a loving way into your understanding
and your definitions. Denying it is not
a spiritual expansion. It is a spiritual
cutting off. Allow yourself to see the
positive side of the physical dimension.
It is a beautiful
reality. Create the things in it that
are beautiful to you. Start with
whatever props you can create and let
them crystallize into what you call the
real symbols. They will use that kind of
energy, use that kind of creativity and
you will find everything falling into
your lap
automatically. I'll give you one final
formula. Now this again will also
perhaps happen in varying ways to
varying degrees but I'll set the stage.
I'll make the suggestion just to see
what you decide to do with it.
Let us now assume the following
axiom. Are you ready?
Are you sure?
All right. right.
Everything
everything that I do not specifically
forbid will happen.
How about that
one? Now repeat after me. Everything.
Everything.
Everything I do not specifically
forbid will
happen. Let's see what happens.
Now once again remember you'll be able
to handle whatever does happen. All you
have just done with that statement is
given yourself permission to allow the
things that need to happen to start
rolling in. It will not happen faster
than you can truly handle it. You are
not going to be out of control. It is
not a big steamroller coming down a hill
to flatten you into jelly.
And you don't have to worry. Did I
forget to forbid something? I don't
know. You already know what you're
doing. You already know what you're
doing. All you have now done is simply
given yourself permission to realize you
already know what you're
doing. Relax.
Relax. We will
now begin the second phase of this
interaction. Halfway through this phase,
we will take a short
break. From this point
forward, we will allow the consciousness
of anima to come through a female of my
society. We would remind you that while we have
We would remind you that while we have
outlined that there are three sections
to this interaction, there are actually
four. The implied force being your
exposure to the frequency of the male,
the female, and then the blended
whole for that centered state is what
will allow you to take advantage of all
the other things. We will
say we will address you once again at
the ending of this interaction. But for
now, we will allow a moment for a
change. [Applause] nice heat.
All right. I'll greet you all this day
of your time and allow us to begin in
the following
manner. Understand that many of you have
had many notions about what you call the
feminine aspect of life. We understand
that there is a great deal of polarity
and a great deal of dichotomy upon your
planet with regard to what you may call
the masculine and the feminine aspects.
But each and every one of you are now
coming to an understanding that each and
every soul is neither just masculine or
feminine, but is both in a sense
contains the ability to manifest itself
from physical life to physical life as
one or the other or even what you may
call a combination of effects.
The idea simply is that it is a
representation in your physiological
terms of one of the ways polarity can be
experienced. For polarity is one of the
definitions of physiological
reality. Now the idea more often is that
femininity has been labeled upon your
planet as the idea of passivity and to
some degree that is so and masculinity
has been labeled as the idea of
aggressiveness and to some degree that
is so. But you all know that there is
feminine assertiveness and there is
masculine passivity. You all know that
you are capable of both sides when you
allow yourself an opportunity to explore
and discover those aspects within
you. The idea of blending and balancing
those issues is what allows you to truly
live in the moment. Allows you to truly
be spontaneous in your own right as the
unique individual that you are. the
understanding of the blending of the
feminine nurturing aspects and of the
masculine assertion aspects of the
outward expressions and the inward
recognitions. A balance of these issues
is what will allow you to live in the
present and in living in the present
that is where you can have the sharpest
tools for the creation of excitement and
the creation of infinite and unlimited
abundance in your lives.
Allow me to remind each and every one of
you just in case you have forgotten. You
deserve all the abundance and all the
excitement you can imagine for no other
reason other than the fact that you
can't imagine it. You don't need a
special reason to say I deserve
abundance. You don't need a special
reason to say I have to earn happiness.
If you can imagine it, if you can
perceive it, if you can conceive it,
that is sufficient to say that you
deserve it. Were it not something you
could have, creation would never have
allowed you the facility to imagine it
because creation does not do pointless
and extraneous things. You know, maybe
you don't know
that. Allow yourself to begin to know
that there are no extraneous and
pointless creations within existence. If
you find within your heart of hearts,
within your spirit of spirits, within
your soul of souls, within your flame of
flames, that you have an overwhelming
desire for a particular thing that
excites you above and beyond anything
else, that desire in and of itself is
the signal that that is true for you,
that that is correct for you, that that
is best for you, that that is your path,
that that is your goal, that that is who
and what you are, or you would be
excited by something else.
ment as Bashar has explained many times
is your physical translation of the
vibrational energy that represents the
path you chose in this life. The things
that excite you the most are the
harmonic resonances that represent your
alignment with your path of effortless
excitement and abundance.
Excitement is the answer that many of
you have always asked for when you say
give me a sign. Why am I here? What is
my mission? What is my purpose? What am
I supposed to be doing? And something
comes along that is more exciting than
anything else. And because of the way
you have been taught many times you say
I recognize that you are very exciting
but I can't be bothered with you now.
I'm very busy looking for my purpose in
life. Everyone has told me that looking for my
Everyone has told me that looking for my
purpose is supposed to be a very serious
thing and so I have to apply myself in a
very serious way and I have no time for
fun. I'm sorry to
say. Be that as it may, the thing that
taps you on the shoulder and says I am
the most fun you could be having is the
answer to the prayers that you have been
sending up. The most exciting thing that
comes along that you can be doing with
integrity. Important point with all the
integrity you have all the unified
unconditional loving service that you
have within you the thing that you can
do that is the most exciting thing that
can be done in that
way nothing else is who you are at that
moment you can try and you can try very
hard to be someone else you can try to
live someone else's story as has been
pointed out and that's when you get
tired that's when you get run down
that's When you get how do you say
diseased because you are trying to be
someone you are
not. Trying is tiring. Maybe that's why
they begin with the same letters. I
don't know. But when you allow yourself to
know. But when you allow yourself to
understand that the doing of the thing
that excites you the most is who you
are. And because it excites you, it's
going to be effortless. And because it's
effortless, you'll be able to attract
abundance before you know it. When you
understand that's who you are, I should
think you wouldn't want to do anything
else. I should think that you would stop
trying and stop struggling to be who you
are not. But as we have observed your
society, some of you don't do that. I
don't know
why. I would think that you would
understand it is the easiest thing in
creation to be who you are. But many of
you have been taught that it is easier
to be something that you're not. You
have all been taught, you have all been
brought up with the idea, well, at least
most of you have, that if you don't
suffer and you don't struggle and you
don't strive, then you'll amount to
nothing. That if you don't work and
sweat and toil and do the things that
you really hate to do, that you won't
build character. You're all characters
character. You're all characters
already.
Laughter is the key. Laughter is the
key. Excitement is the key. For when you
laugh, you are accelerating your
vibratory awareness. You are creating
more of an affinity with your laughter
to the vibration you know is your
birthright. The vibration you know
beyond a shadow of a doubt is who and
what you
are. Let that vibration nurture you.
Let what you call creation the father,
creation the mother, creation the
blended idea, let it support you upon
waves of joy because you were created
out of joy. You were born out of the
joy, the ecstasy of
creation. Do not treat yourselves with
disrespect. Do not treat yourselves with
any less respect than creation has for
you. It created you out of ultimate
ecstasy and joy. Why should you treat
yourselves with any less respect than
that? Why should you believe that you
have to earn the right to
exist? Why should you believe you have
to do something to deserve to earn that
right of existence, something
special? You are already special. And
because you are all special, you are all
unique. And because you are all unique,
no one is more special than anyone else.
That is the paradox of creation that you
are all equal and yet at the same time
you are all
special. Live your
specialness. Live your
uniqueness. You cannot be anything but
unique. Why try to be the same?
Now is the age upon your planet where
you are beginning to realize that what
life is all about is learning to be
natural rather than how do you say
normal. Being natural will allow you to
blend with every other being. You don't
have to be normal to fit in. If you
exist, you fit in. There are no
extraneous creations.
Nothing was made that is an extra piece.
Oh, God will say, "I'm sorry I made you.
You don't
fit. How did you get
there? I did not make any room for you.
I'm sorry. You'll have to
leave." What? There is no outside to
leave to? Well, that's your
problem. You'll have to find an exit
door. And if you don't find that exit
door quickly, I may turn into a jealous
and avengeful God and start throwing
lightning bolts at
you. The story that we have created is
to simply point out that it is from the
feelings of
selfdoubt, from the feelings of guilt
and the feelings that you don't fit that
all manifestations of negative
relationships with the universe are
constructed. Because if you feel you
don't fit, you start resenting
everything that does
fit. And that's when you start getting
angry. And that's when you start getting
frustrated. And that's when you feel out
of control. And that's when you feel
like you're sinking down into black
oblivion. You don't want to be alone.
When you sink down into black oblivion,
you want to take as many individuals
with you as you possibly
can. And that's when you start doing
things against other individuals that
are not
loving. It's because you do not feel
loved. It's because you do not feel you
are empowered. It's because you deny
yourself the birthright that you were
created with to be a part of
creation. You fit. If you exist, you
have to fit. There are no
exceptions. You cannot be where you do
not belong. If you do not prefer what you
belong. If you do not prefer what you
are getting, you have the free will and
the right to change that
scenario. But learn from the scenario
you did create, the one you did not
prefer, because that was your creation,
too. Excitement is where you're at, is
where you
are. Being
impatient, having to get somewhere else
is a denial of the beauty and the
excitement of where you are. And if you
don't live where you are, you can't get
anywhere else. Because every place,
every moment is a stepping stone to
every other moment. And if you deny the
validity of the stepping stone in front
of you, you can't reach the one
beyond. Live to the fullest where you
are. And that now will connect to every
other now you can possibly become.
Living in the moment is what makes
accessible all potential
realities. Nurture yourself. Love
yourself. You deserve it. You are made
of
love. Be as the child of
creation. Speaking of
children, let's play.
Close your
eyes and take three more of those
wonderful deep breaths you have come to
know and
love. If you feel like taking a few
laughs along with it, that's all
right. And allow me to remind you of
this as well.
If you find at any time that there are
tears, let them be tears of release,
tears of joy, tears of
gratitude. Gratitude that you have the
ability that you have the gift of
creation to be whatever and whomever you
desire to
be. Those tears, those tears, they are
prayers. They are communications with
the infinite. They are allowances.
allowing you to be who you truly are.
Remember, we understand the paradox of
the idea of what you call surrender. But
surrender is literally not giving up
control. That is the
paradox. Allowance. What you call
surrender. Going with the flow is
actually being in perfect control. It's
simply that your society is used to
thinking that if you don't experience
effort and if you don't experience
conflict then there's no controlling
going on to you. When something is
effortless means that there is no
control. But effortlessness is perfectly
balanced control. Let go. Go with the flow. Going
control. Let go. Go with the flow. Going
with the flow does not mean you have
lost control.
Your ego will not
die. Blending with the whole will not
render you less of an
individual. In fact, it will strengthen
the unique individual that you are.
And now in your
imagination allow yourselves to
see a bright grassy green
hilltop any time of day, any time of
night, trees or any scenario you
wish. But you are looking down onto a
vast limitless meadow of lush green rich
reality. And you are not the
adult but the
child. You are a child. Let us say
anywhere from oh 3 to 7 years of
age and you are looking upon that meadow
with the bright eyes of
discovery as a child once
again and there is a child next to
you of of
similar
sexuality on one side and a child next
to you of opposite. opposite sexuality
on the other side. And you reach out
your hand, your little child hand, and
you grasp the child hands on either
side, and you look down into the
beautiful meadow of promise and
abundance, and you see the abundance in
that meadow. You see with the eyes of a child
meadow. You see with the eyes of a child
that meadow is limitless. It is full of
discovery, full of new things. Every
step into that meadow is the first
step. You do not know what you're going
to
discover, but you are willing to find
out because you know that there is
absolutely nothing absolutely nothing you could
nothing absolutely nothing you could
ever discover that cannot be applied in
a positive way.
You are brimming with
excitement and you take your first steps
hand in hand down the hill into the
meadow of tall, lush, wet, moist, rich
green grass. And you feel it on the
bottom of your
feet. And perhaps you roll down the
hill, laughing and crying and releasing,
feeling the sun and the wind and the
moon and the stars on your skin, feeling
the soil and the richness of the green
growing things and the living life
around you. And your heart hammers like
a child with great
exhilaration. And you run and you play
and you laugh and you yell and you
express and you declare who you are to
the universe and you are not afraid to
be who you are and you have no fear of
rejection from the universe. The
universe wraps you in waves of warmth,
sends you waves of love, and enjoys your
frolicking and your playing.
enjoys the raw creativity of your
childlike being and
rejoices in having given birth to you.
For you are a delight in the eyes of
creation because you are literally made
of living
light. Explore your meadow.
Laugh and run and play and sit and
contemplate. Talk and
sing and
dream. Lay back in the
meadow. Clouds
overhead, stars
overhead. And close your imaginary
eyes and dream.
and dream as a child.
Dreams of all realities, none of which
are impossible. All of which you feel with
impossible. All of which you feel with
all your emotion, with all your
excitement, with all your conviction.
For a child is the very essence of
trust. A child is the very essence of
conviction and does everything to the
fullest that the child can do. There are
no halfway measures for a
child. There are no halfway steps for a
child. There are big bold steps, great
steps, great
strides, infinite
realities, unlimited
potentials, surprises around every
corner, corners everywhere to turn,
challenges and expansion. And as
And as
always, there is
love, freshness,
freshness,
newness, and as always, playmates to run
and hop and skip and jump with. Never
alone unless solitude is what you will
unless solitude is what you will
enjoy. But even in your solitude, you
are never cut off. the vibrations of the
living things around you. Life
itself wraps you in a blanket of
love. You are
alive. You are
vibrant. All creations
are alive within your
heart. You are the pulse of the universe
as every child knows.
Breathe now as a
child full breaths of
full breaths of
life. Full and
exhilarating rebirths. You are your own
child. You are your own mother. You are
your own father. You are all your
playmates. You are all the little girls.
You are all the little boys.
You are the playground of
life. Play
freely. There are no fences. There are
no
[Music] chains. There are no
chains. There are no
bells to call you back to
structure. You are the structure of your reality.
You are the structure of your reality.
You are the framework upon which you
will build your new
adulthood. The adulthood you prefer to
be because you are the child you prefer
to be right
now.
Relive the childhood you prefer to live
and you will become the adult that is
the result of that
childhood. Breathe it in and so it is.
Breathe it out and there it is.
Breathe it in and melt down all the old
realities in the crucible of your
heart. Breathe it out and crystallize
the meadow, the forever meadow of
infinite play, infinite combination,
infinite manifestation, infinite
manifestation, infinite
creativity, infinite love.
Dream and play. Play and
dream. Breathe and
be. You are
living light. Focus
yourself. Open your
eyes and look through new windows.
You are a new child
reborn. And this is the first half of
your excitement, the first half of your
abundance, the first half of the
tool. We will share
more after you have enjoyed a loving and
playful and exhilarating break.
We will rejoin you in approximately 10
to 15 of your minutes of
counting. In those 10 to 15 minutes,
remember that you are no longer the same
person. Drink deeply with your senses of
the reality you are creating around you.
Allow the refreshment to come from
within. We thank you and we will reconvene as
We thank you and we will reconvene as
you say in a few moments of your time.
How's everything going? Oh,
All right. Allow us to continue in the
following manner. We have now discussed
the idea of the child within each and
every one of you. We have discussed the
idea that you can create around you a
meadow of infinite depth, infinite
abundance and infinite
play. We are talking about abundance. We
are talking about your right to attract
into your lives those things that are
representative of who and what you
desire to be.
It has been shared with many of you our
definition of abundance and as a
refresher once again we will share that
definition one more
time. Abundance is the
ability the
ability to create what you want when you
want to create it. Now once again
understand that there is specifically no
mention of the word money in that
phrase. Abundance can be money. In no way, shape
Abundance can be money. In no way, shape
or form are we denying the idea of that
particular symbol upon your planet. But
what you call money is only one of the
ways that you can experience abundance
in your
world. The ability, the ability to
create what you want when you want to,
that is abundance. And the ability can
come into your life in many ways. The
paradox once again of the situation
is that when you relax your
need for money to be the only way you
can imagine abundance can come to you.
When you relax that particular avenue.
When you allow other avenues to allow
abundance into your life other than just
one. When you are not so insistent on
one way being the only way that
abundance could come to you, then
paradoxically you will usually find that
you will have as much of any particular
symbol of abundance as you need. You
will have whatever you need to represent
the expanded idea of yourself that you
are willing to be. As was discussed
before, whatever level of conviction you
have in acting out physically acting out
those things that you desire in your
life, whatever level of conviction you
are willing to have to express the being
you say you want to be will be exactly
the reflection you will get from the
universe as to what you will be handed,
what kind of tools and what kind of
symbols of abundance you will be handed
to work with. Because the universe is
not going to give you a symbol of
abundance if you're not acting like an
expanded enough person. If you're not
acting like a person who believes they
can handle that much wealth, that much
success, that much abundance, the
universe will only give you exactly no
more and no less what you say you are
capable of handling.
Many of you may have many different
definitions about abundance, about being
successful, about being rich in many
different levels physically and
spiritually. And it is these definitions
once again the blueprints of your house
which can create a seeming difficulty or
a seeming inability to create the
abundance you say you desire. You can
have all the desire in the world, but if
you have a definition that blocks that
desire, then all that desire is only
going to bring you a buildup of
frustration. Allow yourself to recognize that your
Allow yourself to recognize that your
definitions can be very
intertwined. And therefore, it is always
very important and very critical to
clarify the definitions of your
abundance or your definitions of
anything you relate to in life in order
to understand what you believe and why
you are getting what you are getting.
Because you are getting what you are
getting because of what you believe.
Whatever you believe to be most true,
whatever you believe is the most likely
scenario that you can get in your life
is the one that will manifest in your
physiological reality. Let me give an
analogy. Many individuals in your
society have been exposed to different
notions of how an individual is when
they are rich.
It is a standard symbol in your society.
And I will use your common vernacular in
this just to paint the simplest possible
picture to think that when an individual
all of a sudden comes into a great deal
of wealth that they must begin acting
like an
idiot. None of you wants to act like an
idiot. If you have been ingrained to
believe that you cannot have wealth
without having
ostentatiousness without having bad
manners. If you believe that people who
have wealth run over other people, look
down upon other people. If you believe
that people that have wealth do not care
for other things are greedy and are only
focused on what they want and you do not
want to be like any of these people. And
if you make a strong
association, a strong association to the
idea that this is what wealth brings
you, then you will usually feel that you
cannot have wealth without having all
these things you do not want. If you
feel you cannot have wealth without
having all these things you do not want,
then you will keep the wealth at bay. As
long as you make an association that one
must come with the other, you will keep
what you want at bay. But when you begin
to understand that your definitions are
your prerogative and that you can create
any kind of definition that you want and
that the definition you create will be a
distinctly different universal reality
from any other definition you could
create. Then you can be very specific
about the type of reality you desire.
You can say all right well I want
wealth. I have come in my examinations
to realize that I believed that in order
to have wealth I had to be an idiot or
that if I got wealth I would have to
start acting like an idiot and I do not
want that. Why did I believe that?
Perhaps I was simply brought up
believing that idea. But now now I know
I do not have to believe that any
longer. I understand that the concept of
being successful, that the concept of
having abundance does not automatically
bring with it the idea of all of that,
all of the negative, all of the better
than thou attitudes. One does not have
to go hand in hand with the other.
Therefore, I can clarify my definition.
I can define what type of successful,
what type of abundant, what type of
wealthy individual I prefer to be, how
it is I prefer to express myself as a
wealthy individual, knowing beyond a
shadow of a doubt that everything that I
expressly define that does not belong in
the definition I prefer will in no way,
shape, or form have an ability to
manifest itself in my reality. What I
know is my preference will be the
reality that I get. What I know is not
my preference will have no way to sneak
into my reality. Unless, of course, I
choose to believe that things that I
don't prefer can sneak into my reality,
and that's a belief. Many of you have
those beliefs. I will paraphrase one
that we hear quite
often. Many of you say, "Well, all
right, let's say I choose a positive
reality. Let's say that is really my
desire." Well, it's going on and on and
things are being wonderful and positive
and as you say in your language, hunky
dory. And then many of you say, but how
long can this
last? This can't go on forever. I don't
know if I have the strength to maintain
this positive reality. All of these are
variations of the same idea that
something can slip in against your will,
against your decision. It cannot be so.
It has never been so. Your assumption
that something can slip in is definition
enough is belief enough to make it slip
in. But you are choosing to have it slip
in by your choice in your
belief. The idea is that you can be
doing something very positive. And here
is the phrase many of you use. And all
of a sudden you can slip out of a
positive reality into a negative one.
back as you say I might slip back into a
reality I don't prefer how is that so
how is it that you can slip in that way
let us paint this scenario you have two
mountains A is a positive mountain B is
a negative mountain in between is the
valley if you're going to slip off of
any of those two mountains the only
place you can slip to is the valley at
the center you cannot slip from a
positive mountain all the way over to a
negative mountain. You have to make a
choice to climb one mountain to believe
in one mountain or another. If there is
any slippage that occurs at all, you
will simply wind up back in the center
at rest at the bottom of the valley and
can still make your choice from there as
to go back up the positive mountain or
go up the negative one. But you will not
be in an automatic negative state. There
is no reason to assume that negativity
here is the important point. Are you all
paying attention? Thank you very much.
There is no reason to
assume no reason to assume that negative
reality is inherently more likely to
occur than a positive one. It is simply
how you have been trained to think.
Example, here is a story of individuals
that are going through many conflicts
and many struggles and many strivings
and maybe they succeed here and maybe
they fall back there as you say and then
maybe overcoming great odds they finally
succeed and they wipe their brows and
they are proud of themselves and you
walk away from the story saying, "Oh,
that was very realistic."
And over here someone says, "And this
person met this person and everything
was wondrous and everything was fine and
they lived happily ever after." And you
say, "Oh, what a fairy tale. Who
believes in that? That's not real life.
That's not reality." But why not? It is
because you have been trained to believe
that. It is because you have been
trained to believe that there can be
such a thing as too much of a good
thing. It is because you have been
trained to believe that good things may
not last. It is because you have been
trained to believe the following thing.
That in order to maintain the reality
you prefer, you have to have some sort
of stamina in order to do that. That it
requires some sort of effort or strength
to keep that reality from slipping back
into something you don't want it to be.
As if that reality were not a natural
state. It is a natural state. Whatever
you decide is your reality at any given
moment is your natural state. The only
way you can experience any other reality
is if you choose to. You cannot slip out
of your natural state. You can only
transform into other natural states
based on your beliefs, based on your
choices. Allow yourself now to begin to
truly understand that you are in control
and that the decisions you make stick
until you make another decision that
counters the first one. You are always
in control. Even when you are creating a
scenario that makes it seem as if you
are out of control, you're controlling
that. You are very sneaky
people. You are very clever people. You
are very creative people. All beings in
creation are that creative. And you have
for many thousands of years exercise
your creativity to play certain games of
hiding portions of yourself from other
portions of yourself. Now you are
through with that game. You have played
that scenario all the way out as you say
to its hilt. It is now that you are
learning that there are other games to
play. Games of integration, games of
remembering who and what you are. And
now you are beginning to explore those
games. And that is why we are capable of
having this interaction with you this
day of your time at
all. Now that we have discussed the idea
of how you play as a child, let us
discuss the idea of the adult that that
child has become. Let us take the
scenario another step further. And you
may all flutter your eyelids and go
deeply into your centered state of
perfect
peace. Three delicious
breaths. And as you
breathe more and more deeply, allowing
yourself to feel that perfectly centered
place. Once again allowing all sounds,
all feelings in,
integrating, integrating, inviting, acknowledging,
integrating, inviting, acknowledging,
inviting, accepting,
integrating everything in, everything
that you experience is a part of the
picture. Nothing extraneous. As you now
drift into that centered state of deep
and relaxed
breathing, allow yourself to see the
adult that you
are. See yourself standing there in
whatever you take to be your bodily
form, whatever comfortable form that
is. And allow yourself now the following
imagination
scenario. Standing approximately 10 ft
away from you and facing
you is a replica of your
body. See it, feel it in whatever way
works best for
you. Walk over to that
body. Look at that body.
Walk all the way around that
body. Float above and below that body.
Look at it from every angle. Become very
familiar. Begin to recognize what you
have created. Begin to see the
symbologies in what you have created as
they are representative of ideas that
you are working with, notions that you
may be working
through, directions in which you can be
moving, things that can give you a
suggestion of directions to move in. See
the encapsulization, the incorporation
of all the ideas. See them reflected in
that form. And
form. And
then face that
body standing once again approximately
10 of your feet
away and see that body. See those eyes
looking at
you. And now extend an
invitation. Acknowledge that body and
extend an invitation as you walk toward
that body. Allow that body to walk
towards you so that you will inevitably
meet halfway. And as you meet, open your
halfway. And as you meet, open your
arms, extend your arms wide, and give
yourself a big hug. Embrace yourself in
acceptance. And as you love
yourself, forgive yourself for
everything that you felt has been
negative in your life. Allow yourself to
recognize that they have all been
lessons. Allow yourself to recognize
they have all been for a reason, your
reason. Hold no grudges against
yourself. And as you accept yourself for
what you are and what you have created
yourself to be, integrate yourself by
imagining the two bodies merging into
one. And feel the hearts beating as one.
Give yourself permission to be one with
yourself and to love yourself
unconditionally. Love is what you are
made of. Love is your right of
birth. And now as you feel yourself to
be one being in this way, look around
and see again 10 ft from you another
body. But this time it is not the body
exactly as you see your own
body. The body that is now 10 feet in
front of you is the body you would have
had had you been born in this life your
sexual opposite. See what you would have looked
opposite. See what you would have looked
like had had you been your physically
sexual opposite. Look at the male if you are
opposite. Look at the male if you are
female. Look at the female if you are a
male. See what your twin would have been
as an
opposite. Go to it and walk all
around. Acknowledge the things that are
there, the shapes and the sizes, the
angles, the dispositions, the attitudes,
the carriage of the body. Float above,
float below. Observe it from all angles.
become familiar with the idea of how you
as a soul would have expressed yourself
had you been born this way
physically. Then go back to your
starting point 10 ft
away. And now allow yourself to
understand. You send out an invitation
and you walk toward the center. And that
body as it looks at you walks toward the
center. And any fears that may come up
dissolve in the light of your love. And
any apprehension dissolves in the light
of your love, in the light of your
understanding, in the light of your
forgiveness, in the light of your
support for anything you feel that that
aspect of yourself may have caused in
terms of
suffering. Forgive and love. It is only
an extension of you.
And as you meet in the middle with open
arms, embrace that portion of you, your
male or female
polarity. Hug and love and feel the
beating of your hearts pressing
together. Nurture and forgive and let it
be all right to love in a clear and open
manner. And then integrate as you hug.
Feel the bodies merging together until
you become one expression, one idea, and
see the bodies glowing with a light and
a life all their own. A renewed spirit,
a renewed fresh idea, a renewed balance,
a renewed
vigor, a renewed
vitality, the ability to give birth to
the self, the ability to support the
self, the ability to assert the self,
the ability to nurture the self, the
ability to support all others, the
ability to nurture all others, the
ability to
inspire all others by being fully the
self. Jealousy is simply when you see
Jealousy is simply when you see
something in someone else and you don't
believe you contain it as well.
Inspiration is when you see reflections
in someone else of that which you know
you also
contain. Be inspired by what you see. If
you have the ability to perceive it in
someone else, you must contain it as
well or you wouldn't be able to perceive
it in them. You can only perceive what
you contain. Be inspired.
contain. Be inspired.
Do not be jealous. You are not at war
with yourself. You are not your own
rival. You are not in competition with
yourself. You do not have the need to
split yourself
aunder. Marry yourself. yourself.
Forgive and
love. Acknowledge and go beyond the need
to forgive.
All is as has been necessary for you to
is as has been necessary for you to
grow. Nurture and
love. There is no
betrayal. There is no
underhanded. There is no backstabbing of
the self by the
self. All has been an illusion.
You are now in the womb of your own
birth, of your own life, and of your own
transformation. Love has always been
existence. Love exists now. Love will
always exist.
Unconditional love is yours to tap and
flow through your being so that you may
blossom like the flowers in the meadow
of your
childhood. Be the adult that is the
adult of that child. Be the child of
that adult. You are your own parent. You
are your own
child. You are
an infinite
being on wings of
light. As an
adult, it is all right to play. As a
child, it is all right to be
serious. Be both. Be
one. Be who you know you are. Who you
know you are.
flow with yourself as
yourself. At this point, take three
loving breaths and feel the life of the
universe flowing
through, flowing in, flowing
as who and what you are.
Open your eyes and know once again
beyond a shadow of a
doubt that I am not speaking to the same
individuals I was speaking to a moment
ago. I greet you all a
new. You are all in that sense in every
moment reborn. I wish you all happy
birthday. All your
All your
wishes, all of your wishes do come
true. All you have to do is define what
your wishes are and you will know why
you are getting what you are
getting. You are a great
gift. Surprise yourself in a joyful way
by being willing to unwrap the present
that you are. Share it with all other
beings for you are unique. And remember
also this, one of the greatest gifts you can
this, one of the greatest gifts you can
give is to allow others to give to
you. We thank you for allowing us to
give to you in this way. And we thank
you for giving such a beautiful gift of
yourselves to us. I thank you personally
for allowing me to interact with you at
this time.
and to share with you my
love. There will be a moment of
transition. Our love to you all.
We are old. You are old. We are ancient.
You are ancient.
You are eternal. We are
eternal. You are the fabric of existence
itself. You are a part of us. We are a
part of
you. You are consciousness
itself. Wave after wave of
consciousness manifesting itself in
simultaneous manifestations
multi-dimensionally. Always
dynamic, always
interacting, always creating a
new. You are endless, self-fulfilling,
self-contained. Creation, the eyes and
the dreams of all that
is. Dream
time. An idea that represents the
blending of what you have called
physical reality and non-physical
reality. What you have called
imagination and the dreams of your
deepest sleep. Dream time. A blending of
the two. So that you may be awake while
you are dreaming and creating the
realities that you desire. So that you
may understand that dreams are just as
solid as anything you call physical
reality. This is what you are entering as an age,
This is what you are entering as an age,
as a consciousness. You are creating
your reality to be a dream time in which
you can dream it to be what you desire
it to be, in which you can live the
dreams that give you joy. Dream time.
Many of you are beginning to experience
some of the sensations of dream time.
the idea of having a thought, having a
sharing, having a
communication and asking yourself, is
this something I actually said or did I
dream it? I do not remember. Where did
it come from? When did it occur? I do
not remember. Is it necessary that I do
remember? Not really. For the
communication is the thing is essential
and has been done. It is all that is
necessary. The information that I need
The information that I need
synchronistically comes to me when I
need it. I know what I need to know when
I need to know it. Need I ask anything
else? Need I worry about how it is
coming, when it is coming. Need I worry
about what I have known and when I have
known it, if I no longer need to know it
now. Dream
time. The solidification of all that you
have called nebulous and ethereal in
your lives. the solidification and
crystallization of that which has
formerly been beyond your
senses. Dream time, the breaking down of
all that you have held for thousands of
years to be the sacred solid physical
reality that you felt was external from
you. Dissolving, becoming more nebulous, more
Dissolving, becoming more nebulous, more
ethereal, more of what you may call the
limbo state, the gray state experienced
by many of you as confusion, as
disorientation. as a drifting in life deciding what you
as a drifting in life deciding what you
will and will not
do as being in
between ideas, as having no particular
path, no particular direction. That is
the foundation of dream time wherein you
are in that limbo state, that dimension
of imagination that touches all
realities and through which you can
access all realities.
Whatever you decide to solidify will
come into fruition and manifestation
within you and through you. Express
itself as your physical world. Dream
time. What your reality is becoming from
third density, thirddimensional reality
to fourth density, fourthdimensional
physical reality where you are
accelerated more truly beings of light
living in a matrix of
light where your world is elevated and
in your terms more accelerated and
refined. where there is less connection
to the denser material levels and more
connection to the ethereal realms, where
the ethereal realms become more real to
you than physical matter and where
physical matter is seen to be for what
it is a
dream. You are all dreaming now. You are
dreaming this interaction into existence
now. You are dreaming in every sense of
the word in a literal way right now. The
only difference that you create is that
you say physical dream is different from
all other dream and shall be more real
to me than any other dream. That is your
definition. You are relaxing that
definition now. You will not lose touch with
now. You will not lose touch with
yourself. You will not become insane
except to understand that insanity is
simply a perspective of a reality no
less real than yours that is not agreed
upon by the mass consciousness.
You will look into other dimensions and
know beyond a shadow of a doubt how to
retrieve that information and apply it
to the dimension you are focused in. The
only reason that the idea of insanity
exists in your world in the way that it
does is because those individuals that
perceive other realities have not been
taught that they can apply what they
have learned into the reality of which
they are also a part your normal
reality, your natural reality. They cut
themselves off. They cut the lines of
communication off and are not taught
that they have anything worth sharing.
They fold in upon themselves and become
self-contained loops that spiral them
further into
disconnection. Judgment and only
judgment and invalidation has created
the majority of what you would call the
insanity and disease upon your
planet. When you now understand that you
can validate all
validate all
realities, when you can understand they
are all representative of different
dreams of all that is and that they
interact and intersh and intertwine and
that no one reality is any more real
than any other
reality. You can remain focused where
you prefer to remain focused. And at the
same time, you can allow yourself to
still glean from all other realities
what you desire to apply in the reality
you are more strongly focused in as the
consciousness you are here. For do
remember you are also on every level of
existence that there is. And in those
realities your focus seems to be there
and in many of them there
alone. You always have bleedth through
from one dimension of experience to
another. Anyway, you always receive this bleedth
Anyway, you always receive this bleedth
through as different forms of
information that you need at various
times. This bleedth through will not
necessarily appear to have come from
another dimension of yourself from
another plane of existence because it
will always be automatically translated
by you into a format you can understand
and apply in this reality. So you may
not think that you are cross-talking to
other dimensions of yourself but you
always are. Many things that you simply
find as inspiration within you
automatically as you say out of the blue
come from other versions of yourself in
other dimensions of experience
communicating with you knowingly or
unknowingly. You are doing the same for
them inspiring them supporting them by
supporting the totality of your being.
The notion of a way you can use this
idea to assist yourselves in your
present is by knowing that each and
every one of you will always have a
future self. That that future self in
the way you choose to define it is
someone who has already been through
what you are going through now and knows
that you
succeeded. Be in communication with that
future self. Be that future self.
Be supportive of everything you would
call your past self. Tell your past
self, "You made it. You're successful."
Inspire your past self. Change the
spectrum of your timeline all the way up
and down. That continuity shift. Pull
yourself up by yourself, all the way
from yourself. Be the future self in the
yourself. Be the future self in the
present.
Be expandedly connected to all selves
that you
are. Know that you are always
intertwined. Know that you are always in
touch. Know that you are never cut
off. Imagine this now. Closing your eyes
and once again orienting yourself to
your place of perfect peace with three
deep breaths.
Imagine that you are in the following
scenario. You are now
sitting on a bench on a street in a city
on your
planet. It is an enjoyable day. You are
looking across the street at a building
which has many
windows. In these windows, you can see
there are different activities taking
place. Some of them interest
you and you decide you would like a
closer look. You extend your hand and in your
look. You extend your hand and in your
hand appears what you would call a
telescope or
binocular. and you hold this telescope
or binocular up to your eye and you see
in their lenses a
magnification of those rooms across the
street and the people in those rooms
going about their business. And you
observe and you look around and you see
all that you wish to
see and you are inspired by your ability
to bring your senses that much more
closely to those individuals in that
room. Even though you are still sitting
upon that bench enjoying the
day and you take the binocular or
telescope down just to check where you
are looking and you see that the
building is still there and that you are
still on the bench and you raise the
telescope or binocular up once
again and are greeted by a
magnification of that image.
And as you find that something catches
your attention, you follow it. You
follow a person. You focus on an
object and you see perhaps in one corner
of one room what you would call a
glowing television
screen and it catches your
attention and you make an adjustment on
your telescope, on your binocular to
bring in the magnification even larger
and you become absorbed with what you
are seeing. This information, this
fascinating information on this screen,
you are absorbed and you cannot take
your eyes off of it. It fascinates you
and you begin to realize that they are
doing very exciting things in this
building and that perhaps you are even
considering being a part of it.
And as you watch the magnification of
the television screen, you all of a
sudden realize that the binocular and the
realize that the binocular and the
telescope is no longer there. That your
senses are next to the television
screen, that your eyes seem to have
moved. And you look around and you see
you are in the room itself. And you look
back out the window and there you are
sitting on the bench holding the
telescope, holding the binocular, but
your senses are now in the
room looking at anything you wish to
look at. All objects, bring them up,
magnify them, bring them close to the
sense of your sight. Observe them in
every way, shape, and form. color, size,
mass, temperature, move from object to
object, person to person in the room
just with your eyes as if your eyes were
remote and
floating. You can go
anywhere in the
building, look at anything,
anyone, they will not see you.
It is simply as if your sense of sight
itself is able to magnify anything and
anyone. You are overjoyed and you feel
an exhilarating rush. And in that
exhilarating rush, you allow your sense
of sight to snap back to your
body. And you lower the binocular and
you lower the
telescope and you look around and you
are sitting on the bench and you look
and there is still the
building and you realize yes truly your
sense of sight was in the
building and you did not have to rely on
the telescope or the binocular any
longer. You had magnified your
experience. You had allowed yourself,
your consciousness, your sense to extend
beyond the idea of your physical form
because you
know that your consciousness contains
your physical form and that your
consciousness can expand as a bubble
beyond your physical
form. And that anywhere the skin of that
bubble chooses to expand, your
consciousness is there and can be
anywhere on the surface of that bubble.
And it takes no time to travel around
the surface of that bubble. You can open
an eye in one position and close it and
open it again in the next. No matter how
far apart those two positions may be,
they are interconnected and are a part
of the surface of the skin of the
expanding bubble of your
consciousness. And now for a moment,
simply rest upon the bench.
Let the binocular and the telescope fade
into the
air. Fade out of your reality. Let it
dissolve. You have no need of it for the
moment. And look around. Look around and
begin to see all of the physical reality
around you vibrating with bright
sunlight until it seems to vibrate with
a life and a color of its own. Every
object, every lamp, every tree beginning
to vibrate, reflect sunlight brighter
and brighter until everything looks as
what you would call a mirage,
shimmering, vibrating, becoming more and
more transparent, more and more liquid,
more and more air until you can begin to
see through these
objects. And you are
fascinated and you play with this idea
allowing them to become
solid and then allowing them to heat up
and become mirage
like and you
realize that all of these waves of
energy are emanating from your sense of
sight itself. that your sense of sight is
itself. that your sense of sight is
responsible for the creation of all that
you see. That what you see around you that
see. That what you see around you that
you thought your eyes were receiving are
simply projections of your sense of
sight. And as you move your head from
left to right and up and down, all is
seen as a wavering mirage.
The bench upon which you are sitting is
a solid thing. The only solid thing
which now floats in a sea of wavering
energy like waves of heat rising from a
hot pavement. Everything is
pavement. Everything is
fluctuating. Everything is
undulating. And slowly you begin to
perceive the following idea.
There seemed to be other objects that
were not there
before. In between the ones you were
familiar with, overlapping, fading in,
double, triple, quadruple exposures of
different realities. You are bridging the
realities. You are bridging the
barriers, the veils from one dimension
to another, from one parallel world to
another. You are seeing the comingings
and the goings of many individuals who
do not see you, who do not see each
other, but pass through each other as if
they were specters and
ghosts. You are seeing overlapping
vibrational realities. Each reality you
perceive thinks itself to be one solid
reality to the exclusion of all others.
But now you see the amount of traffic
that actually exists in the same place
simply on different wavelengths,
different frequencies. So they do not
interact with each
other. And yet you all see that they are
made of the same energy and the same
energy connects them all and they are
manifested out of the same energy that
manifests you. So that you know on some
level they are all in
communication. Even though they may play
that they do not know it so as to
maintain the focus of their world for
the specific idea and the specific
experiment and the specific game they
wish to play because that is creative
too. And you begin to
understand that many of them are
different versions of you going on about
their business. And you decide to get an
business. And you decide to get an
idea. And you look around in those
different realities. And lo and
behold, you see
reflections of different
views sitting on different benches. All
staring at you.
all staring at each other, all realizing
the reality of each other's existence at
the same
time. And you feel something in your
heart, and you feel something in your
solar plexus, and you feel the prickling
and the tingling sensation all up and
down your spine that you now see each
other. And you now know each other
exists. And you also know that you are
extensions of the same one being, the
same one consciousness. And that all of
the different fragments sitting on all
the benches, they are not who you are.
Whatever that combination is of all of
those U's, whatever that space is in
between all of those versions sitting on
all of those benches, whatever the
interaction is between you, that is the
actual you. You, the consciousness that
you are, is the interaction itself that
gives rise to all of the observers and
all of the interacting components. You
are the event
itself watching itself from all the
different angles, all the different
points of view, all the different
realities that it can possibly watch
itself from. You are a self-reflecting
multi-dimensional multiaceted
crystal. This realization washes through
you, washes over
you. You are
everywhere. You are every when you are
every one.
All things are the same one thing
manifesting in all the multi-dimensional
simultaneous dynamic ways that it
can. And you feel the expansion and the
exhilaration. You are not alone. You are
never alone. You are intertwined and
interconnected, eternal and infinite.
You go on forever in all the infinite
combinations that can possibly occur.
on and on and on. Sitting on benches of
different makes, of different styles,
sitting on the grass, sitting on the
ground, walking, standing, running,
flying, swimming. You are looking at
yourself in an infinite variety of
combinations forever and
ever. And each and every single
one is at the center.
Allow yourself now to look from the
point of view of as many of those other
individual U's as you care to. Seeing
you, looking at all the other U's.
Seeing from all the different
perspectives through all the different
eyes, tasting, feeling, smelling,
sensing what each of those worlds are
like. You know them all. They're all
within you.
The doorway is through you. Magnify
yourself and you contain them
all. Breathe. Breathe.
Breathe.
Breathe. All of you in all realities are
breathing simultaneously at this moment.
For this moment, you are all breathing
one breath.
breath.
Breathe. Feel the expansiveness. Feel
the crystallization through your
corporeal forms. You are one body, one life, one
forms. You are one body, one life, one
pulse, one
being. You are the fabric of
consciousness itself. You are galactic.
You are the power of the rotating system
of stars. Millions upon millions of
consciousnesses shining their light
through infinite space. You are infinite
space in which the light shines. You are
a projection of these things. These
things are a projection of the you are. Three deep
breaths. Bring yourself to the surface
now of your bench. Refocus on your
reality. Resolidify. Recristallize. Open
your eyes and recreate a room. A room around
eyes and recreate a room. A room around
you. Recreate individuals around you.
They are not the same. It is not the
room. It is a new
room. These are not the individuals.
They are new individuals. You are not
the same person. You are a new
being. This is not the same dimension in
which you began. This is another
Earth, an Earth more representative of
the reality you prefer to be. When you
change the vibration of your being, you
create around you and attract to you the
earth that is representative of who you
now are. Others around you may seem to
have changed. You are the one that has
changed and taken yourself to the earth
populated by beings that are more
representative of the you you are
now. If you wish to see anything in your
reality change, change
yourself, your
beliefs, your
emotions, your thought pattern, the
prism of your
existence. You are crystals. You are
light. You are
one. One moment. [Music]
All right, I'll say how do you all feel?
Oh, thank you. We are feeling wonderful
as well.
Allow yourselves an opportunity to
understand truly over the course of the
next 72 of your
hours that all manifestations, all
symbols that are reflective and
representative of the reality you say
you prefer will now begin to leak into
your manifestational physical reality.
Remember that you are dreaming right
now. Wake
up. Live the dream that you prefer to be
manifest through choice. Conscious
choice. Remember that unconsciousness
and subconsciousness in a sense not meaning
subconsciousness in a sense not meaning
to invalidate them are simply convenient
labels and convenient compartments to
put things you are afraid to look at.
You are one consciousness. You do not
really have an unconscious mind nor a
subconscious mind except as you create a
scenario where you need a bridge the
subconsciousness to a portion of
yourself that you have detached the
unconsciousness. Remember you can say well I know I do
Remember you can say well I know I do
not consciously know it but I know I
unconsciously know it. To say you
unconsciously know it is the same thing
as saying that you consciously choose to
not know. Allow yourself to balance this
know. Allow yourself to balance this
equation. Unconscious knowingness is
simply conscious lack of willingness to
know. There is nothing that you could
ever discover about yourselves that
would ever be able to harm you in any
way, shape, or form if you did not
choose to believe that scenario. There
is nothing that you could ever discover
about yourselves that cannot be applied
in a positive way because you say so.
You do not need another
reason other than because you say
so. Conviction, spontaneity, acting it
out, being not becoming, being the
person you desire to be. Always
being living. It is your
living. It is your
choice. It is up to you.
However you choose to do it will be
correct for you. And we will always
cherish any tool, any ritual, any path,
any method you choose to take because we
know beyond a shadow of a doubt that no
matter what you choose to think of
yourselves, you are worth believing in
that you are absolutely self-empowered.
We know that beyond a shadow of a doubt.
I will hesitate not one microsecond to
say you are capable of
anything. Some of you know that. Maybe
not in a positive
way. But allow yourself now to know that
you are remembering who and you are and
you are waking up from an old dream. A
dream of segregation. A dream of
separation. A dream of limitation, a
dream of
negativity. And you are awakening into a
new dream of integration and
unification, of joy and
spontaneity and
ecstasy. Define the reality you
prefer. Live it. I guarantee
100% you will get
it because you are it. It does not come
from somewhere
else out
there. All travel in space and time is
traveling within. Your technology will reflect
that. At this timing, we extend to each
and every one of you once again our
deepest appreciation for the cocreation
of this
interaction, your willingness to view
all the facets of your being. And we
thank you for allowing us to enjoy and
to cherish all that you have created
yourselves to be. Exciting dream life
and life dreams to you all. An
unconditionally loving and fond good
day. [Applause]
How did it go?
[Applause]