look at this is everybody here from in
Alm New York can you believe
it anyway so I just want to turn it over
to
introduction going let you give it oh
no then you ask me
question thank
you empty seat seat you see here we need
two hey
people mentally or
[Music] physically up
understanding of most channelings or
medium ships is that they usually are
not in every case but usually seem to be
the product of an arrangement or an
agreement that is made prior to the
physical life itself and that your life
contains whatever kinds of scenarios it
needs to contain to get you to remember
that you made the agreement and to give
you whatever skills are necessary to
fulfill the agreement if you still have
a mind to and um how everyone gets there
of course is different depending upon
the style of Life they're living and the
type of person that they are and how
they need to arrive at that
awareness for me the biggest turning
point was about 14 years ago on two
different occasions within the same week
with four friends with me on the first
occasion and two friends with me on the
second occasion we had very close
physical broad daylight sightings of
Bashar spacecraft over Los Angeles first
time about 150 ft distant for about 30
40 seconds second time about 70 ft
distant for about the same amount of
time in both cases the same small
equilateral triangular dark uh gray
metallic craft about 40 ft on a side now
what I didn't understand at that point
aside from being excited about seeing
what everyone called a UFO and what I
understand now is that that physical
sighting those both of those physical
sightings were his way of tapping me in
the subconscious memory to get me to
start learning the things I needed to
learn to fulfill the agreement because
after the sighting I began doing more
research into UFO phenomenology and
metaphysical studies found that they
were quite intertwined in the literature
at that time and still are and in
reviewing that literature and
researching that literature came across
many other ideas such as channeling
eventually several years later someone
introduced me to several channels who
were practicing at the time in Los
Angeles and I went to check that out and
after a while when I had satisfied
myself that the information coming
through the channel seemed to be
workable the uh entity coming through that
the uh entity coming through that
channel offered to teach channeling for
whoever was interested because there
were several people that had expressed
an interest now even at that time I took
him up on the offer but it wasn't
because I thought I was going to wind up
doing this there really weren't very
many books on the subject and I figured
well I'll go into the class because I'll
see something new in action I'll learn
something new so I did go into the class
and when I was in a receptive state from
the guidance and the meditations that
were given from the other entity through
the other channel Bashar and his people
made the telepathic connection with me
as soon as they made that telepathic hit
the memory of having made the agreement
prior to the physical life came back
what came with it was the memory of who
they were who I was to them why the ship
sighting had occurred and many many
dream conversations that I had
completely blocked from my conscious
memory all came flooding back at that
one moment and I saw the path of
preparation that I had taken in order to
get to that point at that point the
telepathic message basically summed
itself up by saying okay now that you
remember you made this agreement do you
still want to fulfill it because it was
a choice and it all was is a choice
obviously I said yes and that was about
4 and 1/2 years ago and I have done it
for the last 4 and 1/2
years now Bashar does present himself as
a member of an extraterrestrial
Community they are in another
dimensional plane but they do have a
physicality it's not identical to ours
but it is similar in many ways um
I have through the sightings and a lot
of other experiences my own validations
for Bashar being who he says he is but
the one thing in particular that I
really like to stress especially to new
people is that there is absolutely
nothing about these interactions that in
any way shape or form insists that you
have to believe that Bashar is who we
say he is because I can't prove it to
you now anyway bashara said that maybe
in about 10 or 20 years when enough
change takes place on our planet he and
his people and other civilizations may
be able to more blatantly present
themselves and interact with us on a
physical level right now they're doing
it this way in much the same way that
disembodied Consciousness does it
through the channeling phenomena
expressly for the purpose of staying in
the background so that the information
in the interaction is the most important
thing and not who's delivering it he has
said many times that he's noticed in our
civilization that we have had a tendency
in the past to sort of lock onto the
messenger and throw the message in the
garbage can so he wants to make sure
that that doesn't happen to the best of
his ability so they stay in the
background so that the information is
really the only thing you can get a hold
of and through that information you can
if you use it prove to yourself that it
works but it's not critical to have to
believe that their opinion or their
point of view is any more important nor
more powerful than our own about our own
lives they're simply here to reflect to
us the ideas that have worked for them
and if we want those ideas to work for
us we can apply them or not it's
completely in our hands and they want us
to realize that it is in fact completely
in our hands so they're being very
non-interfering about their
sharing the word itself Bashar is not
literally his name in their society and
their evolution right now they're pretty
much telepathic and do not use names as
such but he realizes that we still need
it for convenience in conversation so he
chose the word out of one of our own
Earth languages it's actually Arabic
which is partly my background which is
why he chose it and the word even though
I didn't know what it meant when he
chose it cuz I don't speak Arabic seems
to have several different meanings he
gave one meaning and a lot of other
people who do speak Arabic have given me
different meanings over the years so
even though it has many different
meanings each and every one of them does
seem to apply to what it is he's doing
and the first meaning he gave is that
the word Bashar means Commander which is
something similar to what he is in his
Society the second meaning is just on a
very simple level means either the man
or the being and on a broader sense
Humanity in general I think perhaps the
most appropriate meaning is the Armenian
dialect because in that dialect the word
Bashar means messenger and that's
basically what it is he's doing is
acting as a go between between his
civilization and our
civilization so we use that as his name
just to refer to him
by now the one thing uh I know a lot of
you are familiar to some degree with
some of the tapes that we have done I
don't know to what extent a lot of you
are familiar with that but um one thing
I would like to underline especially for
people that are new to it is that Bashar
is a very direct entity he's not shy in
the least so I would ask that you don't
be in return in terms of your
interactions with him he's not going to
pull anything from you that you don't
want to talk about but I would like to
ask that you don't hold back from
talking about something or asking a
question if the only reason you're
holding back is because you feel it's a
silly question or you'd be wasting
everyone's time there's no such thing
every single interaction that anyone has
ever had with them has somehow served at
least the vast majority of the people in
the interaction so please recognize that
everything you're here to talk about if
it really is something you want to talk
about it's a gift and everyone can learn
from it so please don't hold back on
that account now when he comes through
he will usually say something first that
he feels is indicative of the group
Consciousness or he feels is necessary
to help unify the group Consciousness
and he'll just talk for a few minutes on
whatever subject he wants and then he's
basically going to turn it over to you
and he will do that by saying how may I
serve you or sharing both those phrases
basically means the balls in your court
you can ask a question have a discussion
anything you want the way we usually go
about this now is we have a line over
here these are the first four
questioners as each of them asks a
question and takes their seat next
person who wants to ask the question can
come up and fill the seat at the end as
they move up and we can just keep it
flowing so that there's no Gap in
between what we would like to ask if at
all possible um and I know sometimes
people forget this just because you get
caught up in the discussion you get
caught up in the moment is make an
attempt if you possibly can to
consolidate it to the single most
important question one question two
questions max if you can just because
that will give the most amount of people
an opportunity to get up here so it
doesn't monopolize the time very often a
lot of other people are going to ask the
questions you wanted to ask that you
didn't ask anyway so you will usually
get the answers through the course of
the entire evening so please you know
focus in on the single most important
issue and discuss that if Bashar carries
you further with it by all means follow
his lead but keep it concise if you can
so we can get as many people in the
interaction this evening as possible
since we are relatively limited for time
this will only be about 3 hours there
will probably be a break about halfway
through for about 10 or 15 minutes and
then it will continue for another hour
hour and a half after
that um if however and this is this is
the second important Point aside from
the idea of not being shy about asking a
question what's going on here as far as
I understand the mechanics
is basically it's a telepathic link up
my Consciousness becomes diffused or
defocused as the Persona that I normally
am when it is softened in that way I can
no longer analytically think I can only
feel directly and experience direct so
what happens is in being in that state
it allows his Consciousness to link with
mine and my Consciousness takes on for
lack of a better term the frequency or
the vibration of his thoughts so what
you're actually getting is a model of
his Consciousness made out of my energy
I'm acting like a translation box the
words that you hear he's not speaking
they are simply drawn from my
subconscious automatically to make the
most sense out of the concepts that his
thoughts are sending so I'm acting sort
of like a human telephone in that way
where you speak into one end it's
translated into electricity and
retranslated back into words at the
other end you're getting kind of an
indirect link up but because that's the
mechanism sometimes the concepts that he
talks about if they really are alien or
foreign to us may not make sense at
first or the word because they're simply
being automatically queed in may not
necessarily fit the concept precisely because the
fit the concept precisely because the
concept is different than something we
thought about basically what I'm saying
is that if for any reason any of the
information is not understandable to you
and you want the concept to be clear
stop him shout out loud Bashar I don't
get it could you clarify please no
matter whose question it is stop him in
the middle of the question if you don't
understand what he's saying and ask for
a clarification now the one thing I
would like to ask you is don't take the
opportunity to sneak in your own
question but let him clarify it and let
him get back to the questioner that he's
already dealing with so feel free
however to relate to him that directly
and that informally it's not rigid
there's no controls to this he relates
directly to individuals and it's a very
open Forum kind of a
discussion when I am going into the
altered state and when I'm coming out
because of the defocus of my
Consciousness I get a little bit
disoriented n none of this tires me none of it
n none of this tires me none of it
depletes me it actually energizes me but
when I do come out at the break and when
I come out at the end when he says
goodbye it takes me a minute to refocus
what I would just simply ask all of you
is that when he says take a break or
when he says good night don't get up and
talk or move all at once let me refocus
just for a minute and then I'll let you
know when I'm back if you all start
talking at once it's just a little bit
jarring and it scatters me because it's
like having a whole bunch of people
screaming in your ear when you're trying
to wake up in your bedroom in the
morning let me remember where I am and
who I am and I'll let you
know when I'm back and then you can run
around and scream and use the workout
equipment or whatever you want that
point it's
okay also when I'm going into the
altered state there will be a few bodily
adjustments none of this is painful I
only say that because sometimes people
say it looks like it is I'm having a
wonderful time so don't worry about it
it's just an automatic adjustment to the
energy much in the same way that your
muscle might twitch now and then if you
get an extra jolt you know of
electricity through your nervous system
um and also especially for the people in
the closer rows there will be a volume
change so don't be too startled it will
get a little bit
louder um for the people asking questions
um for the people asking questions
please if you're up here speak loudly
and clearly so that not only do we get
you on the tape so it's not a one-sided
conversation to the people listening to
the tape but so that also the people in
the back of the room can really hear you
so everyone can participate if someone
back there cannot hear someone up here
please feel free also to say could you
speak up please so that everyone can
participate to the best of our
ability I don't think there's anything
else I have to say at this
point I think you got
it okay um once again thank you very
much for coming bottom line to all the
is to really have as much fun as you
want the more light you are about these
interactions the lighter Bashar will be
with you so have a good time and I'll
see you all later thanks
[Music]
say how are you all this evening of your
time as you create time to exist perfect
are you all alive
allow us to begin this interaction this
evening of your time by laying down a
few of the following
foundations we have discussed with many
of you the whole
issue of the fact that you as many of
you already know are the creators of
your own physiological reality but not
many of you understand how you do that
what the mechanism is by which you
create that physiological reality we
have discussed many times that this
mechanism is directly Interlink with
what you call your definition
your belief system of the physiological
reality you think you ought to be
experiencing the physical reality you
have been taught to think you ought to
be experiencing the idea always falls
down on the notion of
definition your own physicists now many
of them not all of them but many of them
are beginning to realize that your
physiological reality really does not
have an empirical existence apart from
you that there is no such thing as
physical reality without your definition
of it without your imagination to give
it life to give it breath to give it
existence the idea therefore is that if
you are capable of getting in touch with
the definitions by which you have
created the physical realities you have
been experiencing for many thousands of
your years if you can change those
definitions to form whatever pattern you
desire them to form then you can very
simply and very easily create the
realities you desire to create when you
want to create them and exactly the way
you do in fact want to create them as
long as you understand that you are
doing what you are doing that you are
expressing the desires you are
expressing through Joy through love
through light through service through
Integrity there is absolutely nothing
nothing nothing nothing nothing that the
universe will withhold from you you have
a Birthright of ecstasy you are made of
light and love you are made of Joy it is
the proc fundamental vibration of
creation that what you call
unconditional love you are made of it it
is the prime frequency the prime medium
the prime Essence the prime substance
out of which all physiological reality
is shall we say
crystallized everything is energy
everything vibrates at different
frequencies the only reason there are
different things the very definition of
the word different simply is because
there are energies and frequencies which
are different rates different pitches
than other frequencies those difference
in frequencies is exactly what
determines what you perceive to be this
object from that object this person from
that person everyone is made out of the
same one homogeneous substance shall we
say the only reason you appear to be
different in that way is because of the
pitch the vibrational rate at which you
operate the level at which you operate
the level at which you define yourself
to be because you are and every being
within creation is a self-aware
self-reflective free will entity a
holographic representation of the
Infinite Creation you have the ability
to operate on any number of frequency
levels that you desire to those
frequency levels are automatically
determined by what you buy into most
strongly as the belief you believe is
most true for you now because of the
type of society you have created many of
you have been for a long time shall we
say heavy into self-
invalidation and this idea of being
self- inv validational has allowed you
to buy into belief systems that are not
necessarily representative of the belief
systems that would be precisely
reflective of who it is you have created
yourself to be of who it is you desire
to be many individuals may put
invalidation and judgments upon you and
you may without sometimes even
consciously being aware of it buy into
those invalidations and say yes you're
right I'm this I'm that it's not what I
really want to be but you must be right
because so many people tell me this idea
now sometimes sometimes individuals can
be reflecting to you something that you
may be doing that is not necessarily in
accord with who it is you could be
sometimes they can be reflecting to you
when you are not necessarily working
with within your integrity but that's
all right if you can simply take the
advice in the best light of
unconditional love and know that your
desire your overall intention is for
integrity then you will always be able
to use it in a positive and a
constructive way but when your Society
creates patterns and habits that are
generally negative generally domineering
generally power removing then those
particular atmospheres are not
necessarily just because you hear them
over and over again and representative
of something you really need to work on
just because everyone else has an
opinion of what you ought to be doing is
not necessarily mean that it is who you
are or what it is that you are best at
the idea is to remember that everyone is
a mirror that is how every being in
creation has been designed but a mirror
doesn't mean that what you see in it is
an absolute one toone reflection of
exactly the things you need to work on
sometimes an individual will attract
into their lives certain individuals who
may seem to be be
invalidation because in attracting those
individuals by not accepting their
invalidations they reflect back to those
individuals an opportunity to see what
it is like for an individual to stand on
their own two feet when they are
absolutely sure of what it is they
desire to do and can give back to that
invalidating individual an opportunity
to stand on their own two feet for what
they believe in for what everyone
believes in is also just as true and
just as valid as any other belief all
truths are true true in the ultimate
sense because you create your own
reality some of them may lack Integrity
some of them may have a high degree of
Integrity but nonetheless they are all
real experiences they are all true
dimensions of reality and not any one of
them is any more or less valid than any
other as an experience as a lesson every
situation has the potential for you to
learn something from it in whatever way
you wish to apply that idea it is
completely up to you when you are as
clear as you can be about the
definitions of life you have bought into
then you can use every situation and see
how it matches up to the definitions you
prefer to have you can take advice where
it works for you you can let it go where
you believe it doesn't and later on if
you change your mind that's all right
too because you have that capability you
have that capacity and you have that
right first step in the whole idea of
creating your reality to be what you
really desire it to be is in ceasing to
invalidate yourself because you you you you you are
yourself because you you you you you are
the only thing you have to work with in
your Universe you are the representation
in your way of the infinite and if you
invalidate that any part of it then you
do not allow yourself to function as a
whole being capable of using whatever
information may come to you from other
individuals in a constructive way if you
do not allow yourself to love yourself
unconditionally then you do not know who
you are and you do not have something to
stand up for to reflect back to everyone
else so they can see in you the shining
example of what they can also be in
their own way are you all following
along is this translating into your
language adequately thank you very
adequately thank you very
much the idea therefore in all of the
interactions that we have with you the
bottom line as you say for all these
interactions will be to remind each and
every one of you of your own personal
power that you already are aspects of
the infinite and to put you squarely in
touch or roundly in touch or
triangularly in touch with your
definitions so that you know why your
reality is the way it is so you can
create it to be the way you prefer it to
be as soon as you believe you are
capable of doing so it is completely up
to you completely in your hands
completely at this timing we will take this
at this timing we will take this
opportunity to thank you and extend to
you our deepest appreciation in allowing
us to experience your
Consciousness to us our civilizations we
are always most full of gratitude in
being given the opportunity to
experience the gift of your sharing for
through you we are allowed to see that
many more ways that Infinite Creation
has created itself to be and that
expands our understanding of creation
and what we have to explore and to learn
as well remember everyone is an equal
teacher and a learner and therefore a
sharer like anyone else we do not know
everything we know everything we need to
know to be who we need to be at any
given moment you also know everything
you need to know to be who it is you
desire to be at every given moment when
you need to know something else you will
know it when you become something else
you do not need to know it before that
you can know other things but remember
everything you discover everything
everything you know can be pertain to
who you are and who you desire to be in
the present remember that the present is
the only place you actually ever exists
and the only place you actually ever
will exist and the only place you
actually have ever existed it is always
now and always shall be now no matter
when it is you are Eternal beings
infinite beings and you are capable of a
multitude of changes in multiple
dimensionality that is what it means to
be made in the image of God in the image
of the infinite Creator a
multi-dimensional being you are
multi-dimensional creators too and in
these discussions and interactions it is
our desire to remind you of that to
reflect back to you what you already
know for remember no matter what you
think of yourselves we believe in you
utterly and so we thank you for choosing
at this time to be
representation of your civilization we
thank you for being ambassadors and
diplomats of your civilization we thank
you for allowing me to be
representational of our civilizations
and the association of worlds for there
are many listening in on this side as
well in return for the gift you are
allowing us to experience by co-
creating these interactions I will ask
you now at this time in what way may I
be of service to you remember to speak
loudly please okay hello Bashar I good
day you can say that's all right okay
good um I have two question questions
number one number one is I had an
experience a while back I would like to
understand a little better all right a
little more about Define um I felt as if
I was I was conscious at this time and I
was lifted up into another place that
was very light it had lights on both
sides but they weren't um defined by
this kind of phys understood good and um
it was a very pleasant place I felt that
yes very content there there were um
beings yes God yes uhhuh on at the end
of it but there wasn't any way that I
could go there I I was informed that I
would have to go back yes that it wasn't
time yet for me to go there correct and
I not permanently so to speak so to
speak and I would like to understand
what that was about very typical it's
very natural all of you are astrally
connected many of you now that you
expanding your senses are allowing
yourself by accelerating your energy to
uplift yourselves to include the
physical and non-physical as one realm
one reality so that you can extend
yourself into what you call the astral
realm the etheric Realms the causal
Realms wherein there are also many
beings very busy doing their business
helping other beings going about many
other projects and ideas and Endeavors
there are guides to assist any and all
from your realm that may float shall we
say up into that realm because you are
now expending your Consciousness and
extending your senses to help and assist
you in becoming more comfortable with
that energy so that you do not run away
from the earth where you chose to be but
so that you take that energy back to the
Earth so that you can use it in loving
and positive ways to elevate the entire
vibration of your planet into that
astral level to become the fourth
density or shall we say the new age
fourth dimensional Earth that you are
heading toward you understand yes so you
were simply in a sense given an
identification an alignment you were
allowed a taste you allowed yourself a
taste you chose to identify with that
energy so you would know what that would
be like so you could bring that down to
earth and Elevate that vibration to meet
it halfway and uplift many individuals
including yourself you understand yes
does that serve you yes second
part I would like to know about the
connection between Orion and
Scientology we will be
brief let us simply say
basically that there have been other
Stellar systems in which many different
ideas have been expressed and some of
these Stellar systems have expressed the
high degree of limitation regulation
negativity those beings many beings
within those Stellar systems that
desired shall we say to break free of
those limitations of that expression of
negativity of those negative
Cycles incarnated in other Stellar
systems such as your own wherein they
perceive there would come a time your
present date now where the whole issue
of positive and negative reality would
be looked at once again on a global
scale so they could bring their
experiences their desires from the other
Stellar systems and assist in the
transformation of that world by learning
how to blend the idea of the positive
and negative into a balanced state so
that positive effects only would be
chosen to be manifested upon that planet
the idea of the particular shall we say
technology or tool that you have called
scient not that other individuals cannot and
not that other individuals cannot and
have not participated it is essentially
an Orion designed tool to Aid and assist
those that have very strong ancient Oran
connections to adapt into the Earth
vibration through a methodology they are
used to some of the idea of outline some
of the idea of structure that they are
used to so that bit by bit that
structure can be dissolved at whatever
rate you are comfortable with so you can
expand in a way that will be of
assistance to the transformation of the
earth you understand yes any way your
imagination now desires to transform and
change it into what works best for you
is the appropriate timing for the
changer any tool is valid every tool is
valid but the idea is simply that when
it no longer works for a new you then
use something
else right everything is equal that is
all there is to
it it was simply designed to allow a
particular kind of energy to reincarnate
into a familiar pattern so they have at
least some sense of home some sense of
idea of this is familiar I can deal with
this I can work with this and I can work
through it now because it has been
softened by being in another system you
understand yes does that help you yes
very much well thank you very much for
your sharing thank you sh hi M and you
good day I have a question yes many of
us here were at one time involved in a
very tight group tight yes close all
right family like family family yes why
are you not family now that's why I was
I'm here now I want to find out how this
intolerance of each other is serving oh
intolerance all right
intolerance remember this if I may
simply reverse the idea into a
particular point of view any Unity that
you desire upon your planet or anywhere
on your planet will only be the product
of the grand of equality and validity to
the infinite diversity of the
individuals on your planet everyone and
every point of view when it is seen as
equal to every other point of view
whether you agree with it or not that is
what will allow Unity to take place you
don't have to agree you don't have to
have the idea of exactly the same point
of view the same
approach if each and every individual
will be willing to recognize that there
is no one way to recognize one's
relationship to the infinite if there
were only one way there would only be
one person look
around every being every individual is
yet another way that the infinite has of
experiencing itself intolerance exists
because your Society has forgotten that
every individual is an aspect of the
infinite and has forgotten that no
matter how different things seem
everything if it exists must fit because
there are no extraneous
Creations so intolerance is only the the
forgetfulness that everything belongs
where it is and that there are no
accidents now each and every individual
can learn through other individuals
differences many ideas not only can you
learn different points of view but you
can take another individual's point of
view and adapt it to your own you can
alter it in what way works for you but
also intolerance does not allow an
individual to really recognize who they
actually are because you can use
differences in the following way as well
many times especially because of the
type of society I have created it is
actually easiest for some of you to
discover Who You Are by seeing so many
examples of who you are
not so the idea is that if you see these
examples of who you are not and you
spend time invalidating them then you
never give yourself an opportunity to
find out who you are because as you
invalidate others you invalidate
yourself because you attracted them in
your life you must attract everything
for a reason if you can understand that
there is always some reason why an
interaction is going on then you can get
out of it what you need to get out of it
to be who you are and you can be of
service to the other individual to allow
them to get out of it what they need to
get out of it to be who they need to be
the idea is not to become like each
other in modality in style the idea is
to be of one Mind by allowing every
individual to be the strongest
individual they possibly can be
individuals forget this because they
think Unity is the product of Conformity
Unity is the product of the granting of
equality to diversity because the
universe is infinite and
diverse understand does that help you oh
very much thank you oh thank you very
much sh hi and who you
today oh there's so many different
things that I could talk about but I
think I'll
I I have some wonderful animals at home
wonderful animals oh yes oh they're
they're just super super animal
super and they bring brought us so much
happiness I have our dog in particular
has been well just lately we've been
starting to call him Sea Dog he he start
fine well he looked like a dolphin oh
all right you know from the sea and he
was moving around do perhaps from the
dog star of ser well you want to
understand the reference I I know I've
heard references to sirius yes Sirius
energy is connected to Dolphin energy on
your planet and since you call Serius the dog
planet and since you call Serius the dog
star it is also connected to the animal
you call the dog in the sense that the
animal you call the dog is the guide on
your planet that generally represents
service and companionship and compassion
yeah well and I'm conditional love yes
yes that's what I've been feeling it was
like when I started calling him Sea Dog
and and you know he all of a sudden made
overtures to me and came up on me and I
we've always been close but all of a
sudden it just like we had a special
bond you accepted the recognition of a
portion of yourself within yourself and
the animal recognized your acceptance of
that portion of yourself and so the bond
is of course very much closer because
it's now within you yes yes and I every
even when he's sleeping and I I think
just you know Sea Dog he'll kind of like
open his eyes
or we also have a cat named wilsy and
She Glows a pink glow around her um and
she she's just so and I know that she
she's been with our family before yes um
many animals do also have
reincarnational existence because they
serve very reflective roles for many
individuals remember that all animal
Consciousness chooses to function as a
guide as a reflection for many of the
things that all of you need to
understand about yourselves yeah well we
made up sort of like a whole idea about
where she came from and one my husband
and I just did this and we got the the
the name air a y are like she came from
air and we made up a whole story about
what that was and everything in kind of
a joking manner
but but remember your imagination on
some level is real because you cannot
imagine non-existence right yeah so I
wondered if that was a real place in a
sense yes remember that you are a
reflection of the infinite Creator and
even though certain places in your
imagination may not necessarily apply to
your physical Dimension if you can
conceive of it somewhere somehow it must
be real because all imagination is
representational of real reality it may
be real in someone else's terms maybe
not real to you in the sense that it is
solid but it is real and an experience
to someone some level of your
Consciousness knows it is an actual
experience that is going on if it makes
sense to you then it is a vibrational
reality that carries the reality it
needs to for you if it fits if you can
apply it into your reality if it
symbolizes what you need to feel then on
that level it is very real and that's
all that counts yeah that's true also oh
yes there are very strong Egyptian
connections between you and that
animal and also between my son too Egyptian name Egyptian name
[Music]
Danny yes some yes
also other Mediterranean connections
uhuh thank you well thank you very much
byebye sh hi Melle you good day I really
just wanted to say hi to you all right
next all right all
right sitting here ask you something oh
all
right I I constantly get reminded of um
some sort of connection with water okay
right um how does that allow you to feel
when you are reminded of that connection
how do you feel about water I like water
a lot
why I like being in water why
uh it's kind of like soothing kind
peaceful all right that's a real good
name peaceful peaceful all right yeah
continue um I've noticed since I was a
kid though it seems to be a constant
connection like I moved to Ocean Drive
I've been connected to schools where the
you know the teenss are dolphins I lived
in Florida roamed up and down the beach
you know so what do you want to do with
this connection how do you wish to use
this energy this understanding this
connection in your
reality I want to well that's what I'm
asking you I'm trying to find
out I'm trying to find out like I feel
that there's something there for me but
I all right that's we will discuss it
with you but only after you allow your
full imagination to come out because
there are many things you have
fantasized about but you are not
considering them to be valid
methodologies making a living in other
words by
doing so discuss first the scenarios
your imagination has already given you
about what you have fantasized doing
with this connection and then we can
discuss this issue
further how have you wanted to use this
recognition have you wanted to play with
Dolphin oh many have you wanted to work
with them in many ways definitely in
what way um how do you see yourself when you
way um how do you see yourself when you
think of the idea of working with them
what pictures come into your imagination
first most easily and what pictures give
you the most Joy swimming with them
first of all just being with them and
enjoying it all right fun all right what
else um talking talking in what way
[Music] and
and
telepathy all that are you getting
pictures uh more yeah
describe the picture go with the flow of
your imagery describe it become excited
about it okay
um well don't let me Force
you I don't want to force you to have
too much
fun you don't really want I pies of like
uh
ocean and and like I was connected to
Marine Research Center all right all
right yes and what are you doing what
are you
doing talking with them yes yes I don't
know what about all right all
right may I ask you a personal question
certainly thank you very much why aren't
you doing these
things I don't know
know
well well you answer
I don't know yes you do why aren't you
doing these things you know very well
why you are
not why
not what stops you what ideas come into
your imagination that stop
you oh thank
you all right what is it do share well
money money uh I guess there's I mean the
money uh I guess there's I mean the
problem so excited about so many things
okay but like my excitement lasts about
a week in this and then a week in that a
week in this well I I feel like I should
focus more on one thing maybe maybe not
why well maybe all those different
things are simply different ways of
doing the same one thing and that is
your overall Focus maybe all those
different methodologies are simply
different tools of doing the one thing
that really excites you you don't have
to necessarily look at them as ually
exclusive you know as contradictory you
know they could be
all experiences you could be having to
help you do the thing you really want to
do and as we said it is our perception
that the strongest shall we say block is
simply that you don't think you can make
a living if
this oh yes it's a wonderful fantasy
it's a wonderful picture but everyone
knows that's no way to make a
living this what we were discussing
before the idea of what everyone tells
you all of a sudden it becomes your
reality because you buy into it give me
one reason why you can't make a living
doing that do you know that there are
that do you know that there are
individuals on your planet that do make
a living doing that really where are
they the ones in what you call those
research centers interacting with those
Dolphins right now you are aware that
they exist yes yes why can't you be one
of
them Give Me One Reason
uh are you one
hold if I may shorten the process I will
simply perceive that you will not be
able to come up with one reason that I
cannot turn
[Music] around I had a feeling that all right
around I had a feeling that all right
there is absolutely nothing stopping you
from doing what you want to do
understand this the things in your life
that excite you the most are what you
are all about that's why they excite you
and if they excite you because they are
what you're all about the universe will
supply you with whatever type of
abundance is necessary to allow you to
keep being whoever it is you are so you
will be able to make whatever kind of a
living you need to you will have exactly
what you need when you need it doesn't
necessarily always have to be money
that's one of the tools that exists on
your planet doesn't exist on ours we do
not need it our interactions are more
direct than that but it is just as valid
as any other tool any other
representation of abundance it is simply
that you do not always need the money
and that the idea of money isn't always
the quickest way in order to have the
abundance you need to do what you need
to do because remember the definition of
abundance is simply the ability to do
what you want to do when you want to do
it that's all if it comes in a number of
different ways what do you care as long
as you still have the ability to do what
you want to do when you want to do it
understand yeah I understand that do you
believe it can you allow it to be that
it can you allow it to be that
simple uh sometimes sometimes all right
fair enough always be honest with
yourself because if you do have
difficulty believing it then deal with
that acknowledge that you have
difficulty believing it don't deny it
denial is the first step to forgetting
everything about who you are don't deny
anything about yourself including the
fact that you have denial allow yourself
to deal with the fact that you may be
denying that you have a certain belief
that you do buy into the idea of doubt
and fear and self- invalidation it's all
right to acknowledge that you have those
feelings if you don't acknowledge them
and you don't deal with them you can't
change them you cannot transform what
you do not own first of all so own it
say all right all right I do it
sometimes because sometimes I don't
think I'm capable it's all right to
think that way you see the whole issue
is that once you own that it's all right
to think that way you have made it clear
that it was your choice to choose the
negative reality and once it's clear
that it was your choice it's back under
your control
understand yes so is it all right
sometimes I don't think I'm capable of
doing what really excites me the most
acknowledge that you believe that and
then get into a very honest discussion
with yourself about why you would choose
to believe that way once again bring it
back to clarifying your definition what
kind of beliefs would you have to have
what kind of definitions would you have
to buy into in order to feel that you
couldn't do the thing that is most
representative of who you are because
that's what it excitement is the thing
that is most representative of who you
are that's why it excites you excitement
is the sign all of you ask for all the
time Give Me A Sign what is my purpose
what is my
mission the thing that comes along that
is the most exciting thing that you
could be doing is the answer that's why
it excites you many of you however in
looking for that purpose in looking for
that mission when excitement Taps you on
the shoulder say go away I'm looking for
my purpose in life don't
bother I am too busy attempting to look
for my purpose to have
fun I'm supposed to be serious about
this yes in a sense you are conviction
is necessary but the idea is that you
are made of ecstasy and whatever it is
in your life at any given moment that
excites you the most is who you are do
it you will be supported as you always
have been supported by the universe
because it always has supported you it's
simply that the Universe can only
support you to the level you believe
you're capable of
receiving that's true
also one very critical and important
issue when we talked about the idea of
following your excitement the whole
scenario an issue of trust comes up
infinite trust and then we hear a
collective psychic groan from many oh no
that's a tough one that's a big one TR
everyone knows here it is again everyone
knows how difficult it is to trust all
the time it's not difficult you know why I'll tell
I'll tell
you because you have never had one
single moment not one single second in
your entire life or any of your lives
where you have not trusted infinitely in
something you see you on your planet
Define doubt as a lack of trust it isn't
it's an infinite trust in the negative
reality so all you have to do is use the
same infinite trust you've always had
and simply redefine that trust into a
positive reality it's the same idea you
don't have to learn to do something
you've never done before you're not
Rusty in this area you always have
trusted you know how to use your trust
flawlessly and all of you do it all the
time if you didn't trust in something
you wouldn't have a reality because
that's how you create the reality you
experience you would not exist to exist
is to trust because trusting in a sense
is simply selfawareness
self-reflection of some aspect of
yourself it is the mechanism of
realization of
manifestation of whatever it is about
yourself you're most strongly focused on
so you've always used that lens to
magnify whatever you were focused on so
simply don't focus on the negative focus
on the positive you'll get that back
because the universe will always give
you exactly what you say you're ready
for but not one crumb more but not one
crumb less
either understand understand there are
many issues that can come up within this
idea of exploring what excites you the
most strongest among many of you is the
issue of deserv ability do I deserve to
be happy forever and ever and ever and
ever do I believe that's even possible
many of you say well why not but you see
because of how your Society has been
trained because of how you have been
taught if you are given a story where
individuals are struggling and striving
in pain and sorrow and conflict you say
oh very realistic story but then someone
tells you a story that goes something
like this and they live happily ever
after you oh what a fairy tale that
is that's not like real
life well what is real life real life is
only what you define it to be happily
ever after is just fine for me thank you
very much now that does not mean you will not
much now that does not mean you will not
have challenge it doesn't mean you will
not grow it doesn't mean you will not
learn and expand your curiosity is
always intact you will always be
discovering something new but you don't
have to do it through suffering you
don't have to do it through struggle you
don't have to do it through pain the
only reason that pain exists is because
pain is the result of resisting your
natural self of denial of your
ecstasy understand does this excite you
yes thank you very much it is up to you
to apply in whatever way shap perform
your imagination so desires thank you
for thank you very much I love to you sh
hello V how you good day thank you very
much for being here and thank you very
much for being
there um one thing I've listened to many
of your tapes and one thing that I
really love about you is your ability to
Unconditionally Love and not judge
another person but you see that serves
me as well I can say it has a very
selfish motive because as much as I can
unconditionally love all of you the
universe supports me that much more
strongly unconditionally that's true serving the
unconditionally that's true serving the
whole is serving the cell because you
are a part of the whole that's true and
that's one thing that I want to
uh jeez it's it's a it's a force it's a
Feeling it's something I have a real
hard time putting into words oh oh what
you don't necessarily have to you
know you understand well basically okay
uh since I've been a real little girl
I've been feeling this tremendous force
and energy I
energy I
remember this Force it's an energy it's
a power that I felt inside of me
recently it's been manifesting itself in
a tremendous amount of anger hiding
anger do you know what anger is all I
know is that I find it to be more
destructive than help oh W right that's
because you are bringing invalidation
into it natural anger does not have to
be destructive can be very constructive
if you use it in a positive way this is
the purpose to the feeling that you are
labeling anger it is simply the energy
of self-alignment of self- recognition
let me put it this way by an example
okay if you see something in your
reality you know is not the reality you
prefer you get a rush of alignment to
remind you this is me that is that
compared to that this is who I am that
is all natural anger is and if it lasts
more than 10 to 15 of your seconds it
has shall we say devolve into
invalidation understand yes I don't know
how to harmonize that feeling unal with
the unconditional love I just don't know
how to put the two together well how
about this way let's say you are doing
something now that polarizes me that is
all it is polarization what do you mean
by polarization makes me angry oh in
other words as we have said you do
something that is not my preferred
reality so I become
polarized I because of what I see in you
recognize much more strongly what I am
compared to what you are that polarizes
us at the same time it unifies us
because I would not have discovered that
were it not for you
so what I can say is oh you have allowed
me a much clearer recognition of who I
am thank you very
much then you can be on your way and you
will abused the anger in a positive way
and perhaps you will leave the other
individuals cracking their
head yes I do I would love it if I could
be that levelheaded about it but why
can't you be why do you not choose to be
remember this these are choices if
you're not being as you say levelheaded
about it you're choosing not to be so
how does not being levelheaded serve you
makes me very right oh very right very
right makes everyone else wronging me
very right it never really works very
well I see do you enjoy being that lonely all
lonely all
right no one is right or wrong at all it
is all a different point of view once
again that doesn't mean we condone
individuals who may act out of Integrity
but the idea is simply representative of
their level of understanding of what
they have been taught the only reason
individuals act outside of Integrity do
what you call harmful things is because
they have never been taught that they
are already definitionally in control of
their lives individuals that do negative
things believe they are not in control
they are out of control they do not know
that the control is already within them
so the only reality they have to relate
to if they don't have an inner one an
inner connection to the infinite is the
outer reality and if they believe they
need to be in control what do they have
to work with nothing but the outer
reality so they will try to bend it into
shape to match the idea they think they
need to see to force their will upon it
in order to gain some sense of control
but that force that issue the things
that make you angry in that sense are
simply exercises or expressions of their
their belief in lack of control you
understand have some compassion for
these
people I probably ought
to it will only serve you all the more
because you will then make connections
and you can transform every negative
interaction into a positive one remember
this perhaps this will serve you as well
and many that wish to apply this in
whatever way shap perform you
care no situation has built-in meaning
we have talked about this few time to
many of you all circumstances to begin
with are created fundamentally neutral
devoid of meaning empty blank zero they
have no builtin meaning circumstances
don't intrinsically mean anything they
are simply a set of neutral
props you have been taught in your
upbringing to assign a particular
meaning to a circumstance when you see
it occur thean meaning you assign to the
circumstance utterly determines the
effect you get out of it in your life so
if you assign a negative meaning to what
you see you will get a negative effect
in your life if you assign a positive
meaning to it you will get a positive
effect that doesn't mean that you cannot
recognize that someone may be doing a
negative thing but you if you simply
recognize that you are there to interact
by getting out of what you need if you
assign a positive meaning for you you
will get a positive effect getting that
positive effect will allow you to grow
and expand in a positive way growing and
expanding in a positive way will allow
you not to force them but to help them
realize they can change too if they want
to but you at least by expanding by
using the interaction to expand in an
unconditionally loving way are at least
giving them the opportunity to change if
you simply match their frequency of
invalidation all you're doing is
reinforcing the reality they are already
creating that you say you don't
like understand yes so actually by
giving into your invalidation you are
actually doing just the opposite of
getting what you want you are doing just
the opposite of being right you are
being just like
them oh
oh in what you call your biblical
literature there is a phrase many of you
are familiar with but many of you do not
necessarily understand what it means
judge not lest you be judged that
doesn't mean you are going to be judged
from outside the infinite is not going
to judge you it is non-judgmental what
it means is that if you judge and
invalidate others you lower yourself to
the same frequency and therefore the
universe has no choice but to treat you
in the same
way understand yes I do does that help
it does does it inspire you as a matter
of fact it
does it has served
you um yes it does is this
sufficient well I think so all I know is that I'll
well I think so all I know is that I'll
probably go out somewhere tonight and
just get all pissed off at someone and
all right you know I guess it's just
something I have to learn about there
are many ways you can still go about it
you know you kind say excuse me and then
you can express your anger and say thank
you I needed that nothing
that nothing
personal something I felt I need to
do I feel much better now
at least if you do that give them the
opportunity to see the other side of you
too I'm a real nice person I really am
yes you I know I am I I think a lot of
you I know I am I I think a lot of
people don't get to see it cuz I'm
always angry remember this also and perhaps
angry remember this also and perhaps
this can be the shall you say icing on
your cake if you have a reaction of that type
cake if you have a reaction of that type
an inv validational reaction when you
see something else in someone else mhm
when you get angry about it in a sense
what you're doing is expressing your own
fear because the only reason you would
get that angry about it is because you
were afraid that you contain it
too you're angry at
yourself if someone can push your button
why do you have such a button within the
definition of your
reality understand oh
yes well of course the you see if I
may if what another individual does
doesn't relate to who you are why would
you be affected by it that
way because I can't relate to who they
are perhaps but perhaps you are not
relating to who you are perhaps you do
not believe in who you want to be and
therefore when you see other individuals
offering you all sorts of other ideas
positive negative you create resentment
because you believe they are not giving
you the opportunity to find out who you
really want to be when in fact that's
exactly what they're doing giving you a
prime opportunity to find out exactly
who it is you want to be as compared to
who it is they have chosen to be yes
understand yes I want to be a a very
well I actually I am a very big being I
want control over everything I want
already my way you already have that
what you are forgetting is this everyone
already has all the power they need to
create whatever they want without having
to hurt anyone else or themselves in
order to get it
remember interactions do not have to be
conflictive everybody can win everybody
you are under the assumption that if
somebody wins somebody loses that's a
definition change it everyone can win
okay all right thank you B well thank
you very
much Shan hi bishar and you good day I'd
like to talk to you about my son go
right ahead I'll pay R attention okay
he's over there sitting on on the other
side and when we first heard your tape
he would put on the headphones and do
his homework and mouth the words that
you were saying all right and I want to
know if you knew him or know of him from
another time because it's he hooked up
with you so easily we recognize him not
from our exact stream but we recognize
that he has the energy of what we
colloquially call a pilot that that can
navigate on Interstellar Lan he has an
inate understanding of the vibrational
frequencies of navigation in that sense
and that realm that dimension of travel
that style of travel is not I shall say
unfamiliar to him he simply recognizes
to some degree a similar energy to
something he is familiar with true cuz
he draws pictures of spaceships come out
of his head and they're very elaborate
yes unfortunately his teacher doesn't
find him he doesn't appreciate him as
much as other people
do all right so I just was curious as
far as school and and his learning if
he's going to do more navigational or be
more towards that that area when he's
older in a sense it can be but it may
manifest in many different ways these
things are not as you say chiseled in
stone the decisions are still within
that individual to make we cannot
predict the future because it has not
been completely decided upon by that
individual understand understood but if
that individual is willing to understand
that there are ways to blend what he
wants to be what he knows he is with the
world he has chosen to be in then
eventually he will discover ways to
allow the two to exist within each Other
Side by side without conflict also some
of these individuals not in any way
shape or form does this mean that it
must be a conflictive change that they
have to get into arguments about it but
some of these individuals are also
giving an opportunity for some of the
sociological and educational structures
on your planet to change
accordingly because many of them are
extremely rigid right I see that I know
I must have some kind of lesson with him
as of course you all chose to be
together right and I know I had hard
time at one time integrating and trying
to structure his behavior into this
pattern on Earth that but you have
provided a service you have oriented in
to some degree now remember that this is
a two-way street as you say and that you
each are learning from each other soften
up the definitions a little bit learn
that you do in fact already love each
other very much or you would not have
chosen to be together and simply look
for what the relationship between you is
rather than what you both think it ought
to be
that makes very much sense to me well
thank you very much thank you very much
sh hello how you good day few years ago
my girlfriend and I created a business
and I'm very forunate that has
expression of design and art and this
sort of thing what I would like to speak
a little bit about art Beauty wavelength
and energy of that in our society also
in your own people we have expressions
of art to some degree similar some of
them not myself in many ways
sculpture okay what about that
wavelength and that energy on this how
does into physiological symbology it is
inspiration and crystallized in physical
form it is your flame your it is a
mirror a reflection it is a window and a
gate for many individuals who come in
contact with that are discover
themselves back to open up gateways of
communication for them to be inspired
and allow that sh through
for these and I'm excited I enjoy it
yes experence manifesting expressing others
experence manifesting expressing others
are way
feel obviously and the fullest you can
be you you are the more opportunity you
give to everyone else to be the fullest
they can be by seeing those Reflections
from you and in your art and in your
expression art is communication with the
infinite thank you second question yes uh my
thank you second question yes uh my
girlfriend and I love each other very
much do and we notice that we
enjoy if you want to that's what
really you like to
fight what we've identified is that it
seems to be an unresolved conflict from
prior existence we have been
Associated pleasure know what the
purpose is ask you personal question certainly
is ask you personal question certainly
is there something that this quote
unquote so-called conflict teaches you
about yourselves that you would not
yourselves that you would not
necessarily discover without it or do
not believe you can discover without it
what have you learned primar that we that we
do
to
information to other lives that may
in a sense create some of these inter we
are always the eye of the past we want
in the present life to deal with
anything that
existense so all you need to do refer
the conf now let's pretend that there is
no other
life where would you believe the
conflict would come from if it didn't
come from any other place but this life
and let me ask you this while you're
pondering
that do you understand why yes explain
the strength I don't let you get away
with [Music]
[Music]
anything what that would mean would be
that it is not so much a losing of self
as a gaining of another self all right
more of the self an expansion of self
but also the following analogy you as a
Persona are created out of many
personality fragments yes yes
you AB
AB
well you will gain the strengthening of
your identity because as we have said
already granting of true strength to the
individual components that make it up so
by blending you actually become a
stronger individual not a weaker one
perhaps the issue is also the idea of
your definition of vulnerability being
weakness as opposed to being
strength exposure thank you that's what I need to
exposure thank you that's what I need to
know all
right true vulnerability or I shall say
positive vulnerability is the
willingness to believe to trust in a
positive direction that as you open up
to everything to the infinite you are
connecting to the infinite and as you
connect to the infinite all you can
receive in your life is Infinite
Strength and support vulnerability does
not have to be seen to be exposure and
weakness thank you
our unconditional love for
[Music] you about a month ago I had a dream oh
you about a month ago I had a dream oh
how
exciting and I uh I all once called a
hand on top of my head and had had a
vision of a enti or something in a uh
dark shroud like uh
cape and uh it was totally un related to
the dream that I was having at the time
it woke me right up out of a sound sleep
and fact afraid to be oh all right can
you shut any light on what could
possibly be the meaning of this
click did the light come
on all right we'll do it another
way there are levels of what you may
colloquially call extraterrestrial
Consciousness that do interact many
times with you in your dream state and T
now and then in the proper and gentle
way to open up another Doorway to more
of yourself the fear is simply old ideas
old beliefs about being able to expand
through that doorway over that threshold
into what you call the
unknown but it's all right you have
friends you have help you're doing just
fine it is simply that you have as many
individuals have many times in your
history been touched
that is the origin of that terminology
touched and that is why individual in
your Society usually relate the idea of
being touched with being crazy because
it expands your senses into other
dimensions that the majority of your
Society doesn't necessarily consider to
be real but the idea is that many of the
contacts that go on take place in the
timing when you say I am ready and they
with their assistance create an energy
touch which accelerates you it opens you
up and may startle you but that's all
right you like Rison you don't want your
life to be boring the idea is to Simply
recognize that all you're going to
discover is more of yourself that you
have opened another door and there is
absolutely nothing about yourself you
will ever discover that cannot be
applied in your life in a positive way
you have been given some assistance
trust that they are your friends because
that is your overall intention you
follow me the dark robe simply
symbolizes the idea that to some degree
some of your Notions are still wrapped
in a cloak of fear in a cloak of old
definitions that's all it really means
it means that you are now breaking
through that Veil and you are going
through the crown of your understanding
the vibrant Violet chakra energy of your
higher Consciousness it means you are
uplifting yourself we thank you thank you does
yourself we thank you thank you does
that serve you yes it does what pleasant
dreams to
you sh good day to you good day to you well
sh good day to you good day to you well
thank you very much uh earlier tonight
when Daryl was getting a line to allow
you to speak to us I found that the most
exciting experience for me all right
thank you very much did you identify
with the energy yes I did and that's why
I'm here asking a question all right uh
I found for me in my life the most
exciting thing I can do is speak to
people about something that excites me
all right you go right
ahead well well actually the question I
wanted to ask you and to address is uh
do I have the ability because this
excites me and what I saw here tonight
excites me very much do I have the
ability Within Myself to channel will
you do me a favor yes will you take that
question mark and straighten it out into
an exclamation point and make a
statement out
it and see how it feels try it on for
side all right now say the statement
again but say it as a statement from
what I have seen here tonight because of
the feelings I have created I feel that
because of that I continue I feel
because of that I have the ability to
Channel all right now that's ition now
do you believe it yes I do well thank
you very much you see how simple it is
okay than thank you
remember that once again the idea may
change May alter may come in many
Fashions it is all right if it does so
whichever methodology excites you the
most excites you the most because that
is the alignment you have made and all
of you are capable of it not all of you
necessarily prefer to do it in a
particular way but all of you Channel
right now in a sense what you all think
of as your rock solid
personalities you're channeling them
because they are only temporary
manifestations of the overs soul that
you are so what you think of as your
personality right now is a channeling it
is only one of the faces your soul could
be presenting you understand B could you
explain over Soul thank you very much on
a simple level the idea of overs soul is
simply that energy Essence that
Consciousness that you are that is
responsible for the creation of all of
the individual lives you believe you
have much in the same way that your hand
has finger extensions each of the
fingers can be considered a separate
life but they all lead back to the same
hand the over soul is the overall energy
of your Consciousness the overall being
that you were created to be that has
fragmented itself and fractionalized
itself into all the separate
personalities in all the different time
frames that you call past present and
future lives you follow me does that
explain it efficiently does thank you
very much so remember you're are
channeling right now thank you may I say
something absolutely I like you very
much I love you
very Bashar good day to you I have been
listening to tapes of you for about a
month oh all right uh probably about 150
hours worth oh all right and and I have
been really appreciating you oh we
appreciate all of you and prior to
having listened to tapes of you I
listened to probably 500 hours of tapes
of other beings calling themselves
ascended masters all right
and I would like you to explain to me
from your Viewpoint who and what is an
ascended Master I've heard their
Viewpoint I'd like to hear from your
Viewpoint an ascended Master is simply
someone who recognizes that they are an
aspect of the infinite and act like
it an ascended Master will be the first
one to remind you that you are all
Masters too an ascended Master flows through
too an ascended Master flows through
life and lets life flow through them
they know that they are in control by
letting go in a sense that is an ascended Master
go in a sense that is an ascended Master
you understand yes it is one who
represents what you may call the god
self the goddess self the infinite self
in whatever symbolic manifestation is
represented by your dimension of reality
in a loving effortless easy way in a
light way in a knowing way in a
compassionate way without struggle
without Strife without strain without
pain many individuals on your planet
have created this reality for themselves
many more are doing so now as you all
Elevate yourselves and Ascend into your
higher Consciousness and become the
representation of your higher
Consciousness on your planet in your
fourth density physical reality the one
you are transforming into it is not have
to be a mysterious title in that sense
does not have to seem to be so separate
from all of you you're all
Masters it is simply in your terminology
a matter of degree of how much
conviction you have in what you say you
believe in an ascended Master is simply
someone shall we say to put it in your
colloquial vernacular who walks their
talk does that help yes that's great
well much I I have one other request
Pro I like what you're doing with your
hands we are telling the story yeah I
see that uh I brought my two children here
that uh I brought my two children here
tonight and they uh we were talking in
the car what they'd like to have you
explain to them but are Sho too shy to
ask you is would you give us a scenario
of what it's like to be a child where
you're from I'm doing that right now
[Music] yeah the idea to recognize is that
yeah the idea to recognize is that
everyone functions in a childlike manner
which means we give in to spontaneous
Unconditional Love by what you call the
age of three in your terminology the
child is off and interacting with all
the individuals that will teach them
what they need to know remember that we
are telepathically connected and no one
is ever out of sight truly and that the
entire planet is really one family the
adults are the parents of all the
children are the children of all the
adults and we are all in one marriage of
unconditional love so it is very exatic
very joyful very expansive very
spontaneous much like what your children
now are teaching all of you to be
like okay does that suffice does that
suffice kids is there something specific
you wish to know about our
children no okay that's it they like to
play but so do the
adults what kind of sports do they play
there are a few variations of ideas but
none in your nature are
competitive there are things that do
involve the idea to some degree of
spheres what you would call perhaps ball
in that sense but the idea is that each
and every individual is absolutely
applauded for their individual Merit and
interaction and participation in
co-creating together together one
particular level of that interaction of
that reality in your terms in achieving
a particular goal understand in other
words they work as all one
team make sense
yes thank you very much thank you there
are many other ideas many other ideas
which we will discuss at other times as
well about different aspects of our
society this timing I will suggest that
you all enjoy a short break we will
resume zoom contac in approximately 10
to 15 of your minutes of
cing project that he felt would help us
with our desire to create world peace
and he called it the peace
clock and so we put the information
together that he channeled through and
it's a very simple project very simple
practice he says it'll have a great deal
of impact however there's basically two
steps first step is wherever you are every day
first step is wherever you are every day
at 12: noon exactly for one minute to
perform your own type of silent
meditation or however you want to do it
for World
Peace the goal is to have every single
person on Earth doing that by January
1st 1990 the idea is that that will create
1990 the idea is that that will create
an electromagnetic acceleration around
the planet by the different time zones
being 12:00 noon 12:00 noon all the way
around 24 segments and help accelerate
an atmosphere on our planet that makes
it more conducive to have World Peace So
the idea of participating in this is not
only to do the meditation at 12:00 noon
for 1 minute every day yourself but if
you would Linda is going to be making
Master copies of this take one of the
master copies she will make keep that
Master Copy for
yourself and then make as many Xerox
copies off of that as you want to and
share it with as many people as you
possibly can in all walks of life to
allow them to also participate and get
them to share it with as many people etc
etc that's all there is to it he says
synchronization synchronized intention
is really the whole key to getting it to
really work and uh Linda will have this
information she'll work up uh Master
copies for everyone and you can get that
from her whenever she gets that worked
up so please feel free to participate
and thank you very
much are you having a good
time oh
yeah can you see me better now that I'm
on the platform back
there and have some more fun say
say
continue hello and good day to you uh my
question I have two questions my first
question has to do with are other
entities such as like yourself that are
operating at a increased vibratory
pattern are you here to help assist in
the change in Consciousness to the
fourth uh Dimension and is it also to
help aid in the physical effects on the
Earth plane yes but the idea of the
physiolog iCal effects on your Earth
plane while we can be of some assistance
the majority of the assistance will come
from your alignment the assistance we
give you in the acceleration itself in
meeting us halfway in elevating the
vibratory pitch of your own reality you
will then be of best assistance
regarding the actual physiological
changes which may or may not take place
and in what Manner they may take place
upon your planet according to the
vibrations you set up on your planet but
we are being of assistance to you in
this way to at least give you an
opportunity to recognize you can change
your frequency and that you can go
through your transformation with an
absolute minimum amount of negativity in
terms of the manifestations as they
occur upon your planet in the changes
that will take place you follow along
yes understood um my second question has
to do with uh when I was a child I was
visited by the tall
shining and I also had a sighting and I
was wondering if they were from the plan
AR system of the pades and if so there
are pleadian connections but there are
also Arcturus connections could you
please tell me a little bit more about
that simply to remember that the idea is
that what you may typically call the
pleadians are very much in very many
ways all of your brothers and sisters
and cousins in a very literal sense
since your humanity is very much an
offshoot of them the idea of Urus
represents the Gate of energy through
which communication from other
dimensions of experience is shall we say
funnel into your dimension of experience
they are the regulating gate in that
sense doesn't mean that it is regulating
in a very structured sense but that they
are the translators of energy from other
dimensions into your dimension into
symbols you can understand and much of
the emanation of energy of dissemination
of energy and the regulation of the
transformational rate that is going on
on your planet and many other planets
within your Galactic system is under the
offices of the arcuris gate they are
also responsible for shall we say
creating a particular type of energy
alignment through which many of your
children now being born are passing
before they are being born so they will
forget less of who they are once they
are born into your
Society understand yes in that sense
they have connections into what you
would call the Angelic
realm and therefore are represented by a
lot of nonphysiological Consciousness as
well okay this is some of what is
represented in your symbology as shining
one some of it are aspects of pleadian
some of it are aspects of pleadian
energy but a lot of it is aspects of
extradimensional energy as it is
symbolized in your material reality and
is it possible to work with these beings
why not you already are if you have
recognition of the energy ah okay thank
you very much in what way do you wish to
work with this
energy I've already started a process of
expanding my own awareness very good um
all you need to do then is to Simply use
the energy in whatever way is a best
service to all in the way that excites
you the most and you will be fulfilling
that purpose
brilliantly fine thank you very much
thank you very much remember remember
your own Stellar
qualities Shing thank
you hi B have you good day I'm so
thrilled to be here thank you one moment
one moment for the last individual we
had interaction with a moment ago there
will also be some assistance in your
dream realities that will not come from
us but from some other individuals thank
you Contin I wanted to mention a dream
that I had that keeps coming up for me
keeps coming up all right keep thinking
about it I haven't ever really explored
or had any connection with spacecraft
before except through my very
imaginative
husband I had a dream that I
saw what appeared to be giant ball
bearings but I knew right away they were
spacecraft all right but they did didn't
they didn't they weren't in our
Dimensions they were it was between two
Dimensions yes very good quasi plan our
reality so that so what I saw was really
a likelihood I just wanted a validation
that that do understand a very accurate
term for all of our type of energy of
various associations and civilizations
has been shall we say coined upon your
planet extraterrestrial is all well and
good but in very many ways it is perhaps
more precise to Define us as
ethereums because our physiological
existence is mostly on what you would
call an aetheric vibration exactly what
it was like yes exactly now do
understand that your
planet is in many ways visited by many
thousands of different ships and the
only reason many of you do not see them
as often as you could is because you are
not on that vibratory plane toce CeCe
them in your dream state you allow
yourself to be on the vibratory plane
where we are very perceivable in our own
natural environment our own natural
level thank you that F that felt good
you see that is why there are these
Notions that exist in many of your
predictions that your Earth will be
saved by the appearance of thousands of
ships and you'll be taken off the Earth
and so on and so forth we are not here
to rescue you we are not here to save
you you not need saving the idea however
is that the recognition
of all of the appearance of those
thousands of ships is a reality but the
point is you will see the ships that are
already there when you raise your
vibration to meet us halfway and you
will simply be able to see what has
always been there that was my
understanding that raising of your
vibration yourself that is the upliftment off the
yourself that is the upliftment off the
old
Earth understand make sense yes thank you does
understand make sense yes thank you does
that answer you the question yes I have
one more question and this pertains to a
physical situation go right I I am not
used to having any I'm not used to
having something control my physical
body I'm I'm used to not paying
attention to it to not being ill to just
being in charge yeah what you always
always are you know that's what I
thought one thing has got me and I want
to get rid of it I was somewhat pushed
into it when I was pregnant threatened
that if I didn't take this certain
substance which is a thyroid hormone
that I would do damage to my daughter in
utero and that kind of thing so I
started it and I've been doing it for 5
years now all right I I tell myself I
can get off it I get off it my hair
starts falling out I get tired I get
anemic and all how do I get myself there
may be in your reality though we may not
be able to be very precise about this
but there may be in your reality certain
of what you would call Natural Herbal
compounds that can assist a rebalancing
of your bodily system you understand
yeah yes I've considered looking into uh
yes I've considered looking into uh
Chinese herbology is that a good lead it
it struck me as being a good lead then
follow your imagination it is there for
a reason it may not necessarily
culminate only in that area but it will
direct you in the direction you need to
go good thank you very much one more one
more it has recently come
synchronistically to the attention of
the Channel's Consciousness that there
is a collective body of work that was as
you say ConEd by an individual no longer
physiologically alive upon your planet
now who goes or used to go in your terms
by the name of Dr Christopher oh yes
these compounds are in your terms
extremely efficacious and Powerful
perhaps researching those list of
compounds will be of assistance to you
oh good thank you I even have one of his
books all right I'm Al I'm all done
thank you very very much we thank you
very very very
much we would also one moment one moment
like to remind you and all of you of
something that we consider to be very
critical very important as a point of
view many of you may have heard this
idea but again we will always say it as
many times as necessary since every time
is the first time to us until it clicks
in whatever way it has to click the idea
once understood can cause profound
changes in your reality from this one
simple understanding and it has to do
with the idea of the notion of the
separateness of your spirit and your
body they are not separate things your
spirit does not exist inside your body
literally I know that's how you
experience the idea in your
physiological universe but that's only
your physiological
interpretation your body is your spirit
in physical
terminology your Consciousness does not
exist inside your body your body is not
literally a
shell your body exists within your con
Consciousness understanding the
difference can have profound effect on
your ability to create your body to be
represented in any way shape or form
that your Consciousness deems it ought
to be
represented because there is no
separation between Consciousness spirit
and body not really not fundamentally
they are simply different faces of the
same one thing understand yes do that a
sister very much so well then breathe
deep and enjoy the fire within you
ignite yourself and find yourself
aligned to your highest vibratory
aspirations sh hello Bashar how you good
day um recently I've experienced um
quite an expansion oh thank you quite an
expansion yes of myself a little louder
please okay um I've experienced an
expansion of myself in my
um I guess coming to the fourth
dimension that I don't quite understand
that but well that's all right it is
simply an escalated idea of vibrational
pitch it will still appear to be
physiological to you but things will
move easily as if it has all been
lubricated in a sense it will have been
with love I don't see that to be true yet but
love I don't see that to be true yet but
I feel I feel as if somebody wanted me
to enjoy water and forgot to teach me
how to swim all right and I feel a
little frightened interesting you know it's
frightened interesting you know it's
it's wonderful it it feels Wonder
wonderful but I just it's like I'm lost
all right like where am I going now
thank you why do you not find someone
who is willing to teach
you I guess I haven't I haven't looked
well it can be that simple you know
doesn't have to be a big
mystery if you feel that you are ready
to do so attract someone who will teach
you in a loving way and will allow you
to get back in touch with the ideas that
you may have in the past cut yourself
off from being in the water will put you
back in touch with many aspects of
yourself and you can attract someone who will
and you can attract someone who will
teach you in a very loving way so that
it will not force you into something
that you will not be ready to face
understand yes I am it is simply looking
deeper into the self and understanding
that there really is nothing there to
fear not really not intrinsically
remember there is no circumstance that
is inherently fear causing only your
definition of it creates the fear
reaction the situation itself does not
contain the fear understand mhm so
attract someone who might be willing to
teach you there may even be someone
present this evening of your time
synchronistically thank you very much
thank you I've done nothing does this
serve yes it does thank you well swim
deep and
strong perhaps you can also enlist the
aid of some of your dolphin friends
since all of them interact with many of
you in your dream realities and can
teach you many things about being
comfortable within that particular
medium of existence do remember from our
point of view your planet has two alien
species land human water satation they
are in many ways like you they are not
animals as you understand that term they
are another alien Society you have right
on what you call your own doorstep and
opportunity to form a first interaction
with another alien Society without going
to the
star it's very interesting it happen to
live right near the Keys and for I must
have put myself there for a good reason
that are no accidents take advantage of
it they are there to help you call them
with your heart they will come they will
teach you thank you it does not
necessarily have to be a human that
teaches you how to swim you
know sh for sure good day to you good
day uh I'm an inventor a Creator oh W
right okay uh I would like to have you
put yourself in my place I know about uh
Fusion uh do you mean of the nuclear
variety yes do I also know about
propulsion systems that would Propel
crafts to other galaxies using both to
do so but both what fusion and
propulsion um what type of propulsion
well let's not get into that now all
right okay here's what I want to talk to
you about if you were in my place
knowing of these things yes and I have
gotten this information from patents
that people that have done the research
and has also uh been eliminated because
of it because it could be cheaper to
supply energy to the public and cannot
be monopolized how would you if you were
in my spot uh put this out to the public
so it would be available so they would
be able to travel and have abundance and
limited amount of thank you very much
first of all I would not buy into the
idea of the fear and the paranoia I
would simply assume that this is
something that really excites me really
interests me I will automatically be
guided by myself and by others into
whatever Avenues will allow me to put
the information out in the way that
serves the best of all concern and that
it will not be interrupted nor stopped
do remember that anyone who has in your
terminology been suppressed has bought
into that reality and has reinforced it
with their fear and their
Panic so first of all I would not buy
into the idea that that particular past
scenario has anything at all to do with
me step number
one okay so you say if you don't buy in
how would you spread this out through
the planet I would simply do it in
whatever way excites me the most knowing
that by doing that the word will spread
because I will attract the individuals
who will be most capable of spreading
the word and I will spread it myself
when any other individuals come in
contact with myself that would be
interested to learn what I am doing at
the same time I would also treat now in
no way shape or form is this derogatory
to what you are exploring for what you
are exploring is necessary but I would
also understand that the ideas that you
are referring to of fusion in the
nuclear fashion uhhuh is going to be
rendered relatively obsolete very soon
the idea is to understand that the
electromagnetic field of your planet
will supply all the energy you need for
the type of propulsion that isn't really
propulsion at all it is more of a
retranslation of matter tapping in sych
I know about this already uh this has
already been done back in
1934 but the the person MO
um and many other and yes and many
others uh they have also been suppressed
understood but that was then and this is
now is it not yes so Define what reality
you live in now Define what world you
live in now and remember do not relate
to the idea of your government as a
fearful thing because that's the only
thing that reinforces the ability to
suppress remember that you are your
government and that simply whatever
reality you prefer you can start living
as if you are in that reality now and
whoever you attract you will be able to
interact with them in a way that will
still allow you the full expression you
require as long as you do not buy into
the fear of the
suppression okay thank you very much
well thank you very much for propelling
yourself quite rapidly
along welcome and to you good day okay
um I take care of interior plants and
interior plant plants that are Brad
inside and they're not always happy
about about being in these um controlled
environments that we have made for them
right um some of them are manifesting
symptoms of of insects and I'm having a
real problem I would like to be in
direct contact with the nature Kingdom
and I welcome them but they're not
coming fast enough I'm an impatient
person and I want to why I don't know
yes you do why because you're not living
in the moment I'm not living in the
moment okay plants live in the moment
how can you identify with something that
lives in the moment if you
don't all right how do I take care of
from I mean what how can I raise the Vitality
I mean what how can I raise the Vitality
of a plant so that that they're not
manifesting a sickness symptom well
first of all bathe them in love remember
that they are basing in your atmosphere
should I be using more Flower Essences
specifically with them more herbal
compounds will be of assistance but also
one more one
more an electromagnetic frequency
similar to what you call your Earth
vibration can also be of assistant
student oh explain that that's confus me
electromagnetic pulses low in nature
very low amperage as you would call it
leaking into the soil in which they are
planted trickling in low energy pulses
that are synchronized with your Earth
harmonic of 7 and 1/2 cycles per second
now there may be a slight range to this
for different plants but you can test
the idea of their electronic frequency
with measuring devices and in a sense
discover by testing what you would call
Healthy areas what the electrical
potential of that area is and recreating
that electrical potential in the soil
with the minerals that need to be there
because when certain minerals are in the
soil and a certain electrical potential
is set up it crystallizes in a
particular way and gives vital energy to
the plant that it means that it has been
cut off in terms of its natural Earth
setting so should I be working more with
radionics to some degree you don't not
have to go as you say overboard without
some also crystallin manifestations
planted in the soil will be of
assistance as well such as Sports and
amethyst and various ideas experiment
with it and see what the plant
likes me later and talk with that person
later to see what you can get from that
do trust above and beyond everything the
synchronicity of relying on the
information that abounds all around you
take what you believe will work for you
you don't not have to take everything
but do trust that within any Gathering
within any interaction there is usually
more than enough information to serve
all the parties that have attracted
themselves to that
interaction okay rely on yourselves you
all are very very resourceful please
bash shall explain the seven and a half
whatever per cycles per second yes
please each and every planet each and
every world has a particular
electromagnetic pulse a frequency that
represents the base stable vibration the
signature frequency of that planet the
way you find that frequency is generally
as follows by this equation
if you take the
circumference of your planet and divide
that into your speed of light you will
get a number that represents the
electromagnetic frequency in cycles per
second in this case of your Earth 7 and
1/2 approximately understand by aligning
approximately understand by aligning
something with that electromagnetic
frequency you are allowing it to be
identified with the signature vibration
of earth that is most nourishing now
there can be overlapping vibrations that
will take care of other specific ideas
but the fundamental ground vibration
that heartbeat of the earth is what will
nourish all life on the earth you
understand yes and how do you how do you
tell us to align if we want to be one
with it how do we vibrate at that rate
by very centered breathing calm living
in the moment relaxed states of
meditation is a very good way by toning
something that represents a vibration
that hits you where it counts in your
heart what strikes your cord whatever
feels like it moves you is aligning with
your particular signature frequency by
identifying with that energy by allowing
yourself to simply enjoy sometimes in a
detached state of attachment the idea of
nature itself can put you absolutely in
alignment with that state of being that
state of Vitality that state of health
you will know it when you feel
it mostly it takes relaxation because in
a sense you're already automatically
aligned with it all you have to do is
let go of all your resistance and you
will usually find that you will slip
right back into your natural state of
alignment remember that the idea of
health is not someplace to quote
unquote get to as if it is foreign it is
someplace to Simply let yourself float
back to because it is your natural state
of existence understand yes it is
letting go of
resistance then you pulse in harmony
with the reality that you are a part of
automatically it's is an automatic
setting so anything at all that will
inspire your imagination to allow you to
drift back to that state of Joy will
automatically align you with the natural
pulse of the earth you follow yes
sometimes also certain frequencies and
you can experiment with this of blue and
violet light will also Aid in the growth
of the blant
Consciousness but we will leave that up
to you to experiment with okay thank you
very much well thank you very
much sometimes also crystallin energized
water can assist
them shy thank you Bashar for explaining
that 7.5 that's been several recent
tapes and good day to you as well now I
have a couple of questions about
spacecraft spacecraft speak up so that
all may all right first one is I have
always wanted to be able to see them or
to see them and I never have right have
I simply failed to be looking at a place
where one was or is there something uh
deficient in my perceptions are they of
the wrong vibratory level or something
not unable to perceive in fact all of
you have seen them but for various
reasons have blanked that
out the idea simply may not serve your
immediate identification of who and what
you need to be at that moment do
understand it is not that critical that
you see our craft the idea is to focus
on your own being right now when you
really need to see it you'll see it
nothing will stop it nothing at all but
the idea right now can simply be to
focus on your own life and again
remember that the issue is to meet us
halfway to some degree yes it has to do
with vibratory rates but all of you have
seen them it is simply that you do not
necessarily need to retain the memory of
it because in many cases it would impede
allowing you be who you are in the most
natural and spontaneous way where it
serves to remember the incident you will
remember okay then how does one raise
one's vibratory level by doing what
excites you the
most what excites you the
most this sort of thing I just wanted to
know in general then why not build your
own yeah well okay your civilization is
yeah well okay your civilization is
capable of doing it do your research
can I ask you a second question
absolutely okay uh a friend of a friend
of a friend of mine maybe no just a
friend of a friend knows the author of a
book called communion which is this very
scar story uh account of that individual
went through a lot of fear recognition
yes there is nothing inherent within the
encounter that was fear inducing Orion
UFO no wasn't no was Association
reticulum Zeta articul mhm the idea of
the fear comes from the individual
himself not from the encounter because
remember a higher vibratory
State exposing itself to a lower
vibratory state will raise the vibration
of the lower being to force it to face
many things it has not been willing to
face within itself and that is what the
being is terrified
of understand but that being is dealing
with it is integrating the fear and the
terror and transforming it a positive
understanding and that has been one of
the purposes for those interactions
because it was understood that that
being would communicate his experiences
and allow other individuals to come to
terms with their own fears so that by
the next shall we say wave of
interactions there would be less fear to
integrate I understand that but I my my
reaction was that the book might be
scaring more people than it's uplifting
that's all right because in a sense it
will still allow them to face certain
ideas to come to terms with them
the idea simply is however also that
these things are done with agreement do
not forget your entire plan on one level
is agreeing to this particular type of
teaching it doesn't have to happen that
way but it is completely up to your
world as to whether or not it will wake
up or be shaken away well I sort of
think that that book is perhaps disadvan
the progression because no it's sort of
the opposite effect of of for instance
your teachings I understand what you are
saying but there are many indiv ual that
simply cannot relate to the idea any
other way and therefore they have been
given the tool that will work best for
them it isn't for everyone that is true
but it will hit those where it needs to
understand yeah now do not necessarily
see it as a disvalue because then you
will reinforce the inability of certain
people to absorb it
right understand that it will hit home
where it needs to it has already
awakened many I thought that that
particular count pertained to Orion type
negative negative craft which
occasionally no no no no no no no
no that group of be is to some degree a
recent part of the association and is
represented by the star system in your
language called Zeta reticulum these
cases have cropped up on your planet
many times now you are very familiar
with many of these cases
and it is usually the same group of
beings because they are the facilitators
for very specific reasons some of which
we cannot get into at this time the idea
however is that other groups will also
assist them in many different ways but
that both their civilization and your
civilization have agreed to do this in
this way to serve both of you in the
ways you need to be served for they are
getting something out of this too are
they Advanced ahead of ours oh in a
sense but there are ways in which you
are more advance and that is what they
are learning mostly it is an emotional
understand that's that's why that book's
so upsetting because they're sort of
almost below us in that sort of a way
they are more of a mass mind which is
something that many of you fear greatly
you are far more individualistic which
is something they fear
greatly okay thank you very much thank
you very
much sh I have a sh and do you
they you mentioned earlier tonight about
an overs soul with tentacles coming down
as individuals well yes did not mean to
make it sound like your
octopus but that is a good enough
analogy yes in the idea of time all
being now then all those existences
would be simultaneous and can a person
explore the different uh ones of his own
yeah the easiest way to do so however is
to live in the now in the one you are in
so that you will open a gate where they
all overlap in other words do not do it at
overlap in other words do not do it at
the expense of your present life or
under the assumption that you absolutely
need that understanding in order to
understand what's going on with you now
you can gain an understanding because
you have all the ingredients necessary
to live the life you are living at
present and that is true for every life
however it is a very valid and can be a
very exciting insight into the self into
the overs Soul into the entire idea of
the themes that you explore through many
life you can approach it in many ways trust
you can approach it in many ways trust
your imagination that's what it's for
one suggestion is what we have called
the film or the projectionist analogy
remember that the different lives are
like unto the characters that exist on
separate frames on one of your film
strips those characters can only
experience their reality one frame at a
time this Frame coming now this Frame
coming then this Frame coming after that
is their sense of continuity however to
the projectionist the entire film strip
exists all at once that's the Viewpoint
of the oversold so you can use that
analogy perhaps in a meditative state to
Envision and imagine yourself pulling
back from the film strip of this
particular life and viewing the entire
film strip all the frames and then
allowing your vision to sink down into
another film strip representing another
life see if that works for you see what
you get it isn't as difficult as it
sounds the only reason sometimes it is
more difficult than you think it is is
because what you get you invalidate
that's too easy that's just my
imagination I'm just fantasizing that
isn't real
but very often you get very accurate and
very valid information and you simply
discount it because it seems like it
actually comes more easily than you have
been taught such things are possible to
get that's great thank you does that Ser
yeah it really does well thank you very
much curtain going
up
yes good evening Michelle and are you
good day ever since I was a young young boy
day ever since I was a young young boy
the one thing that I was really striving
to to bring about was a certain quality
of fearlessness fearlessness
fearlessness all right boldness of
conviction yes thank you I think a lot
of it has to do with the fact of the
society we live in in terms of being
male oriented no all right that's that's
how I Define it all
right there are fearless females however don't quite don't quite
[Music]
here would you like to meet one
[Laughter] uh living on there
uh living on there
[Applause]
in what way at this time may we serve
you what I am curious
about is the
inhibition that I am finding in order to
to bring this about what what I would
like to do with this is establish this
as a base
as a primal
self-image in which from that
Foundation any type of creation whatever
whatever vibration can come
about and there's been a certain
Block it's driven me
for as long as I can remember to do
certain things some of them a little on
the edge and I'm just curious about it we
edge and I'm just curious about it we
thank you for your attention to this
detail the idea simply can be understood
in the following manner if you
wish first it comes from the heart and it is
first it comes from the heart and it is
simple knowingness that you desire the
idea of your conviction the conviction
that you see does not necessarily have
to be expressed through
forcefulness conviction is a knowingness
within the self is a certain part of the
S and conviction comes from a blending
of the masculine and feminine polarity
within each and every individual within
your society and most importantly of the
unconditional love you give to yourself
in knowing that you are created to be a
complete being and that you are a
complete being still rely on that idea
that you are still a complete being and
allow yourself to nurture yourself to
give birth to yourself the self you
prefer to be for you are female and you
are male you are both as a soul a soul
is not one way or the other in that
sense it is the essence of all poity
those polarities May manifest themselves
in your Society because your Society by
definition is one of polarity in that
way but you do not have to require
stamina in order to express the idea of
conviction stamina is an effort stamina
is a struggle all it takes is the
knowingness of the self the trust of the
self and the allowance that both sides
the female the receptive and the male
the assertive in that sense the positive
and negative not meaning good or bad but
simply the balance of energy in that way
will allow you to exist within the
center of your being and do all things
with deliberateness with absolute blend of
deliberateness with absolute blend of
spirit and will with the expansiveness
of love and at the same time the
conscious Commandment that you require
in your physiological reality all it
takes is an act an act of being it is
the action that is important in your
reality for you are a physical being in
a physical world and it is your right to
enjoy that and it is your right to allow
all the manifestation you desire to
happen with ease and Clarity in your
sight but it begins by nurturing
yourself from your feminine side and
allowing yourself the understanding of
your Clarity of purpose and your
strength of resolution and remembering
that the decisions that you make will
stick and that your reality does not
have a mind of its own only you decide
what is true for you you understand yes
I do I have I have no problem with the
idea of the masculine feminine and
bringing forth that feminine polarity I
have no problem with that because
there's a lot of things I like to do and
and think about that are of that nature
but what seems to happen is
that through the inability
to to integrate this there seems to be a
certain rigidness or a certain solidness
that some abilities just that I want that I
some abilities just that I want that I
know I can have just aren't there just
can't be realized may I ask you a
personal question certainly why do you
assume you have an inability to
integrate and if you were integrated how
would it appear how would you recognize
it total extroversion
complete does that mean that you will
never be
introspective does that mean you will
never be meditative does that mean you
will never nurture your yourself within
the very core of your being remember
there is much information in silence
remember there is much power in being at
the center and the idea of extraversion
is simply in the deliberateness of the
ACT no matter what the ACT is it doesn't
not mean that you have to have to be an
extrovert someone who is exemplifying it
in an externalized manner if you simply
have decided that you shall be quiet
that is a deliberate decision and is
just as much an expression of
extroversion as anything M I am an
extrovert enough to decide that I will
be introverted for a while because that
is what I
prefer understand yeah yes I do Perhaps
it is only those definitions that make
it seem as if you have an inability to
integrate what truly is already
integrated within you and really has
never been separated at all I I don't
understand that you are assuming that
these ideas are not integrated you are
assuming that the idea of one polarity
should not be experienced that the
expense of the other polarity the idea
is to blend them both by allowing both
representations both the outwardness and
the inwardness to be just as deliberate
representations of conviction as
anything else I don't feel that's the
problem why do you feel you have a
problem let me ask you another question
can you create in your imagination a
picture of what you would be like if you
were operating in the way you say you
desire to operate M then why do you not
simply act like that person okay that
gets into another area because I was
going to ask you about deserv ability
all right what about theer
ability I guess what it is I have a a
problem with the idea of saying okay
would you do me a favor uhhuh you don't
not have to I will but I will ask go
ahead would you recognize that what you
are labeling as a problem is simply a
situation that you believe is difficult
to change and therefore do not
necessarily assume nor label that you
continually have a problem or you do not
you are reinforcing a reality you say
you don't want so why say you have a
problem why not say you are simply
exploring a new understanding of
yourself and become excited about
it okay well um so the new understanding
you exploring is rather than the problem
I am having is okay that that's all time
related it's because it's been going on
for what I consider to be a long time if
it was like a year
you have to go any faster than you are
going but since you are involving Us in
this interaction we will assume that you
may desire to accelerate your pace yes
therefore whether it is time related or
not who do you want to be now do you
have a picture of that then why are you
not acting like that
person um some I don't know some there
there's a there's a difficulty if you
say so okay I did back up Pard me back
up the first response was I don't know
why are you not acting like that person
I don't
know then why not act like old habits
hard to change old habits you know what
that is all about you understand that
the minute you recognize you have a
habit you don't have it
anymore because by definition a habit is
something that you do that you don't
know you're
doing once you know you're doing it you
don't have it anymore and if it keeps on
happening it's because you choose to
believe it must why choose to believe
that you have to be Beyond it in order
to know you had
it
okay because the reality that desire is
seemingly hard to just fall into and
believe why I I don't know it doesn't make then
why I I don't know it doesn't make then
don't believe that it is not don't
believe that it is
it's the old rhetoric you know just
because that's the way things have been
and why do you keep falling back on that
excuse I guess it's handy I don't know
yes it
is it is very handy put it beyond your
reach you don't need it anymore it's not
a tool that serves you anymore why do
you keep picking it
up simply for the reason that if a
person says he is this yes and he acts
on that to become that there is
something about that that is just not
credible that is because you do not
necessarily believe in
conviction I I understand
philosophically what it's what it's all
about why is there a difference between
philosophy and reality uh you are making
many separations and it is this the
making of many separations that is
creating what you are calling a
difficulty you are very analytically
labeling now if this is something you
enjoy by all means continue it but do
understand as long as you insist on your
shortcomings you will
get okay I understand that all right
then do not label if you do not prefer
remember that all of these issues that
you are basing other issues on have no
more weight than the issues that you are
basing them on you are creating them to
carry whatever weight you want them to
carry they are all made out of tissue
paper no one of them has any more weight no
no one of them has any more weight no
one of them is any more a fabric of
existence a law of reality than any
other you are basing assumptions on
assumptions on assumptions on
assumptions yeah I I want to get away
from that being I'm I'm done being
analytical that didn't work stop stop
just stop just stop see the person you want
stop just stop see the person you want
to be in your
imagination use your imagination in the
sparkling way we know you can't use that
imagination create the image of the U you prefer to
create the image of the U you prefer to
be and then key and lock all your senses
into it get involved in what you may
call a visceral way a tactile way
visceral yes visualize it see it okay
see as that person see what it would be
like to see if you were that person see
in the way that person would see taste
in the way that person would taste hear
in the way that person would hear touch
in the way that person would touch act
like that person be that person in
thought word and deed in all your
actions and be excited about being that
person because if you were that person
you would be excited would you not then
be excited about that person you see
Junction with it merge with it blend
with it be that person fall into the
role and you will be that person and you
will have the lifestyle of that person
you see this is what your imagination is
for my friend this is what your
imagination is for it's for you to
create the template and for you to allow
yourself to blend and merge with that
template and then you will get the
reality that is represented by that
Persona because remember the Persona
that you are is an artificial construct
it is created out of belief emotion and
thought and when you change the
definition of your belief and the
reactions of your emotion and the
patterns of your thought you change the
person that you are and whatever person
you change yourself into now is the
reality that you have and you can have
no other because you cannot experience
the vibration of a reality that you are
not the vibration of
understand yes I do that is what your
imagination is for Let It serve you for
it serves you well but you are in
control create the you you prefer to be
and copy what you see in your
imagination in all the action that
person you want to be does not act in
the way you act now does not approach
things in the same way does not have the
same attitude have the attitude and the
attitude have the attitude and the
approach of the person you say you want
to be and you will have the resultant
lifestyle because you can have no other
by being that person it is that
easy thank you very much one Qui
question who are you being right now I
am representative of the idea you call a
female aspect of the esani civilization
and I have taken upon myself the
nomenclature of
Anima I am the female counterpart of the
being you know as
bash do you understand his wife we do
not have exactly that
idea what do you the entire Society is
one marriage and all inter relationships
within our society take place within
that one marriage if you wish you may
simply say to explain it in your
terminology that we are more like
brother and sister in simply the way we
have arranged our relationship and I am
his feminine counterpart I am my own
being and I have my own masculine side
which you are seeing some of right now
but the idea also is that Bashar has his
own feminine side which you get from
time to time but I am my own distinct
female personification and you would
recognize me as female and for I am
approximately under the idea you would
call 5 ft of height and I have white
whitish gray skin coloration very wide
upt almond shaped eyes and very long
white hair the idea simply is that we
are similar in aspect to what you may
call Mongolian in your racial types
although we are not identical to that
idea but similar in that sense I taken
upon myself the nomenclature of Anima
simply in the same way that Bashar has
called himself Bashar to facilitate
conversation between us and wherein we
recognize that in your definitional
language the word anima means the
feminine Principle as it exhibits itself
through a
man which is what is happening right
now we thank you for your inquiry we
thank you for your expression of
willingness we thank you for your
co-creation and we give all of you are
unconditional heartfelt
love have this been of service to you
this has thank you very much we thank
you sh AAR I good day ever since a few years
sh AAR I good day ever since a few years
ago I have been drawn
pering all right and every time I'm
performing or auditioning to perform yes
I think of my mother
why I don't know all right they maybe
many connections but I'll give you one
per second each and every time you perform
second each and every time you perform
since we have already talked about the
idea that Persona is an artificial
construct and every new person you
become is really a new person in a sense
you are also thinking about the Eternal
energy that gives birth to each and
every one of those new personas because
you are literally giving birth to a new
person every time you become shall we
say lost in a role a literal new person
I am not talking philosophically I'm not
talking the idea of what would call
analogy I'm talking literal every time
you define yourself at any given moment
to be a new person you are a new person
that means you have a new past and a new
future you are who you are right now
that is a birth of sorts and that can
connect you into a maternal energy can
connect you into your own maternal
energy and perhaps some ideas that were
unconsciously transmitted to you from
your literal physiological maternal
parent in terms of what the agreement
was between you that you made for her to
reflect to you in this physiological
life that is one specific that we pick
up on is that anything else about this
you wish to explore no that's it do you
find that you perform with passion yes
as much as you want or would you like
more no if I didn't anymore I'd be
overacting
let it seep into every level of your
life does this serve you sufficiently
yes it does well thank you very much
thank you sh hello Mr have you good day I was
you sh hello Mr have you good day I was
wondering about humor and seriousness in
our present Society yes seems to be a a
polarization yes I
know Monday mornings seem to be serious
the weekends are
humorous well perhaps because you
classically begin your week with the day
of the Moon which represents the delving
into your unconscious states where you
may still have many things to process
and it allows you to be a little bit
meditative about that idea and the final
seventh day is the day of the Sun and
Enlightenment and it lightens you up and
accelerates your vibration to give you
the energy necessary to go into the
contemplation once again on the day of
the Moon to find more of yourself and
integrate it is a polarity cycle it is a
pendulum cycle yes but it is a lovely
process thank you thank you very
much sh hello B and to you good
day tell me speak up so that all may
share be bold okay can you tell us
anything about Pyramid Power Pyramid
Power yes the idea of what you call the
tetrahedral structure and the pyramidal
structure four and three sided are
basically lenses for the electromagnetic
field upon your planet and will distort
that electromagnetic field much in the
same way that a Glass Lens focuses light
it will distort and focus that
electromagnetic field and many different
effects can be created from placing
vibratory life within the field within
the focus within the atmosphere the
bubble that is generated by those prisms
those electromagnetic prisms they are
crystallin forms and therefore are
representative of particular pulses of
the electromagnetic spectrum and those
pulses can be utilized in many different
ways especially for the creation of what
can be called stasis fields or
interdimensional gates in which when you
are in that atmosphere you can get in
touch with many other levels of yourself
and contact many other dimensional
realities how's that is that yes
and Sh hi Bashar and do you good day uh
what excites me the most uh is doing
abstract visual art oh very good I
lately I've been using a lot of color
triangles almost exclusively very
abstract a lot of different primary
colors prime colors yes very powerful
you are dealing with the basic building
block of physical reality the
tetrahedral structure and the Triad
which is the basic polarity with the
Apex that represents putting the
polarity into integrative motion yeah
I'm using Symmetry
and can you tune into my work I have two
questions one can you tune into my work
I would love to get a fourth density
opinion what secondly uh what is art
what is visual art like in the fourth
density is it
abstract doing here do understand this
it doesn't necessarily have to be that
much different than what you are doing
now it simply is done with absolute
passion without doubt without worry it
is a flow it is a sharing and in the
fourth density it also truly contains a
perceivable life of its own it truly
reflects the artist's Consciousness in
many ways and can actually allow
individuals to fall into TR States and
explore their own Realms of
Consciousness even while they have been
triggered and catalyzed by the art that
they are viewing that is more of a
fourth density representation because
all art is holographic in nature and
only represents a thin
slice of an overall structure so look at
it that way you can paint
holographically if you understand that
what you are doing is a slice of a
holographic structure you can put
implications in it and signals and
symbols in it that can lure the
individual that is seeing that slice to
delve further and explore further into
the entire structure that may be
invisible more or less behind and in
front of and above and below the canvas
or whatever is your
medium thank you oh thank you very much
also in time you will be dealing with
energy itself even as we do now and
will'll have energy sculptures
wow created by mass mentality we also
have this as an art form this is very
enjoyable to us We Gather three
individuals together and space them
equilateral distances apart and they
focus into the center and as they focus
into the center they create with their
mentality shall we say for now a
thickening of the energy atmosphere into
which a non-physical being can project a
symbolic representational form of itself
to make itself seen and perceived in
that physical Dimension very much fun
[Music] does this Hur yes it does we thank you
does this Hur yes it does we thank you
for your art remember life is Art live
it as an art thank you we thank you at
this timing we extend to each and every
one of you once again our deepest
appreciation for allowing us to
experience the love and the sharing and
the co-creation of this dream reality
remember you are dreaming right now
right now so wake up and live the dream
you prefer to it's your choice it's your
right you deserve it remember if you
exist you deserve what you can conceive
of because if you did not deserve it you
would not be able to conceive of it all
that is the Infinite Creation has
created all
beings if you did not deserve existence
you would not exist treat yourself with
the same respect that all that is has
for you no one is extraneous everyone
fits and if you have some form of
expression you desire to release there
must be must be must be a stage
somewhere wherein that expression can be
played out for there are no one sided
coins in creation you can always match
and attract
the opportunity and the circumstance to
allow you to express yourself to the
fullest that you believe you are capable
of always and you will Attract it
effortlessly and you will accelerate
your ability synchronistically to do
that all you have to do is trust in the
positive self that you are love yourself
love the infinite be of service in the
way that excites you the most all the
details will fall automatically into
place feeling like if you are not
controlling anything is being completely
in control it is simply that your
Society is so used to feeling that you
have to push things into place that when
it becomes effortless you think you are
actually losing control when in fact
that's how you gain it go with the
flow we thank you for this interaction
our unconditional love to you an
exciting dream life and life dream to
you all and a fond and loving good day
[Music]
thank How It Go [Applause]
and thank you Linda and friends for
having us here we've enjoyed it immens
day thank you for being here tonight
we're going to Toronto tomorrow to share
with with that group before we get that
those who want a copy of tonight's tape
you can have it tonight it's just 10
bucks for the two tapes we like to
provide those we've got 25 sets uh we'
got the first the first tape made and
we'll make the at the second tape right
now and you can pick them up on your way
out if you
like you only have 25 thank you all very
much the rest of them uh you'll have to
order uh you'll have to order by mail
order which the sheets are back there as
well we also have the self-empowerment
workshop with just four solid hours of
guidance meditation by Bashar and also
the new the new metaphysics book thank
you