All right, I'll say how are you all this
evening your time as you know time to
exist. Perfect. Recognize we may begin this
Perfect. Recognize we may begin this
interaction this evening of your time
with a reminder once again that this is
the time of your
awakening. And we will participate in
the continuation of the creation of the
type of energy atmosphere that will
perpetuate this expansion of
consciousness and the idea of further
awakening into the beings that you are
and allowing the change to take place
upon your world within your civilization
that you desire to create, that you
desire to perceive, that you desire to
participate in. Each and every one of
you as an individual has the ability to
create a profound impact in your
civilization. So allow yourselves the
benefit of imagining what many of you
together aimed and focused in one
direction can do. Recognize it is not
additive but quite geometric in energy
in this way. And if there are two of you
it is then like four. If there are four
it is then like eight or 16 and so on.
Thus, when you allow yourselves to
immerse yourselves in a particular
focus, especially when you release and
expand your energy within the dimension
of your
imagination from the place of
unconditional love through your
emotionality, emotion, energy motion,
then you will be able to spread this
energy effect completely throughout the
entire matrix of your world, the entire
matrix of your civilization to be able
to be as you say picked up upon by any
individuals so willing to be sensitized
or sensitive to that energy of love, the
energy of sharing, the energy of
integrity and the energy of expansion
and acceleration in that way. So it will
be our joy to share with you as we have
said last week of your time the
continuation of the idea, the exercise,
the technique that we refer to as the
awakening to allow you to align to
center within yourselves and recognize
that it is time for you should you
decide to let it be time to wake up and
dream. Are you all ready?
Then relax yourselves in whatever manner
is comfortable for you. Recognize first
and foremost that no matter what
position you are in, no matter how you
may have felt about yourself during the
course of the day, that whatever it is
your imagination will allow you to do
right now that represents an idea of
centering and an idea of relaxation will
be exactly the appropriate thing you
need to do to have an effect. Leave your
invalidations of yourself for now
behind. Let us play.
Take three deep breaths slowly in a
relaxed state. Let yourselves breathe in
rejuvenation, refreshment, and breathe
out the ideas of
stagnation, the ideas of
static. Let yourselves with every breath
become more crystallin in your
imagination. Allow yourselves to know
that in whatever way your imagination,
your visualization capability chooses to
interpret what we are about to say, what
we are about to suggest is exactly the
way you will find that our suggestions
will work best for you. Do not attempt
to force yourself to imagine exactly
what we are saying, but let it come in
whatever manner is appropriate to the
being you have chosen to be. That is how
you will be going with the flow of
yourself and not attempting to create
some sort of rigidized matrix or
structure in which to mold or fit
yourself. The idea is to function as the
individual that you are but function
cohesively with and in accordance with
all the other individuals that you are
doing this idea with. You follow
me? All right. Now recognize
that what we will be
doing will be as before three
imagination visualization scenario each of which
visualization scenario each of which
will be 33 of your seconds in
duration. I will give you the counting.
You do not have to worry when 33 seconds
is up. Allow yourself, however, with the
counting when we describe the picture,
when we describe what you will be
envisioning, to put every sense you
have, every ounce of energy you have
into the creation of the image we will
describe. Now, we do not mean force
yourself. We do not mean concentrate so
hard that you give yourselves a
headache. No. Allow yourselves rather
the type of energy expansion that comes
with ecstasy. When you are excited above
and beyond anything you could ever
imagine being more exciting than what
you are feeling, evoke that feeling of
energy, excitement, pure and utter joy.
You may find at first that with it may
come a little bit of initial disbelief
that something could actually be that
exciting or that ecstatic. That is all
right. Allow yourself to envision this
idea. Allow it to sink and vibrate
within every single cell of your body
and allow yourself with each count to
become more and more and more excited.
put more and more energy, channel more
and more energy into the idea in
whatever way your imagination allows you
to do so. And then just when you think
you cannot add another ounce of ecstasy,
joy and excitement or you feel you will
burst, add more. You can always add
more. Let yourself explode with ecstasy.
out. Upon the count of 30, allow
yourself to go into what we'll colloally
call overdrive. Let yourself feel that
you are so expanded and so ecstatic that
you merge with everything you can
possibly conceive of that exists in the
reality around you and pump more
ecstasy, more joy, and more excitement
into it. If it will be of assistance to
you, simply in the background of your
mind as you focus on this particular
idea, we will suggest simply allow
yourself to
imagine what may have previously seemed
to be the most impossible thing you
thought could never happen in your life
all of a sudden coming true that you
desire above and beyond anything else.
Imagine how you would feel. Imagine how
you would react if all of a sudden what
you had always thought was impossible
were not only possible, not only
probable, but absolutely certain beyond
a shadow of a doubt. You all follow
along. When I say
33, cut the image
absolutely off. Do not fade it out.
I will assist you by providing other
images in rapid succession. Let your
imagination focus on the new series of
images. It is important that you cut the
primary image immediately that you have
been focusing on for the prior 33
seconds. You all follow
along. Three more deep breaths.
As we begin, when I begin the count of
one, the first image will
be to allow yourself to imagine and feel
with all of your tactile senses. Put
everything you have into it. Hear it,
taste it, smell it, touch it, feel it.
With all of your senses, imagine and
envision a brilliant and warm soft,
completely and absolutely penetrating
orange light in whatever way you wish to
imagine it. expanding from your being,
radiating over the surface of your
planet through your planet, and
enveloping every being on your planet,
including yourself. Feel the emotional
vibration of the warm orange
light. Build this vibration until you
think you can stand it no more. Then add
to it.
Beginning now. 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11
12 13 14 15 16 17 18 19 20 21 22 23 24
25 26 27 28 29 30 31 32 33 Cut ice blue
snow water flakes gentle leaves falling
ocean sand birds sounds forests dreams
clouds relax deep breaths The next
The next
image will be to
imagine a
crystallin electric
blue light and energy radiating from
your being and enveloping every being
upon your planet.
Allow yourselves to feel the mental link
through the electromagnetic sea in which
you are all immersed. Feel the
electromagnetic the
ethermagnetic fluid in which you all
reside. Feel yourselves to radiate this
electric blue light like ripples would
radiate from your body if you were
immersed in water. And recognize
therefore that in accordance with this
analogy, just as if you were in water,
every time you make a
motion, you radiate ripples that touch
everyone else and vice versa. As you
say, allow yourself to trust that the
energy you are feeling will not be too
much for you to handle. Your
consciousness knows what it is doing.
Have faith and trust in yourself. Grant
yourself the unconditional love of
infinite creation and you will allow
yourself to modulate this energy in
whatever way will allow you to derive
the best benefit from it and be of best
service with this idea.
Therefore, in a similar
fashion, allow yourselves to radiate and
pump more and more intention and energy
into that bright crystallin blue
electromagnetic light. Beginning now.
2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15
16 17 18
19 20 21 22
23 24
27 28
29 30 31 32 33 cuts glaciers hot fire
burning embers smoking ash forests of
green solid stone babbling brooks birds
in trees relax Three deep
breaths. In the final expansion of
energy, you will allow yourselves to
envision that your
entire body, every atom, every molecule, every
body, every atom, every molecule, every
cell in your body will
radiate a blinding
ing yet yet
tolerable white
light. You will become
incandescent. You will be a glowing
bodily form. Allow the aura, the
magnetic field around your body to
switch on like a light.
Radiate that white light and imagine
that white light in a very positive,
loving, integrated and beneficial way
interpenetrating all solid
form. Allow the white light to show how
all of that which you consider to be
solid is a shadow, is an illusion real.
while you are in
it, but an illusion
nonetheless. Allow the white light that
you radiate
radiate
360° in all directions, enveloping the
earth, enveloping the universe from you,
the central
point. Allow it to allow everything in
physical reality to become crystalin
clear and transparent.
Crystallization of your entire body will
then begin on the count
begin on the count
of 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15
16 17 18 19 20 21 22 23 24 25 26 27 28
29 more. 31 32 33 cut blackness of
space. Stars, planets orbiting
throughout the galaxy, spinning power,
energy, coolness,
breeze. Nature, green trees, nature,
green trees, nature, green
trees. Relax in that forest for a
moment. Breathing
deeply naturally in a relaxed
manner and
and
knowing beyond a shadow of a doubt at
this particular
moment that what you have just
done without forcing anyone to do what
they do not want to do will still have a
profound found impact upon the reality
you will experience from this point
forward as your seemingly externalized
reality. You will see from this point
forward accelerations and changes taking
place in your civilization that you may
have previously not believed possible.
You have now elevated
yourselves, accelerated yourselves to
another plain frequency, vibrational
level of
existence. This frequency can therefore
from this point forward only attract to
itself that which represents the same
frequency, the same level. Though you
may still be cognizant of other
frequencies going on all around you,
your experiential physical life will now
experiential physical life will now
unlock and begin to contain only those
things reflective and representative of
acceleration in positive synchronous
directions and dimensions of experience.
You will see changes. Let them occur.
You do not have to make or force them to
occur. You have made a difference.
Believe it. Believe in
yourselves. We thank you for your
participation and your willingness to
crystallize yourselves and become more
homogeneously representative of the
dream you wish to be.
How are you all?
Dream doorways will open for you this
night of your time and every night
forward as well.
Sharing you. Yes. Um, I have a a
situation that I'm going through right
now which I'd like you to comment on.
Okay. I have a situation that I'm going
through right now which I would like
your comment on maybe. Okay.
Um well, it's a situation in which I
feel sort of um betrayed by people I
love very much and trying to deal with
my feelings on it. I go I seem to flip
around. I feel hate. All right. And then
I feel love. All right. And I just Now
do remember first of all before we
continue that your feelings are
reactions to what you already believe to
be true. Feelings are secondary to
belief. You do not have feelings without
already believing in a certain idea. The
feelings you have are always completely
reflective back to you to show you how
you believe your reality to be. You
follow me? Sort of. All right. If you
feel the emotions, if you feel
betrayed, whether or not the other
individuals in your life may actually be
acting outside of their integrity or
not, your ability to intract that
particular attitude or point of view
that allows you to feel as if they are
betraying you, as if it actually
directly affects what you do in life,
comes from a belief that you can be
betrayed, which doesn't have to be possible for
which doesn't have to be possible for
you. You can allow other individuals to
function outside of their integrity if
that is what they are doing without
necessarily taking it personally.
You follow me? Yes. So if you know you
are self-contained and self-reliant,
then in that way you will not have
extended the idea of your power over to
someone else to such an extent that you
can feel that they can ever actually
take anything from you. You're right.
Yeah. Now, do you wish to explore the idea of
Now, do you wish to explore the idea of
your own integrity? Yes. Go ahead. Thank
you. Is this assisting you? Yes. Is there any
Is this assisting you? Yes. Is there any
other aspect you wish to carry through
and explore further to bring it out into
more specific delineations?
Well, I I don't really understand my own
emotional swings on this.
All right. What is it allowing you to
learn? And what is it allowing you to
experience? What is it allowing you to
do? How is it allowing you to be of
service to others and to understand the
belief that you would prefer to exist in
your reality? Well, I don't feel it's
allowing me to be be of service to
others at all. Why not? Is it not
allowing you to be more
yourself? Is it not allowing you to
stand up for yourself, for your
integrity, to center in your being?
Yes. No, maybe.
Well, I guess, but All right. Would you
like to be sure? Yeah. All right. Is
there in any way, shape or form within
your imagination
that you can perceive that there is
anything positive you are getting out of
this at all?
Yeah. What?
Okay. Well, I have looked at the idea
Well, I have looked at the idea
of if I were in these other people's
position, how would I have handled the
situation? see a difference in how I would handle
see a difference in how I would handle
it. All right. And that teaches me
something positive. So now you have a
comparative mode. All right. That is one
idea. Yeah. Now is there some
way that you can be of assistance to
them by being yourself? [Music]
[Music]
Well, I I define the scenario as you
perceive it to exist now. Oh, boy. You
do not have to. Yeah.
No, do not be afraid. Anything you have
to say will be a gift of sharing that
all individuals can learn something
from. Well, be bold.
Yeah. Well, I'm not going to define the
scenario terribly much here, but um
terribly much. All right. Very
specifically, I put it that way. You do
not have to. Yeah. But um how is it you
feel you have been
betrayed? How do you define the
betrayal? Okay.
Well, I feel like
um I was
uh being of assistance. Yes. And um in
what way?
Well, I was um helping these people do a
lot of things. Yes. And it was through,
you know, for me it was a a labor of
love, so to speak. All right. And
um the situation was terminated, but it
was just
like just so fast. Yes. Now, you say it
was a labor of love. Yes. Yes.
Therefore, by that definition, there
wasn't anything in particular you
actually expected to get out of it other
than the doing of it. That's right. So,
how can there be a betrayal if you did
not have an expectation of getting
something specific out of it other than
the doing of it?
because I'm not able to do it anymore.
So why not? Why can you not do it in
other ways, other forms, other places,
other times? Okay. Can you at least to
some extent? Yeah, I can I can imagine
it. Can you yourself not be an expression of
Can you yourself not be an expression of
your own infinite momentum enough to
simply always trust that you will
attract into your life the appropriate
situations to always be able to allow
you to function as you truly desire to
function. Whether or not the situation
changes immediately around you or not is
not the point. If you believe that that
is truly what excites you the most in
life and that is what you continue to
wish you want to do then in some form
one way or another you will do so. Why
not simply assume that the timing of
this endeavor again whether they are
functioning within their integrity in
terminating it or not is still something
that will allow you to add this
experience to the overall understanding
of your being. So that the next level of
this idea that you will be doing will
then be appreciated by you on a slightly
different level from a slightly
different point of view. Having now
integrated this experience into the
overall understanding of yourself rather
than simply putting all of your focus
into this one experience and creating
nothing with the energy but regret that
that particular manifestation of the
experience is no longer going on. If you
focus on the idea of regret of something
that is no longer happening, then you
are not looking forward to the ability
of the next level of the experience and
you will not see it when it arrives
because you are looking backwards to
where you wish you still were. If only.
Yes. Do not forget nothing happens without a
Do not forget nothing happens without a
reason. Nothing. And you are in that
scenario for your own reasons. And you
have attracted yourself to a scenario
that terminated itself when it did for
your own reasons. So simply ask yourself
what those reasons might be. And whether
you have conscious analytical awareness
immediately or not of what they are,
what you can do is always trust that
sooner or later by simply the
continuation of the living or your life,
you will understand why it terminated
when it did. As we have reminded many of
you many times, do not simply determine
any particular event in your life only
against what has already happened, but
also against what is yet to come. Have
there not been scenarios in your life
that at the time they happened you did
not understand why they happened in the
manner they did and then later on when
the situation changed you say oh well
now I understand if it did not happen
that way then this could not have come
about. Yes. Then why not simply assume
the positive attitude and assume that
any situation this so-called termination
is for the opportunity of other things
to take its place that represent the
furthering of your momentum and the path
you chose to be rather than regretting
and moping about it. Right. You follow
me? Mhm. It is up to you utterly to
determine what you get out of your part,
the part you are playing in the
co-creation of that overall event with
the other individuals. They will get out
of it what they need to get out of it.
You get out of it what you need to get
out of it by simply centering in the
fact that you are you and that you are
self-empowered and in a sense no one can
betray you. You attracted yourself to a
situation that terminated itself when it
did. You obviously must have done so for
a reason. Yeah. If you are willing to
have that much faith and trust in
yourself, then you will look upon every
scenario in your life, not as an
interruption in your life, but as a
continuation of the path you chose to
be, does this assist you? Yes, it does.
Thank you. Thank you for being willing
to share of that aspect of yourself and
the multi-dimensional crystal that you
are. Thank you. Sharing you things one
I've noticed that the speak up that the
group of uh consciousness around me the
last week is different than the group
say for the last 3 or 4 months. Can you
comment on that extraterrestrial?
Yes, we understand. And they haven't
identified themselves. That is because
for now, as we have said recently of
your time, the labeling is not
important. Only that you increase your
sensitivity to the energies you are
picking up upon to simply allow yourself
the opportunity to become sensitized to
the many changes that are going on to be
able to perceive the foundations that
are being laid. The whole idea is to
simply relax into your sensing of the
flow without necessarily specifically
labeling anything for everything is now
merging together in one idea so that it
can all come together in one burst or
one leap through the transformational
doorway. You follow me? You are
experiencing a compaction of energy.
That is why you might be experiencing to
some degree some thickening of the
atmosphere around you. You follow me?
Yeah. Also along that lines, I seem to
be I don't know coming more into the
higher self idea. Yes, that is the whole
point of the transformation that each
and every one of you allow yourselves to
function as the complete idea that you
are without needing us to assist you.
That is why there are no labels because
you are now being shown a reflection of
your own version of the energy that many
of you have for so long only relegated
to us but which you have always had
within yourselves.
Thank you for riding the flow. Thank you
for nice the turmoil that I'm going
through. Would this be a reasoning for
like you just said with the other person
previously that is something in my life
to further myself and go on on with
perhaps. What is your specific
definition of the so-called turmoil? Uh,
leaving a job, moving relationships. All
right. Is the idea of the so-called job
you are leaving representative of
something you are not truly excited
about doing? Yes. Then what is it you
are truly excited about doing? I'm not
sure. You're not? Why are you here? To
further myself. Do you mean that you
were excited about being here this
evening of your time? Not at first, but
now I am. Yes. If you were not at first,
then why did you come? Because uh
someone enlightened me as I thought it
might help which it has to an extent. So
you have created your own interpretation
of the idea of your signal, your own
excitement, your own arrow to point the
way. Now that is not to say that it is
specifically us that you need to come to
for it is not. But the idea at any given
moment is to simply act upon whatever at
that moment is the most exciting thing
you are capable of acting upon. Live in
the moment. Take it a moment at a time.
When you trust that you can follow what
excites you at any given moment, that
excitement in that moment will always
lead you to the next most exciting
endeavor you need to allow the path you
chose to be to unfold in an effortless
manner. You follow me? All
right. Excitement, what you call
excitement, you follow me? Yes. is the
physical translation of the vibratory
energy that represents the path you
chose to be in this life. Do you follow
that? Yes.
Therefore, when you finally make the
decision to detach from those things
that do not excite you, it is now an
open opportunity to draw into your life
at any given moment the things that do
excite you the most and therefore the
things that are
synchronistically harmoniously in accord
with the path you chose to be in this
life. Therefore, at any given moment,
when we say the thing that excites you
the most, we do not necessarily mean the
thing that will ever excite you the most
with regard to your entire lifespan. I
do not know what that is. That is not
what we are saying. We are saying that
the thing that excites you the most at
any given moment if you act in full
trust and faith upon that opportunity
will always lead you in the direction of
the overall things that will excite you
the most according to your entire
lifespan. You follow me now? Trust and
faith are all that is necessary to know
that coincidentally, not accidentally, there
coincidentally, not accidentally, there
are no accidents.
Co-incidentally, synchronistically, when
you act at any given moment upon what
excites you the most, are willing to
fully be in that moment and share of
yourself in that opportunity as you are
now doing, you will be putting it out to
all the individuals you interact with in
that moment as to what it is your needs
are to be the individual you desire to
be. You do not have to always know the
details consciously. They will fill
themselves in if you but act in full
conviction and faith and trust upon the
opportunities that present themselves to
you that seem at that moment to be the
most exciting thing you can conceive of
and are able of acting upon to act upon.
He's told me one will always lead to the
next. It is excitement that lets you
know that those events whether they seem
to be connected on the surface or not
with each other are connected to each
other. You follow me?
Now let us exercise your imagination a
little bit. Again, not that you have to
come up with something, but it has
generally been our experience that when
you do relax into your imagination and
allow yourself to cease
invalidating what your imagination gives
you as something that may not be or you
have been taught to believe may not be a
viable living because it is silly,
childish, ridiculous.
Then you may find that you do know many
things that you truly would like to do
but you simply are invalidating them by
not assuming that there is a way that
they can support you in life. What one
thing if you are willing to at least
come up now with one thing anything at
all what one thing aside from what you
are doing right now would excite you to
be doing in your
life anything at all.
Peace of mind. Peace of mind. All right.
But that is a natural state that comes
from doing what excites you the most.
Racing. Racing. In what way? Formula.
All right. Do you find that to be very
exciting? Yes, it was. All right. Is
that something that you wish to continue
to do? Possibility. Yes. A possibility.
Do you find that there is something that
might be even more exciting than that
since you do not sound certain that that
is something you really want to do?
No, nothing at all. No.
Let some pictures run through your mind
for a minute. Just scan all the probable
things you could be doing. At any point
at one of them stops and sounds like it
would be interesting to you, then say
what it is. When we say excitement, it
doesn't mean that you have to be jumping
up and down for joy. What may be your
version of excitement will be the simple
knowingness that this is something you
can do that you would enjoy
doing. Does anything present itself to
you at all? No. I do not believe you.
You are in my estimation not to be
derogatory simply being
stubborn. Why are you here?
Let us backtrack. Why are you here? Why
did you come? What interested you in
coming to this interaction? More
knowledge. More knowledge. All right.
What will you do with that knowledge?
Try to absorb it and understand. There
is no need to try. You will absorb it in
whatever way you need to. But what will
you do with it when you absorb it and
understand it? How will you use it? You
are a physical being in a physical
world. How will you apply knowledge into
my business deal? Is that something that
excites you? Occasionally. Yes.
Occasionally. Do you believe, if I may
ask you a general question, that it is
possible for that idea to excite you all
the time? Yes. Do you wish it to do so?
Yes. Do you believe truly that it can?
Or do you hesitate to believe that that
is possible? Do you hesitate to believe
it is that simple? It hesitate to
believe. All
right. How does it serve you to maintain
a belief that it will be difficult to
allow what you truly find exciting to be
exciting all the time? How does it serve
you to maintain a belief that that
cannot go on? Only when I have control
of the situation. When are you not in
control? When other people intervene,
but you are still controlling the idea
that you are out of
control. You are never not in control.
That's your first
understanding. Never not in control.
Even when you give your power away to
someone else, you are in full control of
your ability to do that. You are never
not in control. You follow me? Yes.
Therefore, if you decide that you are
giving your power away and you decide
that you don't like that, then simply
cease doing it. But do not berate
yourself for having gone out of control
because you are always in control. Do
not regret what you have done because
you have learned something valuable from
it that you need to learn in order to be
the more complete being you desire to
be. You follow me? Yes. The first step
is always to recognize that whether or
not you create positive or negative
events in your life, they are still
there by your choice, by your belief.
And you can always integrate the
experience you get out of it in your
life in a positive way. You follow me?
So, first and foremost, what might be
most exciting to you is to simply begin
to recognize on a daily basis that you
are always in control. Therefore, begin
to take responsibility for the things
that occur in your life. And when you
take full responsibility for them, not
in terms of blame, but in terms of
recognizing that responsibility means
freedom of choice, then you will know
you are always in control. And if
something occurs you do not prefer, you
will always know you have the capability
to redefine the belief and recreate the
reality in the manner reflective of what
you do prefer it to be. Exercise your
integrity and that will bring you joy
and ecstasy and excitement in whatever
you do. All right. Yes. Sleep on it.
Pleasant dreams. Sure. You uh I've in
the last uh I've been going out of town
the last having a good time. Oh, very
good time, sir. Very. Yes. Well, it's an
affectionate term I use. Thank you, sir.
Yes. Thank you, sir. You are welcome,
sir. Please continue. I will do it.
Thank God.
Um, I've been going out of town and my
up to Minneapolis north and my
dreams have been fuller. And at the
beginning of each dream, I have seen
your uh your ship or a ship, a huge like
a huge uh space station that kind of
glides in. Define
um define the way the ship looks. egg.
It's um flat
bottomed. Looks
[Music] uh like it could
be six stories high and
uh comes to a point in the
front. And is it cylindrical or dislike?
My recollection dislike.
[Music] Do you mean in your terms after the
Do you mean in your terms after the
fashion of a very large saucer shape?
Well, what well what I saw what the
picture that is the space station in
Star Trek 4. Uh the it's just like
um did it have protrances or was it
smooth? The bottom was smooth and the
top had
[Music] protrances. We feel this to be your
protrances. We feel this to be your
interpretation in your own terms of
something that you did experience, but
it does not exactly look that way in
your physical terms. I I it it seemed
like it seemed to be the the
introduction to each dream. There was
always this ship,
this ship,
this vessel. It was like a vessel, I
guess. Let us say
simply that our perception of what you
are tapping into is not exactly what you
would call a station, but a very large
survey craft.
It is not what you would call a mother
ship. A very large survey craft. That is
where you got the connotation in your
mind that it is a station since it
carries upon it many different functions
of what you would colloquially refer to
as scientific instrumentation. And there
were also other little ships that would
go out from it. Okay. And I was
wondering about the significance though
of it coming like at the beginning of my
dreams and just kind of hovering and
then actually going into a specific
dream. You are using it as a reference
beacon. You are tapping into the
wavelengths and you draw yourself to its
sphere of influence in a non-dimensional
sense in a non-physical dimensional
sense. You are simply orienting on it as
a starting point because you know that
now that you have discovered it that if
you orient upon it you will
automatically take yourself to a
starting point that will give you an
advantageous point of view to go from.
You will already be let us say beyond
many of the things that would let us say
colloally involve having to work or
process yourself to get to that level
ordinarily. You simply have found
something to focus on that allows you to
elevate to a certain level immediately
and then you proceed from there in your
travels so to speak. Oh, so I use it
like like a diving board or a launching
because in a sense that is what it is.
Oh, I see.
All right. And thank you. Uh and I have
uh another question. I've had this uh
cold or bronchitis for about 3 and 1/2
months and it keeps
recurring. Um and I I know I've created the
Um and I I know I've created the
situation of of the bronchitis and for I
must enjoy it because I I um the idea is
not that you
What do you imagine would be the most
likely reaction to clearing the air?
Uh, loss. Law. Loss. Yeah. Loss of I
mean I mean I I know it's like an idea
in a picture. Uh but it's like loss of
friendship, loss of love, loss of um do
you mean rather than the creation of
friendship, the creation of different
forms of love, different and new
experiences of those ideas? Why just a
loss? Why are you looking at it as a
negative rather than a positive? Why are
you looking at it as a going from rather
than a going to? [Music] [Music]
Do you
feel a slight rise in temperature in
your chest?
Then let yourself continue to feel it
while you ponder the idea of what the
so-called consequences would be of
speaking in accordance to the being you
know yourself to be. speaking what you
know to be true for
you. If you say what you know is true
for you, are you going to be doing so to
be consciously malicious to someone else
or consciously hurtful? No. Then
understand you are not responsible for
the reactions of others according to the
truth you know is true for you. As long
as you know you are functioning within
your integrity and you will simply be
taking yourself to other levels where
then you will attract the friends and
the love that are representative of
those levels you are taking yourself to.
You are not losing anything. You cannot
lose anything. You will be allowing what
you already have to simply transform
along a different definition. I think I
know that intellectually it's been
emotionally that I have all right. All
right. Another wonderful phrase your
society has taught you to keep things
separated and to keep you from knowing
that you do understand it better than
you think you do. I know it
intellectually,
but that's right. Pump it out.
May I let you in on a little secret
which is no secret.
The outside is the inside. The inside is
the outside. If you
outside. If you
find that you believe that in order to
be
yourself, you will obscure and cloud the
outside, then you will obscure and cloud
the inside simultaneously. If you
understand that being yourself will
always promote clarity in all the
situations in your life in the outside
then you will be clear on the inside
simultaneously. You follow me? Yeah. It
is all
one. If you hold it
in that does not mean it's not going to
leak out. No, I I realize that it has
been leaking out.
You do not need to hold on to these
fears. They do not serve you in positive
ways. Trust yourself and trust the
reality outside you that is
representative of the self you are. What
you choose to be on the inside is what
you will experience on the outside.
Trust it.
Yes. Will that allow you to breathe more
easily? I I believe it
I I believe it
will do. You may also sleep on it and
tap into that same vibrational warmth
that you are feeling now. Create that
for yourself. In any time you find yourself
yourself. In any time you find yourself
to be in a relaxed state, let it burn
brightly within
you. All right. All right.
Funky. Hey.
Then do speak up by all means.
I'm choosing to create a good harmony
with my stepmother. Oh, right. Use a a
picture. which might explain how I feel
when I talk to her. Someone take their
hand and their nails and run it along a
blackboard. And that's what it's like
for me when I talk to her sometimes. And
I feel like the confrontation we're
having is that sometimes I attempt to
point out that she doesn't have to run
her hands along the blackboard and she
doesn't want to hear it. and she
interprets my giving her an alternative
as telling her what to do or lecturing
her. And I find myself
um getting angry at her because I can't
interact with her. All right. But you
are obviously interacting with her. All
right. But then I can't. Perhaps the
question we have for you is why is the
blackboard in your reality as well as in
hers? That's a good question. Do you
have a good answer?
Um, no. I remember a good answer, I
guess. How about a suggestive exercise?
If you're going to maintain that
blackboard in your reality, then write
upon it 100 times. I have no blackboard
in my reality.
It is up to you. We are playing with
you, but we perceive that that in a way
is what you need. a little
recess rather than so much
schoolwork with that particular teacher.
You follow me? Now you are teachers for
each other in many different
ways. The idea, one of the ideas is to
truly allow you to be your own reality
even while you are connecting into her.
It is to allow you to decide that even
though you do wish to interact and wish
to be of service, that you do not have
to create all of the same props in your
reality that she may be creating in hers
to do so. You follow me? Yes, I do. And
I recognize the fact that when she's
when she expresses herself and I don't
agree with her, that there's a part of
me that that invalidates myself or
questions myself as to whether I'm, you
know, have my own facts together. Okay.
So I understand that she's again
allowing me to to uh assert myself not
over her but within myself to hey it
does not mean you have to become
conflictive in that way and to some
degree as you have already
discussed you can experiment with the
ideas of simply in this way if she is
insistent upon what she believes herself
to be agreeing with it. Okay. I I had
people suggest that to me and there's a
part of me that feels like I'm
swallowing myself doing that. All right.
We do not mean agree with it in the
sense that you give up your own
understanding. Agree with it. go with
the flow and still express your point of
view by using her as a
springboard by saying all right this is
the way you believe I
agree with you and by agreeing with you
this is the reaction that agreeing with
you causes within me.
This is how I will interact with you if
you want me to agree with
you. You follow me? Yes, I do. Okay. You
can still state your case, so to speak.
Well, to be honest with you, I don't I
guess the whole thing is I want to not
have
any arguments with her. All right. And
that's not going to stop it. But
understand it always takes two to
argue. You are doing your part in
believing that you are arguing with her.
Again, the idea of the so-called
agreement we are referring to is not the
reflection of a swallowing what you
would like to share, what you would like
to say that represents you standing up
for yourself.
But the idea is is that if you simply
recognize that arguing is not in your
reality, you will simply allow many of
the things that are said to pass right
through you because they will find no
foothold. There is no blackboard in your
reality to have noise made
upon. You follow me? Yes, thank you.
Okay, I'll give it a go.
See what happens if you do the little
exercise we suggested.
If something during that process occurs
to you in terms of changing what you are
writing on that blackboard, then by all
means change it. You may use the
blackboard that now acts as your
bane to be something that can assist you
in revealing to you the belief systems
you have within your subconscious. an
unconscious mind. And when you find them
clicking in, write them on the
blackboard so you can see them. When you
write them all out, then erase
them as no longer valid in your reality.
Okay. All right. Is it possible um that
during the second half at some point
would be able to grind the channel to
some degree? Do you recognize the
timing? The idea is the appropriately
timed 1210. The idea in this way being the
1210. The idea in this way being the
representation 1012 of the Earth Orion
connection 1111 Earth Essani 1210 Earth
Sirius. Thank you for your recognition.
To some degree this will be possible.
Thank you for sure. you the rules. I
haven't been sharing my beliefs with um
some of my friends and my uh parents
because I feel like my my beliefs are so
different from their belief that if I
there's no one that says that you have
to share the idea in a blatant way
simply by being the being you are based
upon the beliefs you now hold to be true
for you. You will be sharing them by
doing what those beliefs are
representative of. You do not have to
force these ideas on anyone by simply
assuming that you must verbally
communicate these ideas with them. You
are not doing anything wrong by not
communicating them directly. If such is
necessary, you will find yourself
attracting into your life opportunities
and situations that will make it obvious
that it is an easy thing to do to share
some of these ideas. You follow me? Yes.
I I'm not sharing them because I'm
afraid that I will be rejected if I do.
and I'd like to share them, but I don't
know how to like tone them down so that
they could
accept or put them into a form that they
could more readily
understand. For now, we would simply
suggest that you allow yourself to
believe in them yourself a little more
strongly because then you will not care
who accepts or rejects them.
And then is when you will paradoxically
attract to you the appropriate
situations that will give you all the
knowledge you need in terms of the
format in which to deliver the
information. It will be obvious as to
how to deliver the information. You may
even get the surprise they may bring the
subject up. Oh well I've heard about
this thing the other day. Say you ever
heard anything about this idea? Well,
yes, I've heard a little bit. What I
heard is such and such and such and
such. Oh, really? Well, I can go along
with the such and such, but well, not
the such. Well, all right. Well, that's
simply what I heard. You follow me? Yes.
I was also looking, is this idea related
to the idea of bleeding? It seems like
I'm bleeding a lot, and I was wondering,
is this like the same idea?
It can be connected in many metaphorical
ways. You might in a
way be representing some connections
that you have had before with each
other. You might still feel that the
only way to get someone to accept you in
that way is to absolutely give up your
life's blood for them. in this way
perhaps to evoke the idea that you are
being drained, the idea of perhaps to
some degree pity. Even though this may
not be on the surface, there is no need
for the idea of choosing to believe that
what you believe to be true for you must
make you a
martyr. Martyrs often
bleed. You follow me? Yeah.
There is no need for you to shed your
life's blood in order to believe in what
you wish to believe in. You understand?
Relax. Lighten up on them. Lighten up on
yourself. All right. No need to push.
They do not have to understand
that. They will understand if and when
they need to, if and when they want to.
You have your
life. They have their life. You share
what you share by
agreement. If you believe in the things
you say you believe in, then let your
life be an effortless and obvious series
of opportunities to share when and where
it is most obviously appropriate for you
to do so. Doesn't have to be a struggle.
No heavy decision. You follow me? Relax.
Enjoy. You will
radiate. They will perhaps come to you
and say, "You know, you've changed a lot
lately. What's going on?" Well, I have
changed because I now believe this,
this, and this. Oh, really? Well, seems
to work for you. Tell me more about it.
You follow me?
Relax. You have been a family many
times. You are a family now in many
different ways. Do understand that you all agreed
ways. Do understand that you all agreed
to be together this life. So on some
level they do understand you. You follow
me? Relax into that level where you know
you all understand each other and you
will allow that level of understanding
to rise to the surface of your life as
well. Do not forget the outside is the
inside. The inside is the outside. It is
all one. All right. Thank you very much
Mark. Yes. Um I have not been real happy
at my job for the last couple of months
or so and at one point so what are you
going to do? So I well at one point I I
examined my options and nothing appeals
to me a great deal about excitement. But
the the least or
the least worst. No the thing the only
thing that I could think of that would
be acceptable was to take a leave of
absence. All right. Because I didn't
really want to look for another job. And
all right then if that's where the
excitement lies do it. And in that
absence you may find what you are
looking for. any that's what I was going
to do because I was excited and I've
been on leave now for a week and a
half and even though it wasn't an
exciting idea sounded okay to do and
ever since I've been on leave I've felt
really fantastic wonderful uh can you
tell the difference
do not forget something even though we
may from time to time perceive the
so-called overlays of the things that
quote unquote bother many of you. To us,
almost all we ever perceive of you is
your excitement because we have absolute
unconditional belief in all of you.
Okay. We always know you will always be
all right. Oh, yeah. I know that, too. I
I know. Totally. Throughout my body, I
know I'm going to be okay. You feels
wonderful. Fine. Anyway, I was at the
mall on Saturday uh doing a little
Christmas shopping. Mall. All right.
And at one point, is that M A L L or M A
U L? [Music] All
All
right. At one point, uh, I decided I
don't know what I was thinking about. I
was just walking. I was not in a sto.
And it felt like a being came through
me. And I thought of you and I thought
of Ethasani in general and I got very
laded but it was only in the right side
of my body and even my my leg. Let us
say simply for now let us say it was a
projection of a portion of your own
future self identifying with our energy
in that way. I it was wonderful very
strong and my leg buckled under and I
just kept going. And I thought, gee, how
great. Anyway, uh I also had a dream, I
think Monday night, which I thought were
interesting and oh no, Sunday night. Um
I had been thinking about writing a
letter to million and
um there there are a couple of things
that I wasn't too sure about. So I I I
guess I just thought about it and I
dreamed about that letter. The dream
started with that letter. I don't know
if the rest of it that I want to ask you
about is related, but we're all in a
room and we're supposed to write that
letter. And I said, "Well, I can't write
a letter with all these people around."
And the person said, "Well, you'd all
have to come back and finish it after
dinner except
for well, that's nice. I can do it on my
own the way I want to do it." And very
good. And then we we went outside and
looked at birds. The theme was sort of
vague, but the thing I want to ask you
or tell you about is we were looking at
these birds and then at one point I
found myself way up in the air with just each
myself way up in the air with just each
arm supported by a pole, a long long
long pole. And my body was just hanging
up like I didn't know where the pole was
supported from because I was up in the
air and there was somebody in front of
me. And I thought, well, I'm going to
slide back to see where the loop is
between the two poles because I had one
pole under each arm. And I was getting
very, very uncomfortable. And I kept
moving back and I couldn't find the
loop. And at one point, I said to the
person in front of me, I said, "Well,
oh, I thought to myself, I'm going to
have to just let myself drop and die."
And I said, "Okay, that's okay. It
doesn't matter if I die. I mean, I just
can't feel that discomfort anymore."
Very good. And just at the point when I
said, "I'm going to let myself drop."
Yes. There was this huge tree behind me
with big instead of branches, it had stumps
big instead of branches, it had stumps
like a staircase and I just put my feet
on it and went down and got to the
ground and it was very easy to get down.
Supported by your own naturalness. Very
good. letting yourself know that death in your
letting yourself know that death in your
case in this sense is only the allowance
of complete and total transformation and
it is actually a birth. It is your
willingness to allow the natural creator
that you are to support you. You do not
have to play the balancing act.
You are utterly all of you supported
completely. Understand it is very
similar to the reason why the
physiological channel feels no
expenditure of effort after these
channelings. The energy is total blended
supportive. The body of the channel is
expending no effort.
You also expend no effort when you allow
the automatic creator that you are which
is represented by what you call nature
to support you
unconditionally. You follow me? Yeah. I
was I mentioned the dream to a friend
and she said boy you were really literal
and she was thinking in terms of the
pole being that I was exploring
polarity. You are balancing on the idea but now
You are balancing on the idea but now
you have gotten tired of the balancing
act. Right. You are letting the idea
come together to support you as a
natural extension of all that you are of
your natural sense. Okay. Thank you.
Thank you.
You venue. Thank you. Um some weeks
back, probably a couple of months ago,
speak up. A couple of months ago, I
asked you
for your viewpoint on how I could stop
having nightmares or how I could
outreate my nightmares of having dreams.
And I'd like to give you a progress
report if you wish. Um, in the form of a
sharing. All right, speaker. I went home
that very night, the night of dreams,
and wrote down the goal on a paper next
to my bed that I was to have the dreams
and not nightmares. Oh, right. I
succeeded in that. The second night, um,
by the way, that was the first night I
had not had nightmares in as long as I
could remember. The second night, I also
added to that goal the goal of slowing
the dreams down enough so that I could
relax and enjoy them. Oh, very good.
Fiber circus going. And it's progressed
and progressed to the point now that
typically um when I decide to write down
my dreams the next morning and interpret
them um it's become very very
easy simple without any doubt whatsoever
at very good and this is coming from a
background before I started coming here
last summer when I had been taught that
dreams mean absolutely nothing so I had
never bothered paying any attention to
There may be some cause and effect with
that of nightmares because there may be
some invalidation on other levels
occurring. Yes. So mostly on this level,
right? Um I want to thank you for that.
I would also like to ask you a question,
but I really wanted to take that to full
circle because it's very upsetting to
know that not only do I have complete
control of my dream reality and my awake
reality whenever it's not being
invalidated by myself, of course, right?
Um, but that I not only can control my
dreams as well, but learn from them. And
right and I see that it is a continuum
of the awake reality or physiological
reality and the dream reality.
more and more real. Thank you very much.
Thank you. And I would also like to ask
a question. Other than the fact that I
was named after my aunt who is my
father's sister, would you care to
comment on the choice of the name Faith?
You mean aside from the obvious? [Music]
[Music]
I am finding that or I have found that
uh
does it give you something to live up
to? Yes, it certainly does. Talk about
experiencing polarities. Wow. That's um
I've never I've never had the attitude
of wow, I have to live up to that.
However, recently with what I've been
[Music] learning, it it is actually
learning, it it is actually
becoming more of a challenge. I guess
I'm confronting it now. Whereas does not
have to become a confrontation in that
sense, but simply a realization of one
of the phrases we have said and shared
with you many times in terms of the
creation of all you experience in your
reality. Faith is all there is. But why
me? Why not?
Why not?
I just wonder why me as opposed to
anyone else in this room, for example.
Well, you chose it. Why not? I chose
your vibration. Now, that's interesting.
If I chose it that I I know if I chose
it, I know why I chose it because that's
a lesson I am here on earth to learn
this. Thank you. It is that obvious when
you let it be. I somehow thought my
parents chose that for me. The whole
idea is a cocreation, right? You chose
the vibration. They simply were
sensitive to it and gave you the
representative name.
You all make agreements together and
everything works in accord. Even when
someone chooses a vibration for you that
you find you wish to change later, that
serves purposes as well. Right. I'm not
unhappy with it, but I I never
really dealt with it. I just kept it
very light. Now that I'm
uh now it is clearer that you are more
willing to act on simple faith. Right?
Keep it simple.
Thank you. Yes.
I have been creating a duality in
relationship in my Oh, you are not
alone. It is the time of the exploration of
It is the time of the exploration of
polarity. Please continue. I would like
to unify in what way?
I have uh I separated from my wife two
years ago. Oh wow. And uh during that
intervening time I have started a
relationship with another woman. Right.
And the my wife and I the relationship that
the my wife and I the relationship that
we shared was one that was
extraordinarily spiritual. The
relationship is still going on very
strong. There are no wases to any
relationship. that that relationship is
going on very strongly in this moment.
And yet we had difficulty uh in the
day-to-day realities. All right. Um the
other woman who entered my life was
somebody with whom I enjoy
uh a great deal of joy in the day-to-day
realities. Very little of the uh
spiritual journey that uh inspires me.
So you are finding the idea of
relationship in pieces so to speak.
Indeed. All right. Unify the
relationship within yourself first and
all relationships can reflect that
change within you. The idea is to
perform the marriage of your own
polarities. The idea is that you then
become a reflection of a completion of a
unification within yourself rather than
seeking it in other individuals. When
you are married to yourself in that way,
when you marry the feminine and
masculine aspects within yourself and
the polarities of positive and negative
within you and allow them to be equal
and valid within you, then you will be a
radiation of that equality and you will
attract individuals who will be a
reflection of that equality of that
balance. You follow me? I do. To some
degree you are functioning in a triad
format and you may find that there will
be a third individual who might be able
to be the pinnacle of the reflection of
the blending that will take place within
you. Do remember at any case that any
individual that may change so to speak
when you change that may begin to wish
to incorporate certain ideas or
understandings within themselves to
become more equal to the idea you are
becoming will not be the same individual
anyway. So it does not matter whether
they are physiologically the same
individual who seems to have changed or
whether they are a completely other
physical individual who brings with them
the reflection of what now you need to
see as a reflection of what you have
been willing to blend. Are you following
this? I am. My dilemma is your what? My
dilemma. Your what? My question all
right is that as I have embraced both those
is that as I have embraced both those
parts of myself. Okay. In the
intervening time, I have been able to
bring each of those two people whom I
love dearly in my life uh towards that
central point as well. Yes. But this is
the whole idea of the fourth density
transformation and it's very similar to
what we explore and experience in our
civilization wherein every single member
of our civilization knows and acts as if
they are married to every other member.
Indeed, it is all equal. You have
relationships based upon the reasons for
why the relationships are there to
reflect to you what you need to learn so
you can reflect to them what they need
to learn. Once a relationship is
started, it never ends. No matter what
the physiological definition of that
relationship and every single one of
them are equal in their own rights, on
their own terms, for the reasons you
have attracted each other into those
relationships. Precisely. The question then becomes in
Precisely. The question then becomes in
our world, it's very difficult.
I find
H in whose world? In my life, I find it
very difficult. That was then. What
about now? If you truly begin to believe that
now? If you truly begin to believe that
you are functioning as a blended being,
then it will become less and less
difficult. Because if you truly are
believing that you are that blended
being then you will simply begin to only
attract other blended beings or other
beings who have a high potential for the
experience of that blending and it will
not be difficult at all. Let me clarify
what the difficulty is that I'm What is
your definition? The difficulty that I
have is then
um in a
monogous world it's difficult to go
forward with two people that I care for
that have but your world is not
necessarily going to remain in that
form. That's the
point. So if that is your world now then
simply relax into the understanding that
you are creating these relationships
with integrity. You do not have to
create or go along with the idea of the
belief that you are not functioning in
your integrity and simply relax into the
understanding that your universe is your
own universe and you will only
experience the reflections of the idea
of the universe you are being and will
not be physiologically affected by the
beliefs of other individuals. And you
did only. And then your willingness to
do that and function in that way is what
will paradoxically allow because you are
willing to put that vibration into your
reality other individuals to draw from
it if they also decide to choose that
reality for themselves. In any event,
you will generally only attract the
individuals into your life that will be
reflective of that reality one way or
another or individuals who wish to see
that reality reflected from you. If you
truly know you are being truly yourself.
You told me. I do indeed. Thank you,
Barry. And thank you.
You may all take a short break.
How's everything going? Wonderful.
All right. Now say allow us to begin
with the
understanding of what we have referred
to as the serious energy that being
representative of the higher consciousness aspect of
of the higher consciousness aspect of
the triad consciousness energy that is
created by your civilization, our
civilization and their civilization.
three parts of the same overall
consciousness that create the three
systems or civilizations you perceive us
respectively to be including yourselves.
This energy in functioning on the level
that it does is mostly what you would
call non-corporeal existing in a type of
non-corporeal existing in a type of
energy see energy dimension.
That is why certain interactions that
many of them have had in energy ways, in
mental ways with various members at
various times of your civilization has
usually created in your mentality the
interpretation of these beings as being
literally physically amphibious which
they are not. However, due to this
projection and due to this affinity for
that particular metaphor or analogy, you
will find that they have been able to
establish a quite strong rapport as it
were with the idea of the other to us
alien species upon your planet. That
which you call the dolphin whale life
forms, the Satasian life forms. For you
are as we have said land human and in a
sense they are the water human or you
are if you wish the
lancetasian. In this way though we
recognize that human and sitasian are
the descriptions of the relative
exterior physiological forms. You are
like us together. Human dolphin the same
type of soul. and in times past and to
some degree beginning again now share
many of the same interchangeable
reincarnational cycles. You are availing
yourself of interaction with them. And
by so doing, you are gathering the
experience you require to be able to
communicate with what you perceive to be
the typically as us extraterrestrial
civilization by getting used to the fact
that you have an alien civilization
existing alongside of you on your very
own planet. They are very willing to
assist you at this time and you will
find that they are very open to you in
that way.
Now there will be more of this
communication on slightly different
levels. One moment. [Music]
Allow us to begin this interaction this
evening of your time with the idea of
the sharing of the dolphin consciousness
that is now paramount in your reality.
The idea that you are sharing this
evening of your time, the idea of
basing, of forming a foundation, forming
a base for the idea of the expression of
the interaction, the interchange between
yourselves and that which you call the
dolphin consciousness. Recognize that
the symbols you are creating in your
physiological reality, the symbols you
are creating in your human reality can
be the various usage of the many symbols
of the description of the idea of the
dolphin consciousness in your forms of
art. Many ideas of the expression of
literature, many of the ideas of
expression of what you call your film,
many of the ideas of the expression of
what you call your paintings. Observe
the idea of the symbol that you have
within the house in which you are
residing. The idea of the dolphin
consciousness as is presented to you in
the idea of the format that when you
know that you have this symbol before
you, you automatically when you focus
upon it tune into this specific
vibration necessary for them to know
that you are open in your mind, open in
your heart for their ability to
communicate and interact with you. In
that way, you can utilize the idea of
any symbol, any representational symbol
of the idea of the dolphin form. In this
way, once you gaze upon it, your
mentality will automatically focus. Your
mentality will automatically go to this
specific register or frequency of
vibrational analysis vibrational of open
communication with them. They will pick
up on. They will receive the idea.
Anytime you focus upon anything that
represents their energy to you, you will
be directly opening and accessing the
idea and allowing them to open and
access the idea of your heart, your
empathy, your telepathic communication.
You will begin to allow yourself to
focus and soften the idea of the
barriers you have created in your
society. In this way, in softening those
barriers, you will begin to melt into
the idea of the openness of your heart.
You will begin to melt into the same sea
which you share in your dream realities.
for they are in your dream realities
constantly in this way. Recognize at
this time therefore that the idea of
allowing yourself to participate in the
creation or attraction into your life of
any such symbol that represents the
dolphin or whale citation form anytime
you use it anytime as you focus upon it
within the idea of your meditation will
allow you instantaneous access to the
idea of receiving the energy which comes
from them which is always being sent to
you in that way. Allow yourselves the
participation. Allow yourselves more
physiological interaction in this way.
They desire to interact with you. Not
only on a mental level, not only in an
emotional level, but on a physical level
as well. For in many ways, as you have
said, they are your brothers. They are
your sisters. You share the same planet,
even though you are what you call two
alien species upon the same world. You
share many ideas. You have intermingled
and interacted with each other for
thousands upon thousands of years. In
this way, share these ideas now,
bringing them back out into the dream
realities you are creating upon your
planet, the dream realities you are
creating upon your society. begin to
blend and share and merge and leap for
ecstasy, leap for joy in much the same
manner that they show you. Allow
yourselves to begin to learn how to play
as they play in this way. Allow
yourselves the opportunity to see the
gleam and the sparkle in their
consciousness as you see the gleam and
the sparkle in their eyes. They know
you. They love you. They wish to
participate and interact with you. And
more and more you will understand that
as this permeates the very society core
in which you exist, then you will
recognize that they exist on much the
same level as you do, in this way will
allow more freedom of interaction to
take place. even among the ideas of the
cultures upon your planet that now does
not consider them to be the idea of
equal sharing with you that considers
them to be in the idea of the animal
kingdom in this way. Not that the idea
of the animal kingdom is deserving of
any less of your respect in that sense,
but recognize that you can form the
basis for a conglomerate world
confederation of the idea of the two
species that you are and allow yourself
in mingling and blending this idea of
the federation that you are upon your
world with two alien species. that as
you enter the idea of the association of
all other worlds, you will bring into
that association the idea of membership
of two distinct species in that way a
very rich and joyous gift that you will
give to us by allowing yourself to share
and enjoy the experience of the blending
of the two alien worlds that you are
side by side on your very own world. Are
you all following along? Allow
yourselves the opportunity therefore in
the sharing of this joy and the sharing
of this play. Open your hearts in that
way. Allow yourself to let them in. For
they only wish and only to share in the
idea of your wishes do they wish to
participate with you in this way. You
are capable of swimming as freely in
your physiological realities as they
swim in what you call to be the oceans
of your world. In this way, as freely as
we swim in the energy sea, out of which
we are homogeneously created as one
single identity and as respectively all
the identities that we are within the
energy sea of the world that we are
round about the star you call Sirius,
which we refer to in your vernacular as
Cine. In this way, allow yourselves to
participate and understand that you
yourselves even on the physiological
land masses of your planet do partake
and participate and are immersed in an
electromagnetic sea. As Bashar has
talked to you about the idea, you are
swimming in this sea. You are swimming
in your own sea of dreams. Allow
yourselves to know that even though
interaction is taking place upon the
idea of the reality of the dream world
in which you sleep, you are very much
awake in those worlds and very much
participating with the ideas of many
friends you have made in the dolphin
consciousness layer. Allow yourselves
once again to let these dream realities
filter and focus and flood into the
physiological realities that you
experience as your dayto-day events.
Allow yourselves to begin to live your
dreams and swim in the sea of the dreams
and the energy that you are. Expand your
heart and allow the fluid of this
electromagnetic sea to beat through the
valves of your heart. Experiencing with
every breath out and with every breath
in that you are ingesting that you are
breathing this energy C in that way that
you are made of the same material as the
energy se and that you are simply in
this way. Let us say a crystallization
of the same the very same
electromagnetic ethermagnetic material
out of which that sea is created. You
are in touch with the pulse of creation
in that way. And as you become more
sensitized to the waves and the currents
of that electromagnetic sea, then you
can feel yourselves moving with the
flow, moving with the currents and
allowing yourselves to be caught up in
that wave. You will find yourself
peeking at the crest of that wave in
joyous ecstasy for all the remaining
time you wish to experience in physical
reality upon your planet. You follow me?
Then our joy to you, our love to you,
and allow us once again to remind you,
wake up and dream. Give yourselves the
opportunity to swim in the energy sea
that you are. Swim and drink deeply of
the energy that you have created
yourselves to be. We thank you very
much.
And so allow yourself the
opportunity to remember
that it is not so much that you require
a very specific technique in order to
get in touch with the dolphin
consciousness, but that
even the idea of settling your eyes upon
any representation of their
form, as you know, if you are paying
attention to yourself when you do so,
will create within you a
softening, an opening of your hearts as
you simply even peer upon the
representational form of their
This opening will send a frequency to
their consciousness which is always
being sent to you. You will form that
identification, the blending that will
allow you and they to interpret the
creative energy of the infinite in the
same way or similar way so that you will
know each other's thoughts. Not so much
because you are directly reading each
other's minds, but because you are
identifying with each other so closely
that you do swim in each other's oceans.
Benny, thank you. Uh, my roommate couldn't be
thank you. Uh, my roommate couldn't be
here tonight and she wanted me to ask
you this for her. She said she's been
having um trouble or a hard time with
the idea of trust. All right. She said
uh self trust and trusting others. She
feels that when she's trusted others in
the past, it hasn't worked out. And the
idea is first of all, of course, to
trust the self. Yes. And again to cease
assuming that things aren't working
out. When you again paradoxically allow
whatever occurs in your life to be
reflective of what you believe is the
most likely possibility, then you will
gain something from it in a positive
learning way because then you will give
yourself the opportunity to determine
how to redefine what you don't prefer.
If you
constantly use the energy and express it
in the form of regret, self-rrimation
and failure, then you are not allowing,
she is not allowing herself to use those
scenarios in a positive direction.
Understand she is and always has been
absolutely and all of you are absolutely
at any given moment using trust
100%. It is simply that she has more
trust in the idea of
failure more trust in the idea that
things can occur in her life that cannot
serve her. That is simply where her
trust is being channeled. She lack no
trust. It is simply up to her to
determine in what direction and with
what attitude and point of view she
wishes to use the infinite trust she
always has. You follow me? Yes. Will you
share that idea? Yes. Thank you. Why?
Yes. Um, I heard from some people in
your audience that the constellation
Orion was associated with negativity in
some way. To some degree, particularly
in what you would call time past, there
has now been many blendings within some
of the beings of the systems that you
are referring to. Even though it is not
simply, let us say, restricted to what
you colloquially call the Orion
constellational system. In this way, you
will find that many individuals from
those original systems have reincarnated
upon Earth for the express purpose of
learning how to balance the polarities
of negative and positive instead of the
continuation of the repetitive cycles of
in negativity that had occurred within
the original systems. The reason I ask
is that I believe I have an intimate
relationship with the constellation
Orion. Oh, what? Uh is that would that
be so for me then that I had was a
negative being at some time in the past?
Well, you have all been in relationship
to the Orion constellation. Basically,
you have some association in that way.
But what are you learning now?
What am I learning now? I'm learning how
to learn in the consciousness of God
every moment. All right. Then you are
learning how to balance the idea of
positive and negative polarity. Yes or
no? Yes. All right.
When you find you have any particular
affinity or attraction to any particular
symbol, including what you call a
constellation, it is usually an
indication that you are creating that
affinity for a reason to remind you of
something to represent a certain degree
of momentum or an idea begun at one
point that you are now perhaps
concluding at another point.
The idea
basically is that what was learned in
those original systems and what is being
now understood by many of the original
individuals from those systems is that
to attempt to fight
negativity is only the increasing of
negativity. And the idea is to allow
there to be an
equality of positive and negative. So
that then not any one
side is intrinsically given more power
than any other side. This then is what
will allow you to choose from among
equal alternatives what it is you
actually desire to experience in the
physical reality in which you exist. You
seem to speak from a very impersonal
level. When you speak, when I ask you a
question, are you speaking uh addressing
me personally that that is so that I am
in relationship to the Orion
constellation or are you just speaking
universally? Both because there are many
many many individuals present this night
of your time that have the same
connection. So what is the connection?
So what is the connection?
The connection is that you have had many
lives there and you are relying upon
your memory of what you learned there to
learn what you are learning now.
You follow me? Sure. But those
connections are going on simultaneously
with any life you are living now because
time linear time is your illusion.
You follow me? What is the relationship
of Merlin in the constellation Orion?
The relationship contains many other
things other than a direct connection to
Orion, but it will contain some of the
original energy because what you
represent on Earth as what you call
sorcery or magic very deeply figured
into much of the Orion original system.
You have brought from those systems many
representational ideas. We are being
general you with you to earth to
represent your understanding of your
connections to nature. But now some of
the aspects you now represent as the
Merlin consciousness represent not just
the Orion understanding of what you call
to be magic but also some of the new age
understandings of what you call to be
magic. Merlin in that way is more
representative of what you are all
becoming. Even though it does contain a
high degree of the polarity of what you
have all been with respect to your
ability to actually create and
manipulate so to speak the physiological
reality you experience around you, the
matter itself, the energy itself. Are
you a scientific being to some degree
although our science is not exactly as
your planet would call science in all
endeavors? Oh, so you're existing on a planet right
Oh, so you're existing on a planet right
now? Right now I am in my spacecraft,
but yes, we have a physiological
representation that you would recognize
as a planet not too unlike your own. So
you are in a physical incarnation.
Thank you. Does that serve you? Yes.
Thank you.
Hey. Uh, I have a couple questions
concerning uh dream
reality. This morning uh I had a dream
where there was a a male figure that I
did not recognize, a female figure who
is a friend of
mine, my cat, and myself.
And we were doing a seemingly a
ritualistic uh
suicide. Okay. Which didn't seem to
upset me at all. All right. And we did
it with a uh like a disc uh a couple
inches in diameter and very thin and
very sharp and inserted it in the lower
pelvis area.
and the male and the female
um passed over relatively early and it
was the cat and myself left
and I held the cat up in my arms and I
was going to put some music on. I go,
"Well, maybe I'll die to an interesting
tune this
morning." All right. And as I did that,
I go, "Well, who really cares about
that?" Because I could see the cat was
just about ready to go under. And I just
took the cat in my arms just as she died
and I felt myself like a real heaviness
coming over me and then I woke up
and um but it was a great day. Yay.
You I had blended the polarities of the
masculine and feminine within you in
that way and then left the idea of the
exploration of what you might call the
mystery within yourself. And as you
absorbed it into yourself and saw the
external symbol fade away, you added
that energy to your being felt a little
heavier for the added energy for a
while. But that act extra heaviness is
simply your remnant habitual
physiological interpretation of what
happens when you add more energy to
yourself. Eventually it will actually
uplift you and enlighten you rather than
feeling heavy because now you still
equate energy with mass. Mhm. And today
I didn't in uh physiologically I didn't
feel heavy or anything. I felt real. You
simply gave yourself the symbol in a
physiological interpretive way. Okay.
You have incorporated many of those
fragments within yourself now and are
functioning more completely on those
polarized blended levels. You are now
your own mystery containing all the
questions and all the answers.
You follow me? Yeah. You are walking
through many new gates and many new
doors. Enjoy. Thank you. I have one. All
right. One other question also. During u
my sleep time and this has happened for
years and it's still continuing. I have
a real tendency to grind my teeth like this. Okay.
this. Okay.
And put my hands over my head sometimes
ring them or like wash them or other
times just do real simple movements
until with my wrist. Now I've never
actually seen it myself. All right. And
I wonder stand up.
Spread your arms to either side, palms
outward as far as you can extend them in
a cross formation. Okay. Put your head
back approximately 30° facing
up. Breathe three deep breaths slowly.
[Music]
Repeat after me.
H again. H And one more time. H. Clap
your hands
together. Sit
down. Very well done.
Now take your
hand and shake them
out. All right. All right. Give them a
good shaking. All
shaking. All
right. All right. Now take your hands
and place them in this
configuration. Place them in this
configuration. and then place them in
this
configuration. How do you feel about
yourself right now? Four. Do you love
yourself? Yes. Do you find that you love creation?
Yes. Do you find that you love creation?
Yes. Do you find it sweet?
Yes. Do you find it surprising?
Enjoyable? Yeah. Yeah.
Then our
suggestion is that when you
retire, when you go to sleep at
night, take three deep
breaths, give yourself and the universe
three claps. One, two, three.
and go and enjoy whatever you find. For
everything that will come to you in that
state will be something you can use to
the expansion of the awareness of the
being that you are and therefore the
expansion of the awareness of all that
is. Release whatever you are hanging on
to as luggage that used to carry things
you no longer have in this life.
Everything you need is within you. You
will find it there. You are not going to
leave anything behind. Nothing is going
to leave you
behind. Now, no
Now, no
need to be anxious with any new energy.
What may seem to you to be a new
energy. Relax. Open up.
Relax. Open up.
Vulnerability is love, is strength, is
openness.
Relax. Let the light of infinite
creation shine from within and upon
you. Relax. All right. Very good. Pleasant
Relax. All right. Very good. Pleasant
dreams. Thank you. One moment.
More and more as we perceive the
radiation of the being we were speaking
to before this being, we sense more and
more a very definitive, direct and
strong Orion connection. This
This
focus, the degree of
focus is what will allow there to be a
reciprocal degree of
expansion towards the creation of the
positive manifestation in life. Degree
of focus on what in your path connection
of
Orion. the degree of
focus of your approach in life to
life. You follow me? Yes. The degree to
which you have been focused on
specifics will be the degree to which
you expand into
generalities in the transformations
taking place within you.
We simply give you this on many
different levels. Allow this idea to make itself
levels. Allow this idea to make itself
more clear in your dream reality as you
begin to allow your physical reality to
be an extension of the dream.
We thank you. Thank you.
There we go.
[Music]
Hey, sure. Hey, sure. Then you
I would like to have you take a trip
with me on an adventure. Speak up so
that all may share the adventure.
I would like to go to the infinite
universe. You are already there, but
proceed in whatever manner you
desire. We had
uh frozen
truth 3,000 years ago where there was
earth, fire, and
water. And we knew that to be true. And
now we have a higher level of ignorance
which I will use terms which I I'm sure
you'll understand because it will be
technical but I'm sure you can
comprehend them. The universe first of all I would
them. The universe first of all I would
like to say the universe is I believe
and I would like to have you confirm
perhaps is truly infinite and truly
limitless in time. Yes.
I would like to review a present state
of ignorance on subject. Right.
Everything being valid of course for the
time in which it is created. Truth being
this is the truth as we know it for
ourselves alone and at the present
moment fully recognizing our ignorance.
So how can you speak for yourself? I can
speak for myself. Thank you.
Uh at the moment we feel
I that at the moment I and other people
I for now I for now I believe that
the smallest form of matter consists of
consists of quarks and
lepttons which represent basically the
leptons are the structure of an
electron. basic ingredients. Okay, perhaps of the
basic ingredients. Okay, perhaps of the
electron. To some degree, this is
accurate. Although there is a slightly
smaller form, yet that is the
transitional form between physiological
and non-physiological reality. I accept
that the quarks being basically the
basic some of the basic
ingredients of proton or those which are
ingredients of the
nucleus and they are
bound of force known as
pick one. It is not actually a force. It
is an exchange. They are extensions of
each other. They are bound because they
are different aspects of the same one
thing. That is what binds them so to
speak. It is not actually what you would call a
It is not actually what you would call a
force. That which we now call
electromagnetic instantaneous
electromagnetic radiation bonding forces
between the quarks. But it is not
electromagnetic radiation. It is that
they are
intrusions into an electromagnetic
space. What you conceive, what you
perceive of as the so-called
particles are the interactions of a
principle with the electromagnetic
field. It is not the electromagnetic
field that holds them together. It is
the electromagnetic field that allows
them to be represented in physical
space. They are held together, so to
speak, because they are different ends
of the same
concept, poking their heads, if you
will, into the electromagnetic fluid of
physical reality. One on one end, one on
the other, like a tunnel. Two ends of a
tunnel. Are you following? I am
following. Those we call blue arms.
The gluons bind. The electrons are bound
to the nucleus. What we call the weak
force in our ignorance. Now it is not
necessary for you to keep referring to
the idea as ignorance. Everything in its
own time is perfectly what it needs to
be. Oh, what can
be? Um, the nucleus is held with blue
arms in our presence understanding. Yes.
And [Music]
[Music]
uh we feel I feel and I believe that
there are they are fundamental particles
which participate in the ultimate
universe. I define the ultimate universe
as being we now know the universe to be
are in total ignorance. I will say the
cosmologists tell us the universe is 35
billion years old. When in fact if the
universe is infinite and it is
expanding. If the universe were
infinite, it would not be expanding nor
contracting. It would be infinite and
time would be infinite. The idea of any
particular localized expression of what
you may call an immediate universe may
be able to have a time factor
representation. But that immediate
universe is not the totality of all of
what may be called the true universe. It
is now proposed that the universe, the
known universe, the only small portion
of the universe which we now know is 10
the 18th seconds old and will be
redistributed to the true universe in
107 seconds as far as we can guess now.
So we all matter will be redistributed
in something like 107 seconds perhaps if
we're right.
So now let's get back to the universe
beyond the known universe which is now
consists perhaps of quarks and lepttons
and perhaps of what we call protons. But
you are speaking only of one particular
physiological reflection of a universe
the infinite universe perhaps. But what
you are describing as built out of
so-called particles by definition
therefore can only be one facet of a
multi-dimensional infinite crystal. We
are there now. You are in that
particular facet case. You and I can go
beyond the present univer the known
universe. You and I already exist beyond
the present known universe. Okay. If we
now that we are there I see I
see such things particles as quarks
leptons photons of a variety of
frequencies. You are interpreting them
in that way. Yes. But it is only an
interpretation. Now my question is as
what do you see?
We see an infinite
interplay of interactions. We see
everything as interactions and we see
what you perceive to be the particles
that represent the interactions to be
the side effect of the true material so
to speak of the universe which is the
interactions
themselves. We see the
interreationships. You see the particles that define the
You see the particles that define the
inter relationships to us. It is the
inter relationships that define the
particles. I define a level present
level of ignorance and that's why I call
it
ignorance. It is simply a matter of
perspective. Each is true in the
universe in which it exists. We define
our universe. You define your
understanding of your universe. But your
understanding of your universe is at the
point you have that understanding truly
the universe in which you exist. When
you change your understanding that's
when you discover more things in the
universe. It is not that they have
always been there per se to discover.
The change of idea, the change of the
interaction that you are with the idea
of the universe is what allows you to
experience the discovery of more
representational particles or symbols to
represent the new idea, the new
interaction you have become.
Before leaving the matter, could you go
to the glue on again,
so to speak, but again, we do not
represent the idea as a particle. I I
merely just
turned Could you could you go through
could you explain to us it is a
connective tunnel so to speak the
so-called gluon is your representation
of the interaction we are talking about
it is your material concept of the
actual act of
interaction the beingness the creation
itself that which gives rise to the
existence of one thing interacting with
another thing. But these things are
simply mirror reflections of the fact
that the real universe is the
interaction itself or that which you
would call the interaction. There really
is not terminology in your language for
what we are exactly perceiving or
describing. In a sense, that will have
to
do. But we are speaking about a universe
in which we perceive it to actually be
the interactions that create what appears to
interactions that create what appears to
be the matter in
it. The universe is the interaction of
itself with itself. That interaction of
itself with itself is what gives rise to
the material forms you then perceive and
are able to track backwards to the
initial
interaction. Is this making any sense?
Absolutely. From that point of view, but
I last asked one question other
question. Oh, right. Can we go to the
infinite universe beyond the known
universe? Now, again, yes, because you
are already there on one level. I see. I
I I have been there. You may not be able
to have, let us say, from the physical
point of view in which you now exist, a
complete comprehension or appreciation
in the terms of the physical universe,
but a portion of the being that you are
as a co-creator already is that
universe. Understand perhaps this idea
as well to go along with it. The idea of
the expansion of your awareness and the
acceleration of yourself from level to
level, plane to plane is the
recognition that you actually are the
dimension of reality that you thought
you existed in.
You discover that you actually are the
dimension of experience in which you
previously thought you existed
in. So as you expand, you constantly
realize that the universe you are
discovering is actually
you. And any way you wish to interpret
it, you are already going to find that
when you get there, you're going to meet
yourself. You are always going to be
waiting there in another form in a more
expanded form infinitely forever.
Thank you. Thank you very much. Sure.
All right. You venue. All right. A very
quick question along
um a quick astronomical question.
Um currently um um astronomers uh have
discovered um let's say x amount of of
mass in the universe. X amount. All
right, I mean we understand the term.
Um, and in order for the universe
actually this physical universe to be a
closed one, we need 10 times X. But they
have realized that much of the so-called
matter is not visible to you. Exactly.
But nonetheless, still not still not
detected. And if enough intergalactic ma
mass in fact exists to create sufficient
gravity, the universe will ultimately
stop expanding and collapse. what you
perceive to be your immediate universe.
But again understand this idea is simply
one aspect of the true universe. Let us
say the true universe is actually a
multiverse. No, I understand that. But
but in terms of of the specific closed
universe in this spaceime created x
billion years ago, is there in fact 10
times the amount of matter? Is it in
fact going is it a closed loop or is in
fact it not a closed loop? There is
approximately 33 times the amount of
matter you now believe there to be. So
it's a closed loop. So ult but not
really because the idea even upon the
creation of the idea of collapse will
propel you into and through a gate
through a door energy field that
interact or react with the non-physical
template to give rise to the physical
universe. One of the definitions of the
physical universe is the polarity of all
things. Therefore, when that
intersection takes place at any given
point in the holographic matrix, you
will always see the creation of the
polarity pairs. Now whether they
continue to exist in that format or not
will depend upon the local ideas,
pressures or dynamic tense or fields of
the gravitational matrix of the
particular physiological universe and
that will be determined utterly by the
template manifestation based upon the
consciousness or let us say the idea
that the universe is being created to
experience. Is this making any sense?
Is the string theory total nonsense?
No. you you
one
representational form of the actual
form of the actual
structure of the template itself. Let us
say the
outlines of the template itself, the
edges of the template itself. And even
within those edges which is an aspect of
our universe we are just beginning to
explore experientially ourselves. We
have discovered that there also exists
another form of
consciousness. In those strings so to
speak in those edges are completely
different dimensional experiences
slightly out of phase with the
experiential universe you consider to be
real in what way? Different frequency
different direction so to speak.
In this idea, you will find that what is
a seeming structure or definitive matrix
upon which your universe is built is in
and of itself its own series of
universes in unfolded in a sense within
your own. Is this making any sense? Oh yeah.
own. Is this making any sense? Oh yeah.
Thank you.
you then you I have a question about the
male and female blending within an
individual. All right. Is the desire for
this blending or integration within one
enough to accelerate the process or is
there something that I it is enough to
completely absolutely create it. Period.
Beginning and end depends upon your own
belief systems and your own
willingness. the degree of the desire,
the degree of the willingness to believe
that that desire can be enough to create
the blending fully. So if there are
people in my life that are reflections
of extremes, in other words, a lack of
integration of the female quality, then
that would reflect back to me that this
is not fully believed. Not
necessarily. All the reflections in your life are not
All the reflections in your life are not
necessarily a onetoone reflection of
what you are actually experientially
being in your life. You could be
attracting those individuals in your
life to allow them to see the reflection
of the blending within you to give them
the opportunity to blend as well. You
follow me? Yes. Does that assist you? It
does. Thank you very much. Yes. I
appreciated your comment on the whales
and the porpuses.
Next month I sail to Magdalina Bay in
Baja to spend time with the whales. I
hope to have a good time with them. Hi.
And say hello. I will. I've had many
wonderful experiences with corpuses also
who will come up alongside my boat and
just turn on their side and look me eye
to eye. Good. But some of my most
rewarding experiences scuba diving have
been with the spotted eagle ray and the
manta rays. Are they also in the same
class? No. But they are natural
reflections of certain understandings or
aspects of your own personality in many
different ways and have been a symbol
for you before in other lives. In many
different ways they do to some degree
represent simply because you are more
let us say aquatically oriented than
atmospherically oriented the idea of
what the bird or the eagle usually
represents in the air. They are your
version of a Thunderbird. You are
flying. You follow me? You are soaring
in the water. I see freedom. Freedom.
Freedom. They are gliding through the
water. They I can call them in. They will come
They I can call them in. They will come
from like 90 or 100 ft. They are your
reflection. They are the reflection of
what your soul is all about to you. They
are your symbol. I see. Aren't they a
little bit more like pets too? Like
dogs? I mean, people pet some of these
fish. They're affectionate just like
dogs are sometimes to some degree,
though they do not exactly generally
represent exactly the same
symbol. Dogs are more specifically
oriented to the idea of service. Even
though all animals are of service as
reflections and
guides, this is more specifically in
this case at least representative of the
individual's feeling of the soaring of
their own soul through the medium they
wish to interact in.
Thank you.
You can. Thank you. I have a little
story to share with the group. then
speak up. That was passed on to me from
a gentleman who was here last week. Um,
he works with dolphins in Florida and
has for 30 years or so. And I told him
that I had had the opportunity to swim
with dolphins, but was just a little bit
hesitant and I wanted to check with him
should this opportunity occur again to
see if there is any reason whatsoever to
feel unsafe in the water with them for
any reason. And he said in the 30 years
that he has swam with them and observed
others swimming with him um only once
has there ever been an injury and the
injury was to a woman. Um the woman was
swimming with a dolphin and the dolphin
hit the woman in the rib cage very hard
with his snout. And when the woman was
taken to the hospital with a large
bruise on the outside to see whether any
ribs were broken, it was discovered that
there was a malignant tumor underneath
the ribs. Nice. That was indeed a gift
from the dolphin.
Beautiful story.
[Music] Thank you. You're welcome. Yay. Is the
Thank you. You're welcome. Yay. Is the
universe structured according to uh the
golden ratio uh such as in plant life
and the structure in proportion
basically? Yes. Well, then in our
man-made system such as our economic
system that we created, if we would
institute a system of economics that was
based on this, would that be in align
with nature? Let us say it might
function more harmoniously. But the idea
of absolutely reflecting that particular
harmonic structure is to recognize that
the economic so to speak system is
simply one based upon
you. The idea of being of service to all
other beings and synchronistically
interacting with whatever beings need to
be of service to you to provide what you
need so that you can at the same time
provide what they need by simply each
doing what it is you love to do. That is
the economic system that is in total
harmony with that ratio. Well, at the
current time, wouldn't you say that our
energy systems are not in in the
harmonic proportions because of the
pollution that we're creating? They are
slightly out of phase. case. I've been
reading in a direction that would point
to where we have to create a system
based on uh suction theory similar to
what was created in a to in a tornado as
opposed to nuclear energy which is
usually splitting of the atom which is
uh I guess throwing the proportions out
of whack so to say. The idea is that
your own planet and the universe itself
can provide all of the energy you need.
This has already been understood for
quite some time in your civilization.
Though because of the structures you
have created your civilization to be,
this information is basically always
suppressed. The current that's what I'm
getting at because I've been finding
these things out. But what uh PE are
there people or in the government or
somewhere that are trying to implement
these systems, the so-called
Tesla system? Some Yes. Uh-huh.
Uh, is there some way I could get
involved with that or or is is there
allow yourself to be your government and
attract the individuals to you and
attract yourself to the individuals so
inclined. Do your own research into your
own literature and simply act upon and
according whatever moves you, whatever
attracts you, you will attract them to
you and you to them and interact with
each other.
One moment. What did you wish to share?
On the 16th and 17th, um Joseph Newman
is going to de demonstrate his free
energy device. Very good. In Jackson,
Mississippi, he's built a he's built an
auto um which is powered solely by this
um which is powered solely by this
generator which is fuelless. And just to
demonstrate that it's not run by hidden
battery, he's going to run it around the
Mississippi Coliseum for about 48 hours.
Have a wonderful time. Many of these
ideas are now making their way to the
surface of your consciousness because
now is the timing to allow these things
to come out because now you are
beginning to equalize yourselves all the
way across the board as you say so that
there can be equal sharing of
information, equal communication among
all the different aspects and facets you
have created your society to be. You
will find that a very
strong sharing of this energy is also
coming up in approximately what you call
the springtime of your new year coming.
Much more of this information will make
its way to the surface now that you are
allowing things to be more overt than
covert. Now that you are allowing
yourself to recognize that you are your
governments and not creating there to be
a
separation. You follow me?
Yes. Yes. Thank you. You then you
Someone told me that I was connected to
dolphins. Actually, they said that I was
a dolphin long time ago. They said that
uh although again everything is
simultaneous, right? She said that she
was difficult for her to explain. She
said that I would become or that I'm a
projection of or that Yes, you are
phases or facets of each other.
H so Atlantan times and that was the
case. Yes. But since those times are in
one-dimensional plane still going on, it
is right with you right now and
therefore easily perceivable. You see
those things are easily sensible because
you are not
actually reaching back into the dim dark
depths of the past or stretching into
the dim foggy recesses of the future to
sense those things because you are
creating the past and the future from
the present.
And also she said snow leopard.
[Music]
This will evoke certain ideas of energy,
clarity and
purity, some of which you have
experienced in what you might call a
Tibetan mode. You are very
mode. You are very
familiar with the snowcovered
steps in many different ways.
I have one more question guys. What are
quazars?
They are as far as we perceive
them energy gates wherein you are
witnessing the
compaction and
expulsion of entire other universes
interacting with your own. So would that
be like a white hole or in a sense they
are what we perceive to be interfaces
between different universes, right?
Someone else said that there was a
energies from different dimensional
directions and same thing. Yes. Thank
you.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. I'd like to know
what you do those weighting exercises
the orange, blue, white. Yes. It's about
after the orange or the blue I start
feeling very emotional. That's the whole
idea. You are opening up. You are
allowing yourself to experience yourself
as emotion. Energy in motion. Am I
feeling the color? In a sense, you are
also feeling your connection to
everything you are sharing that energy
with. You are recognizing yourself as
everything you are sharing the energy
with. You are what we call junctioning
with other individual consciousnesses
and other levels of your own
consciousness. Well, I don't know if it was the same
Well, I don't know if it was the same
thing, but when you when uh Erica asked
about Shabbat, nice and you said 1012
and 1210, I don't know what you were
talking about at all, but all of a
sudden I start getting these real like
chills. And thank you.
What you call the particular scenario of
this agreement, this channeling with
this physical
being represents itself, represents the
connection of your world, our world and
Sirius in a specific fashion. This
specific fashion translates into your
mathematical ratios as three particular
dates in your calendar. Energy gates in
your calendar. The first gate will be what
calendar. The first gate will be what
you typically call the birth day of the
physical channel
1012. The second will be 1111 which is
represented as my birthday in your
society. The third 1210 this day of your
time is the representative colloquial
idea of a birth day of the serious
consciousness you call chapat. These
three dates therefore are the
representative energy gate of this
particular triad channeling. You follow
me? Who is
Who is
that? It is what may be colloquially
called my future self in the serious
civilization. Just as am I the future
self of the physical channel before
you. We are three aspects of the same
consciousness. So I just have some kind
of a connection to all that too. That's
why it kind of rings my Yes, you have
your own similar connections. Very aptly
put. Thank you. If you did not have these
Thank you. If you did not have these
connections, you would not be
interacting with us.
You follow me? Yes. Thank you.
All right. No. Thank you. Um if yes, you
speak up. Okay. There is this being
speak up again. Again, there is this
being Yes. that I have been interacting
with whom I have a great deal of love
for this. I have learned a great deal
from my interaction with with this being
about opening up
to loving an individual no matter what
their um apparent mode of operation or
living state or beingness or whatever it
is which was a great gate for me to have
opened up. Thank you for choosing to
open it. Yes. No, it was it's been
incredible. Now
find you. Now there has been I want to
also thank you for your assistance in a
situation that came up in regard to this
being where I've been trying to help him
open up and see his own um strength as a
being in spite of his seeming
self-destruct type of um flying cube.
Yeah. And I really, really, really
appreciate the co-creation that was
involved. As do we from you. Okay. Now
there has been Yes, it is. Pardon me.
Yes, it is now. Yes. Okay. Now there is
a Yeah.
There is a new cycle that is occurring.
Oh, right. with the same being where I
am recognizing that even though there is
this
incredible, you know, this incredible
love that I have for this being, the
energy that he is creating in his space
is so destructive,
[Music] self-destructive, that when I'm around
self-destructive, that when I'm around
it, I have observed that my energy goes
completely as Well, that is your choice.
I don't want to choose that. And I do
understand that that's
identify with the idea far enough to
understand what he is creating. So you
can help him on his own terms without
completely adopting that framework into
your experiential reality.
Right? Create it and accept it in your
life as a
model, not as the absolute experience
you must
share. Use it as a reference
framework. If you must, let it have a
slight detachment from you. Look at it
with a tool of apparent
objectivity. Do not take it to heart.
Right? Because then I start to be it.
Yes, you are identifying because you
know you need to identify in order to
understand the individual on their own
terms. But that is why you are doing it.
You are not doing it because you are
weak or susceptible or giving your power
away. It is only you believe that you
are doing it that makes it seem as if it
is overwhelming you. It is not.
You have the power to be able to handle
it or you wouldn't be interacting with
that individual. I totally agree and
understand that. All right. The um
let me see if I have this correct. All
right. If I'm duplicating what you're
saying, if there is in an
interaction a blending of the energy so
much that I'm duplicating this person so
much and becoming that energy, right?
Yes. That it is your version of that
energy. Right. Exactly. that it is
creating in me
similar similar vibrations and efforts
that are going on with that being so you
can understand his perspective right
they don't have to be your reality right
and they definitely are not my then use
it as a tool and know you are being of
assistance and that will center you okay
well I want to be of assistance but I
also don't want to have myself go down I
just said you don't have to I know and
I'm trying to get you are what but I'm
getting I'm there is no need to try
right okay relax remember relax right
okay if you couldn't handle it you
wouldn't be involved right trust
yourself right trust your strength
vulnerability is not weakness it is
infinite strength it is infinite openness you are
strength it is infinite openness you are
simply still interpreting the
vulnerability to some degree as weakness
and susceptibility instead of absolute
indestructible core strength right now.
Yes, it is.
I understand what you said and I totally
duplicate it. And if I move back a
little bit from the situation so I'm not
identifying so totally with it. Up to
you. Well, I don't want my energy to go
negative and completely. Why should it?
That's what I don't understand. Why
should it? It doesn't have to. So don't
believe that it will and that it won't.
So that is the only thing that that is
hinging on is my belief that it will.
Yes. And understand it is hinged upon
the fact that what may appear to be a
symbol that used to represent negative
manifestation doesn't have to be given
the same meaning if you know you are
different. Remember no symbol has
built-in meaning. No situation means
anything. All symbols and situations are
fundamentally neutral. The meaning you
bring to it is the meaning and the
effect you get out of it. All right.
Yes. Well, thank you very much for your
joy and your strength and your
love. Thank you at this timing.
Allow us to extend the understanding to
each and every one of you that you are
your own beginning and you are your own
ending and at the same time you are
eternal and
infinite. You have all you need. Wake up
and dream. Give yourselves permission to
dream. Give yourselves permission to
love yourselves unconditionally even as
infinite creation has created you to be.
unconditional creators, our unconditional love and
creators, our unconditional love and
energy to you and our appreciation in
allowing us to share with you the dream
together. We have chosen to be. We thank
you. A fond and unconditionally loving
good evening.