All right, I'll
say how are you all this evening of your
time as you create time to exist.
Perfect. Thank you.
So allow me before we begin the eye of
sharing to
address something we have been
discussing of
late that we feel does pertain still to
many of the ideas many of the questions
that you have formed within your
reality. The idea that we have discussed
which we call
faith. Recognize as we will put very simply
Recognize as we will put very simply
that many times when
individuals create in the discussion
with us with other individuals the topic
of
faith they understand to some degree
that it is the mechanism by which they
can create the reality they
desire. But in this way as you have
created cycle of repetition for your
thousands of years of the habit of
separation of yourself from the all that
is that you are. Many times even when
exploring the idea of integration you
will start out from a separated point of
view or separated approach.
Therefore, many times, even though you
will recognize that faith is the
mechanism that will allow you to create
the reality that you desire to
experience. Once you get to that point,
the next thing you usually will be found
to say is, "Well, faith in what?" Now,
understand it does not matter. The idea
is that faith in and of itself is the
mechanism. Does not matter. Faith in
what? This is why your faith can create
any type of reality. Faith in whatever
you believe in is what your reality is
about. Therefore, allow me to
simplify that. That is why in what you
call your biblical
literature with the idea of the
individual you call your Christ, you
will recognize that when that individual
defined the reason for the abrupt change
of any physical manifestation in the
reality, then he ascribed it to the
working of faith. But did not say faith
in what? simply that your faith is
responsible for this change in your
health in this in that your faith has
saved you quote unquote. It is a
description that it is the faith in and
of itself that is the activation
mechanism and whatever belief you plug
into that faith will be the reality that
you experience.
Therefore, there is no need to
complicate the idea by saying, "Well,
yes, I understand it is faith, but faith
is what?" Simply know that faith is in
and of itself the exercise. It is in and
of itself the action. It is simply the
willingness to know that you are the
creator of your reality on whatever
level you have created yourself to
realize this.
No need to continue to create a need for
another process to discover what it is
you are supposed to have faith
in. The idea of faith in faith is what
it takes. You follow me? Yes.
Yes. The idea of simply knowing that you know
The idea of simply knowing that you know
is all it takes to know whatever you
need to know. For you will allow with
that activation of
faith your life will be allowed to bring
to you to attract to you to attract you
to whatever situations are necessary to
reflect the path you chose to be. And
then you can simply automatically act
upon what you give yourself. For what
you attract with your faith, with your
knowingness, will never be a struggle
nor a strain.
You will find yourself expressing and
exercising the ease of creation with
effortlessness by simply acting upon
what you attract to yourself in all good
faith that it is representative of the
life you chose and not an interruption
within it. Now, do you follow that idea?
Sharing for sure. new venue. Yes. I
think this sort of relates to what you
just say said. I'd like to share briefly
that ever since you first mentioned
uh the idea of becoming one's future
self, imagining what one's future self
is like. And in becoming it, I have been
practicing it. And I'd like to share
with everybody that it really works very
well. And I have suggested to a lot of
friends and you can say it to anybody
without going into a lot of metaphysical
things. It's a very simple thing. Yes.
And so I thought I'd like to share that
with everybody. Thank you very much for
that creation and your willingness to
recognize your own idea of acceleration.
Thank you. I have a quick question. All
right. Voyager 2 is going to be passing
Uranus in two days and I was wondering
if you knew if you could tell us
anything that we don't know yet that
will be discovered in two days. do not
want to take all
night. Understand that in the same
manner that your probes discover much
with regard to your other planetary
bodies, you will discover that much yet
again. There are many ideas of what you
call a new
understanding of the mechanics of
planetary formation that will become
clear. But also there will be in your
terms a thousand new questions that you
did not know existed. I'm sure that's
true. Well, just as a very simple
example, right now they know that there
are nine rings and five moons will and
they expect that they will get there is
the potential for the probe in the
trajectory that it is on to see at least
two or three more moons.
Okay. Thank you. I I just thought it
would be an interesting thing to have
you comment on. Oh,
you'll be sure. I have um for the last
few months, my right eye has been blurry
and and I can um first of all, I wanted
to share the purpose that I feel behind
that is that enabled me to kind of move
into another reality while still being
here at the same time. All right.
Because I'm not You are becoming
bifocal. Okay. But I also get scared about it
Okay. But I also get scared about it
because of my I think I've mentioned to
you my fear of blindness and um all
right so that I that but understand that
the idea of your fear of blindness in a
sense was a precognition of the symbol
that you would choose now to give
yourself this opportunity to become bif
focal only then from your separated
point of view in the precognition did
you assume that it meant literal
blindness. You follow me? Yes. Okay. And I I feel
You follow me? Yes. Okay. And I I feel
that this is a temporary condition as
far as that blurriness. It just feels
like there's a um like a little a film
over my eye. Yes. Okay. When you follow
your eye, then the rest of you will
catch up. And then you will be vibrating
equally once again in another density.
Okay. That's exciting. Now, is there
this there's I also get ever since I was
a teenager, I've also had aches at times
around the eyes. Um I don't know if it's
in the muscles of the eyes or if it's my
sinuses or something, but there it's not
really a headache that we think about as
a headache. It's like an ache around the
the eyes. It is sinus connected to some
degree. In this way, it will simply be once
In this way, it will simply be once
again symbolic of the changes in the
shifting in pressures within the bodily
system as regard to the energy flow that
you have created for yourself with
regard to who you think you are and the
connections you have made to other
consciousness on other levels.
Many times you will find that it will
be, I'll say,
symbolically natural and not unusual in
your society at this time for those that
have very strong relations within their
consciousness to the idea of other
consciousness outside their own
planetary system to create the symbol of
having breathed alien air and being used
to alien pressures, alien energies. Many
times this will simply manifest in your
society as conditions of pressure within
the sinus area as it will reflect the
idea of the shifting of pressure in your
body to that extent. Follow me. Yes. Is
that the same as the ear aches that I've
had in my left ear and it is connected?
Yes. Okay. Is there anything I can do to
alleviate to make myself more
comfortable with these aches that I have
and also with that that my right eye
being blurry? Is there anything that I
can do physically to to our perception
is that temperature would be of
assistance warmth of temperature.
The idea of allowing the entire area
here, here, and here to experience
warmth, not too hot, but warmth all at
the same time to even out the pressure
systems. Okay. What rinsing? I I started
rinsing my right eye with with clear um
sparkless water. And is that a good
idea? And it feels a lot better. Should
I should I warn is up to you. You do not
have to warm that but simply you may
immerse one of your cloths in the warm
water and apply to the entire area
equally. At the same time, take not cold
but a cool cloth and apply it to the
back of your neck. Okay. All right.
Thank you. This may last about 10
minutes. Okay. Thank you. Cool on the
back. Right. Cool on the back. Right.
Yes. Um, a couple questions, short
questions. To what degree in terms of
clarity of perceiving events is your
spiritual vision open? Understand first
of all that there is no such thing as
predicting the future. No, no, I'm not
talking about predicting future. I'm
talking about seeing now. Yeah. And like
in in past things you've said to people
that there have been things connected
from their past that you've seen which
are causes or linkups with present
circumstances and I want I'd like to
know to what um degree of accuracy um is
that open within to no degree of
accuracy whatsoever 100% validity. Yes.
Okay. All right. So then so then if it's
if it's if your knowledge of the past is
100% valid then that tells me that it's
100% uh what occurred. In other words, one
uh what occurred. In other words, one
moment accuracy and validity are two
separate things. All right. So then if
you then are linking up a past situation
with one moment, do you understand the
difference? Uh no then I don't. Thank
you. Recognize this. You are creating the
Recognize this. You are creating the
past and the future from the present.
What any individual cocreates with me,
what I cocreate with any individual is
valid. Okay. for that individual in the
co-creation for whatever reasons they
have cocreated. That the idea of
accuracy in terms of representing
something that physiologically happened
in your historical concept is not always
necessarily present to allow there to be
reality to the experience that is being
cocreated. Okay. So,
Okay. So,
um, let me see if I can get my question
here put back together again.
From time to time, we will be able from
time to time, we will be able when
discussing such an idea with you to
point out whether or not we perceive
that it happened physiologically, okay,
or not. What what entails then um being
able to perceive it physiologically? the
purpose for the co-creation. And if the
idea of making a physiological
connection in terms of the accuracy you
request is
either in the overall sense interferive
or does not really exactly pertain to
the reason for why the whole concept has
been created then it will not funnel
through us. Okay. So is that uh by
individual choice or that just sort of
occur otherwise can you can you do it by
choice if you wish? Allow me to explain
in this way. We have chosen for
ourselves to interact with
you in a whole concept that we feel
represents the validity of the
experience you are requesting. That's
just subjectively in a sense. Yes.
Everything is. Everything is. There is
no such thing really as
objectivity. Recognize therefore that it
is not so much that we specifically
screen any information at any particular
moment, but that we have already created
the idea that if it will not be of
service, it will automatically be
screened and kept from our own
knowingness in the interaction, even
though maybe we will know about it
later. Okay. All right. So then my next
question then would be this is um maybe
blasphemous but I decided blasphemer I
decided I decided today that that I'm
going to um not really care about um
very good uh other people maybe being
upset or whatever but I decided to test
you test
me. All right.
No, no, no. Only because I decided that
if if something is true, then I should
be able to investigate and doubt in
order to Well, all right. That is up to
you. But what is truth? Well, truth is
something which I guess you could define
it in many many ways, but for for for
number one, truth is something that uh
the energy of of spirit is manifested
within it and there's nothing covering
it. All right? It's it's a bit purer
than something that that that has
covering some kind of covering on it.
So, we understand your terminology. The
reason that I would ask this or even be
in this frame of mind is because I think
to myself, well, I've been coming here a
couple times and been asking questions
and sometimes personal questions, deep
questions within myself. And I and uh I
would like to I would like to understand
more the source that reflects back these
questions. But I put my faith in through
the medium of you. So therefore I you
know I'd like to test you. All right.
But understand therefore that you are
then testing yourself. Oh no doubt. No
doubt. All right. But you're on a hot
plate too. Feels very cool to
too. Feels very cool to
me.
Recognize I have already said that
neither am I in the desire to nor can I
ever prove anything to anyone.
This is not my function. Yes. No. I
understand that. I understand that. And
my and my my desire for questioning is
not at at all to to lessen any of the
value that's occurring here at all. It's
just um um what it is. What what it is,
man. Do whatever you wish. Okay. What
did I do today?
I mean, what what did I do
today? Now, understand
this. I at this moment do not know.
recognize the idea of what you are
asking in this way. First of all, before
we get back to that question,
many times in your
society, when you
perceive the idea, now when you begin to
examine the ideas that you call
telepathy, extrensory
perception, and all of the psychic
manifestations of spirituality, of
astralness, and all the different labels
that you give to this experience that
you say,
exists in your
society. You are still many
times creating your viewpoint of this
phenomena if you wish to call it that
from the methodology that you have used
all along to define your reality. Now
you may call this if you will at this
time what you usually refer to as
scientific methodology.
the creation of a series of questions or
tests to create what you feel to be a
certain proof. But recognize first of all that
proof. But recognize first of all that
science, even though it has set itself
up to be so, is in no way, shape or
form, the final arbiter on what is real
and what is
not. First of all, understand that even
though science in and of itself No, I
says that it is all right. I'm not
finished. Now recognize
Now recognize
therefore that when it goes about
seeking to understand things it does
not, it will usually still apply the
methodology it is used to using to every
new thing it encounters. Now this is the
transformational life. You are beginning
to bridge the idea of physicality and
non-physicality. And in many ways, even
though some of your modern physics has
begun to understand the necessity of
rearranging its equations to include
some aspects of
non-physicality. What it has yet to
understand is that the physical science
will not be able to come up with a
methodology to define non-physical
science. And in this way you will still find
And in this way you will still find
therefore that from time to time when
science seeks to explore to experiment
to test to prove something when it is
still putting its own habitual
scientific methodology upon that idea.
It will then create what it thinks is an
accurate definition of how science
thinks this new idea should work. and
when it goes about testing it will apply
the parameters that it thinks represents
the way in which such a subject should
be tested to get the results you think
you want. But recognize this, there is
much you do not understand about why
things like telepathy and psychic
functioning work.
Many times in scientific point of view
something is valid or not valid
depending upon how many times it can be
repeated under controlled
conditions. Now
recognize that the very
essence of that type of
experimentation is
cancelling to the very essence of the
function of psychic ability.
May I say something there on on that? Um
yes, if you will let me continue. Yeah,
sure. Sure. Um but I just you you put so
many ideas out and I just want to be
able to feed back and understand. Um one
thing that you said about subjective um
now since objectivity then is really
another or a secondary phase to
subjectivity. It's an extension of
subjectivity. Then if you're in tune
with subjectivity
which is primary Yes. and more on the
intuitive then knowing the objective
must be right there too. Very good. But
understand in this way that knowing you
are subjective means you know that you
get the result that you designed the
experiment for. Mhm.
Therefore, with regard to how your
science usually now understands the
non-physicalized origin of psychic
abilities or
telepathy, the way it designs the
experiments to test these
things have nothing to do with the
understanding of why those things
work. And basically what we are saying
is this.
When you realize that psychic
manifestation and telepathy and all of
these ideas is not strictly in your
ideas is not strictly in your
terminology a mental phenomena but an
emotional phenomena and a belief system
phenomena. Then you will
understand that the
circumstances the
circumstances in which you can then so
to speak prove the existence of psychic
phenomena are not the standard
laboratory conditions of sterility.
They are circumstances that are
emotional, interactive, congruent with life itself.
interactive, congruent with life itself.
It is an active science, the science of
mind, the science of understanding bonds
of
consciousness. It is an active science.
What standard classical science on your
planet seeks to do is stop a process so
they can pick it apart to understand it.
But stopping the process completely
erases any evidence that they wish to
find. Therefore recognize that because it is
Therefore recognize that because it is
an emotional bond, an active bond, a
feeling bond, a living
bond, usually when there is occurrences
of psychic knowingness of telepathy of
ESP as you say, they will occur when
there is a great need, desire,
excitement, emotion to know these
things. They can occur from time to time as you
They can occur from time to time as you
say spontaneously just by saying, "Well,
how much change have I got in my
pocket?" "Well, 37 cents." Well, yes,
you're right. But understand that those
in your terms at this point in your
society are the
exceptions and usually not repeatable.
But science cannot understand why they
are not repeatable. It is not repeatable
because who cares how much change you
have in your pocket when you can reach
in and find out for yourself in a
practical everyday
method. The idea of what you did today
is not something that you are radiating
in such a way that comes across to me as
something that allows us to be in love
with each other about the sharing. Well,
what would occur though? You see, if if
if you were to know exactly what I did
today, it would
um put it this way, it would it would
put me at that point above just a you
know, in religion and all the religions
that that I've come across, usually
there is a source, a knowledge source or
a point of emanation of information. And
to a great degree, most of the people
that follow um
uh they don't inspect the information
because it becomes like a a whirlwind of
hey, let's get into this. I believe it
feels great. It's more fun to believe
than to question. All right. Because
when you question, you you have to find
out about it. And sometimes it doesn't
matter because what you know. So if you
were to know what I did today, what it
would do for me is it would put you put
me in tune with you on a okay all right
we understand what you are saying but
understand again it is not our purpose
to put them anywhere. Now recognize also
that what you are defining as these
individuals with regard to their
religions and following such an idea
without questioning the idea of following in
questioning the idea of following in
that way is not knowing.
Right? Therefore the analogy in that way
does not hold. The recognition is that
if they were not following but knowing
then they would simply know they do not
need to follow and would also know that
they do not need to create question they
would simply
understand. Now again the idea is
backwards. Allowing yourself to be already on this
Allowing yourself to be already on this
idea of equal sharing will allow for the
manifestation of the type of telepathy
that I experience in my own society all
the time. Not the other way around. Not
making it well if this happens then I
will go for this. Because you say what
you are saying is that I want to believe
in this and so if this happens then I
will believe in this. But you are asking
me therefore to do something that will
in a sense affect your choice of belief.
Well, it's not even that. Now, one
moment. One
moment. Therefore, this is what I offer
you in exchange for what you want from
me. I cannot and will
not prove anything to you in this way.
However, I will assist you to prove that
such a thing exists for yourself.
Well, I know it exists. Then what is the
point? Um, I'm I'm talking to you. So what?
Um, I'm I'm talking to you. So what?
Only because you're you're a source of
information and questioning for myself.
And so you are the source. I am a
reflection. Understand that that is the only
Understand that that is the only
function that I
provide. Not a source of information, a
reflection of you as the source.
Period. What you hear from me is
reflective of what you are willing to
be. Now, for example, there have been
opportunities many times in your
terminology for me to know what someone
did during the course of a day. But that
is not because they need to know in the
terms you are asking, but simply because
they recognize themselves as the source.
They are simply involved emotionally in
the conversation and because they are so
open with that idea and not shutting
themselves off pro- offering a test
which means you are hiding things then
it is simply there to be picked up upon
emotionally and many times we can read
that emotionality when no one is
thinking that they must test for that
emotionality is only when it can be
read. Therefore, when you least expect
it is when it will work the
best. Therefore, our suggestion is that
if we simply continue to
interact, there will be more
opportunities for us to simply pick up
on the creation of what you are and
reflect that back to you if it is
pertinent to what it is you are
exploring about yourself.
Okay, that's cool. Thank you. Can I pick
up on that further? Yes. Is what's
happening here? Is he looking for having
faith in his belief? Ask him. Is that
what you're looking for?
Okay. I'm trying to understand what you
were talking about before about faith
and belief and you're making a
differentiation between them. All right.
Belief is simply one of the facets of
the personality structure of which the
other two are emotionality and thought.
Faith is the activation through the
personality of the knowingness of the
higher consciousness.
You follow me? Yes. Now we we discussed
belief as uh being composed of two
aspects. That is two pretends. One is
the first pretend and pretending that
I'm not pretending it. And that is the
way of creating a belief. You can change
a belief. Yes, that way. Well, is there
some other way of understanding belief
other than
that? Belief
self is a reflection many
times of the combined personality
constructs idea of itself through the
ego. and therefore will
and therefore will
reflect what you think and feel and
believe. The method should be for you as
a person to explore the situations that
your higher consciousness has given you
to
explore. You follow me? I can't say that
I do. All right.
Simply belief is what will allow your
belief is what will allow your
personality to
create something to
sense through the senses it has created
it. It is what creates the
It is what creates the
reflection of
how you consider your
person and what you consider your person
to
be. Follow
that as as for example I'm here in this
room. I'm looking out through these
eyes. I'm seeing you. I'm seeing other
things. Is that a a an example of
belief? Yes. I see. and uh and the way
you are seeing them defines the type of
belief. Now what would the how would faith fit
Now what would the how would faith fit
into this? Faith is simply the
knowingness that this is all a part of
you totality. Yes. Faith is the mechanism of
totality. Yes. Faith is the mechanism of
allowing you to tap and be congruent
with the higher consciousness's
awareness that this is
you. Your belief allows you to
experience it as not
you. Your entire personality, emotion
and thought and belief cocreates the
reality that this is not you.
Faith knows this is you. Very good.
Thank you.
Um, a belief need not ne necessarily be
intellectualized. I mean, we have a lot
of beliefs that we've never even
considered. We're beliefs. We just kind
of walk around in our reality with
beliefs. Yeah.
That seems to me that um if we were to
intellectualize a belief, we'd have to
realize that the belief does not cons contain a
that the belief does not cons contain a
consideration that it is not so. I think
doesn't faith also if you were to
intellectualize the idea of faith. Uh
the consideration that it is not so or
that it can't happen or something like
that in another sense. Yes. Just absent.
Yes. Okay. This is why we say that you
will find that in your terminology of
so-called hierarchy, it is knowingness
and then belief and then emotion and
then thought. Mhm. For belief will
retain to some degree some of the
aspects of knowingness in physical
terms. And that will be one of them. The
idea that it does not consider
itself to not be.
Okay. Would faith then be uh kind of a
component of knowingness or would you
say it is knowingness?
Faith as you define it in your physical
reality is the realization of
knowingness. Okay.
There are some things that I I have
total certainty that I know. Yes. And
other things that I just kind of accept
on faith that I well I know it's going
to happen although I don't know what the
circumstances will be. All right.
Basically, yes. same thing. But when you
say, well, I know and I accept on faith,
it is not so much that that is
dissimilar, but you are still making
somewhat of a recognition of the
mechanism of the knowingness channeling
through into physical reality, which is
a separation from the knowingness,
right? It definitely acknowledges the
higher. Yes. You are simply feeling the
flow, right, of the knowingness,
watching the mechanism work, right?
Right. Aware of the mechanism itself.
Got it. bug you now that I still have
your attention.
Um I'm interested in understanding what
the 11 dimensions that our physical
reality is made up of. Do I understand
correctly that since we have our three
XYZ dimensions are there three
additional spatial dimensions that are
kind of curled up six additional spatial
dimensions in a sense? Yes. The idea of
the multiverse can be looked at as what
you call unfolded. Okay. This comes out
of super string theory. Yes. Okay. Then
what are the remaining two dimensions
plus and minus time? Time will be there.
Now understand the idea that we have
defined as what we call the template
structure. I do understand that. All
right. In this
way the six faces and the five points adding
the six faces and the five points adding
up to the idea of 11 will simply yes
point to the idea to some degree of
different directions. But when you get
beyond the idea of physical space and
physical time, then in and of itself the
time, then in and of itself the
direction in which things actually are
contained is not even so much a
direction as it is let us
say a bias if you will. All
right. That time plus n minus would
still be one dimension. Yes. Okay. Well,
then that covers 10 dimensions. What's
the 11th?
It is the totality of the concept in a
synergistic fashion before it goes on to
the next
level. Have our
scientists come upon this thought in
their own uh so
yes. So I'm wondering if they are aware
that it we are living in an an 11
dimension reality. I I have not found
anybody to define all 11 dimensions but
I've seen within super string theory the
three spatial dimensions the six curled
in spatial dimensions the single
dimension of time and then nobody's
mentioned what the 11th dimension is.
All right. Now to some degree again I
will say this will be difficult in the
terminology available to me through the
physical channel but if you wish to give
it a definition in those terms allow me
to define it in this
way. It is the
recognition paradoxical though this will
sound of the structure that exists
within a point. Okay.
All right. Kind of almost inverse space
sort of kind of kind of like I said.
Yikes. Okay. Thank you. Now one moment. Understand
Understand
that very recently there has been a new
awareness, a new
understanding that will allow for what
you have been calling the idea of
understanding all of these dimensions.
and the forces so to speak within it as
a unified field as a unified oneness as
a homogeneous whole.
You have just learned of the
idea that gravity in and of
itself has another type of structure to
it that allows it to be in your terms
coming and going
simultaneously rather than
unidirectional as you have for so long
considered it to be. This in and of
itself is now being separated out as
another force but will very shortly be
reintegrated when there is the
understanding of what gravity
represents. It is not like in its
manifested sense the other things that
you recognize as fundamental forces.
This new clue which is being called
hypercharge in your society will allow
them to understand the simultaneous
nature and more awareness of what they
have for some time called quantum
interconnectedness but not have been
able to make sense of in what you call
mathematical or practical terms. This
will allow them to see how such a thing
is possible. simultaneously and it will
lead them to rewrite the structure of
the mathematics inventing a new
mathematical relationship that will then
include more of the idea of
consciousness. Are you saying that when they blend the
Are you saying that when they blend the
ideas of gravity and hypercharge that
will be in a sense factoring in the idea
of consciousness? It will be the first
step toward realizing that. Okay.
Thank you. Bashar.
All right.
Okay. Um, hi. I'm so glad to see you
again, Bashar. You know, I don't see
you. I'm so glad to be here with you. I
have a couple
questions. Um, I'd like to tell you a
couple of images I had in several
different dreams, but all in one night.
And see if you can work with me on this
possibly. I um woke up in the dream. I
was on a cruise. But I was on a ship and
with a crew of people seem to be the
same people I was in the movie crew with
that I'm working on now. Maya, interrupt
you. Yes.
Are you going to go through these
descriptions already knowing what all of
this means for you? I don't know what
they mean. We will
see. We have done this before you and I.
You will go through your entire
illumination and then when we discuss it
with it, you will say, "Well, yes, I
knew that." Well, of course I know it.
But I like to have you reflect it back
sometimes. You know it consciously. I
don't know it consciously. All right. We
will see.
Okay. I mean I know bits and pieces but
it's not. Oh, here it comes. Bits and
pieces. I know. I love you. Even though you my
I know. I love you. Even though you my
expression sometimes
um that we find to be impossible. I
[Music] know. Excuse
know. Excuse
me. Something we do on earth sometimes.
Um, okay. I was on the
crew like that. Yikes. I was in the
crew. We were going some place. It was
very, very, very cold. The coldest place
in the entire universe. And
oh, okay. And twice in that night, twice
in that dream, I woke up crying. I mean,
physically crying in my bed. And I woke
up crying. One, I was having a
conversation with the being that I know
you know I'm talking about, the woman
being that with. And the other time was
on the crew and I wasn't sure why I was
crying. In the same dream, and this all
sounds crazy, they were feeding us
lobsters. And for some reason, I thought
the lobster had something to do with the
Piscian age. And then later in the
sequence of the dream,
right? Now, see, I don't know what any
of that means. Oh, hogwash.
Why not allow them to be literal?
Someone's going to see me lost you.
What? I don't know. Symbolically literal
as you have already defined and
described the feelings that those
symbols gave to you.
The idea for yourself first of
idea for yourself first of
all that you know that you are involved
in a process with many
individuals that you know in your
mentality it represents a journey to
somewhere you think you need to get to.
The idea that you will be fed from the
bounty of your own abundance along the
trip and the idea that it is not a
gamble to do so.
Well, if I knew that, you certainly put
it in a nice time.
The play seemed like one
moment. Understand that you have
Understand that you have
had the ability to know all of this in
exactly the way I have defined
it. But there is one thing you are
creating for
yourself. The idea of the
coldness is
symbolic of what you call
superconductivity.
the idea that the force can flow
faster when the molecular structure of
something is put into a crystallin
matrix. This
however does not need to exemplify
itself outwardly in terms of being hyperactive.
outwardly in terms of being hyperactive.
If you would but
relax, which is the idea of centering,
which is what the crying was for. That
was the crying.
The center. Yikes. You were centering
from what you perceive to be a negative
experience. And it is only your
And it is only your
symbol that you are in the overall
understanding of the trip you are
on still attempting to get out and help
push the
boat. Now, if you would allow yourself
in your terms to slow down a bit. I feel
like I'm slow already.
I know you feel that way.
But if you would but listen to
yourself, you discharge so much
information so rapidly
that many times it is not an allowance
for the individuals you are discharging
to to assimilate at their own rate. Mhm.
If you are a part of the cruise,
then understand that you are all going
to get there on the same boat at the
same time. No, understand
No, understand
simply that you can enjoy the
abundance that you can partake of on the
cruise. You are not gambling.
And in this way, simply
recognize that everyone is on the same
boat. They will not disappear.
disappear.
Therefore, enjoy the programs that are
offered to you on the cruise.
Take some time off. Yes,
you are on vacation with these
people. They do not want to be
reminded of all the work.
Follow me. They do not want to think about
me. They do not want to think about
paperwork.
They do not want to know all the little
details. They do not want to be
bombarded with information. That is why
they left on this cruise.
Therefore, if you are on this cruise
with them,
join them
by simply moving at the same rate that
the entire ship is moving.
You do not have to get out and push. You
do not have to jump into a rowboat with
a line and begin to row faster to pull
the boat. It is still going to move at its
boat. It is still going to move at its
own pace on the current. It has squarely
placed itself in the middle of that sea
of
consciousness, left its port at exactly
the right time with everyone on board,
and will arrive at its next port at
exactly the right time, everyone on
board. All right.
When I saw the streak of light in the
sky, I thought it was a falling star.
Can I determine
if you was a craft? Um, now was not a
craft. It was a symbol. But it was a
symbol. Do you know in your society what
the moth symbolizes?
Knowledge. But in this way also
But in this way also
One moment. It was an energy idea. All
right. Now, understand there is polarity
to this symbol as well. And the idea is
that it does represent knowledge and as
long as it takes advantage of the
natural flow of the air currents, it
will stay aloft.
When you become focused and fixated on
needing to express that knowledge too
quickly is when that idea spirals down
into the flame and is consumed.
Does that have anything to do with the
spiral that I see in my to some degree?
Although simply you will know that is
the definition of the centering of
yourself. Yes. Yes.
Now simply
recognize in this way there is no need
to consume
yourself just because you are an idea
and recognize that you
are in every way that you express
yourself. Relax. If for some reason you do not get
Relax. If for some reason you do not get
to say everything you wish to
say cuz you have slowed down, then
understand that everything you did get
to say is exactly what needed to be
said. You do not have to compact the
information so tightly.
The information seems to come at such a
fast speed. Sometimes I keep up with it.
But you can then I get pieces of it like
I have pages. You get all of it. You get
all of it. Only the idea of your
franticness to want to share with
everyone so
quickly is what makes you feel like it
comes so
frantically. When you choose to relax,
it will come at a relaxed pace. Or if
you perceive that the actual momentum
does not change, you will be able to
assimilate it in a relaxed manner. It
does come down to faith. Yes, faith is
all there is. I know. It's so funny.
It's like when I don't have the faith,
it's when I start talking so fast, I
think it doesn't make sense because it
does make perfect sense. But the inner
journey, do you understand what it's
like here to have the outer journey? But
it's really not the outer journey, but
about the outside world to some degree.
Yes. Do not forget I have had a wife
there. [Music]
Believe me in that sense and when I make
that connection to that portion of my
consciousness I understand.
Therefore that is why I can with all
faith and conviction let you know that
you can be easier with yourself.
I have learned that this is so thank you.
Hi, I want to talk
Hi, I want to talk with you about
cigarettes. All right.
Are you offering me one? No. No, thank
you. Thank you.
Um, I've been smoking for many, many
years and I come to a point to realize
that I don't really want to quit
smoking. Oh, what? I want to
um feel in control. In other words, I
want to be able to like maybe one day
forget about it. Just like coffee, you
know, I take coffee maybe once a week or
maybe then how about one day you forget
about it? Well, that's what I want to
talk with you about. All right. You
can't forget. No, it's really I was
hearing people talking about that it was
really addictive. Can I say say it's
really an addiction? A drug that you're
addicted to and we understand the
physiological idea. But again to us
everything physiological is the result
of an idea of consciousness. Right. And
I feel like it's at the tip of my tongue
but I want to be on it so I can kind of
faster because of that. All right. Now
you two can also relax with your Yeah.
Okay. Recognize that when you no longer
Recognize that when you no longer
contain the idea, then you will simply
not feel like smoking. You don't have to
force yourself to quit. I don't want to
quit. All right. I love smoking. All
right. Then you do not have to worry
yourself about whether you quit or not.
Recognize that if you know you are of
the belief
system that simply contains that idea
without detriment to you, then it will
be no detriment. And once you allow to
accept yourself in all that you are,
then you may find maybe maybe maybe that
you will in fact lose the
urge. Once it is not important to you
whether or not to make the decision, you
may actually lose the urge. as you
accelerate beyond that
idea. Now, if you do not, so what?
Right. But it is the worrying about
making the decision that is what will do
you the detriment.
Yeah. But I stopped I stopped for a
while trying to make a decision about
it. All I want
is smoke one once in a while. Then do
what you want. Now
Now
understand in your terms physiologically
if you wish to discuss this okay the
idea of the physiological addiction
the majority of the addiction in an
overall sense so to speak is the sugar
your tobacco is cured in sugar and that
is the most addictive thing in it.
And the paper got sugar.
Really? Yes.
I really eat a lot of sugar. I really
love sugar. That is why you also love
smoking. Interesting. Now simply once again
Interesting. Now simply once again
recognize that if you do not put so many
demands upon yourself, you will allow
yourself if that is a part of your
purpose to evolve out of even wanting
the idea. Therefore, you will simply
lose the urge. You do not have to force
yourself to continue or force yourself
to quit. It will not even be a matter of
making the decision.
Great. I like them. Oh, why you mean
nicotine is not addictive? Yes. But
that's the main thing in cigarettes,
isn't it? Sugar.
Not nicotine. Our scientist said these
termin are they Yes, it is. No, no, no.
Simply what we are saying is there is a
higher percentage
of sugar of sugar addiction. Yeah.
Because sometimes when people stop
smoking they eat a lot of sugar.
[Music] That is the most addicting thing about
That is the most addicting thing about
the habit.
Not that the idea of nicotine is not,
nor that it is not a great deal of the
addiction.
Yes. Um, I've had asthma. Um, I'm 28 and
I'm Those two things have something in
common. My doctor told me that the asthma um for
My doctor told me that the asthma um for
some people leaves after a 15-year
period and for a certain time period
within a person's life if they have
asthma that there's a phase that it gets
most intense and then it just
leaves. Lately, I've been
having asthma and it it becomes a a
choice between me wanting to be with
people or be in any type of environment
because if a person's smoking or if a
person um I can't be with them
uh so that I can get some fresh air or
I'm I just acquired a cat because I love
animals and um I've been living with
this cat week now and my asthma is
changing and very good. I'm very happy.
Yes. Very good. I'm exciting.
Does the atmosphere round and about you
feel a little bit different? Yes. Does
it feel different in terms of
temperature? More electrical component?
Does it feel more electrified, more
invigorating? I've kept it colder in the house. Yes.
I've kept it colder in the house. Yes.
All right.
You are then yourself in your oric field
charging the air
and you are acting as your own filter
creating the reality of the atmosphere
you wish to breathe so that it filters
out what you do not.
You are oxygenating the air and ionizing
it with your oric field.
What is that? You will find as we said
before that the IB of aligning these
electrostatic balances will cause this
energy field to become a little bit more
of a crystallin matrix and that allows
for superc conductivity.
The idea is that a reduction in
temperature creates the crystallin
matrix which allows for the more easily
manifested flow of the electromagnetic
fluid in which you exist to create the
type of reality you want to be.
The creation of this magnetic field and
electromagnetic field becomes
superconducting when the temperature is
lower. Thus you will find many times that this
Thus you will find many times that this
is
why the idea sometimes of what you call
psychic phenomena in that way will cause
there to be vast temperature differences
in the bodily structure many times
particularly in the hands.
When there is the idea of the outlay,
there will be a reversal of the energy
and you will find the heating to occur,
the sharing of the energy.
Is there also something I
could loosen it? It's it comes Why do
you assume that you will not continue to
do so? Well, it's lately it's been more
lately it's been more intense than usual
and I found that
um any place I go I can't
breathe and what are you doing now? I am
breathing now. There are times when I
am relaxed and able to
breathe. And there have been times when
Yeah. I'm spacing out again.
I'm spacing out again.
[Music]
Good. Perhaps you will be able to
breathe that. Keep that space with you.
that. Keep that space with you.
keep that space with you.
Is there something I need to know about
my mother and myself? Um because I've
I've heard that the asthma condition is
connected to mother's love which is type of mother
to mother's love which is type of mother
love that is mother.
Why not talk to not the physiological
mother but the mother within you?
Have a dialogue
with your own motherhood
and find out if you think you are a
smothering mother.
I've been starting to enter into a
softness. All right.
Then you will be breathing easier about
yourself which will be reflected in your
which will be reflected in your
reality physically. Okay.
Breathe easy about
yourself. Lighten up on yourself. Okay.
Love yourself unconditionally.
All right. Yeah.
Thank you.
All right. Venue. Venue. Um, do you have
something like summer where you live?
Like where it gets hot during the year?
Something like it. Yes.
Do you um We have seasons. Yes. Oh, but
not so extreme as you. Even California.
California is not extreme. Even less
extreme in California.
less extreme. Well, in the summer, do
you run around naked?
There are from time to time in any
season individuals who may not be
partaking of the idea of clothing.
Okay. Um Okay. And how come the men
don't have clothes, but the women do?
Like, does it fit a purpose for them?
But not Thank you. This is a remnant of
an idea in our own past history that had
to do with the
exemplification of the polarity of
maleness and femaleness. And in this way
was a representation of the
mentality of our own civilization. And
the idea similar to what you have in
your own civilization of the idea that
the removal of the covering from the
head would allow there to be a more
symbolic manifestation of the idea of
outward mentality.
So for us it is a physiological symbol
in our society that is a remnant of an
idea we had of ourselves and continues
to some extent in this way mostly simply
because we have no need for the hair
back. Right. Well, do the men have like
eyebrows or beard or something like that
or hair? You will find that there will
be no beard. There will be very faint
very faint idea of eyebrow. Very
faint. Almost in your terms invisible
against the whiteness of our skin.
Um, are you wearing a silver outfit?
It is blueish silver. Okay.
Um, does everybody wear the same color?
No, it is up to them. Is that your
favorite color?
It is one that is my favorite when I'm
in the mood for it to be my favorite. Quick question.
One moment. All right. When about your
appearance and so on, I've been very
curious about why it would be such a
shock for us to see you physically.
Understand? It is not the physicality
that is the shock. As we have explained,
the idea is that our oric field is a
reflection of the integrated being that
we are and we couldn't take it in a
sense because understand in this way
that what happens is as our acceleration
to you is faster, more integrated. If
your oric field comes into contact with
it, you are swept up in the greater
acceleration and forced to look at the
integrated awareness of yourself.
So, so how is it that we that we
wouldn't be the same? Because
individuals when they create such a fear
of looking at all the different portions
of themselves may find them in shock
about what they see about what they are
forced to face of their own being that
they are not yet ready to look at. I see
I feel that I could many of you can but
understand again it is a matter of
timing that is of the greatest service
to all concerns. Sure. Sure. One moment.
Do you have some other question?
Okay. Ken Gatson wants to know.
No. Ken and I were talking the other day
and we decided, we decided on a
question. Mary said, Mary decided, but
Ken said, "Go ahead. Go ahead. Ask what
I want to know, but Ken would not mind
hearing also, is do women like have a
period every month?" No. Do they ever
have one? No.
has nothing to do with the idea you call
luck. Now
Now
recognize simply that we do not need
that symbol in the way you manifest it
and there has already been change upon
your own planet and you yourselves know
it is not in your own terms for everyone
what you call a regular thing. Yeah. Not
for the male, that's for sure. All
right. Not even for the female.
Recognize there are individuals that
have perhaps in your terms maybe four
times a year.
Maybe once, maybe not at all. For many,
many, many months, maybe years, then
maybe again. Oh, understand it is a
product completely of the mentality of
many things that are incorporated into
the idea of what the female
consciousness is viewing itself as
becoming in your society. Can you talk a
little bit about why every month and
what are why they have it at all? All
right. First the idea of why at all. It
is a reflection of the great deal of
separation that has occurred between the
male female energies in this way. It is
a tearing a sunder and the idea that to
bring into the reality any idea that
will accelerate towards the blending
comes from the idea of the separation,
the pain, the sorrow, the tearing us
under in order to be born in this way.
It is a reflection symbolically of that
sense of separation of the male female
nests. It is in a way, if you permit me
to be a little bit poetic in that sense,
it is in a way more the
idea that you
call the bleeding of the heart
for what is experienced to be a loss.
The idea of the lo wasps in the womb of
the completeness of the beings that they
are giving birth
to. You follow
me? Now
this is changing.
However, now the idea of the
regularity of once a month is connected
to the idea of your lunar cycle. For in
this way you will find that the lunar
vibration is what reflects the feminine
principle of energy in your society.
Do you follow me? Yes. Do you follow me?
I didn't. Moon. The idea of the lunar
vibration, the polarization of light
that occurs in reflecting itself off the
body of the moon in your terms and in
many other symbolic senses reflects the
female intuitive inner awareness
vibration. The vibration of the night, of the
The vibration of the night, of the
nurturing, of the cloaking.
Now, if we didn't have a moon, would
that be so? Perhaps not. Not in that
way. Now understand also also since you have
Now understand also also since you have
brought it up our planet does not have a
moon. Oh
Oh
now we do give physical birth in what
you term to be seven month gestation.
Is it painful?
No way. Does not have to be. So women
carry a baby in them.
Oh no. Repeat. Do women carry babies in
them like we do? In a womb? Yes. So they
have a womb? Yes.
When you come here, can we mix the
civilizations? Can we can we has been
done before in a breed? Will we be doing maybe?
It will not necessarily be necessary.
Darn it.
So women have ovaries like we do.
There is some
differentiation but basically the same.
And then
when a
through the conscious will of
this integration between
now understand again that in our
civilization we are always in
communication with the being to be
born consciously
and like your
civilization what you recognize as the
consciousness of that particular being
in a sense enters as you say the body
just prior to physical birth.
I have a couple questions. Um, one is it
I have an Indian guy who I've not really
been in contact with for a few years and
I miss him. East or west? Um, I
understand him to be an American Indian.
All right. And I want to know how to
open myself up more to
right with him. All right. What does it
feel like to you to be an Indian? Use
your imagination. How does it feel to be
an Indian? Feels very strong. Very
strong. Very strong. Very centered. All
right. Can you in your imagination then
allow yourself to act like one?
Probably can. Probably.
I can. I
did. Then you will form the type of
identification pattern that will allow
you in that state of being to know you
are in contact. For in this way you will
find that the American Indian culture
always knew it lived in more than just
the physical reality and had
communication with many different levels
of consciousness. Par for the course, as
you say. All a part of the day-to-day
existence of being an American Indian to
speak. moving west.
moving west.
Okay, follow me. Yes, I do follow you.
Leave myself open. Yes, act more. Okay,
for sure. For one moment. Um, next
question is, when I was a young girl, I
for about a year I would walk in my
sleep and I would wake up. I'd have to
go through two rooms in order to wake up
standing at a window, an open window,
crying, and I would be waving goodbye to
what appeared to be an 18th century
horsedrawn carriage purse with two
people dressed in black waving goodbye
to me. The horse would be going one way
and the people would be on the back end
waving their body. And that's something
that I've never been able to out or
understand what it was. It happened
every day for a year. I would wake and
I'd wake up hysterically crying at this
open window. Well, who do you think was
in the coffin? I never really saw a
coffin, but it was it was that kind of
person. Well, come on, take a guess.
Well, it was when I was around 13, so
possibly it was me. Yes. But I used to
wish it was my parents. All right.
But it was
you. Now the idea also is that you are
at a very high time in your society of
what you call psychic manifestation
during that adolescent stage and a very
very easily connected into all that you
have ever been and it was simply the
idea of saying goodbye to another one of
yourselves and becoming a new self.
Because there was a time period that I I
always believed to have been alive.
Yes. My last question is, "My husband and I
My last question is, "My husband and I
have been trying for four years to have
a child."
Trying as much as we can.
Why not? Keep practicing. It's getting
too intense. Too intense. All right.
It's too much pressure. Back off then.
Okay, that's very easy to say. Yes, it
is. Say it. Back off.
I have tried to back off.
Try to back off. That is difficult.
Backing off is easy.
Trying to back off. That is easy too. If
you are attempting to be trying to back
off, allowing myself. Oh, allowing.
allowing myself. Oh, allowing.
Now that's a different story.
Now then, if we are talking about
allowance, then it works both ways.
Allow yourself to know that any
agreements you are making with any other
individual to be born of you physically
in this way are the product of perfect
timing. Therefore recognize that when
you come to this timing it will then
feel like the right
time. No need to rush. Understand you
are becoming the type of being that will
then be the person who is to be the
mother of that individual.
You follow me? Yes.
Then by simply allowing yourself to
proceed as you are that is what will
accelerate you towards being that person
and allow you more quickly to manifest
that agreement. Okay. What? So I should
really just continue with what I mean on
infertility. So is that something I
should discontin? I would suggest that
you discontinue it.
Is this something I manifested in prior
in my life? This problem. This is not a
problem. Understand again that you know what you
Understand again that you know what you
are doing. You are waiting until the
time you agreed.
Because then you will be the person that
you need to be to give birth to that
person. Otherwise, you will not
understand them.
All right, then relax.
Um, I I have several things I want to
say. Um, go ahead. Speak up. Okay. Uh,
one is that I really appreciate uh,
being here and all the other people who
are here and yourself of course because
uh, the questions that are asked are
questions that that I would never never
even think about and that they're asked
and I think about them in that. So, I'm
really happy. This is why everything
that anyone says has to do with everyone
that hears it or they would not hear it.
Oh, okay. Uh the second thing is that I
would just like to make another
announcement about my performance and
there's information on the table uh
concerning it and I would appreciate it
if anyone would like to participate that
they would give me their telephone
number because I have planned the first
meeting. All right. Okay. And statement
of your own boldness. Yes. All right.
Um I forgot to All right. Then you may
take over now. Thank you, Bashar. Oh,
wait. No, no, I didn't forget. I We'll
come back to you. Okay,
I am involved as our um two other women
in the audience tonight in a group of
sisterhood, a group of women who are
healers, right? And we meet from time to
time and do universal healing and also
individual healing. Right. What I am
interested in is we have a sense of
ourselves from a past perspective in the
moment and our difficulty is really in
the future perspectives in the moment
and I want to know if you have anything
to say about that. Well, what do you
imagine your future to be? Oh, it's
incredible. It's what? Incredible. It's
what? It is completely wonderful.
Therefore, credible. Yes, of course. All
right. Now, you do not seem to have any
Now, you do not seem to have any
difficulty with that. Well, okay, then I
really need to say what my real question
is. Oh, thank you.
I come here week after week with
wonderful questions formed and by the
time we're all done, they've all been
answered. Only I haven't ever said
anything. All right. And so I feel as if
I want to say something. So, well, then
make a sharing. You don't have to have a
question to communicate.
Um, the idea is that you are willing to make
the idea is that you are willing to make
a statement of conviction.
Questions are sharing too. Questions are
learning too. But if you are willing to
make a statement of
conviction, then you are centered and
considering yourself to be equal to the
entire experience of everyone that is
here. So
share what is you as your
future. I'll ask the question. Thank
you.
I don't know how to answer.
Do you know how to be it? I am it. Then
that is the answer. Thank you very much.
Perfect answer. Thank you. All right.
Okay. Um the question has to do with uh
creativity uh and sexuality. Um a
channel that I used to see a year ago
went off on sexuality for many many
weeks in a row and basically
well had a dissertation on on sexuality
and creativity for week after week after
week and they said that um they kind of
said that that it was almost necessary
to have sexuality in order to to let
your creativity flow. Well, you have
created yourself to be a sexual being.
Yeah. Therefore, simply the idea is that
if you attract an opportunity to express
yourself that way, there is no need to
deny that experience from yourself.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Well, that's what the
question has to do with um because my
creativity has been flowing flowing
flowing and uh suddenly a few days ago I
realized that I hadn't had sex for four
months and then I decided to do
something about it. So, I made a date to
have sex and
It was it was a complete failure and it
didn't a complete what? A failure. It
didn't happen. One moment
there is no such thing. Okay. Well, look
at it from another point of view.
How did it serve you? Uh
what did it show you? It made it made me
see that I've really cut myself off from
people. All right. Very good. Then it
was a complete success. Now that it has
served its purpose for that particular
scenario, you can use the ease of
creation to attract other
scenarios. Now that you allow that to
serve its purpose, otherwise you will
only attract the same thing over and
over and over again until you recognize
what you are trying to show
yourself. Now that you know what you are
trying to show yourself, then let that
be all right. Do not judge yourself and
then you will be the complete person
that will attract the relationship that
will complete itself.
You follow me?
Um kind of. All right. Now, come on.
Keep it simple. It is very simple. You
just said it showed me I have cut myself
off from people. All right. Now, you
have the idea. It is now you. So, you
are now integrated with that idea as
that idea. Now, if you can allow that to
be an all right reason for the scenario
to have gone the way it did, then you
will be saying that that portion of
yourself and the creative way you showed
yourself that idea was valid for you.
And now that you know yourself to be a
more complete individual in terms of
your awareness of the overall
completeness that you are, you can now
use what you have now incorporated in
yourself to attract another situation
that will not have to play out the same
way for simply you gave yourself an
opportunity to reflect something that
you had done. Now if you accept that
then you will transform into something
else. So, I don't necessarily need to uh put
So, I don't necessarily need to uh put
put out or or do I? I mean, I feel like
for years I've been wanting a a
relationship, a really loving
relationship. All right. But again,
understand that the idea of
relationships is not to need them to
feel complete. Right?
Therefore, simply this is an opportunity
for you to know that you are complete
enough to create the kind of scenario
that would show you what you are
creating. You are functioning perfectly
because you are giving yourself messages
about the type of reality you are
creating. And if you have been cutting
yourself off, then that is the
reflection you got. All right, it is
over and done. Now incorporate that
symbol within you knowing that you are
still working perfectly because you were
able to create the scenario to reflect
what you were doing so that you can be
more aware of yourself as a complete
being and therefore attract the idea of
a complete
relationship now that you have decided
to I'll say get back in circulation.
Okay. But is it am I going against
myself by by making affirmations to the
effect that I do want a loving
relationship or is that helpful? No, it
is simply a recognition that you are
yourself a loving relationship.
If you know you are a loving
relationship, it is not so much that you
need an affirmation. You can simply know
that that is what you are. are and
therefore that is what you will
attract exactly in the way you need to.
Okay. Now let me ask you
this. Would you want to not be complete
before you attract someone that you
think you may like to spend some time
with?
Can you say it again? Would I not? Would
you not like to be complete? No. Right.
I would like to. All right. Then allow
the way you have allowed yourself to
recognize all of the ideas you have been
separating to serve the purpose of
putting you together so that you can get
what it is you have wanted. Well, then
but if I have that I feel complete, then
you have no need for someone else.
Correct. And that is why you will
attract them because then you will be
sharing not needing. Okay.
Thank you. Now you may all take a short
break.
All right. Shouting. Yes. [Laughter]
[Laughter]
Thank you. Um you you mentioned superc
conductivity within within the concept
of a crystal structure. Yes. And I'm
wondering if quartz crystal also
exhibits manifestations of superc
conductivity of the type of energy that
it transmits. Yes. Yes. Is
this uh an energy type which our
scientists are aware of? Some aspects of
it. Are they aware of the superc
conductivity of it?
In a sense, yes. Because they understand
that by
definition, a crystallin form is in and
of itself a type of
superconductivity, the superconductive
arrangement of the material.
Right. Are they utilizing that facility?
Some. Yes. You mean some scientists are
or they are to some extent using it?
Both. Is it to a small degree compared
to what we can be using? Oh yes yes yes.
Maybe maybe somewhere
around two to 5%. Uhhuh. Are they aware
that the potential exists far beyond
what they're utilizing now? Yes, but
they do not know exactly in what ways it
will manifest yet. Uhhuh. Would you be
willing to suggest a way that um
one will
be the replication of something that
existed so very long ago in Aalundian
times the idea of
taking crystallin I'll say
crystallin I'll say
rod if you will and wrapping around it
copper wire many times and introducing
electrified current through that idea
than experimenting with the different
types of caps or end stones and
different cuts of facets on either end
and seeing what type of electromagnetic
fields are generated from that. Now
recognize that it is this configuration
that served as different types of
generator power generators in Atlantean
times that gave rise symbolically to
what you have created to be a symbol of
power through the ages that you call
your scepter.
What what kind of instrumentation would
be required to detect the uh fields that
you're referring to?
ones sensitive to electromagnetic
sensitive to electromagnetic
fluctuation some sensitive to
slight I'll say static electricity
charges to some degree temperature variation depending
variation depending
upon the
strength of the original field
instruments that can detect what you
call ionization. We
ionization. We
perceive, though in your terms this may
or may not be accurate, that you do not
yet have the degree of sensitivity in
certain instruments to detect the
gravitational fluctuations that are also
there.
Certain animals that in your terms
navigate by the use of the
electromagnetic field also would be seen
to exhibit certain types of orientation
sensitivity to this
field because of the
magnetite. In that way would you also
possess in your in this
cavity. Sometimes sometimes again
depending upon the juxtaposition of the
fields and the reinforcement of certain
wave fronts there may be the chance to get
fronts there may be the chance to get
auditory manifestations from this as
well.
Therefore, have both
infrasonic and ultrasonic detectors.
What is infras? Below your normal range
of hearing.
Okay. What frequency of electromagnetic
radiation would this manifest? Different
ones. This is why we are suggesting so
many different ideas. For you will find
that it will depend upon the way the
energy is fed, the length, the diameter,
the clarity of the material, the type of
endstones and so forth. We're talking
about very very short wavelength or or
long wave can be both. Okay. Depends
upon the amount of
wrappings, the strength of the original
electrical field and so forth. The
proximity of the wrappings to the
crystal and so forth. The closer to the
crystal, the higher the frequency. The
farther away, the lower.
So there's no um natural range or
frequencies that it would exhibit. It
would just be anywhere within the entire
range of electromagnetic radiation
configuration. Yes. Great. For you.
Oh, good. Um I want to share about and I
have a couple questions on you. I want
to share a dream I had a few nights ago
where um I was in someone's house and then I
um I was in someone's house and then I
noticed another little area that was
seem to be being built onto this house
and I asked about it and so this person
brought me down to the area and he said,
"Well, this is an apartment that I'm
building on to my house." And when we
went down there, I noticed it was like
right on the water. It was really
pretty. And I thought it was a tiny
little space. And I thought, "Oh, how
cute." you know, but then I was as I was
walking through this apartment, it like
was endless for a while. It had a lot of
rooms, a lot of bedrooms, bathroom, the
essence of fourthdimensionality,
the idea that the inside can be bigger
than the outside. Well, that's what when
I woke up, I felt like it to me symbolic
of myself like all the different
compartments of myself that I had that
but also the unlimited expansiveness
that you contain. Right. Right. Now
understand that there is and you will discover this
that there is and you will discover this
in times in your future. There is also a
way literally to create this type of
literally to create this type of
physiological
technology wherein you can have what
seems to be an exterior of limited
proportions and an interior of vaster
ones. Oh, very interesting. And it was
on the water. I thought that was
interesting, too.
Um, now let's see what else we say. Oh,
I um we're talking about periods. I've
had my period now for like the last two
weeks. I'm It's getting to be too much
of a habit now. It's like it's just I
just find it's interesting that I I
would have my period for that long. All
right. Um, when
when
you are complete with the idea
of
shedding old
ideas and complete with the idea of
preparing for new
ones, it can alleviate
alleviate
now to some degree.
Agree. There is a
particular substance which you can
substance which you can
ingest which may not in your case
necessarily that it will but may be of
assistance.
Yes, it is.
Okay. Um, take it in T form. T form.
Okay. And if that's something I feel
like I need to do. I mean, I I know my
pural spot. All right. I just it just,
you know, seemed like a long time. It
hadn't that hadn't happened to me before
as I can remember. Not if
for two weeks.
Then that was maybe the last time ever.
What then seemed like a long time.
Maybe you're getting them all out of the
way. [Laughter]
With any variation of this idea that you
wish to. Yeah, I was also thinking about
the idea flow idea of flow. Very good
things to flow. Now also the
idea that you are exploring one end of
the spectrum of the idea of the
regularity of a
cycle and then you will then explore the
other end. Oh, I am it's like it's it I
get my period more often right now and
now just
all right. You can
find that within what you call three
months of your time. Mhm. The
periodicity can begin to increase and
increase and increase and increase and
the resonant vibration become deeper and
more connected to the
earth. And in that way you will find
there will be less need for that symbol. They will
They will
increase in the period of time between
them as you now extend the swing of your
as you now extend the swing of your
pendulum.
Okay. And be in sync with the vibration of the
And be in sync with the vibration of the
earth crystal.
Okay. Does that mean you got to be a
swer? I am
a baby. Now I have one more thing and I
talked to you earlier about my eyes. Um
do you see at this point any reason why
I should go um to an eye doctor for any
physical reasons? I know maybe if you
feel that your belief system will be
accommodated if you do then do so but
otherwise physically um to us there is
no difference. Well,
Well,
if it will put you at your ease, do so.
If it does not really matter to you,
then do not.
One way or another, you will see what
happens. [Laughter] One moment. Will
Will
you for a moment
moment
place your facial structure on the three
points of the channel's hand forehead
and two what you call cheekbones. Okay.
cheekbones. Okay.
Describe any change in sensation in any
way that it manifests. Uh stopping the
thought, some
heat, a vibration in my right
eye. Now I feel like you're staring me.
Feel like it's steering. Go with it.
Relax into the motion until you become
sensitive to the direction and simply go
with it. Relax
it. Relax
more. Move with direction. Very
direction. Very
good. Take your hand and do this to
yourself and think electromagnetism.
moving from the right to the left. Is
that it does not matter.
Okay. Electromagnet
then the other way. Electromagnetism. All right. Then bracket
Then bracket
yourself. Electromagnetism. Okay. Okay.
Then electromagnetism.
Okay. Same. Same. Same. Same.
Okay.
Now you have in a sense symbolically
taken a
scan of your entire apparatus.
You have the picture complete within
your imagination. Call that picture up. What
imagination. Call that picture up. What
does it look
like if you were to look at it, so to
speak, like an X-ray, but not
necessarily restricted to the
skull? Any variation in color at all?
Um, orange red comes to mind and where
Actually, I nowhere in particular. See,
it's kind of like an outline of my head
in orange and red with checks in the
background. All right.
To what area is your attention called,
regardless of what your
physiological idea is? My nose. All
right. Up in the top or down at the
bottom? No top. All
right. Then place a little tiny bit of
pressure on that
area and allow your eyes while
eyes while
closed to look as far up as they can and
as far down as they can.
and then let go and come back to center.
Okay. What do you feel?
[Music] Um, what comes to mind is center? All
Um, what comes to mind is center? All
right. Is there any action in your
temple areas? Was there any sensation in your
areas? Was there any sensation in your
temple areas?
Um, no.
One more time. pressure on the upper
bridge of your nose. Is it the temple?
Can like the the forehead area? Temple.
Um like the eye just above the eyebrow.
Temple. Okay. Oh. Oh. Okay.
Look up. Look down. Let go. Look center.
Any feeling in the temple?
Well, there's
um a slight aching when I look up and
down. All around the whole eye area. That's
All around the whole eye area. That's
that aching that I told you about. All
right. Just up, just down.
Anything below the ache.
Below the stand question. All right. Describe
the stand question. All right. Describe
in any way that words come to you any
sensation in the temple area other than
the ape.
Um, tightness.
What about fuzzy reverberation?
I haven't done that one.
Fuzzy reverberation. Yes. Um, like you
might imagine a low sound beating against your
imagine a low sound beating against your
eardrum might make.
Now place the pressure on the bridge of
your nose. again. Look up while your
eyes are closed. Mhm. Look
down. Come back to center and let go.
Open your
eyes. Now imagine that your temples are
vibrating slightly.
When you do that, as if you were pushing
them out of shape and then letting them
come back, but you still can feel the
back, but you still can feel the
reverberation a little bit and then it
dies out. Okay. Follow me. Mhm. All
right. Now do it one more
Now do it one more
time and let it
go and allow the fuzzy
reverberation to begin to blend with the
idea of the pain.
Oh, okay. So that it becomes more like
one sensation. Mhm. All right. Okay. Can
you do this? Sure. Yeah. Does it feel
like that?
Tell me when it feels like it is a
blending of the two ideas.
I have this thought that I right this
moment I can't blend the ideas and
that's the thought that I have. It's
like I feel the pain and then and then I
the idea the fuzzy do not make too much
of a demand on yourself.
Simply use your imagination. Become lost
in your imagination for now. You know
that the pain is still there. That is
all right. Okay.
We are not asking you to get rid of it.
Mhm. We are asking you to blend it with
something else. Okay. Right. This
moment. Yes. Right.
Yes. Right.
Now begin in your essence energy
connection. to dialogue with that vibration, to
to dialogue with that vibration, to
identify it for
yourself and use it as a symbol to
represent the underlying energy that
manifests the pain.
You say it again, please
have communication with the vibration
through the experience of the idea you
already know about communicating with
essence. Then allow that vibration to
Then allow that vibration to
symbolically represent the idea of the
underlying energy which creates the
pain. It is the energy you are using to
create the idea of having pain. Okay?
The more you begin to talk to it as
energy, the less it will need to
complete the manifestation in physical
terms as pain. Oh, okay. Mhm.
Allow yourself this exercise
anytime you feel like it for the next
three of your weeks. Okay.
Great. Thank you. Now, yes. If at any
time during this exercise you should
think of the moon, then also think of
the earth. If at any time you should
think of the earth, also think of the
moon. Okay.
And see what kind of vibration you come
up with at the end of 3 weeks. All
right. Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Over
there. Female. Yes. Could you please
tell us what your planet looks like?
Very much like the green portions of
your own to some degree.
It is mostly what you would term to be
parklike. There are forested
areas. Recognize that the surface of our planet
Recognize that the surface of our planet
has very few structures upon
it. They are very simple in form and not
congested together. The majority of our
together. The majority of our
civilization at any one time lives in
spacecraft off the planet. fully
twothirds of the population. Therefore,
there is no need for there to be many
dwellings upon the surface. It is, as
you would say,
temperate. In
climate in general, there are slight
fluctuations, but not to any great
degree. Do you follow me? Yes. Will this
have answered your question? Um, do
Um, do
you enjoy the water and the green like
we would? Yes.
Thank you. Why
you
question being an epileptic for 30 years
and stopped taking medication the last
three years. My first question would be
is why did I ask or put myself in that
position of requiring an order.
First allow me to ask you what has been
the result for the past 3 years.
More attack but no
attack but no
not every day.
Do you feel that it is easy to love
yourself? Unconditionally?
Unconditionally?
All right. Can you picture yourself
giving yourself a big hug?
How does that feel?
Now the first thing therefore I will
suggest is that if and when you should
create the idea of a so-called attack
that you carry this image with you into
the attack and it will allow you to
attack and it will allow you to
alleviate bit by bit any reasons for the
attack. For you will be taking the love
of yourself into the attack and you will
be using the weapon in the attack of
love. So nurture yourself in the midst of the
So nurture yourself in the midst of the
attack and you will snap
out of the scenario of being attacked.
For the most
part, this is to some degree why the
idea of getting through with very
quickly the idea of attack in and of
itself since it has played a great part
in many of your lives.
You now saw very
quickly that you wish to
consolidate and put yourself through an
accelerated version of what you now may
call a sense of
infirmity or
instability or having a shaky
foundation so that you can accelerate
yourself very rapidly. ly through this
idea so that you will be in step with
the transformation as it is going on.
Seeing as how in your terms up to the
very last moment, so to speak, up to the
very last life previous to this one,
were you still going through in very
bold physical ways all the ideas of
being attacked and attacking
others? how you are attacking
yourself. And in this way, it is an
opportunity for you to accelerate all
the ideas that have to do with the dominion
ideas that have to do with the dominion
of self- commandment and the idea of
self-empowerment and the
love that allows you to recognize
selfmpowerment. You will now find that there is no need
You will now find that there is no need
to attack yourself for having attacked
others or creating the scenario where
they can attack you in other lives.
This is why you have given yourself the
opportunity to place upon yourself all
the attacks that you have ever done or
perpetrated or had perpetrated on you so
that you would in your terminology in
your way of thinking physiologically
balance all of that idea of self-created
karma and so very shortly be in sync
with this transformational life and then
allow this physical life to be the last
one that you need in the earth cycle.
What I don't understand is I just became
aware about a year ago that if I was
really offered the chance to erase it
this minute uh that I wouldn't really
want to erase it in totality and it's
been more like a friend than an enemy.
Yes. because it has been serving you. As
we are saying, it allows you to feel the
sense of the overall eraser of all that
you have done in previous lives with
regard to attacking and you will play
out everyone that you need to play out.
But now that you are understanding this,
it is an opportunity for you to wean
yourself out of the scenario by going
into each attack loving yourself and
hugging yourself completely. So that
when you awake out of this entire dream
that you are creating, you will be able
to stand solidly, firmly,
stably recognizing the core vibration
that is unshakable within you,
unassalable, unattackable within you. And then with
unattackable within you. And then with
that clairvoyance of your own life, with
that clear light that you will know
yourself to be at that point, you will
then be in step with the transformation
of the entire
civilization. You will be of service in
that way. And then you will know that
you have because of this acceleration in
this light allowed yourself the
opportunity to know that you are
completed with your earth cycles of
reincarnation. You follow me?
Therefore, simply take with you into
each attack love of yourself and they
will lessen. For now, you can begin to
wean yourself slowly from this process.
Wake up from that dream into another
one. All
together. All together. You may
You may
also take with you our unconditional
love into each adventure within
yourself. You have our support for the
very creative way you have chosen to
express your
beingness and the unique facet of all
that is that you are. We thank you for
your expression of love and sharing. Thank you.
Um, do you on your
planet think the way we do in a sense
that you observe different pieces of
data and put them together and process
it this information to come up with new
information or do you just know? It is
more along the line of knowing. Although
we will still create some idea of
processing in time but not in the manner
in which you do. It will be more simply
the jumping of relationship to
relationship. Okay. Now when you've said
that you are exploring sixth and seventh
density. Nice. What kinds of processes
do you use to do so? Simply in this way
the idea can be done in many ways.
mentally can be a meditation of sorts.
There are some technologies that we have
created upon our planet that create
certain types of fields that will assist
us in generating the projection of our
consciousness to those
levels. Simply much of that is what you
call out of body experience.
Okay. When we are in different states of
uh brain wave frequencies like alpha and
delta and so on are we actually in
different densities
or no you are in different ideas of
third density. Uhhuh. Okay.
You are
enacting some of the idea of conscious,
subconscious and unconscious separations
that you have created in third density
reality. what you call
alpha somewhat conscious, theta
subconscious, delta unconscious.
So when we have out of body experiences
um I don't know what the brain wave
correlation is to that the brain wave of
the body at that time is usually in
delta delta um since you are unattached
right and the body is functioning
automatically. Okay so the experience we're having
Okay so the experience we're having
doing those out of body experiences
would be first density types of
experiences. Yes. You are no longer
physical as you understand it. Okay. So,
it is the non-physical fourth density.
There is a physical and a non-physical
fourth density. Okay. Now, in in one
process I did once it's it was a long
process. There was several segments uh
of experiences and in one of them I I I
came out of it and I said, "Wow, I just
experienced eternity."
uh and there's no way I could describe
what would have h what happened during
that time except the feeling I had.
Correct. It is an experiential idea but
the funny thing I did remember was that
you know Mr. Spock from Star Trek
series. Yes. He he was in there and I thought I
Yes. He he was in there and I thought I
asked myself some Bashar type questions
like you know what does he represent to
me name and so on. Yes. And uh I thought
maybe he was in there because it was
paradoxical. Very good. Could uh do you
have anything to add to that? The idea
simply that many times paradox will not
fit into logic as you understand it.
Right. And it right. Uh the other thing that I
And it right. Uh the other thing that I
was but that
that in and of itself is the type of
experience that we were speaking of
before with regard to the idea of being
connected psychically. To those that exemplify the
psychically. To those that exemplify the
idea of pure logic, it may not seem
logical, but it is real. And it is the
experience in and of
itself that simply does not have terms
that exist in the old logic that you
have created upon your planet.
Okay. Well, the other thing that that
Mr. Spark sort of represents is the the
the half Vulcan, half human, namely a a
blending in a way and a conflict between
two civilizations. All right. Would that
have anything to do with with being in
that experience as well? You are simply
telling me that the entire idea behind
that being is one of paradox. Right. I
see. Is one of polarity. That's true.
Right. So, uh can you tap into that
experience I had and tell me what
density I was experiencing?
It was in a sense a fourth density
experience. But the symbols that you are
using are third density symbols. Okay?
Because that is how you can make sense
of it here. That is not reflective of
exactly what it was you actually
experienced in fourth density. That was
simply more of a knowing understanding
than when you came back so to speak. You
created the scenario that seemed to
occur at the same time of the experience
but did not really but gave yourself the
symbols by which you could
understand the understanding in that
state that you had of what polarity is
all about and how they are both in you.
and from you. Okay.
Thank you. Thank you. Yes. Then you um
I I just I just want to share this
experience with you and then I'll get on
to what I'm willing to say. One moment.
This is something you do not really want
to say. What you are willing to share.
No, I didn't say that. Huh? Yes, you
did. Well, that's not what I meant.
Thank you.
Um there's been a few times during the
night um and the other time and the
other council that have been here as
well where
the seems to be emotion I don't know if
it's emotion it's not an emotion I know
common
to whatever anyway um then perhaps it is
not emotion okay then maybe it's not
emotion where I I I have this feeling. Yes. And
where I I I have this feeling. Yes. And
you by answering somebody else's
question, it seems as though you're
speaking directly to me. Of course. All
right. We are addressing the mass
consciousness as well as the individual
consciousness. And thus you will always be able to
And thus you will always be able to
perceive that whatever idea you resonate
to and vibrate to you will translate to
yourself for your individual needs. Thus
we are in an overall sense speaking to
each and every one of you collectively
and individually.
The band of
communication touches all of those
levels and you will tap into whatever
level you wish to tap into and make of
it how you wish to perceive it. Well, I
can't seem to stay on the level to get
my question answered or the seeming
conflict resolved. What conflict? Um,
well, it's been suggested to me by my
sister who's a nurse and by a
um kind of like a priest, but not a
priest, not a Catholic church, that what
occurred to me almost seven years ago
was actually traumatic amnesia rather
than an exchange of
consciousness. Yes,
consciousness. And what do they think is
the reason for the traumatic amnesia?
You are getting hit by a car. All right.
Now, understand first of all that as we
have discussed
before the idea of all the different
states in which consciousness can
manifest itself all serve
purposes. And in all reality, if I may,
I'll say be general in my
terminology, it does not really matter
what label is put on an experience if
simply you have utilized the experience
for the understanding of yourself.
Now if you wish to identify with the
idea of exchange of consciousness then
that is what gets you where you want to
go. If you wish to identify with the
idea of traumatic amnesia that is where
you need to go in that idea.
also recognize that in our civilization
as we have said previously, it is not so
much a matter of accuracy.
accuracy.
Yikes. Otherwise, why would you feel so
ill at ease about your own situation and
need to seek outside yourself for an
answer?
You are asking me to tell you what is
going on and it's if you're a reflection
of of me. Okay. This does not remain
outside myself and one
moment the idea of a
reflection is still contained within
you. Yes. But because you have created
it to be something separate.
The action of knowing for
yourself without needing to create a
question then exemplifies that you are
not making a separation out of the
reflection but that you are being the
reflection and discussing equally the
idea. Now this is our perception of your
Now this is our perception of your
situation.
You used the incident of what you call
the car accident to put you into a state
of traumatic shock that would allow you
to completely
change the level of the consciousness
that you
are. In a sense, you did make an
exchange, but basically you exchanged an
old idea of yourself for a completely
new idea of yourself, which in all
reality is a different
being. This to us encompasses all the
labels that you have used and is
accurate and valid on every level that
you wish to describe it. It is a state
of traumatic shock. It is amnesia in the
sense that of course you do not have the
memory of another you. You have your
memories because you are a new
being. It is not amnesia in the sense
that there needs to be any idea of a
continuous flow from an old you to a new
you because you have created the new you
completely and therefore you have your
own memories and your own reality which
are all valid to the new you that you
are. Not the old you that you were. You are a
Not the old you that you were. You are a
new reality, a new concept itself, a new
universe itself.
That is how we perceive why you used
that incident to jolt you into a higher
state of
existence. That was your symbol, your
method of kicking yourself upstairs.
Now, therefore, the
exchange of personality and identities
and memories is the product of the
willingness to be that new you. And
compared to the old you, it is a new
being. You follow me? Oh, yeah. I sure
do. I'm I'm
not
I got to the You see, it's not it's not
the lack of
ac. It's not the lack of acceptance of
what of
um Oh my
god. It's It hasn't been the lack of
acceptance of what has taken place, not
the accident. Not Oh my god, I can't
believe this person.
the fact that the the the um it's not
it's it's like knowing that the change
has taken place and
everyone it's like those who have known
me from the past have kind of shoved me
back into some sort of hole into their
idea of Exactly. Exactly. And I'm
fighting. Do you know that every single
person that has that has been before the
accident often even Am I making sense?
Yes, you are. Perfect sense. Okay. There
has there's only two people in my life
right now that exist as present time
friends. Steve and Lynn. Everybody else
has dropped off the line or and and it's
been almost miraculous that oh, for some
reason they don't want to be part of my
life anymore, which has been like God's
gift to me. Oh god.
Now that you are enjoying yourself,
then simply relax into your enjoyment
and love the you that you are
now. And then you will allow the reality
that reflects the you you are now to bring
reflects the you you are now to bring
you whatever friendship is there in it
waiting for you.
Thank
you. Thank you for allowing
us to love all of
you. There will be in your terms a few
more minutes remaining.
shouting you um than you may recall
several months ago I asked you about the
fact that when I placed my thumb little
finger and forefinger I guess similar
fingers on the opposite hand it didn't
do anything for me and when I rotated I
got a sense of some kind of sensation
and you indicated that I was more
interested in alternate we call that yes
well I found it quite interesting since
um particularly since November I had
been integrating my integrating my
future myself and I've come to the
realization that now the um the
symmetrical relationship has a lot of
meaning to me. I just want to share that
integrating my future self is just a
real kick. I'm I'm having the greatest
time ever that I can ever imagine. It
was just it's just been terrific. So
that's my sharing.
Thank you. Oh yes.
I recognize myself as the idea of
blending of
visualization and I have a couple
different ways I can go with it. One is
I wanted to ask you to leave that in a
short meditation
um with the idea of integration the
resonance of
integration is I wanted to hear some
words or the resonance of the kind of
teaching or learning you're doing um
related to the serious energy
All right, my human friend. Now
therefore allowing yourself to center in
the being that you know yourself to be
within this blending of the conglomerate
of all ideas of consciousness. You can
then at this time allow yourself the
manifestation in your oric field of the
blending of all oric fields and the
ideal of the creation of a spin of an
energy vortex exactly where you are
right now. The entirety of your being,
the entirety of every being with you
right now. the idea of the blending of
an energy vortex so that you can partake
of the idea of the motion that is what
gives rise out of the fundamental
unconditional love of all that is in the
energy field that is the foundational
experience of your physical reality.
That motion that gives rise to the idea
of the momentum in your reality. The
idea that you are a spinning sphere 360°
of yourself in every direction
infinitely for every direction both
outwardly and within. And therefore the
idea of all the colors, all the light,
all the energy, all the beingness, all
the fabric, all the material, all the
matter, all the ideas of focus, all the
ideas of expansion, all the ideas of
crystallin, the clarity, all the ideas
of polarity, all the ideas of the
support fluid, the
electromagnetic that you all breathe in
and out and speak with to each other's
minds. The one thing that connects each
and every one of you together. The sea
in which you exist. That is your
lifeblood. It is the lifeblood of your
physical mentality. It is the idea that
your personality has chosen to be. It is
the idea individually. It is the idea
collectively. Live and breathe through
the gills of your own understanding.
This fluid so that you may take in the
fullness of the breath of all that you
are and all that you have created this
planet to be. Understand Understand
that
every idea that you
are can at any time be
manifest through the particular facet of
the multi-dimensional crystal.
and any idea of the co-creation that
each and every one of you have attracted
yourselves to be within this night of
your time as you create this night to
exist for the purpose of recognizing
yourself as this
relationship. Then we will be able in
this way to function with you as that
relationship. And on that level, if you
allow yourself to experience for the
brief period of time for which it is
created, the momentary snap of the idea
of the centering of yourself within all
the density levels that you are, the
identification of the primal
existence, that is all that is. Now
is. Now
then we will share with share with
you
the as was
offered by the female who chose to
represent the
symbology in your
mythology that you called
Spock. The idea
exemplified which was the one idea of
that polarized
character that
indicated the blending of all polarity
within itself. And for yourselves and to
yourselves you can apply this
idea. Quote, "A
Quote, "A
difference which makes no difference is
no difference."
unquote. Therefore, that to which you
Therefore, that to which you
identify is the reality that you
are. Your
symbols for the purposes that you have
created them and love yourself for doing
so. For then will your symbols
become the reality
experientially. You are
one. We are one and together we are the
sharing that continues
forever. We extend to you our
unconditional love. We bid you good
night.