[Music]
All right, thank how are you all of your
time as you create time to exist.
Perfect. Oh,
Oh,
once upon a time, I believe is your
phrase. Third
word, let us say a
gathering of what we shall using your
terminology call gods.
These gods
gods
realized that they were the creators of
all that they wished to
experience and that they could create
anything that they could imagine to
experience as a real reality in any way,
shape, and form that they so decided to
experience that idea. Let us
Let us
say one
day they all got
together and decided to
experience the
idea of being
of being
unaware. For they were always aware,
always awake, always
knowing. And since they were always
knowing one or a few does not matter how
many suggested well then the
suggested well then the
experience that we have not had is not
knowing. How about let's create the
experience of not knowing. All right.
Sounds like fun.
So they all created an idea into which
they could project
themselves and in which for all
practical intents and purposes they
would no longer be awake but would be
asleep. They would no longer know but
they would
forget. And in the creation of this
reality, they discovered
something that the creation of a reality
in which you can forget
forget
means that along with that
experience, you may create the idea of
continuing to forget.
This they discovered but in a sense did
not know they had discovered it for were
not cognizant of what forgetting really
means. For they even forgot that there
was something to
discover. But the whole idea was all
about in creating a realm of
forgetfulness. They even forgot why they
had created
it. And this created the idea of the
cycle of always looking toward that
realm and never anywhere else. For to
them they had forgotten that there was
anywhere else to
look. And thus even upon leaving the
physical form once they had projected
themselves into
it, they never looked beyond the idea of
that which they had created. And so
continuously returned again and again
and again to that
experience adding more and more and more
momentum more energy to the idea of
forgetting even more and more and more.
No, after a
time there were beings who had also
chosen to play that game to different
extents for different
purposes in different areas of the
diversificated universe. Some in your terms were I'll
universe. Some in your terms were I'll
say ahead of others, some behind so to
speak. all experiencing the idea of forgetting
all experiencing the idea of forgetting
at different
rates. Now in the course of time which
was a creation along with the realm of
forgetfulness let us say another side
effect another fringe benefited that
perhaps was not counted upon
exactly there came to pass in many
different areas that beings did begin to
remember and as they remembered
They remembered that there were other of
their kind, other gods that went other
places to play the same
game. So now that they had remembered
and in a sense more or less gotten
through a certain portion of the game,
at least enough of it, so that they
became aware that they were in fact
playing a game. They desired to look up
the other gods and see how they were
doing. Well, some of them remembered,
some did
not. And thus it was understood the idea
of the different rates of time, the
different dimensionalities that were
created in the creation of the limited
idea of universe.
The idea that there is variance and
diversification in that way allowed them
to realize that time as a concept now
existed and that not everyone got
through with the game at the same time
and some were still playing certain
portions that others had finished
playing many many years
before. In this way, there are also the
gods, portions of the gods that have not
in your terms ever
chosen to play the game of physical
reality. Now, those
beings that remembered themselves and
went searching for their friends and
found their friends not
remembering many times were
open enough to their memory to know that
they could communicate with those that
had not yet chosen physical
reality and went to
them to discuss the entire idea of the
differences that now
existed. Since they know they had those
that had not yet been physical, let us
say a larger overview of all of the
differences within the oneness.
To those overselves, those gods who had
not played that game of limitation, a
game of
forgetting, there was even some time
spent getting them to even believe that
such a thing as time existed before it
could be discussed as to what had
happened to the rest of the gods.
Once they basically
understood, they
agreed in this way to always be
available. Should anyone choose to
remember so that it could be immediately
recognized that there was and is a
mirror and a
reflection beyond innocence outside of
innocence. the limited game that some
gods continue to
play in this way.
Therefore, there is simply the
opportunity for the gods that are still
playing this
game at any moment to remember that they
are in fact playing a
game and to remember that they have
created everything in that game.
For those that have played and those
that have
not are
aware that those that have chosen to
play have chosen so simply because it is
one more thing that does exist within
all that is and the
enrichment of experiencing everything
that all that is has to
offer. Well, let us say it is a very
well-rounding experience.
For those beings that have not chosen to
play that game, have not experienced in
that sense every corner of all that is,
and in this way cannot relate to the
gods that have chosen to play the game
in many
ways, and are choosing in and of
themselves to manifest their own
manifestation in ways that have not in
their terms, in your terms, partaken of
all that all that is has to offer.
Whereas the gods who have chosen to play
the game have
And in this way
therefore once they remember that they
are playing the game can remember that
they have given themselves the
opportunity to play the game so that
they will then
contain that experience as one more
experience that all that is has to offer
and will then
know once they remember that they do
contain all of all that
is that they are all of all that is that
they are the creators. These
gods, the creators of the
universes, you are those gods. As if you
did not
get, you are the gods that have created
the universes. All that
All that
is did not
create the
universes. All that is created
you. You created the
universes. All of
them. If you wish to say all that is
created the universes, then all that is
created the universes through
you. Do you follow me?
All that is is the
universe did not create the universe.
universe. You
created the universes.
And what it means is
this. That all that you consider to be
learning is simply
remembering who and what you
are. Do you follow me? For you are the
universes and in that
sense anything goes.
Shing you. Hi. I would just like to
shared that I had my first by accident.
He comes right into the room and listen.
So, so he's not sure if he he at this
time doesn't believe that you So what?
Yeah, he doesn't matter. He calls you
Bashar the punk philosopher. Oh, right.
I will joyfully accept that.
But the other night while I was
sleeping, I woke up because he he was
talking in his sleep and he and what he
was saying wasn't he wasn't speaking
English. He wasn't speaking, you know,
he was it seemed some kind of um
extraterrestrial himself because what
was was portions of himself, right?
Okay. It it seemed like what had or
everything that you experience with
anyone else has significance for you because
else has significance for you because
you have cocreated it and because you
experience it, it obviously has some
validity on some level of your
consciousness or you never would have
been there. You only only
only experience in your reality what is
the product of your belief system about
what you think should be there only
true. Okay. So what what he was saying
I'll go you know then simply take the
vibration for what it has meant to you.
let him take it for what it has meant to
him and get on with your lives.
Okay. So it doesn't there was no
particular there is always a particular
message but in this way the idea simply
is to show you that you are cocreating
your own
symbols. You are let us say jockeying
for a commonality of communication.
You are attempting to seek out common
ground upon which to communicate with
each other.
Follow me.
Um sense he does for there is let me say
a
thrill that is somewhat conscious
somewhat subconscious but it is there.
And and do you happen to know or can you
comment? It is an emotional language. It
is not what you would understand as a
physiological language. It is simply the
vibrations that feel right according to
what is being felt, what is being
communicated. You follow me. Um, right.
Where I thought I had heard it was here
when Lisa was talking about some
particular language. What did the idea
make you feel like it made when you
heard it? it. Well, it made me feel like
uh someone was trying to communicate,
right? Anything else? Uh and I didn't
understand what was being said. That is
not what I asked you.
How did you feel? I was excited. All
right. Then understand that what I am
calling an emotional language comes in
whole concepts not in the type of
alphabet you are familiar with. You do
not get a letter or a word at a time.
You get entire feelings, entire
emotions, entire concepts. The idea of
communication, the idea of
excitation is in of itself a
message. You do not think it valid
because your analytical mind must render
it down into something that your
analytical mind can make sense of. But
the feeling is what the emotional
language is for, not for your
mind. You follow me? Yeah. You got the
message where you needed to. Okay. So,
it was not for your ears. It was for
your heart. Okay. Okay. Thank you. You
guys. Uh, hi. This is Doran. Um, more
true than what it is. Yeah. You know the
way you you kind of clarify for Why are
you concerned about that? Well,
because if you're right, then I can't.
What does that have to do with anything?
I will never be right or wrong. You know
what I'm saying? Yes, but you don't.
Yes, I do.
[Applause] Just please I cannot answer it in the
Just please I cannot answer it in the
way you expect me to. Then don't ex
don't look at me. What are you expecting
from yourself?
Hey, the question
the question
is I want certainty that that if I asked
you the condition of my body right now,
you are coming from a point of knowing
what occurred then. And I will have the
certainty of knowing that you are right
by what you tell me. But you are
creating that idea. Oh my.
You do not understand the idea of mental
communication. You are expecting that it
is one thing and it is
not. You are measuring the idea of that
ability to communicate with you by one
specific parameter and you are not
understanding how it works. Because my
words come across the way they come
across which leaves you to believe that
however you want to put it okay isn't
necess may not necessarily be what I'm
asking what I'm saying then ask what you
are asking ask what you are asking I
want you to tell me what damage took
place at the point of the accident do
you not know yes but then why should I
have to know it is not something I'm not
I'm not saying that you know yes you are
no I'm not I already told you that if
you can tell
me what the damage was. Yes. Then I will
know in present time with my next
question of what is
there. I will know that you are looking
at what really is for my um
constellation not yours.
Understand this. You are telling
this. You are telling
me that in order to continue the
communication in the way you want to,
there is something that I do in fact
have to know that you already know.
Otherwise, you will not continue the
conversation. It's not that you have to
know it. It's that I have to know that.
But you I cannot do that with you. Why
not? Because that is not the way it
works. Do it the way it works. I am
doing it the way it works. Child,
I know that there have been people that
stood in front of me and that I could I
could see by do that. But did they
challenge you to know or did you just
know? Okay. I came off as a challenge
jokingly. I wasn't serious. I'm not
challenging. Yes. And the point is if
you already have the knowledge then
simply act on that idea and I will
discuss the entire idea with you. Yeah
but against my uncertainty as to whether
but you are requesting validation matter
with my body right now. First of all it
is very tense.
It is very tense.
That is what is the matter. Okay. And
why is it tense? Because you are
creating that idea.
of needing self validation and you are
seeking outside yourself for it. I
cannot prove anything to you. I'm not
asking. Yes, you are. That is the point.
You do not think you are, but you are.
Okay. I don't think I am not.
Okay. Then how can I if I were to say to
you, all right, you broke the lower leg bone
all right, you broke the lower leg bone
and in your estimation that was so to
speak wrong. Then you would simply have
created that too for yourself because
that is what you wish to find. You
design the experiment and you get the
result that you designed the experiment
for. You're sitting there telling me
that I'm designing a wrong experiment.
You're wrong. There is no right and
wrong. Good. Then don't use the word I'm
used. The process that I want to take
place, I know can take place. Yes, it
can. But not when you need it to.
Only when you don't expect it to. That
is what I am saying about your lack of
understanding of the process. When
individuals can read each other, it is
because there is an emotional bond of
love. When you say to that individual, I
need you to tell me what happened in my
life before I will trust a conversation
with you in a certain way, you are
shutting the information off from them
by making it a test because you are not
acting in love. You are not
communicating with their very soul and
not allowing them to communicate with
your soul so they can know you. Okay.
Well, then let's push all that aside. less. less.
Now
address what it is that is actually on
your mind and perhaps the information
you have asked me first may come out
enough so that I can pick it up. Okay,
if that is even important by that time,
which it is not since you already know
the answer.
The point is simply what you've called
psychic knowing in that way works from
the vibration of love and trust and the
trust has to be there first before the
effect of the knowingness happens. It is
not the other way around. I don't know
how to I am telling you how simply get
involved in the conversation with me as
per what you really want to know. You
don't need to know what bones were
broken because you already know this.
No, no. I'm not saying that. I want to
know what the What do you really want to
know? I want to know how much you can
really see. I just told you how much.
Only as much as you let me and only when
you are functioning from love exchange
with me when you are not expecting that
I need to answer you in a certain way to
prove something to you cuz I can't prove
anything to you. You can't prove
anything. Do you know what I mean? Yes, I know
Do you know what I mean? Yes, I know
what you're asking. But that type of
validation is totally the product of
your own creation. Fine. So then let's
push all that aside. All right. I and
really get down to business here. Is
there any business to discuss? Yes,
there is. I don't know if there's any
business to discuss. In my perception,
in a sense, there is not. You know what
you are doing with your life. You do not
need to answer any questions for you.
You have all the answers and you know
you do.
Now if you wish to simply share who you
are with me fine maybe somewhere in
there certain ideas I will learn of you
I can share back with you but only when
there is equal sharing okay I'll I'll
start with the first prince and we'll
open this body but it is all right with
me if you don't
you understand I trust you care whether
it's all right with you well then you
are not willing in that
to form the trust that is up to you if
you wish to assume then as all right
what is your trust based on you see
trust is the idea of unconditional love
are you putting conditions on your trust
you are saying well I will trust you if
you act this way a certain way that I
will accept and therefore something I
can trust that means it is conditional
love I hope you guys don't mind this
energy No, no, no, no, no. This is very
very loving, very very teaching on your
part. They are all learning something.
Yeah. Now they just haven't figured out
what does not matter.
Now simply all I am saying is that the
idea of trust and the idea of love is
the same. It is unconditional. When it
occurs, it occurs unconditionally. If
there is conditions, it doesn't work.
The communication does not exist if the
trust and the love are not unconditional
to begin with. My civilization has
telepathy, so to speak, between all of
its members. And we know what has
happened to all of its members because
we are all in love with each other to
begin with. We do not put expectation,
well, you act this way and then I'll
think about trusting you. We do not put
conditions on our love. We accept them
as they are for whatever the
communication is that occurs because we
know that whatever we receive from them
is the product of what we co-created
with them. And we trust them and we
trust ourselves to have created exactly
the interaction that we need. I cannot
trust. That is your choice. Then it is
your choice. If you simply cannot do it,
you cannot do it. But that is your
choice. Fine. I'm telling you my choice
right now. Okay. And I'm presenting the
the shits of that choice in order to
clear it up. Will you shut up and listen
to me? Very well.
Thank you. You are welcome.
Something about trade routes or military
routes. I'm not sure. And he and there
were like lines of light connecting
possible. Can you tell me who was this
man and and uh is he a warrior or a
merchant? And what what are these? Now
it is not specifically that that
individual is a warrior or a merchant in
that way. The lines do represent the
idea of energy routes between different
civilizations that are in your terms
often traveled. The idea of seeing the
polarity stems from you from your own
I'll say relationship to yourself as a
merchant in lives as a warrior in other
lives because you can recognize trade
routes as having both potentials in your
society. They can be used for trade they
can be used for war militarily. Now the
individual in a sense is a connection
and a combination of your own higher
consciousness but also connections that
you have with the plleadian system in
that way and other consciousness that's
there and simply you are using the
senses that you have in much the same
way that your ancient sailors got I'll
say directional sense you can know that
when you fly the stars you can gain that
directional sense of simply knowing
where the energy lines the trade roots
are following your instincts. In that
way, you have given yourself a
physiological symbol that you can
physically see these lines of energy.
They are simply representative of the
connections in your consciousness you
are making to the Plleadian system
because individuals in the Plleadian
system have that sense and you are
making a connection to them from
yourself. Thank you. Um, I have a few
more questions if possible if we make
the answers short. All right. I was
wondering if you could do me a favor. Is
that possible within your depend um
there's a war going on in Afghanistan
right now and I was wondering is it
possible for you to transplace or
transllocate their equipment? No, but it
is possible for you because this is your
world. We do not interfere. You have
created this idea. You are the ones
responsible. Take the responsibility and
take your power. And in this way, center
yourselves. be the reality you wish to
experience. That will be the reality
that you see in your world. Okay. Um I
noticed you said I was going to ask you
a question. You every time I just
realized that I was going to say do you
ever say you're welcome and then you did
tonight. Yes. Thank you.
I didn't even have to I didn't have to
waste time. Um I got a few more here if
I can be if I can get through this fast.
Uh according to raw cancer can be cured
by a type of meditation fasting and
allowing the roots of mindic way as the
fasting draws toxins from the body. That
is a creative tool like any other way
that the idea of cancer can be
transformed. Any way your imagination comes up with
Any way your imagination comes up with
for you is the right way for you. Then
in other words to cure cancer for
anybody is just whatever they feel like
using they always have to cure
themselves anyway. realize that now you
can suggest to them ideas that they may
enjoy but even if they so to speak take
your suggestion and do it for themselves
they will still only be doing it their
way. There will be the slight variations
that represent their particular
vibrational energy and they will make
the alterations according to how they
can accept with their belief structure
how that suggestion can work for them.
Then if they decide it can it will.
Okay. A couple two weeks ago during one
of these sessions right in the beginning
I saw like it was looked like a belt or
a ribbon about three inches uh high
about 3/4 of an inch wide was I you have
just told me that you did okay the
understanding one moment one moment one
moment the understanding in your speech
pattern is simply from the habit of
assuming that what you call your
imagination does not represent real
reality and it does okay because what
you think of as Your physical real
reality is only the product of your
imagination to begin with.
You follow me? Yes. Now, what was it?
Well, it seemed to be some kind of
connection uh forming between it. It
seemed like connect. Is that what you
were talking about earlier about being
able to connect with somebody? Uh what
you were just talking to the young lady
about the pathway being open? Yes. In a
sense, you recognized that there was
that idea of communication and you
physicalized a symbol to represent it to
you. Oh, I imagined what it would be
like. In other words, that does not mean
it is not real. Yes. Okay. You are the
creator. You are the manipulator of
energy. You get energy to fall into
whatever form you want and that energy
does so and it is real. Okay. Last week
you mentioned a group that is beginning
to be ready to be self-empowered. U you
mentioned Yes. What can you tell us more
about that group or who they are or
where they're from? Simply those that
have connected themselves to that
individual. Oh, okay. Sure.
Uh you have mentioned about a bargain
that an agreement. Yes. An agreement
rather. And no bargaining.
Agreement. And um I have two. How do you
ask them? I Well, one is 8 months old.
So, what has your imagination? What has your
what has your imagination? What has your
heart told you? How do you see yourself
doing it? If you were to imagine that
you would do it and be successful doing
it, how do you see yourself doing it?
Uh, in a very loving, open way. Um, what
does that mean? Well, I'm a very
uh I guess I'm right. And um well, I can
say with my three and a half year old
that I would Oh, very good. Simple,
isn't it?
Yeah. Now, as long as you don't put
expectation upon what you hear, you will
get your answer. Well, you had mentioned
that they forget somewhat. Active three.
All right. All right. You do not have to
take that as chiseled in steel. I was
wondering if I was like running. You are
creating your reality and you are
co-creating it with them. If they chose
the type of mother that would still
think that even beyond three and a half
she could have that communication then
be true yourself. Right. And I have
another question. All right.
Do you have any sense as to whether
every being on your planet has
communication constantly.
Now, whatever agreement you have made
will determine what lines of
communication you pick out to be more
real to you than all the rest. But lines
of communication exist to every
possibility at the same time. You follow
me? This is why to us it does not mean
anything in our civilization. When you
say, "Well, what's specifically this?
What's specifically that? What you
recognize as the specifics are the
product of your own focus. You pick out
what is important to you and make it so.
But it is all there. All of it. Anything
you can think of, anything you can
imagine, it is all
there. What you focus on reflects back
to you the things you are looking at in
this reality. You follow me? Yes.
reality. You follow me? Yes.
Thank you.
You um my roommate uh the lady that I
brought with me last week. Yes. Um she
had an experience uh this morning about
4:00. Told her how I showed her in the
sky. You mean a craft? A craft? Yes. And
um so she she being a fairly psychic
person, she had wanted to call me, but
she wanted to also stay there with her
too. And what was her feeling
towards those individuals?
Well, loving entities. I mean, she
didn't see them as something to
interfere. Uh you mean like everyone?
Well, yes, but in her case, she at this
point has developed it to a level that
All right. She uses it consciously,
right? And in as much as I am beginning
to Well, then since you are beginning
to, why didn't you tell her? Well, I
didn't know the answer to that. Are you
psychic? I'm beginning to uh get some
bits and pieces. All right. What are the
bits and pieces you get about this?
Well, very good. You are being honest with
very good. You are being honest with
your own pieces. Well, yes.
Okay. I didn't tell her that. But why
not? Are you ashamed of your I was not
Are you ashamed of your I was not
ashamed. I was just so into her going
through her explanation of it all
because we talked so much. Very good.
Now, hold that thought. Yes. While you
were, so to speak, into her, while she
was going through, were you paying
attention to the information that was
coming to you, or were you throwing it
all out the window as subtle bits of
this, subtle bits of that that you
weren't paying attention to? Well, I
knew it was a sign of something because
I'm beginning to watch every time. A
sign? A sign? Yes, it was a sign of
individuals doing something.
Are you making it mysterious? It is not
mysterious. as little as possible. But
all right, if you see an individual pull
up in front of you in one of your
automobiles and get out and pick up a
flower and get back in, what is that a
sign of? Why is that mysterious? Is this Oh
of? Why is that mysterious? Is this Oh
well, better go to Bashar and ask him
what that meant.
What? Let now I am making the analogy
for this reason. Let the feeling of
seeing an individual in a car be the
same. Do not make more of the spacecraft
and those beings. Okay. Well, what I'm
after actually is um she also does and
um yes, of
course she
can. Anyone who has allowed themselves
to exist on the vibrational level of any
being that they have
perceived can form a communication with
them in any way they
desire. Now because you are connected to her, so
Now because you are connected to her, so
can you. And if automatic writing is the
way you wish to do it, do it. Well,
that's the way she wishes to do it. How
do you wish to do? How I wish to do it
is I want to in the flesh to the bone. I
I mean I really want like months ago you
know before I moved out there. All
right. Then that is possible too. But if
that is the only way then you will be
creating the amount of time that you
wait until that happens. Well, no it's
it's not the only way. In fact, I went
to take a walk up the hill to All right.
Here is a suggestion for you. All right.
Okay. go back to that spot
and assume that the incident did not
occur in a past which is separate from
the present and they will still be
there.
When you allow yourself to get used to
the idea of what you feel between you
and them
by I'll say in your terms for now
practicing the idea that the past you
think they were in is still the present.
When you come to terms with that more
and more and more and
more, then you will determine you you
will be the determiner of the rate at
which you will allow them to interact
with you
physically. Because the exercise of
creating the past and the future to be
in the present will be the coming to
terms of your own nowness. and equality
to them, which is what will let you
vibrate on the same level as them and
will let you see them in the flesh in
the bone. Right. Then
bone. Right. Then
you Good evening,
Bashar. My name is uh Freddy. And if I
can just get my tape in here and get it
started. Okay. Good evening, Bashar. My
name is
Freddy. You said that already.
I just wanted to put it on.
Good evening, Freddy.
Uh, I thank you for your greeting and
I really needed that because I've spent
a great deal of my life trying to
embarrass some of the people I have
liked the most. Thank you. But I did not
embarrass you. Oh, you chose to be
embarrassed. Yeah, right
again. Uh, not right.
Uh, not right.
Uh, just you just you just me. Okay. Uh,
I have a multitude of uh relatively
unimportant question.
Well, all right. I'll I'll Okay. I would
like All right. Not important, but to
you significant. Yes. since you are
creating them. This is true.
I suppose what have you learned from
them being in the state that they are
in? I've learned that the the coming
into this life and what I chose was my
feet. All right. Why that? Why? Yes.
Why? Because I could see them every day
when I looked in the mirror. All right.
And I would always know that I had not
made the grade that I had before.
personal realization. All right. You
know, uh uh godliness. If you say so. I
say so. What you mean in my perception
anyway is that you are not willing to
believe you already are the grade.
The grade is nothing you have to
achieve. Perfection is not something you
strive for. Perfection is what you are.
You will always grow. But everything you
do is a perfect manifestation of the
thing you are doing. Thus, everything
you do is perfect. That's true.
Therefore, what you are now attempting,
so to speak, to create is not an
achievement, but the recognition of that
which you already are. Exactly. All
right. Then remember
remember what you are all that is. You
are the creator. You have created the
idea of giving yourself this symbol.
Uhhuh. Now if you know that it has
already served its purpose, yes, let it
go. Do not put the expectation now that
it must change in ways you think it
should change. Because obviously if it
is still there, it is still serving you
somehow. And perhaps only to remind you
that you do not have to do
anything to achieve the state that will
allow them to in your terms correct
themselves, but simply to recognize that
you already are that state and allow
them to reflect what you are already
willing to
be. Not be
someday, be now. I see. And yet, well,
are they more important than any other
part of your body? They are not less
important than any other part of my
body. No, they are not. But are they
more important?
Uh, yeah. Well, then why are you
singling them out and putting them in
the embarrassing spotlight? Because I
put them in the embarrassing spotlight
first. It is my responsibility and my
duty now to care for them. They have
served me so well and now I All right.
But the message coming from them to you
is that they are already cared for. Only
you don't know it. I see. You are
already caring for them. Yes. Now they
wish to return the favor in the sense of
letting you know that you don't have to
worry about
them. You and them will take care of
themselves. Uh therefore, lighten up.
If you put them in the spotlight, they
understand it as being expected to
perform. And that expectation is what
gives them stage
fright. They do not change. I see. They
are in the spotlight. I see. You are
narrowing your focus upon them. Ease
your focus back out to contain the
totality of yourself. Not just
physically, but all of you. I see. Then
they will say,
Now we can change.
He is not putting so much responsibility
on us. He has taken it back for himself.
You think that I should keep my mouth
shut in public?
That's
a good I see. I understand what you say.
And all right. Now understand this as
well in terms of your tools of your
imagination that you create for yourself
to come up with whatever you think you
need to allow yourself to do this
transformation to allow the
transformation to
occur. One idea can be
this. Your body is an energy
system. You follow me? Yes. It is one
thing. One energy system.
If you can view your body as one energy
system, you will sense the patterns of
flow. Now, the idea of putting a focus
on one specific portion of your body
creates a divergence of that
flow and does not allow it to partake of
the I'll say natural flow of the energy
system. You are damning it
up causing a backwash in that sense by
the focus you are distorting the energy
field in a specific way by focusing on
any one
point. Therefore the idea of containing
the totality of yourself is to contain
the idea that you are at any given point
the perfect representation of the idea
you are willing to be. But
then you simply do not have to perform.
They do not have to perform. You can
simply determine what reality you are.
And the reality of allowing everything
in your physical form to be what it
quote unquote should
be is to simply live all of yourself
when you live. Not just live for your
teeth, live for your spleen, live for
your heart, live for your finger, live
for your aura, live for all of yourself.
And then the rest of yourself will be
able to hold hands with your teeth
again. I see. Thank you. I've done that
as you were telling me. I understood
that and I done that. All right. Now,
but remove the expectation on what
should happen.
Then recognize simply that if your
physical reality has not
transformed, it is still serving a
purpose. Look and see. Now recognize
also that your interactions, as you say,
opening your mouth in
public and allowing individuals to
interact on this idea of your focus with
your teeth can be one reason for why you
are maintaining it. For then that focus
is of service to them because they are
learning something about what you are
doing. Therefore many times individuals
will keep what they call a
disease for the purpose of being a
reflection that other individuals can
relate to and thus be served by.
Yeah. Now if you know that you can serve
the same purpose without the disease
then you will not need the
disease. If you get in touch with the
fact that the reason for why it is still
there is serving a purpose you will let
yourself see what that purpose is and
then can choose another way to fulfill
the purpose. Follow me. Yes. What do you
purpose. Follow me. Yes. What do you
imagine it to
be? But extend this idea beyond yourself
for you are being of service by being
here. Therefore, purposes can be simply
what you find other individuals relating
to you about this idea. I'll suggest
this during what you call your break
time. Discuss with whoever is willing to
discuss with you what they imagine this
discussion from you has done for them.
Then you might recognize what one of
those purposes is and begin to collect
more and more purposes that are being
done with different individuals from you
as a service which will then give you
the general idea of how deeply connected
you actually are in everything that you
do. What you do, what any individual
does is never
isolated to that individual alone. When
you search for well reason, purpose for
why this, why that, many times you only
think that it has to do with your
immediate understanding of yourself
rather than understandings of your
extensions of yourself that you can find
reflected in other individuals because
you are all other individuals and all
other individuals are you. That is true.
I've known that for a long, right? All
you need to do is act on that knowledge
rather than just simply keep the
knowledge to yourself. Well, my my
purpose cannot overcome theirs in an
interaction with their cooperation with
their then act upon this. If you know that is
then act upon this. If you know that is
the purpose, you do not have to
wait. You see, that is an expectation.
You are waiting for a physical sign
before you will be willing to act on the
knowledge of the purpose. You are
saying, "Well, they're not going to
believe me if my teeth are not the way
they should beh." Uh-huh. But who said
you can find a way to explain the idea
and by acting that out you may find that
with each individual you interact with
one more tooth will be all right. I see
I I now understand the exact as to my
belief within and without of this system
the star system. All right. Food for
thought. Yeah. that that uh I needed
only to to overcome that not the
affliction itself but but to stimulate
the and thus by acting acting since you
are physical acting on that knowledge
that is what will stimulate the
reflection of the growth in the
physiological form that reflects the
growth you are willing to act out in
your soul. Acting that growth out first
is what causes the physical reality to
react to you. I see. And the last my
last statement is that you are using and
everyone is using 100% of your brain.
You are using it in exactly the ways you
need to recognize that though your
science has said you are only using a
fraction. The idea that you are only
using a fraction comes from some other
part that they do not recognize that you
are using. Oh you are using it all. You are
using. Oh you are using it all. You are
complete in exactly the way you need to
be complete. You can change the idea of
yourself. Simply that. Again, the
willingness to act, the willingness to
change the idea of yourself by
acting will always allow everything in
your physical
reality to reflect that idea. Now
understand this. Your physiological
brain does physiologically change with
every thought you have. Every
thought you understand? Yes. Therefore,
the thought of yourself as you are
willing to be will put the brain into
the pattern to reflect that. If increase
into those glands is necessary, it will
be there. If it is not there at the time
it is not necessary for what you are
doing. Thus at any time you are always
complete for what you are doing. You
follow me? Yes. Like more of yourself
and more of yourself will be there
physically and spiritually.
I see. Thank you, sir. One
moment. Is it
I'm not clear how to put together the
idea. Yes. There's an ongoing process.
There seems to be a value placed on
at the same time we're perfect now. If
we're totally perfect now, why is there
any impetus to change? As I said, there
is growth. But at each stage of growth,
you are still perfect in the stage you
are at. The stage you are at is a perfect
at. The stage you are at is a perfect
representation of that stage of growth.
You follow me? I follow you. Does that
mean that there are there may be degrees
of growth but all is perfect for what it
is. It is like saying are there degrees
of
infinity? There is one
infinity. There is one perfection. There
is one all that is. All the growth that
takes place within it is is still taking
place within the perfection of all that
is. And so is perfect for whatever it is
doing because it represents one of the
ways all that is has of creating itself
to be perfectly in that idea. You follow
that? I think so. So for example uh
remove the idea of judgment and
invalidation from any experience and you
will understand that no matter who
creates and what they create the
experience they have created for the
idea they hold themselves to be is a
perfect reflection of what they think
they are and therefore it is equal to every
are and therefore it is equal to every
other idea he could choose to be.
Then if you know all ideas are equally
perfect, all ideas are equal, then it is
easy to make a choice as to which one
you prefer to live because you will not
have to fight something that is more
powerful than you, nor reach down for
something that is less than you. You
will not have to expend effort because
all choices will be on the same level.
If you know all choices are perfect,
then it is not a matter of judgment of
the choices you do not choose. It is
simply a matter of preferring what you
do choose, knowing that that represents
the idea, the perfect idea you have
chosen to
be. What sorts of the idea of who you
are. Anything is your choice. You are
the creator. You tell me. You make it
up. What do you prefer in any given moment?
What do you prefer in any given moment?
That is your reality. That is the idea
of your selection. You are the creator.
Understand what it means to be the
creator. You can do anything. Therefore,
you do because you can.
Okay. Does that clarify the idea? It
helped. Thank you. All right. You may
all take a short break.
break.
Hey, one moment.
All right, Rosie. Um, I would like to
thank you uh for last week you gave me
All right. Thank you for creating with
your imagination that activity of your energy
imagination that activity of your energy
field for yourself and I will thank you
for allowing me to reflect your own
knowledge to you. Oh, very good. Now,
since that was so successful, I'd like
to call it Now, since that was so
successful, and since I have just told
you that you did it, Uh-huh. what is
stopping you from applying the same
ability to these other things? Um,
nothing. Absolutely nothing myself. Did
you wait to talk to me before you even
considered doing that? No.
Have you applied yourself to this? Um,
yes, I'm in a quiet. You are turning off
that which does not represent your
reality. Ah, you are phasing into
another reality. Phasing out of that
one. Okay, follow your cycles. You are
creating them. That is a representation
of going with your flow. does not mean
that you have to consider the idea as a
judgment. Simply in this way, what you
are experiencing as boredom is simply
not allowing yourself to interact with
the portions of the event that exist on
the level of the reality to which you
are going. You are still assuming that
you have to relate to it in the same
way. Ah okay. And that dichotomy is what
leaves you hanging in between those two
ideas. I see. Okay. Understand this as
an energy being. Mhm. The idea of the
system physically in your body that
actually most closely represent the
energy balance of your
system is what you call your glandular
functions. Mhm. And as you in a sense
loosen up, you may find that your glandular
up, you may find that your glandular
systems may also loosen up a bit. And in
this way, the secretions of the
chemicals and enzymes that regulate the
flow of this energy balance may be more
freely given for a time
adaptation. As long as you still
consider yourself to be a physiological
being for you the symbol will occur in
that way.
Okay. Basically. Okay. Thank you very
much. Is simply the representation that
since you are now functioning more from
the idea of allowing the right
hemisphere of your brain to be equal to
the left. Then the idea of the left side
of your body is receiving a backlog.
Because the left side controlled by the
right is simply not used to functioning
with that degree of
freedom to resolve with the least amount
of bloodshed. Let me put it that way.
How to end the war or win the world.
First of all, transform out of the
idea that war exists in your reality at
all. Yeah. And then after doing that, I
will see a news report that there is
then you have not done
it. Now understand this. You have agreed
to perceive the idea of war in your
society. But for you, you yourself,
okay, you are not experiencing the idea
of war in your you have agreed simply to
perceive that it exists for other
individuals. Now, if you wish to assist,
to be of help, of service in this
way, then simply act like the being for
whom war does not exist in your reality.
regardless of whether you see it or not
act like you know that war can transform
into something else into peace and if I
do that instantaneous still I'll say can
be instantaneous it can be but it will
depend upon the degree to which you are
willing to believe
that now understand again you have made
a co-agreement with many individuals and
it will not serve them necessarily in
the way you want to serve them. If all
of a sudden you instantaneously do not
perceive war at all, all right, that is
all right, too. But then you will go on
about your business, never perceiving
that war exists. And then you will not
be able to serve those that still
perceive it does exist in the way you
have chosen to help them. So you will
hold on to the idea for now that
everyone is not going to instantaneously
perceive that war does not exist. But by
acting that way for yourself, you will
be granting them the opportunity to
choose to an offering that does the most
help. The offering in and of itself and
the offering without
expectation that they have to take it in
any certain way, shape or form for you
to still know in your heart of hearts
that for you war is not a reality.
And then without interaction with these
other individuals, it is interaction and
you can have interaction. But understand
that when you form interaction, you will
be forming interaction with the you that
does not contain the idea of war. Okay.
Then they will see in you that that is
possible. Oh, I see. Okay. Be a role
model. Yes. I've got another question.
Not weapons, not shields in this way.
recognize that that idea to some extent
can exist in different civilizations as
per the play the scenario they are
working out understand this in your
third density all right I'll put it
density all right I'll put it
pragmatically there is so little
understanding of what that they think
that they can invent something like a
psionic shield it is a direct
misunderstanding of everything that is
going on. The idea of utilizing psychic
abilities for what you call negative
purposes completely. Okay. What about a
psionic box being used to create
realities um using technology? There is
no such thing as influence unless there
are individuals who choose to believe
they can be influenced. Now there are
individuals who choose to believe that
and thus if they attract for themselves
a group of individuals who build
something that symbolically represents
those individuals ability to influence
someone else who is willing to be
influenced then that interaction can
happen. But it is something that is a
complete agreement and a total enactment
of what they both have agreed to believe
and has no power outside of that reality
to someone who does not contain the mass
belief system. Could the masses or the
mass consciousness have on a
subconscious level? Something like that
has been agreed to.
However, the rate at which that belief
is changing is such that it will be a
very fleeting effect. I see you now.
Yes. Okay. Good. Thank
you. Yes. I want to share something with
the group and walked a little too far and
group and walked a little too far and
was getting started to get well wasn't
really pretty good.
pretty good.
That's using your imagination and
letting it be real
and allowing the nature that is the
automatic creator that you are to serve
you in the way you created it to
I want to ask a question. Thank you very
much and you are very welcome
more than you.
Um some earlier session someone asked
you about but that is only an idea as it
relates to your consciousness.
Allow me now the opportunity to tell you
that that labeling is in all senses
truly meaningless, fourth, fifth, sixth,
particularly with respect to what you
are now asking. Who are you? Well, I was
about to ask you about in a sense in
that labeling third, fourth, and fifth
who hovered. No, me. That is only as I
relate to your density.
I'm on I'm the bodies a little bit more
accelerated a little bit more towards
what you would perceive to be fourth
density but made up of carbon and oxygen
and more also becoming because you are
moving into fourth
density have already discovered this
within sections of your brain there is
more to some
degree it it represents itself as a
communicator Well, okay. Yes. It
recognizes the 5 billion separate
individuals as little pieces and
fragments of themselves. Yes. Okay. That
is the overall what we began this
evening discussion with the overall
mentality of the gods that you are.
Okay. That is what you are perceiving as
this oneness of being of the planet
earth. Now does each planet in which
there's life like your planet for every
planet there is a planetary being for
every star there is a stellar beingness
for every individual there is individual
for every rock for every tree for every
atom there is consciousness because it
and then all of those is there then a
conglomerate a an entity a being that is
a conscious but all these are arbitrary
separations that are created out of your
being the creator because this is the
way you wish to look at it. This does
not mean they are the creator and what
you imagine is real. Thus, as you make
the labels, so the dimensions and
universes are created to reflect that
reality in your imagination and they
have their own vitality and they have
their own life and they have their own
self-awareness. Well, it here's another
point. It said that there that you have
created for this physical scenario and
according to this book within the time
frame structure you are creating that to
happen. There are still a few options as
to exactly how that can happen
physically. But what would be the
significance in in physical reality? The
significance is simply a product of the
idea that to create a physical universe
to begin with you have constructed the
concept of time cycle repetition. These
are all offshoots of the concept which
defines the dimension you find
yourselves in physical reality. Thus the
idea of that cyclical expansion and
contraction is only an offshoot and a
product and a result of the idea of time
itself because you think you exist in a
cycle of repetition. And so the universe
you recognize yourself as being in
reflects that repetitiveness. When you
ascend yourselves to the idea of fourth
density, you will begin to realize that
your universe is unending and infinite
in all aspects. And so it will become
and so shall your readings then show
you. Your readings now show you what you
believe they need to. As I said, you get
the results of yourself in the present
state is the way you see yourself and
thus the way you see your universe. What
you call facts, scientific facts are
always changing. There is no set course
in that way. And when you change the
idea of yourself, the idea of your
universe will reflect to you the new
facts. Oh well, now we have discovered
something new. did not see this before,
but well all of a sudden this one factor
was added and well it changes the whole
cure. Forget everything we said before.
I understand that what I'm what I'm
trying to put together for
myself there seems to be it is your
intention that this transformation is
reflective of you remembering more of
yourself and there are people that more
more particularly say you and I are the
same. This is what you are looking for.
They are all right. For each represent
one reality and the beings that vibrate
to that reality, for them that is their
truth. How they see the transformation.
The transformation is a
multi-dimensional thing. The different
points of view about what a
transformation is even in any local will
all be correct because they all come
from the perspective of the universe
that is seeing the transformation.
That is one way of saying it throughout
the all it is and that's why they are
responding to the but so what where is
your confusion? Well, I'm trying to
relate that reality. Okay. connections
to your particular universe in the way
they have described for themselves. So
in their universe, what they responded
to was the so-called cry for help. What
others from other universes respond to
is whatever they create their
relationship to you to leave. Yes. Okay,
I got that. But in the book
went through a a big upset 12,000 25,000
years ago and and the beings who were
the fragments of the planetary being of
Mars according to the raw people were
transported to Earth. Well, that's it
would seem to me is that now there's a
confusion between two planetary beings.
My question is there's a there's an idea
that is shared by some number of people
here that
earth that there's that that the um that
there's some kind of like the drain is
clogged like there's some kind of uh
knot or spiritual problem on earth which
doesn't exist on other places or other
loces or losi of the all that is. All
right. So, so I'm asking well there is
this idea can you respond to the idea
that earth is is particularly
um a particular type of problem that
it's going to be more difficult to us it
is not a problem for a problem is only a
situation that you will not allow to
change shape in this way we understand
what you mean the idea to us as we
perceive it is that yes you have created
the idea that you are blocked. The idea
that you are blocked exists and that is
what blocks you. To us the idea simply
is is that you are very intensely
focused on what? On the idea that you
are you are deeply deeply focused in
that idea. the idea that we're blood
that yes and many other things but the
overall sense of everything that
represents you you are very highly
focused on that that intensity of
focus is what is being interpreted in
many different ways as the block I see
you follow me there are no real in that
sense in your terms discrepancies
between all of the different
information. If you understand that they
are all sensing the same type of focus
of
concentration of limitation upon the
self, but they are interpreting it in
ways according to how different groups
specifically relate to your group. Okay.
Now, to to accelerate the transformation
here, it would be necessary for people
to start letting go of the idea that
we're exceptionally blocked. Yes. Okay.
as simple as that except that on an
individual basis, right? It doesn't seem
to be that simple because the person
is each person is believing that they're
blocked. Right? Merely walking up to
somebody and saying change your
mind historically doesn't seem to be
effective. This is true. But that is
because you cannot walk up to someone
and say change your mind and expect them
to change. The idea is that if you wish
to see anything in your world change,
you change
yourself and do not care whether they
change or not. By being who you know
yourself to be. By being the you you
want to be. That is how you show them
how to change. For then you set the
example that then exists in your world
to give them the opportunity to see that
such a thing is possible. If you simply
say go and
change, they do not see any change in
you. You are still being the same
judgmental person that all of them are.
Change yourself and you will see change
in others. Right? I understand. For then
you will only attract those that are
willing to share the reality you are
willing to be. I have two more
questions. People will bear with me. One
is I wanted your response to just a
comparison between the man we've known
or the entity the being the
consciousness who manifested himself as
we know as Mr. hovered relative to Jesus
of Nazareth being at fourth or fifth
density was hovered. How would hover be
described in similar terminology? You
see third, fourth,
fifth. Let me say
this, the idea stems from
another time track
altogether and is not so much the idea
of third, fourth, fifth. It is third in
a sense. Third, fourth. For third
fourth, fourth being the last density in
which you experience any dichotomy of
physical reality in that way at all.
Thus any idea of that nature is always
third fourth and from where it came from
it was in that way third
fourth in that sense.
Therefore recognize that the coming from
other systems, the parallel time tracks
to your time track brought with it all
the symbology from those other systems
that will require to fit into the
overall idea that would go into the
blending of what this civilization has
become in that way. Therefore, the
service that was provided was for
individuals in certain ways to get in
touch with certain portions of
themselves from those other systems that
they had not faced nor come to terms
with. And in this way, by recreating
some of those conditions on your planet,
allow the individuals then to reflect
and react to that in such a way that
they could then also for themselves
choose whether to exemplify some of
those conditions from the other system
or the conditions that represent what
this system's transformation is all
about. Let me see if I understand what
you just said. What I heard was
that in the same way that the raw entity
consciousness appeared physically on
Earth at some period of time as we
understand time. You're saying that
Hubard is that what we know of as Hubard
was a physical manifestation of certain
consciousnesses from other systems. You
all are. Understand this. In your terms,
there is no one here that is natural of
origin to this planet.
In your terms, no
one. You all in a sense are from
somewhere else. Well, but then what
about the star seed transmissions idea
that that everything on Earth is just
fragments of the planetary being because
that is the idea you have come here to
partake in. You form your origins in
each life. Each life has different
origins. And if any two of them have the
same origin, that is by agreement
because those two lives are being
connected in a specific way. Could you
amplify that again? Right. No, each life
has its own origins. Yes. You mean life
what we call lifetimes? Yes. The idea is
this. Every lifetime you create is unto
itself its own universe and it is
designed from scratch.
Therefore, the idea you wish to
exemplify will come complete with its
own kit of origins. If origins is some
idea that the lifetime is going to
examine or any other idea that that
lifetime's purpose is to examine, it
will come complete with whatever the
ingredients are that are necessary for
that particular manifested personality
to be the
personality the oversoul chose it to be.
Thus, each life can have in a sense a
different origin since you all we all
all all come from here and now. All
all come from here and now. All
universes are here and now. All planets
are here and now. All times are here and
now. The idea of
space, time, these are
illusions. They are definitions of
physical reality. And so you experience
the separation of time and space. But we
all came from right here and we all came
from right now. Anything else is simply
an arbitrary observation of specific
symbols that have been set up to allow
specific purposes and ideas to be acted out. But
purposes and ideas to be acted out. But
once that whole scenario is acted out,
wipe the board, create a new one. They
are all equal and different lives can
have different connections in that way.
Now, specifically with the idea of
parallel time tracks, just to be
specific in your terms for a
moment, recognize that you can have in a
sense a point of origin for each life
that can be the same. If the entire
series of one set of lives was created
from the purpose of one life somewhere
else, it can function that way. But it
does not have to. Say that again. You
can have all right picture this. Let us
say you have 300 lives on Earth. All
right? Then let us say you have 300 lives in
Then let us say you have 300 lives in
another star system. All right. Okay.
Now recognizing that there really is no
time, you can recognize that these two
things are going on simultaneously. Yes.
Right. All right. Now, and each of the
300 are going on sim. Yes. Okay. Now the
idea can be that the reason for the 300
lives here, the reason for why you have
as a being made 300 lives here can come
from one life of the 300 somewhere else
where that life upon its completion
decided that the idea that that life was
required 300 lives somewhere else to
finish its scenario. But that does not
necessarily connect up to all the other
lives which may have their own points of
origin or may have projections in other
systems. Okay, I got all it is all a
massive cross referencing system that
really goes all to the same spot here
and now. Now you use the word oversoul.
Yes. Where does that concept fit
into planetary being and the all that is
and well there are many different
interpretations of oversoul in your
terminology. You can have an oversoul
that has several lives in the same way
that you have a hand that has several
fingers. Okay? You can also have the
oversoul that has several oversouls that
have several lives. In the same way that
your body has two hands, each of which
have several fingers. You can carry the
concept on infinitely. So finally
finally it's the same. It's it's all
one. No, it's finally all one. But the
term oversold for example this entity
that the planetary being and star seed
transmissions is an oversoul for for all
of you for all of us but also there
would be some
intermediary between the planetary being
and things that we know of as human
beings. There would be some oversouls
that would be operating. All right. Yes.
You have made that diversification so to
speak. Yes. There are smaller versions
of the oversoul that filter down
ultimately into what you recognize as
the individualized entities upon your
planet. Right. One last question. It
occurred to me that Mr. Hubard uh was
being pursued for I mean tax evasion and
various lawsuits. It occurred to me that
it would serve many purposes if he were
officially dead, but that doesn't mean
that he did in fact drop his body.
Correct. And so I ask you, you may not
answer it. It occurred to me that
perhaps he really hasn't. He It occurred
to me that he may be continuing to
operate the same body. All right. and
that he just chose to become uh legally
dead for uh you know for various uh to
facilitate certain things. All right.
Then that is the reality that works for
you and I at this time because it is
such a quote unquote pertinent reality
for so many individuals cannot comment
further beyond that. Okay. Each
individual will create their version of
what they need to think and that is what
serves them at this
moment. And to me, as far as I am
concerned, they are all
real. For the idea of any individual,
including the individual you call
Hubard, exists in a million million
million probable
realities. And each and every one of you
define what your reality is. So to me
that is real. If someone gives me
another reality that concerns the
individual Hubard that is real too
because that is their universe. And
therefore in their universe if they
choose to believe the idea of the
individual Hubard as being physically
dead then in their universe it is.
Hubard is dead physically.
If in your universe Hubard is alive,
then he is literally truly really in
your universe alive. Right? And to I'll
say press the
point, you could potentially create on
your world the opportunity for you to
run into him and for the other
individual to see his dead
body. Though the two will probably not
meet because you are keeping your
universes separate so that they will
work for you. Now when you join the
paradox is when you begin to function
from the oversoul which contains all
paradox and thus does not see a
dichotomy in paradox.
So, it is potentially also possible that
you could see both a living hubard and a
dead one at the same
time when you choose to
overlap and agree to share those
particular elements from your reality to
the other individual's reality.
And of course, Hubards,
you follow me? Yes, I do. It is all
real. Really?
Sure. Thanks. Yes. You're welcome. Yes.
I'm next. Uh my name is Freddy. I
brought a lady with me and
um the question that we would like to
ask is uh what can be done to handle a
uh physical problem of the pancreas? Uh
a physical what? You know what diabetes
is? Yes. Yeah. But it is not to me a
problem. Oh, if you allow to be a
situation, then perhaps it can change.
Problems to you do not change. They are
difficult to make go away. Well, I kind
of like it as a problem. Oh, all right.
Because then it challenge my
capabilities as a ghost. And if you wish
to create the idea that you need to be
challenged, then that is why you are
doing it. Well, yeah. I'll But you do
not have to be challenged. No. Creation
is effortless. Yeah. You do it all the
time. Yeah, even in the creation of a
challenge. Yeah. Well, she's got this
problem. See, and uh I want it to be
gone because I say so, and she wants it
be to be gone because she says so. All
right. What can we do to make it be gone
and have it become a reality? In fact,
believe that it is gone. And
um okay. Now, uh will the physical body
uh uh uh accept that reality? And if you
believe Yeah. that it is. Well, and if
she stops taking insulin in the next uh
few days, uh the problem should be gone.
Huh. Is that right? There is no should.
If she believes it is gone, Yeah. and
she stops taking the insulin and it is
gone. Yeah. Then it is gone. If she
stops taking the insulin and it is not
gone, then she does not believe it is
gone. Oh, your physical reality, pay
attention, your physical reality is
always, always,
always an obvious obvious obvious
reflection of what you believe it should
be. Therefore, whatever is happening,
Therefore, whatever is happening,
whether you think it should or not, is a
reflection of what you believe about it.
Thus, if you do in fact change the
belief itself, the physical reality must
reflect that change. Must. It has no
choice. If however you take the step
with trepidation with doubt then you are
not believing
trust as I said is unconditional unconditional
unconditional.
Now one of the challenges you have
created upon your planet is to have
difficulty experiencing
unconditionality. So be true to your belief
So be true to your belief
system. If you feel you can love
yourself unconditionally and in no uncertain
unconditionally and in no uncertain
terms without a shred of
doubt, tell your soul to reflect to you
a body that does not need that situation
anymore. It will.
That simple. If you believe it, I see it
is done. Then it is that simple. It is
done. Yes. Thank you. Uh uh uh. Who is
the being that stands behind me? [Applause]
Now, for what it is worth to you at this
time, my perception is that it is a very
loving female
energy. My perception again for what it
is worth to you is that the hand so to
speak of this entity rests upon your
shoulder quite
often. I perceive it to be your right
shoulder, but that's my perception.
That's correct.
This energy of love and guidance in a
sense is something that lets you
know that that
love is always there, never cut off,
never lost.
that the idea of love is something which
allows you to know that communication
from consciousness to consciousness is
always ongoing forever and ever and
ever. No matter what another individual
may decide to do as an
entity, the agreement you have made with
them for that portion of their
consciousness to remain with you always
will if that is what you wish.
Now again for whatever it symbolizes to
you, my perception
specifically is that the hand that rests
upon your shoulder has approximately at
this position
uh what you call and again this is a
symbol but it does represent what we
perceive of the
energy a sleeve so to speak that ends in
lace.
Yes, she's a lady with red hair. Or is
it brown? We did not get that far. Okay,
we were concentrating on the image of
the arm and the hand and the lace. I
see.
Now I perceive that there may or may
not of this it is not clear for this is
in motion and not stable. May or may not
be a small
ring on that
hand but I do not perceive that that may
or may not be of any
consequence. It might be a connection to
someone else and maybe not specifically
to you. What is her name and in what
lifetime was did I know her as a real
person?
At this point for us this becomes
nebulous for we feel we are stepping
into the middle of a process. However, I
will give you what the energy is to me
as a name which may not be valid for
you. For me, the energy is
Margaret. But that is for
me. I see. And she loves me. Is this it?
Is that true? Yes. I see.
There was a man or a male energy that
would stand behind me and he would not
give his name or who he was and he would
I asked another another psychic. Yes,
him. Who is
that? Again, my perception at this time
is that it is you.
It is a portion of yourself that you
have yet to meet. I see. and I refuse to
give my name. So I I seem to be a
duality here then that I stand behind
myself to see what I'm doing and within
myself physically
as in a mirror or a reflection. Yes. And
you have both the duality of the male
and female energies,
right? And when you marry
them, you will be able to talk with
them. They will be able to talk with
each other. I have tried to do this and
try I have attempted to same thing.
Relax. Uhhuh. There is no need to try.
There is no need to attempt.
Well, I seek a merger with the male and
the female energy. All right. Then as we
said before, first of all, simply assume
that it is already blended. And in
whatever way your life proceeds, assume
that what you have in your life is a
product of that blending. then you will
see how it is a product of that
blending. If you assume that it is not
yet blended, then you will perceive the
things in your life to be a product of
the separation and still assume that you
need to blend
them. Assume they are blended and assume
that no matter whatever happens in your
life is a product of that blending and
then you will begin to get into the
habit of seeing how that is. So then the
being that stands behind me is me to
marry the the the woman who stands
behind me is she part of me as well in a
sense although we do perceive that there
is other in your terms consciousness
involved with her as well I see in terms
of what you would think of as a
separated being to some extent but what
you are perceiving is that entity's
assistance to allow you to perceive your
own femininity and know that you are
male and female blended as one right
now. I see this is true, but I have not been
I see this is true, but I have not been
able to fully realize this. Then simply
act like you have. Well, the phenomenon
that should occur has not occurred. The
phenomenon is because you have assumed
that you have in specific ways and you
are assuming that what occurs in your
life needs to be a reflection in a very
specific way or you will not accept that
the blending has occurred. You are
putting expectation on what is in your
life. If it does not occur in the way I
think it should, it does not reflect the
blending already being there. You are
looking for
specifics. Know that it has occurred.
Understand this.
There is no such thing as an
interruption in your life. Everything
that is in your life is the product of
the unfoldment of the path you chose to
be. The only reason you may or may not
recognize this depends upon how you
choose to look at what happens in your
life. It is only a matter of
perspective. If you choose to believe
that what happens in your life is the
product of the blended energy, then your
life will begin to reflect that without
expecting that it should reflect it in a
way you think it should. Your ego thinks
it should. Let your knowing self reflect
it in the way your knowing self knows it
needs to. Assume that you know what you
are doing and you will begin to allow
your life to become the ecstatic
explosion of coincidence that will begin
in no uncertain terms and very clearly
and clairvoyantly and obviously begin to
be a reflection of that sureess that the
blending is already
there. If you still think that the
things that occur in your life do not
reflect that, then you will only perceive the
that, then you will only perceive the
aspects of those events that reflect
your belief in your still existent
separation of those
energies. Both things are always there.
Both in any event, both polarities are
always there. The way you really want to
see it that reflects the blending and
the way that you want to see it that
reflects the separation. Both are there.
And both are offered to you
simultaneously in every event that
occurs in your life. It is up to you to
choose how you wish to look at it. If
you choose to look at the events as the
product of the blending, you will see
them as such. If you choose to look at
the event as the product of the
separation, you will see them as
such. It is only and always a matter of
how you choose to look at things. your
perspective on life, your
selfimage. Do you follow me? Yes, I
follow you quite well. The the the only
possible aspect I do not totally
understand is yes, I can understand the
marriage of the male and the female and
yet there is this woman who has her hand
on my shoulder. I I don't understand how
she would be part of the blending.
Simply for now. Yes. Allow me to suggest
it would be of best service to you to
forget the symbols.
Male, female, and the third lady. Third
person lady on my shoulder. Do not
continue to separate them into distinct
entities. Make them all one. Yes. All
married. Yes. All mine. Yes. All me.
Yes. Completely. Yes. Within and
without. Yes. Done. Thank you.
Now, now just sit back, relax, and watch
your physical reality begin to reflect
that knowledge. It is happening. Thank
you. Thank you. Yes. Okay.
You're next. Okay. Um, you talked about
Okay. You said everyone has lives like
in other planetary systems. Is everyone
on earth or in other systems of reality?
Continue. Okay. Uh yet you've said that
some of some who feel um certain
physical things like sinus um situation
that feels uncomfortable at times.
You've said um I can't remember the
exact word you use. All right. The
symbol you are referring to reflects a
certain attitude toward the connection.
a certain awareness certain a certain
attitude within the awareness
that is all that is the only reason it
is different from one individual to
another. Now in terms of your
literalness in terms of what you
recognize as literal physical lives. No,
not everyone has a life in every system.
But potentially and therefore to the all
that is that you are really you do for
you are everything in the universe. All
right. But
physically you can have created an
attitude in this life from physically
having a life in another system. You can
have that life and not have the attitude
and not have the symptoms or you can
have the life have the attitude and have
the symptoms. It is up to you. Okay. You
symptoms. It is up to you. Okay. You
know what about um the there's a book uh
called star people. Nice. Okay. And it
goes that is simply a compilation of a
recognition that there are a grouping of
people that have chosen to have the
specific type of attitude about the
creation of their connection to other
idea systems because they have chosen to
exemplify it that way upon your planet
to be of service in a certain way.
Perhaps if only to recognize each other.
Okay. And and so the quote star people
have do have lives on other in other
planetary systems. Is that what makes
them star people? Okay. Okay. But you
are all star people. Right. Right. Yeah.
Yeah. Cuz at the end of the book it
says, you know, if you want to become a
star person. Now it's like I also mean
that quite literally. You are the stars.
Mhm. You follow me? Mhm. Yeah, because
because you they can we can start
causing more separation within ourselves
if we if if I were to uh um make
separations between well this person you
know comes from here and this person
comes from I mean it doesn't have to be
that way but I guess I recognize that
part of myself that could do that cause
separation with those different All
right. That is one of the ideas you
chose to experience by being here.
H okay. Thank you. Yes, Bashar. Uh since
talking with you last week, uh one of
the men that was here gave me a a
thumbnail sketch of I guess the
propulsion or quasi propulsional system
you uh your race uses to uh go through
time space. I was wondering if you could
like briefly describe uh the ideas
behind your system and possibly describe
some elementary experiments we might do
here so that we might develop a system.
or I have already done so but I will be
brief for you. Do not be sorry. Okay, no
need to
apologize. Understand that it is based
upon the idea that location is not
something an object exists within.
Location is also a property of the
object. Change the idea of its location
and it must by definition take up
residence somewhere else. This is the
principle. Your universe is holographic.
That is the potential for every object
exists equally everywhere in the
universe to exist. You
follow? Now light
itself is the medium of
energy and it is in our mechanical terms
altered through the process of what you
call rotational bodies. Because the idea
of imparting rotation, spin to a
body distorts and alters the energy in
very specific ways that reflect the idea
of the cyclical nature of this
particular universe and many universes.
Therefore, what you call a
conductor in your metallic terms such as
your copper in dis
form approximately 6 in across
approximately 1/4 of your inch thick
made to rotate 2 and 1/3 times the
number of your planetary rotation, what
you would call 2300 revolutions per
minute. and surrounded by field of
electromagnets will be one of the first
things you can do to experiment with the
idea of how rotational conductors
channel the electromagnetic field of
your planet through them in different
ways. Take your measurements, take your
readings, see how the field is
distorted, see what effects you get.
Mhm. Okay. Thank you. Thank you. Can I
ask you one more question, please? Okay.
Please bear with me. Uh I am enjoying
this immensely. This does not require
patience on my part.
Uh recently some medical inventors have
come up with a a device that produces a
frequency that enables the brain to
release what are called beta endorphins.
Nice. Natural painkillers that the body
produces. Uh taking that a step further,
are there other frequencies that that
can be produced say artificially or
mechanically that can healing? Now
understand that your physical medicinal
science is beginning to move into a
phase where it will understand that the
treatment of anything in the body can be
done if it is to be done physically at
all through the brain. Everything. Okay.
And simply because everything is a
vibration is a frequency. They have the
entire spectrum of your existence to
play around with. Wonderful. They will
discover that certain ideas in your body
will respond to certain
tones that you recreate in the brain
mental frequency field in your body. Now
does not even have to enter the physical
brain. You have an oric field, an energy
field. A vibration even in the field if
you simply let yourself go with it will
align the entire field including energy
and physical and you will simply redefine
physical and you will simply redefine
the idea that you are with that tone.
You will be saying all
right you are acting as a C flat. Now
here is the
C. That is the idea that you are all
right. I will now align with the C. All
right. Now you are whole.
You follow me? Sure. Oh, is it is it
that simple or? Yes. But it requires
once again like anything else the belief
and the trust that that is real and
not discount your imagination. Is
research going that way? Yes. Oh, okay.
Tonality, vibrational energy,
electromagnetism. Understand that your
electric fluid, so to speak, has
already been noticed to allow there to
be regeneration in certain portions of
your body that you previously did not
think could
regenerate. You follow me? Mhm. You are
beginning to understand that you are an
electric being. You are a being of
light.
Okay. Thank you very much.
briefly. There is not much time in your
terms of time left for this discussion.
All right.
Oh. Um, I wanted to ask you about
something that happened not too long
ago. I um I had seen a hat that I I saw
one wearing a hat and I thought very
lightly, you know, I really like that
and I'd like to have a new hat. Nice.
And then later that night these two
beings and got in, you know, contact
with me and I had a little conversation
with them and they asked and basically
they told me that I should go to Peru.
All right. Then the next day I came home
from work. Nice. And there was this hat
on my table. Nice. And it was from
Nordstrom. It was very expensive and
really beautiful. And there was a a
little note inside the hat. It said to
you from Jesus and me. Sign the wiz. All
right. And I asked my dad where it came
from and he said, "Well, he was walking
over to the park and a delivery truck
drove by and the box dropped out." Yes.
So he picked it up and he brought it
home to me. Right. The ecstatic
explosion of coincidence in full
function. I said it's my hat. Yes. And um
I said it's my hat. Yes. And um
understand that what you have previously
considered to be the impossible can be
your everyday life.
This is how life
works. This is how life works.
Everything in it is your
sculpture. Every physical
object, every
interaction, every concept, every
situation, it is all reflective of what
you are willing to be. Willing to know
that you are connected to everything
that you need to be connected to will
always allow the lines of communication
to be open. Thus, those ideas that
represent the idea you are willing to be
will always be there in your physical
reality to reflect that to you through
what you have previously termed the most
unlikely circumstances. Oh, that could
never happen. Not in real life,
but it does.
Well, I was wondering like is there a
relationship between this hat and this
going to Peru?
Are you paying attention to anything I
am saying?
Then why would you ask that question
when I have just told you that there are
no accidents
when everything is connected and what
you perceive as your symbols no matter
how you perceive them are only there
because you have created them to be and
if you did not create it for a reason
you would never have even heard of Peru.
Follow me. If you hear it in your
reality, it resonates in you. Act on it
in whatever way feels right to you. Do
not judge or invalidate or limit
yourself. Now understand that this
doesn't always mean that once you begin
to act on something that it will of
necessity always act all the way through
in the sense that you might actually
physically wind up in Peru although you
might. But simply the willingness to
know that there is a connection because
that is your obvious
reality will allow you to begin to act
on that idea. And then you will then
allow the idea to change in whatever way
it needs to continue to change to
continue to lead you where you have
chosen to
go. You follow me? Yeah. Yeah.
All right. Then simply act on the idea
of Peru in whatever way suits you. If it
is enough for you to go to a book and
look at the country of Peru, do so. That
is still going to Peru. There's also a
restaurant called Peru. Very good. If
you go there, perhaps you will find
someone wearing a similar hat.
Maybe there has been someone you need to
know. Oh, what a coincidence.
Well, where did you get it? Well, it
fell off
of say, what do you do for a living?
Well, I do this. Well, I have been
looking for someone to do that. I have
been looking for someone who is looking
for someone to do that. This is the way
life works if you let it. You do not
have to make any of this happen. You
have but to allow it to happen. Now end
of
question. I will ask you a question all
of you.
What would be your immediate, let us
say, gut
reaction if I were to share with you the
information that this is the last time I
will speak with you
disappointment. Now,
let that it is not the last time. Let that
that it is not the last time. Let that
however that moment now let that be an
accurate reflection of how much you
really believe you can do it
yourselves. Now look at
yourselves. Let that be a reflection to
how willing you are to know that you
have all the
answers. That is why you have created
these habits because you are only
willing that much.
be willing all the
way and then you will be connected to me
to everyone
instantaneously. No one will ever be
separated from you anywhere, no matter
how far, no matter when, because time
and space are your illusions that cause
the separation to seem to be real.
Thank you for allowing me to reflect
your degree of willingness to be
yourselves. If you find that you prefer
to be a little bit more of yourselves,
by all means do so, for you do not need
me because you have
you. And when you have you, I can then
share with you equally.
We can still chat once in a while,
couldn't we?
That is correct. Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you. Our unconditional
love to you all. To you all very
exciting dream lives. And we bid you
good night.
That was great. Absolutely. Thanks very
much, Darl. Thank you.
Thank you all for being here.
Anyone who would like a tape of
tonight's uh session, you can have it
tonight within the next uh 10 10 minutes
or so. Okay. Important announcement
before anyone leaves, before anyone
talks, put some intention in it. Yeah.
Okay. Listen up. February 14th and 15th
is the event of the month, if not the
year. It's going to be the channeling
with Bashar and Leah. For those of you
who don't have tickets, we have tickets
here tonight. It's called the
information concert. It's going to be
very special and it's going to be on the
power of love. There's also dancing
there. There's also crystal sculptures
and crystal shows there of worth about
$30,000 to the crystals being showed
there and