that each time you
life The discussion Sharing of All The
IDE that all you to begin recn that
you are in in and creating your Reality
that you do have conscious ability
conscious Choice to Create The Reality
You prefer and des
asther such A willingness to allow those
abili those self abili each and One of
you to Come To aaren Come to you Add The
Over momentum of civ and
and by gec
As You find at this Time The
oll IDE Gathering of
momentum That ur s of years AG As
AS am conne
am conne
are between
Society represent that is On A level but
also the forming to all the different
Levels of each member of your Society
has increased to the Point
Now Where compare As you say to 10 years AG
The Rate is As
Follow each and
Every Day am
am
Con that usually years AG
that How ACC you have are
People to All you to the Idea You Know is
For You and to All Every
indiv also are the Idea that is for them
More and More coci More and
More And you are beginning to recognize
that you do not have to  make life work
you do not have to Force Life to Work
But you can allow it to Work by Simply
allowing Yourself to understand that If
Everything is
synchronicity which is the cognition
that Every Single Event occurs For a
reason that Nothing is an accident and
that all events are in This Way
different views of an overall Matrix
All Now The ones you Experience The
succession of events the causes the
Effects The linear aspects of the events
of All The events that are
simultaneously occurring that you Experience
As Your are the ones that are
representative of the frequency you are
on the Idea that you  know be for you
allows to exp particular pattern of the Out
All events That could happen
in This Way The More each and One
of you knows that you are creating your
Reality by Simply being A certain
vibration by acting like an Idea You
Know is exciting For You and therefore
and As More you are your
willingness to trust the
mechanism you Call Trust
allows specific patterns of events to
man in your physical Out all the events
that do simultaneous because you are of
a synchronous harmonious vibration with the
Idea that Everything In Your Life Is there
For a reason and therefore  have a
positive attitude towards fundamentally
neutral situations you then Color all
events in  a positive Way and only
perceive A change of positive events in
Life The willingness you have expressed
Up to This
Point has allow there to be the degree
of acceleration Now that we have Just
defined is
and in our perception
and only continue Grow you All
takee And I have been very scrupulous in
conducting Myself In A diplomacy and
and
disc I hav well Right need
Right need
and i
to All to PR keeping with somebody
Who I'm
wondering I Service to But if you know have What happy I
was also about other conne I
Might had seem so  spontane that begin
With Me In way I was there
A different conne or something like that
perception in a Is there is
we will let you Discover Some of The
ramifications First before We discuss
Fur Thank you was EX We
Add turned was a
360e in
All with
with
understand I have att
toed that perception
you Think it has May I Ask
you a May I Ask All of you a
When you Create A syb for Yourself
that you are in touch with to being that
you are Why do you seek so hard After The
syb rather Taking The Over in am Do you that
Always Yes IE
I did not
was But I Asking is exping [applause] Work
3as I you are saying from a that do [music] inou
would Get much done inal Accept i didn't
abil to in
to in
diens ability also ISIC [music]
Right have you used your Imagination Yes
and the
Imagination definitely develops My Imagination is
very good in my
estimation Right however I have not been
able to reproduce that Experience have
you asked Yourself What purpose it
serves to reproduce
it No a good [music]
A Go If You will all right Do you Think gos is
no Right Can you live in the [music]
[music]
it Keep in Communication With My fellow hum
rather being iden AS VI Now
Let Can you in your Imagination Create
The scenario Where You can have that
Sensation and at the time know that you
can Still Fun Yes eas
all then in that Way Rec
you Asking to Look atal reasons Might
val not having that is not all
right able comm I was anw have Might El so [music] alls V
I Only Ask you that  to on
Another As
You Rec The Experience Do you have even
A
slight of the
Feeling Yes all right course Is only AE
of magn that you have theil to that
Feeling The
you are sugg a magnitude ofer
From All to
in the magnet you are capable of
creating any given to expand by allowing
Yourself to continue to Rec that Feeling
until like a dream You are imed in it I
Shall Work Let
What to call the recalling of the Event
As you say in your Language Get into it
Going on all right  Feel The vibration
you Wish to Rec at The Same Time
realizing that As You Are Feeling it you
are recalling It is being created in the
Present As You Are recalling it
Attention shifts to Elements that were
not Present in the Original
Experience effort
to Thank you very good
then while you are Rec
inam do not exude any New Event
incl include The New Idea of ​​the effort
incl then it Will Be thank
you effort you We Will Be very exc
to hear of your of course How could you
[music] about
about
syon  conscious S that I know Myself by
Still experiences things that I don't
want  to
Experience so even though I know It's synchronized
But that is a judgment UM
let me FR The question all right UM
Some of the best things that Ever
happened to me seem like disasters at
the time in other Words If I got fired
from a Job I thought With My conscious
knowing that was The worst Thing that
could happen to me however Looking Back
I was very glad that it happened Because
I was Still being stuck in that I can
Look Back and Say my Real knew What it was
doing so does that give you an
Opportunity  to recognize that any other such
events that seem to Carry The Same
characteristics can be looked at that
Way Now rather than having to wait to
Look at them in retrospect well It's
beginning to Catch Up occasionally I
have flashes that What is happening is
exactly what I want to And I feel very
Happy about that so i seem to be
catching with What I think is my that
One can use in Order to Catch with that
Real Is It Just an acceptance
without Self judgment of What Is happening there are
Many exercises you can Create are exes that
can  be
SU ones that will be to Will come from
your own  Imagination Because that Is that
We sugg be altered Imagination
toit
can asle ases are Trust
simp Can you tell
mech People any Are [music] inte People
People and integrity Now in This Way if
you are referring to the Idea of ​​What
you Call qu
deceiving that is quite Another matter
but the Idea of ​​Let us say truly selling
Someone on something is being telepathic
in a Sense whether consciously or
unconsciously cognizant of a vibrational
Idea that that Person is attracted To and
being A syb vibration
Mat so that they see Within The Symbol that
The Person is selling a Connection
to something with them that they can use
The syb to allow them to understand More
of them I understand I know some people
not People they Believe
100% thate
Symbol that is what We are saying the
Symbol can Have Many meanings therefore
to a Person to whom excitement is the
selling the
Communication it rarely matters What the
Symbol is Because It is Only A Symbol
For The Action of the interaction between and
that
Up in a Sense they are becoming involved
in the actual Communication and
therefore accepting Whatever Symbol
Comes  with it To receive The
Communication Because It is the Communication
that has served them and
This Symbol is And
I One It
's a Little Bit different The Child
was brought Up Let say his mother and
father didn't Give Him a lot of love
later On in Life he wants to rei that
Feeling I mean having Love so he has to
use his Imagination to get that Love
Right But Why would He Believe his Imagination
If He doesn't have The Experience any Experience Behind The Imagination
Why would there be
Many individuals Who Don't
well How How would you use your Imagination exp Imagination exp
you
Idea of ​​Love is to exp have stepen
Because they are even
aare exp
that imation they are able to even
All to know conceiving
it conceiving It is
and All to do is like What They have
conceived of is Real Because you can
Only conceive What you you
in let you have conception This is I would like to be
you Follow me Yes in
Order to have that conception you must
already be that type of
Person Because you can Only What
vibratory Reality you already Exist
upon to even have  IDE means thate
VI  acting like you know that Because you
have The Concept you must be that vibration acting
Like You are already that
Person acting As if you already had
that Idea is what Will Remove it From
the potential State Into the
real You Know perhaps let me Put it This
Way You Create This soc discrepancy in
Stat of being that Says all right This is
something I want to be But I am not
that Yet you Follow me Yes Now The
Simple question which you can reflect to
Yourself is well If I Were that How would
I Be acting differently than I am
acting Now  then Act that Way if you find there is
a difference that is it You Me
Yeah in other
Words A Person in a Sense Now This May
be in a Sense What you Might Call an Over
the Idea Is that A knows they are AB
and believes that by acting
so will
not read a Book on how to get
Rich so Reading that Book would not be
acting like a Rich
Person you Ask Yourself If I Were abund
How would I Be acting As A
Person be
I differ number one that
can When you Start acting Like You
Believe You  don't Believe really
that Look Experience  and there you Start
acting like it But All Don't Believe
that then you are not truly acting like
it The belief is Part of acting like it
Yes I know You're not truly acting like
it But I'm Asking What would get you to
Act like it When you Keep on having the
belief that You're really not that
Person once again
difficult RE to that you can like
Why not Turn like
not per that have that Wo
n't make a differ How You Believe
then Why not Believe It Because then What
you call the od  are Le
in Because Le If that will happen
and on I [laughter]
[laughter]
cation that ied very situation has ur
Yet I was The Idea
of ​​that situation And
situation And
I TR
Days This has ched
and Why do BR Pay Attention
You will Bring Yourself to the
brink of the symbolic representation
of manifesting What you Visual But then it Wo
n't completely manifest Because You don't
need it to Because you are already
On Your way to the Next
level Because You really don't want to
Stop and have to the whole Out Because
you are  To Go On
So You find Yourself skipping like a
Stone almost having Did Go having Where
Did It Go almost Where Did It Go
But at Every Step recognizing well Wait A
minut I am getting More connected to things
More things are happening More
synchronicity is Going on But it
before you can Go On
Now that is One of the things that
you will find to be a density As that
will First it
was however you also determined The Idea
of ​​man in was not spacecraft
The Idea you
bons Oh Yes Black
balloons [applause
] do that
they were The that would UN But also
But also
also  physic chn
outs recn that you do have The ability
to discern something unusual From
something that you normally see regard
of What so that The
Idea of ​​individuals Who do things that are
Yes you upic equ
andou on the is Trust Okay I Get into
situation sometimes Where What you Just
shared happens and things are Going
really well and then something happens
and Set Off And I go Why did that happen
an Example was I lost my Keys to
my car and it cost me 0 to get Home When
I was Magic Mountain on Saturday And I
didn't  really have
Money Maybe You  don't need
Money May You will have it El May
Opportunity to recn that you are As You Need to recn that ination
you The Money
that was on Hand you May
not to for
you are there as we Just Said you have
already surpassed it did you not have
The Money you needed For The First
situation then that was The product of
your Trust unconscious at first perhaps
But Now was your Opportunity to recn that you The Trust
Never So You had What
you needed Now unc now you
are giving Yourself
Opportunity to  recn you have Trust asic
demonstrated Yourself by having the
Money you needed for the situation that
ur Now All you Need to do is Trust that
you will have Whatever else You Need
Whatever other sit occ in the [music ] you
are What sit What wasp
sit Place
you could have been Stranded without The
Money then you would not have been able
to get into and have Access to the
vehicle
that But you Always have Access to the
vehicle that Moves Because The vehicle
that Moves is you recn
VES Always have some Way of attracting
the abundance or having The abundance on
Hand that is necessary to  have Access to
anything you des so that you can Keep
Moving I believe that I really do and
and What was Inter Is that and
Money But you not need Money
If You Need Money For The sit
Money be
there Money isn't there You don't need
Money recn for each and indiv Society
you begin to Explore The Idea expansion of
your abundance
Money are other
able to do What you Need to do you Need to do
that can Come In The form of aade
well Why ins that has to Why Let Come
can Come form
per having serv  perform for
you can be given
Okay are
Ways Let Come eas Money Turn Out to be
the easiest way then Money Will AR
before All the other
Ways But If Money is not the quickest
way something happ Let happ Let It
happen Trust that Whatever Needs to
be there for you to the Idea you know you are Will Be there
Because the
Universe does not Create Incomplete
ideas Every Idea Comes Complete with all
the ingredients necessary For The that
How do we know
that I know you said it many
times You Know It by doing it and then
discovering that It is True  for you
Words again We know The you have
cre however All we  can Tell you to that
Work Turn thee [music] even
even
Van I Speak Up Speak Up situation
there seems to affect my physical Health
Right I feel that have You communicated
this to the indiv Yes
and She is very defensive andes to Smoke
About A Pack A Day
Right Can you att I don't
know can moved I was moved
canve well our People mov Next them
and Work you are could
May The Company could Move I don't know Move The Why
The Why
Why not explain The situation in
Clear term without accusation without
jud expl The situation in Clear terms
expressing your Point Might What happ it Might be
any I go there's any are you Might exp
exp
that What you Think Might happen
Because that is not situation
What Might happen is not What is go with
What is I
could Non you could also Simply exp the
situation In way Go ahe I would to do
you can that per
to do you that you are in
owners yes yes are
Think things Come
But things
you are owners that From
Someone else you are crea you are agreeing to
else you are crea you are agreeing to
Create your version of that  in
exp have exp have
Age have AG
Age that you
Create  ine and
in We Are Not talking about Idea of
trying to Keep something away We Are
talking about
defers So a vibration that does not
contain vibration of
Idea can
Can you your Imagination again isy lally
to allers can Can
you Right Now in Imagination Can
you enis
enis
Surround are alling
canr and can your Ever exp
Ever exp
All Ever expen are product imation
Add The
imagina of
solidity that Makes it seem As If It is
Outside you But It is not It is all From Within
so allow Yourself to become
excited about The  Idea of ​​the Vision you
are your to Real cloke
cloke
and excit about Vision Okay Let It Be
Real For You breathe deeply of the Idea
of ​​your at All and the Only atmos You
will be breathing is the one you pref to bree
I feel that I really need To
Go ahad But do not Make It A TAS that Takes
effort well do EX Yourself
Yourself
to with All of
Yourself And then you will be
comfortable with All of your and that
means all of that
other individuals refle Back to
you that any
Yourself that you Ever
Encounter in
SY Thank you [music]
and IDE physical
exper He was
All there is sure
Is only the
sensing the Most
prob Man Reality that has The highest Dee of
Man Reality that has The highest Dee of
belief
Energy at the time The prediction hearing
The prediction Just being Made
aware that that particular scenario has
A High degree of Energy Behind it can
alter The Energy Because now you are
aware of It and if you find that You don't prefer The
scenario can use pring El that is
Where you willi ener so
The prediction No
longer Now The Idea of ​​the predictions
so that do  Come To can
in S IDE you do
How Far Down the road They have been pred
But is always indicating the Energy that EX
at the time The prediction is
Made not of anything in the Future
Because The Future does not EX in the
Future The Future EX in Present As EX
in Yes Destiny is
the Free Will
but the Free Will of the conscious expr
in only the Most
generales General term General
General conglomerate events
experiences expen istiny
The Higher consciousness has determined
that your so Destiny As A physical being As
physical fragment of the Higher  Of
The Over is to Experience themes or
events Under  The title of the them of
exploring
abundance posi neely Quick slowly so on
and so that Is Up to you you Always fre in
so that Is Up to you you Always fre in
What the
is
to
let ones are Riding [music]
does that ass
in Yes that istiny and Karma are they
The Oh Yes and to AE Alla is
Self and again The Idea of ​​kation
aum IDE Balan in in
cany the
Idea of ​​recn that you are at All
Times in Complete Control As to How You Experience even
in other EX Let use Ex You M Someone in
your Last Life now you are in the New
Life Let say believing that you have to
Live out the Karma in a negative Way
Can't Create A scenario For You that you attract
Yourself In which You find
Yourself murdered however recognizing
thata exance
Idea perhaps can Rec
per Will serv some
murder Mind M that can [music can [music
] would All
would All
People All them But Many physics are
also Times you can always have
New Family And you
can older ones to else exp in
other Oh Yes you can as we are not Absolute can
agre This  association serve purpose
New so Will asar As Someone has been
with  in thousands Because thee
agre that New
you maying out the
tion so that you can form Let A Balance
with Yourself before you allow Yourself
recn that you yourself are of All integrated relation relation Are For
Are For
Reason When you allow The relation to be
there For The reason Is there and not
Put on What you Think The relation should be
then you will allow to get Out
Service You Need And recn of serv been provided you
about if you want A relation And you do not have a relation is
it Because maybe you too much
Always follow you talking  about We
understand We Understand
Let From
Zero you Always have relation Because relationships are What
you are they Are
Not tru things you have they are What you are you are
relationships Idea can be that you find
your inal [music
] need relation Order
Order
to In way if you feel you Need relation
inorder to Complete You will either More
often not attract a relation a being
that your belief in your own Inc or No
One AT all tole the IDE Inc
When you know you are Complete then
You and att into All
beings IDE [music]
[music]
each other  in Order to Feel Complete So
You Are More than Open to each  other I Feel the
Feel the
strong you May be picking Up on your But
May I you that by Definition
May Ask you
a have
Ever Where After having experienced A
timing After having expen somet  hing
coming into Your
Life whether or not has physically happen
We know you can This in your
Imagination understanding of It When
Something ur in Life And
you If it had urer samee
Trust that If The situation is not there
It is Because The timing Is such
that When it does happen it Will The
All That timing does
for If it did it be and If It is not there
then Why would you want to be there
If
you Follow Yes When you are enjoying Every
Single Moment of Your
Life Because you know that What is
happening at Every Single Moment of  Your
Life is
exact a representation of the you chose to
You will be excited about What is happening
and Will Be about What is not
happening The Idea of ​​impatience Is only created
When you Think you need patience
you only need patience When You Believe that What is
happening Now is not As
Good As What could be happening
later But recognize if you are knowing
that Everything In Your Life is exactly
Where it is supposed to be at any given
then You will Enjoy Every moment Every
moment means patience
Because you are Never Waiting for
something Better there Never Will Be
anything Better Only things different But
Never  Better than What is happening
Now Just different More expanded  perhaps
Grand perhaps on Scale But
Better Because that Perspective is own Idea
in it own Right and has nothing to
do and No Business being compared to
What is Going on Now Because What is
Going on Now exists for Its own sake and
Its own reasons and that has nothing to
do with What's going to Go On lat
Yes I follow you my
What I want in a relationship serves The
purpose it gives you The
Idea of ​​a Symbol having The Symbol The
visualization Can allow you to that
Energy into being To The momentum
Rolling But recn that What  you Visual
Come But ites have to if you recognize
that What you visualize is Simply A
template to allow you to Start The
Energy Rolling then recognize you have started
Rolling then recognize you have started
it Rolling and Stop worrying About It
Let It Take Care of It is autom If You
Worry The Energy along then you are
dragging it Down Hold
it
backing know that your visualization
means that you have enacted in Whatever
Way The template needs to be enacted that
Energy poof It is Out there All you
Need to do is Trust that it Will then
manifest in the Quick man appropriate
timing in the way that represents
Will All you to the Most  fulfill Because
the way The Idea canif that Will allow
you to Feel thef May not be exactly
literally the way you have envisioned it
Because Many things change on the
road But do recognize that No matter How it
Comes Back to you you will recognize
it As The representation of the
visualization you Because it Will Feel
Right No matter How It is From the
Original desp you it thata
again As Always
isal transl of vibrational
ener you CH to that is you can always
Trust your excit No matter How different
the syb look From What
SY Still  A representative Part of the
path you chose to be it Comes in an
unexpected Way Because You don't Want
Your Life to be
boring so trust the
Feeling that is Why and It is associated
with the Idea that Many of have
experienced in your Dream Reality that
even though an individual in your Dream
May Look different you you The What you recn
you Always know The
Content even If It is a new Cover
Because symbols are always ching Because
they are all neutral so you are always
changing the meaning SY ching asing
all right all right Thank you very
much  you
you have Work
worky Here and again The Idea  to you May that
Here and again The Idea  to you May that
you Think it man in exa
thee perh does to El can happ I
Came to the Feeling that the
reason it had Come was Because
itar Right and that seems to would n't be
n't be
by conscious for her A Program of awareness
or Program of Learning in a
Sense But again The Idea of ​​the Higher
consciousness does not become that
specific It is very
General there is Nothing about your
Higher consciousness As Free that denies
you in Will let you in any you because
theer consciousness anything you do is
Learning does Judge
All anything you Do  a Learning
Experience I'm having difficulty Together
these Two things of acting like
something to Bring it at The Same Time
allowing it to happen thank you once
again let me Put it This Way You know
you are being an Idea if you know you
are acting like it you Trust that you are
No matter what the situation is
seems Like according To Your prev way of
thinking About It you must Trust if you
know you are acting like it then This
situation also Som eventually You will
see How it does eventually You don't
have to see it Right away eventually you
will and then When  you do you will
understand Why it waited until  that
Point to could
exp in S there are others Who Will Del
Information The Idea of ​​Merlin is a S
own identity And archetyp conglomerate
of your Civilization
mes AS indiv others More
for Oh Yes
and was Reason for commun to Help People
time you will that some the reasons the
interaction for Communication
and Communications and giving ass for
situations that were created Where such Communication
disconnect Time Call physical destru of [music]
[music]
Pet some that wasen
they could be used for that But
also they had Another For The
understanding  indiv to allow themselves
Out Body experiences they could describe
The IDE
Learn comm inte
into [music] A
Experience Yes to en made
so Back there But I'm Not Where Back What IDE you
Call des des
unes New
mex Yeah I
have a painter and sometimes When
Painting I have Memories of working in
Stone or drawing have
you any Time already spen
to What Call
would Why not Yes no
maybe well Yes I would like to
very much I just Wonder How I would How I
would approach they Will you coming Trust Love
Love
unconditional they Will The ers Will Why
you are there Will Thank you sure
sure
guys can thea sexual dysfunctions like What would can be
for Many different
reasons in This Way can
be For The
Idea fearing to Blend The Male And
female aspects of your own Energy with
your and In way allowing The Idea of
What you to EX Someone El can
El can
also Idea that recn that interactions
with certain Let Idea femin entities
that you interact
with for other reasons other The Idea of
the sexual EX and So You May in that
curb Yourself
that allore other aven Make Con [ laughter] will
to All IDE that there other Levels of
Communication that are More
Paramount so that connections are Made
Within you secondly so that then Third
The wholeness Within Yourself The
interaction and the relationship and the
marriage Within Yourself so to Speak The
relationship in that Sense with your own male
femen then All you to extend
Balance to other en including IDE exp that
exp Can you use your Imagination in that
are Yes First of All Let It Be For a
reason and What you May find Most
beneficial is allow Yourself to Know It is
For a reason and allow Yourself to
Explore The Idea with the female  Partner Who
You will then be allowing to be
Assistance to you on  the Energy Level
Will A Place that Will Create A type of
mum that Will then Flow into
so that you will be Sharing with
All you A SH petroglyph
SH petroglyph
Woman Yes have been Speaking with a Few Friends
Why you your Bak
One with you that some you
finding in People May Sister
Sister
expr IDE have IDE [music]
and to actually approach Indian inquire would
It Be something I would
Just Trust would circumstances
would find
me I mean that Is The Same Thing or can
be For The Indian You will find will be
the  one that is arranged by the
circumstances you so appro Okay and is this connected
you so appro Okay and is this connected
with
Only As an association there are some
portions that are similar and there can
be doorways that in
that we will Simply perce allowing
your to form This Connection in This Way
with the consciousness then you May find
that There are doorways that Will you
Fur perk you The [music ]
The IDE expr AS retrograde asch
upb May that In The Same Dire But
As You Pass it relatively Speaking it
seems relative to you to be Going backwards you
that Only Through The Idea of ​​What you
would [music]
[music]
SL you I Water Dev All Land that happen Earth
Where there was reas
was More IDE you Call in a Sense A
Direct physiological Effect there were
Many other Levels of consciousness that
were connected to it and in your term
This was some Time AG But there was The
Idea of ​​a suspension temporarily for
Various overlapping reasons which we
will not Go into Now The IDE in General
has slan in Orbit
some physical conception But in form
that you find Now rela Speaking it has
Main relit
other SY that primarily  IDE you
Call V and IDE destruction
Back that coming Out Earth com The I
no
asen exc ATM Di Green
you May find Yourself able to Pass
through that dimensional Portal into
What appears to be the Idea of ​​an inner
World But you have also passed into A
dimensional frequency that is exa Third
so that would that would dimens
Dreams like IDE is
also archetype representation of the
ener that form Into The Idea you
Call Come Up Up
our
moree diens
and in area canway
like H Radio operated exem
Long detailed  num May Another
number is an equal sequence of Mat
vibration Is  equ that Record that that is
One Way To Look
at the Record Way
physic linking that Up to a computer On physical Hey
WoW by allowing Yourself to
recognize you are on the way with the
development of What you call the
artificial intelligence computer When
you have created that Idea What you will
recognize you have done is created an
acceptable SYM through which You will be
conversing with your
own it has Access to these
mers that is More A Is that A
mental
More Act weave and fab h i
caning being on ment
Add compu know it by number
Just Into the Act correct that is what
you do anyway you automatically go The
frequency necessary brought on by the
you use
to these minds the subconscious and
these other parts of Mind Create our
Reality our own IM of
our Just Wonder Why there seems to be
From One View these things are
so capable and so it appears
more [music]
More More like more any
any
other A As isolated As The
representational all the relation and
experiences is We see any being As The Access of All
is We see any being As The Access of All
That  is connected to at Le rela to
interaction We
Are  much
that As The interaction is Taking Place the
way interaction Taking served
Tools should We see you physically
Another Will to
something you do have [music]
and really there can M
SM I I could
also The IDE crea a r or Don As You Call
it upon R upon R upon R upon Ring upon R I
so The to a L
and make diameter
More do in This Way Will But tyes of man
some which are me [music ] in
the they All do Get Natural things
Add comp that again We cannot into now
you could  utili Idea For The conversion
of certain substances into
Energy you could in This Way therefore
find that One of the ideas you could do would
be to place what you would Call A
Rod of Pure Silicon in the Center of
This Idea and Bit by Bit at by Atom it
would be converted into Pure Energy
slowly Over Time
As I have Said Yes There are putting
are putting
Into The Effect depending upon the
precision depending upon the other
components depending upon The size depending upon The
Energy level depending upon The
Person depending upon
different things can Range all the
way [laughter]
From Can you sugg that I
Learn compur Technology that
compur Technology that
of Some of them  some them Some of them
Yes But
with primarily Explore The eye once
again of anything that is Magnetic
and in This Way also do not
forget The Idea of ​​insul
Might be able to begin experimentation
with Building any form Idea
anding it Within Idea of ​​very large
winding L Di
with exp Mat The you ach
And I Him
Y and asked and Sur
asked He Said suspect He cancer
And I
don't
Toe how can you be Service This you Communication
As If are Will to be serv being serv
May be Enough to All That to
have The  mily allou
to can Ask How Does serve What posi
ideas can I from This What is the Idea
of ​​having cancer forcing Me and or
allowing me to Look at Within Myself by
getting in touch with those answers then
the indiv May be willing to Accept those
answ in Ways that can be delivered in
Help If I My imagine Hey
Yes that will always be
Assistance For You Are Not supporting
The Idea of ​​that indiv As helpless You
Are supporting them As Strong and that
Will radiate From you and allow them The
Opportunity to in at the time also
suggest to them that their own
Imagination and their own Self Image has
much to do with it As
well He is not doing anything
He is well aware All He ising Out Choice Choice
He that some Reason Force own SU
This to Him P Attention you
Everything Everything in Life Is there
For a
reason there is
Nothing Nothing that you will Ever
Discover about Yourself that can be seen
in a posi
Life he does not have to finding
something about has to can
also that Dream inou
and He can anw own need
there is no need Deny of Yourself C Kill
it in to be  inou
All anything you can Discover about
Yourself can Come through exy
does not have to Come jud does not have to Come Fear
not Come stres Come Yes Will Yes I Will I do
n't quite understand My
tion I have
been But he has attracts into Life You will
Him nurturing The Idea Sharing your
ideas with forcing theming to take
those ideas But byly Sharing You
will be giving Him The Benefit to choose
What He Will and at The Same time you
will be leaving Him Alone to do
it Because you cannot Do It
For  So You can do both The
Same it means he can see From you  that
you love Him unconditionally No matter
what he has created for himself you love that that
canc andar
any has to Discover and To and
kill you [music ]
also colored transparent blue
white Trans
ener see in Mind you Just
Just
Made in the mem of
the SH in was
could exn does so
so
are I would like to
awareness terf Wonderful and All
these things One those [applause
] [music]
also you are
All As AS
could SE ches
Core Take AR
of the Idea exploration of Technology
Will Take Idea using  structure of
so that The Core Will in a Sense not
really seem to contain anything it Will
seem to be empty it will be the Virtual
vacum Vacuum of Virtual probabil Through
which The Communications or Beams of
Light or magnetism can Access All
Dimensions simultaneously and have that
much More to Draw From at The Same Time
in What you Now are exploring As
parallel sequences You Are On that
tye swich me
[music] we Let
360h that Will ACC to intensity according
to
vibration in  intens forms
Let for let you have
360 reference so oneal  Will Be Let 100% of
reference so oneal  Will Be Let 100% of
359 And zer of the last One Another One
Will Be 100% of
358 And zer of Two of them and so on and so and so and
soa can
Yes can that is One
Way The magne Magnetic
Field can in Aser All
Yes and identifying Making
congruent In than You Hi
All Speak Up Speak Up you Some of my
Woman canc I would like More Up I would
like More specific Information regarding
My Brother Who was quite ill and He  had
something called hin disease When He was
16 and One Way that I Know I served Him
was I was a nurse at that Point just
graduated and helped Take Care of Him He
did Very well A Few years AG and He When
He got This disease He was In The Right
Place The Right Time S that The First
cob Machine was In the city Where He was
and had radiation that saved his Life
But May have done some radiation damage
to Few years AG that radiation Burn
broke Down and After Endless search for
the treatment he found to have
massy  and it was not it was not Very
well done bodyy Shall We
Shall We
say State potential of the body to back
to a
Balance the body being in that Balance
then does not contain Anon that vibration ise
asce Channel the Name May transl As A
physan you Call
that and that
Calling As of Science May Assistance in
tring a of
Science For Now that is We
Can you Mat AS [music] like number is recn As Di
you become The dimension in which you
thought you previously exed Order
very good recn that that is what
that level CH of density so that is  what
your density ising As A physical
Universe You Are Yes Yes you would like Thank
You this even has enlightening
and EX We thank you As well
Now for some Reason during The course Word Mind that in [ laughter] laughter]
all
right back to the prision
and What define
prision are we talking about C yes yes
What would Call accuracy of Cut symmetry
precision Of
equipment You understand The term yes I
do now
specific Shape that The termination
should have
rendered What you Might
[music] IDE can
can
and This could also be that Hold All
Together  and What size of caging
something about that Is Up to you
you
Si and level
be  thank you
you talking to
John do mean Strawberry
virs that Point not Building anything The
computer Work Because of the
conscious Of The beings Who built it
correct in other Words they Will Simply be
so
that Right Now with Present level of
computer Technology there is the belief
that The Data The Bits of Data are
actually physically or physiologically stored
sugg A computer would eventually would you F
are Still using A
gradient and Because it
also other
C Oh [laughter
]
What I Learn in not
not
Non it does val with the you have
created to in terms of  What you call
your even though It is created by you
you are Still All agreeing to Play that G
so It is not Non it has validity
Within The System not outside the System
perhaps But Within The System it does have valid do
not forget you have increased your
Speed ​​It is the Speed ​​of the air Over
the Wing so much [applause] [music] Personal
Personal
level Let I jud A CH Try differ designa
something say hey that Person F Versus Hey that
Person I don't like What Words observation is
all right so  judgment is i jing
altering bringing in Another Time
Another Experience As A comparison
Running A polarity
On You can also do
Aaron in obc
without Okay so
The situation soif Fur
so [music ]
As yes yes Thank you recently to recently to
again
and coups heard of theor Over What happ
The dinosaur Never really aced Just got
stuck What happ One The ideas you have
recently been working with As A
Civilization has The Idea of ​​the
validity you are Looking for and that
More Field Ali that of EX
When I heard that theory and
ibed More asing
and end to millions of years
Evolution and  then my was If it ended
How did itur
some Trans other areas that went on recn
that What you Call Of Course your
recognizable reptiles are Off Idea But
also call
the was Ca n't 5000 5000
My
ah contemporary Looking i asked the Guy I
Said does is this What She Look like
and Said Oh Yes we have Ways tracing
that Back and so apparently Maybe 5000
years was Wrong I could have those num
not necessarily That's No it wasn't it wasn't I
Saw  5000 What But  I thought that that
seemed like a Long distance
then
But I Guess She was probably a very
Independent Woman [music
] They have They have They have
They have her
in a Window that you can see her not see
her with They have recreated This Woman
you Culture recn that The Idea that you
generally to As The American Indian
Culture has been What you Call North
American so so
U are are
IDE ccl
that that and the alteration of the
Climate Yeah The We
change Always fla
can decree inure does not have to be As
there  can be some disruption in What
you call your Communication
Systems But it May allow you to use
other Communication Systems that do not
necessarily upon that type of Technology
This is Just like a transformational Bel