[Music] all right I'll say how are you all your
all right I'll say how are you all your
time as you create time to
exist now we will begin before the idea
of sharing discussion
and conviction as we have discussed
previously of your time this time of
your time the idea the new understanding
of yourselves as beings that are now
willing to put into action all that you
have previously imagined previously
thinking that your imagination was not
real to you in this way as we have been
discussing this time of your time you
have created this idea and all the
symbology within this idea you call your
new yeah for the purpose of recognizing
that you are a new you a new personality
a new being a new Consciousness a new
idea of yourself and within this idea
you can also understand that not only as
an individual but as a society you are
transforming changing the idea of
yourselves and willing to act upon those
ideas to have conv to know that you can
express who and what you feel yourselves
to be this time of your time now
recognize that the more you are willing
to allow yourself this freedom of action
the less you will create for yourselves
the opportunities to sit around and
complain about the way things are that
you do not like for you will now begin
to see the idea of the connection of
everything in your society as it relates
to you and as you relate to that and you
will begin to understand that you each
individual within your society makes a
difference within that Society recognize
you have chosen your purpose in being in
this Society at this time upon your
planet and your civilization recognize
that if you were not going to make a
difference you would not be here are you
all following along each individual will
make a difference in this society as a
total as a whole and in this way allows
the society to recognize within each
individual within it the ability of the
society to relate to each individual
specifically and the ability of each
individual to recognize within him or
herself the totality of the society thus
forming the first bridge and Link and
connection from the individual self from
the personality to the mass
Consciousness allowing you to know that
every move that you under take every
move that you support every move that
you create will always because you are
connected to everything else act as a
lever for everything else subtly
shifting ideas in One Direction or
another and in this way you will know
that you are connected in various ways
through the mental fields that you
create upon your planet through the
physiological fields that you create
through the manipulation of the energy
fields of the planet itself all the
ideas that you call your civilization
both physiologically and mentally and
emotionally and consciously and
spiritually all are diversifications out
of the same Primal homogeneous energy
field the Primal Consciousness all are
diversifications out of that and all are
as you have said many times the idea of
the different shells the different
layers so to speak as you say upon your
idea you call the Onion upon your planet
many different layers have been created
by you out of the homogeneous Oneness of
the energy field that is the underlying
Primal Foundation of all creation that
you call physical as you diversify these
layers recognize that because you are
creating the diversification you are
still connected to every single layer
you are connected and pass through all
layers from without and from within all
layers are within you and every move
that you make within yourself is a move
made in the outer physical awareness
because the outer physical reality is
only a reflection of every idea that you
are exploring within the self to travel
to move through the physical reality no
matter what motive your Force no matter
whether you are walking whether you are
running whether you are riding in one of
your automobiles whether you are flying
in one of your airlanes whether you are
in spacecraft any idea of motion through
space is the idea of movement within
exemplified and reflected back to you as
a symbol now recognize therefore the
idea that in this way you each and every
one of you have an effect upon the
society as a whole with every small
subtle movement that you make for every
movement every movement in this way is
not insignificant to any other movement
all movements are equal and go into the
totality of the creation of your society
as you perceive it now that you are
beginning to recognize that there's no
longer any separation between yourself
as an individual and the society you can
begin to recognize that as you move this
Society moves as a whole you are
immersed in the same fluid every other
being every other individual every other
self-created perspective within that
fluid will always feel the edies and the
currents as you make your move around in
the fluid they will always be able to
sense the directions of your flow the
directions of your movement the strength
that you give the energy that you impart
to the fluid in this way and all whether
you know it or not consciously are
sensitive to this activity sensitive to
your willingness to be exactly who and
what you are what you chose to be in
this life are you following along now
therefore for this evening of your time
we will
discuss later on some ideas
specifically relating to
suggestions for what may exist within
each and every one of you pertaining to
your willingness to
communicate these ideas that you wish to
be your ability to be willing to act
upon these ideas in specific ways now
recognize two things one it will not
make any difference to us whether you do
so or not you will be doing this for
yourselves not for us and in this way
therefore number two recognize we are
not charging you with a task recognize
we are simply putting forth suggestions
as we have perceived from you that many
individuals are willing to do these
ideas but simply are still separating
the answer from themselves creating the
question how do I do this therefore we
will offer Suggestions by no means what
we say will be definitive will be the
only way no each and every one of you
with your own imagination May alter what
we suggest and in this way you know that
the way your imagination chooses to
alter what anyone suggests represents
the vibration and the methodology and
the means that is pertinent and quote
unquote true for you you all follow
along we will discuss these ideas after
your break we will also be a little bit
at that time before we get into that
idea discussing some of what many of you
have asked many times about how we
perceive you in this way and in this way
at the beginning of what you call the
second portion of this evening's
discussion there will also be the
creation that was instituted by Anica
and the physical Channel which will be
of some assistance in exemplifying to
you some of how we perceive your Society
from time to time and why many times you
will find that we can with you co-create
the idea of difficulty in communication
with our relative terms as we understand
existence and your relative terms as you
have chosen to create your understanding
of existence therefore within this
entire idea we will now begin the idea
of sharing in this way recognizing that
whether or not you choose to ask a
question or make a statement of yourself
all will be considered equal sharing and
all will be an UNC conditionally loving
gift so that every being that hears
every other being have the willingness
to have the conviction to share vocally
with every other being that you have
attracted to you this night of your time
and with us you will then learn that
everything that is said everything that
you can hear everything that you attract
yourself to here has something to do
with a part of you otherwise you would
not be involved in the interaction that
you are perceiving remember that
everything you perceive you only
perceive because you contain it that
which you do not contain the idea of
which you are not you do not encounter
do you follow me
sh
yes I've been encountering an image
twice on my trip um the first time I did
a tape called time traveler where the
hypnotist takes you back through certain
places on the earth and while I was
under he asked us to go to
Atlantis and I found myself hovering
over the island of biny which I've been
years ago personally and I was very
confused and why well I I didn't expect
to see bimy I mean it was like wow I was
there for but recognize that that was
one of what you call in this way the
westernmost portions of the island chain
that you recognize as at yeah it was
very exciting because then I realized
that I had actually been back over
Atlantis when I was in B it was very
exciting um anyway he said to hover over
Atlantis and then the image changed and
I saw
this uh I call it a crystal Temple yes
it was very very tall and narrow I
believe it was three sided yes pyramid
yes which is symbolic from the yes also
to us oh understand the Triad I we have
with many times
times
and oh I wish
okay okay I also talked to someone and I
observed the propulsion system they used
for certain transport Vehicles ni um now
after this the hypnotist suggested that
we hover over Atlantis and watch its
destruction and I found myself hovering
over this Crystal Temple and I saw a
blinding white light and I felt in my
vibration a hum that was uncomfortable
Yes actually I didn't really feel I
remembered it and I didn't stick around
to see the final Al very very deep
thring yes it was it was
disturbing it did much disturbance yes
um it set up the sympathetic vibrations
in the cross plates that caused the gas
Chambers Subterranean gas Chambers to
collapse which caused the inundation of
those Island
masses um then a few a week or so later
a friend of ours is a hypnotist and he
decided to do a little uh exploration
and he took us under and then he had us
walking through a forest and then he
said I'd like you to come upon a temple
forest and as soon as he said that St in
CST and i' lately this subject ATL
coming into my
awareness and I realized I had probably
lived then because all of you have yeah
many hes uh but I basically I wanted to
ask you what this uh symbology
or the the temple for me was it a
lifetime Now understand that those
structures exist existed throughout many
lifetimes of many individuals in that
area recognize also that the energy is
something that is not uncommon in many
other societies in different
civilizations on and off your planet
also recognize you're making an
association with the idea of the type of
energy utilized by the
league you follow me yeah I it's I just
find it amusing because it seems
everything I bring up has to do with the
Le not everything recognize that you
have chosen the idea to form attractions
to yourself of other pieces of yourself
at this time to serve the purpose that
you set up with
them was I rounded at the distraction
distraction
no you choose to have your last life in
that era before that time
uh before it destruction can you tell me
a little bit about the service I was
performing was I working with you had
done many different ideas you also
recognized and the idea of the
destruction coming up was used by his to
begin to form your connection to the
league you follow me yeah knowing that
there would be a repetition of the cycle
as you are now witnessing the repetition
of on your planet as we have said many
times what you call your culture United
States of America will be representative
of the idea of the replay historically
of Atlantis for you possess much of the
same idea of Technology the same
position in relation to your politics
around the world and contain many of the
same individuals who have restructured
themselves to the point of deciding
whether or not they will destroy the
world again or
not did I work with hypnosis in a sense
recognize that what you call now
hypnosis was something that was as you
say stock in trade of many of the idea
of Educational Systems utilized in
Atlantis there was an
identification I say of a beat that was
created so that the bodily Rhythm would
fall into synchronous harmony with that
idea and while in that state be open to
absorbing all and any information that
the individual wished to learn this was
performed by by what you call the priest
philosophers you follow me of which you
were
one that's interesting because the
second time I encountered the uh Temple
I was told I could go inside and I went
inside and the hypnotist said I'd like
you to wait there for a symbol and I
waited and waited and when it seemed
like nothing was going to happen I
turned around to start to leave and at
that moment a golden chalice appeared on
the on the altar on the table and it had
this beautiful Crystal water inside of
it that I drank and I put the Chalice
down and then I appeared a loaf of bread
which it didn't disturb me but I was
thinking of my Catholic upbringing and
it didn't make me feel too good but all
right but recognize that you were only
making the association in the present
light with some of the rituals that you
partook of in that light now recognize
you are giving all these ideas to
yourself symbolically through this ID
this identification in your hypnotic
state that you were making the associ
that some of the things you had allowed
yourself to pick up on in this life will
still be of service to you in an
archetypical sense through allowing you
to pull forth from these past lives all
of the symbols that you need to
integrate in this life to make an
association that is comfortable for you
so that you can allow yourself to be the
transformational being that will be of
service as you chose to be in this life
you are simply relating to symbols that
are identical in this way and serve
similar purposes though they do not
carry be so speak wait that you will
find you first were taught that they had
in the present life as you will have
created your interaction with them to
carry an association with the past life
and not with the present you follow me
yes I do after I took a bite of the
bread and then when I went to reach with
them again it was like a hologram my
hands I think that I I really want to
find out more about that Temple but
thank you for you always will be able to
do by simply exploring the dimension of
your imagination understand again that it
imagination understand again that it
will always give you what is valid for
you to explore and will always lead you
to the idea that you are always
exploring only your own truth which is
all that you can ever explore your own
truth you follow me yeah thaning for
sure guys um I have a couple questions
one of them is what difference do it
make to you in your perception when you
open the Channel's
eyes will it make a difference in terms
of your this will depend upon several
ideas there will be some slight
differentiation in perception but
recognize that there will mostly be a
willingness at that time for us to
initiate as you would say all right we
will be colloquial kick starting if you
wish in your language the idea of the
Channel's own willingness to allow his
own higher Consciousness to fully be
present in this way it will be more the
idea that we will then be supporting the
totality of the physical Channel rather
than actually coming through stronger
ourselves I
see the other question I have another
question uh the other question I was
listening I wasn't here I chist he but I
was listening to with the tape of it one
moment this is not always the
this is not always the
case it is different for every
individual and for the reasons for which
the channeling has been agreed to be
accomplished continue yes okay um and on
that tape uh Steve was relating a dream
in which that he had asked for and uh
apparently about esani even meeting you
or some other esani people guys
and he said everything was green yes and
you confirmed the fact that I guess is green
confirmed the fact that I guess is green
understand that what we were confirming
with the idea that while it is like
yours more or less a green planet we
also have unlike you a green star and
the reflected light many times will give
a pale green cast to the landscape well
I I was really surprised because I've
done several processes in the past few
years on several occasions I went to a
place that I called the green place of
the Green Planet in my own mind uh one
in particular I was living there with a
friend I had arrived and everything
there was a huge green expanse and just
beautiful vegetation all right thank you recognize
vegetation all right thank you recognize
that primarily what you identifying with
is some precognition of the idea of
identifying with our energy but mostly
what you were identifying with was the
fourth density state of your own Planet
as you will recognize that the C CST in
form we have described that defines that
idea will be emerald and will reflect
the idea of the vibration that your
planet is becoming and to you in
symbolic sense in this way will seem to
be the idea of the exemplification of a
green Planet you follow me yes but I did
feel it was a different planet and it
wasn't Earth it is a different planet
your fourth density planet Earth will
not be the planet you are living on now
in a very real
sense but understand as we have said you
are also co- connecting to some degree
some precognition of your interaction
with us making the connection between
your civilization and our civilization
as we have already told you that your
civilization and ours and the one around
Sirius are three parts of the same
Consciousness thus you will always when
examining the idea of any transformation
of the energy vibration of Your World
Connect into the totality of all the
others as well that have to do with this
particular exemplification and
expression of Consciousness you follow
me yes
thank you no thank
you all right you venue than
you can you tell me about yourself this
my first time what do you wish to
know you are all right for you recognize
in this way that we will consider
ourselves on a level that you would be
able to perceive us physically to be
beings similar to your own species
though different we will be average what
you say 5 ft of your height in your
counting approximately in this way
coloration white whitish gray skin tone
we will in this way in the features that
you understand upon your planet be
defined more closely to the idea you
call Mongolian though different in this
way you will I will say notice that we
will have in your turns very large
upturned ice we will have a
simplification of our
features we will will in this way be
relatively slander in your terms now in
other senses we
are connected to the consciousness of
your world we are our own civilization
but we are connected we are a part of
the same overall Consciousness that
forms your world our world and a
civilization ground about the star you
know as serious in this way we are by
being allowed by you to assist the
transformation has taken place upon your
world we are in very many ways the idea
of your future self while we are at the
same time our own
civilization we are being allowed to be
of assistance to you by blending by
reflecting to you the idea of the
blending of all the levels of your
Consciousness by the blending of
polarity within you positive negative
male female within each and every
individual upon your planet we in this
way are being allowed by you to the
assistance in the understanding of
certain aspects of all the blending of
Consciousness as you make the
transformation from third to Fourth
density reality that is simply the idea
that you are becoming more aware of more
of yourself we are reflections for you
in this way while we our own Society we
are parallel to yours we are not better
than you we are not more than you we are
simply different than you expressing
ourselves as we see fit to express the
idea of our facet of all that is that we
recognize ourselves to be you are
expressing yourself in your own way and
in this way now as you enlarge your idea
of yourself you now begin to include the
idea that there can be other
civilizations and in this way we are
allowed to communicate with you in the
manner we are communicating at this time
recognize that what you call Face to
Face encounter will be something that
will take place within what you call
your near future but as of now it will
be relatively restricted because not
everyone in your Society wishes this
idea for to wish this idea is to wish
the idea of coming into action with the
totality of your consciousness
and all portions of your personality
both positive and negative and allowing
yourself to equalize this idea and for
many individuals upon your planet this
is something you're are not yet
comfortable with therefore when your
society allows itself to be equal to
every other idea and equal to our
civilization and any possible
civilization they could encounter we
will be able to meet with you on equal
terms but not until you are equal we do
not want in this way to be feared we do
not want in this way to be deified we
want to be with you sharing inequality
and in this way we perceive that as we
perceive your energy at this time of the
entire Society we will but this is up to
you it is your choice we are not
interfere of in this way and it is up to
you to allow yourself to choose the
reality wherein it contains the idea of
interacting with other civilizations or
not it is up to you we will abide by
whatever you choose now will this have
answered your question or do you wish
more specifics confused all right very good
specifics confused all right very good
to be confused is to unlock yourself
from one idea ity disorient yourself and
reorient yourself to another idea of
yourself confusion cusion fusion with
the idea of more of yourself so if what
I say confuses you in a sense you are
allowing yourself to grasp it on other
levels as well as just your
physiological you are beginning to blend
your communication with different levels
of your Consciousness now the idea of
your confusion can be positively used by
you allow yourself to Simply clarify
within yourself what it is wish to
identify within yourself with regard to
the symbol we reflect to you what is it
you specifically wish to know
um I'm just trying to understand there
is no trying necessary you understand
what you need to understand okay why people
why people
can understand what you're saying
and and believe in
it understanding this way it is not a
matter that they believe what I am
saying it is that they believe what they
are saying to themselves and I am only
reflecting what they already
know do you follow
me all right you know what you know
yes understand in this way what the
service is that we are providing is to
reflect to you that you already know
everything you need to know you do not
need us I will be doing a perfect job
when you do not need
me when you understand that we are here
to assist you be equal to everything
that there is in Creation in this way
you can choose what you wish to believe
you always do you do not have to believe
me it does not matter to us what you
believe only that you know in this way
that whatever it is you choose to
believe you understand that that is what
is responsible for the creation of
whatever physical reality you
experience you are creating your reality
do you follow that
idea yes and I like I guess that brought
something to my mind
specifically now you talk about
Dimension guys what does that mean can
mean many things first of all it is one
way a vernacular a label to say that
there is a separation a separation of
vibrational resonance in such a way you
can make an analogy with what you call
your visible light you have visible
light and you have light that you cannot
see you follow me you may therefore
understand that the reason you can see
some light and cannot see other light is
because of the rate of their vibration
you follow me all reality that you call
physical is of this nature it all
vibrates at different rates some of it
you will perceive and some of it you
will not usually those that are called
those realities you do not physically
perceive as this one are ascribed to
what you call other realities or other
dimensions of all that is or within all
that is will that have clarify the idea
to some degree yes
and so I guess when you're saying what I
think is a reality what you
believe what you believe
the idea of
Dimensions guys would I need to know about those
guys would I need to know about those
that is up to you do you feel you need
to Now understand this many
individuals create their lives and go
about their business being perfectly
happy and do not know one shred of what
you call metaphysics and do not care to
but they are functioning within
themselves and acting accordingly to the
idea they chose to be anyway you do not
have to know these things to be able to
live it is up to you what you wish to
know about who and what you are
therefore it is not a matter of needing
to know anything you will know what you
need to know for whatever it is you are
choosing to do and you will find that
you are an automatic Creator as you
create your reality you will
automatically attract to yourself those
things which you do feel you required
therefore for example the idea that we
are discussing this right now is an
indication to you that you do wish to
know something about it or you would not
be
here for I would not have attracted
someone who had not created in
themselves an idea that they wish to
know this and share it with me and you
would not have attracted to you someone
who would be willing to discuss it with
you if you did not wish to co-create
that reality with me therefore let your
physical reality be an obvious
reflection of what it is you believe
your reality should be
now at any moment you can change your
mind you can say all right well I
understand enough about Dimensions no
need for any more of that or you can say
well this interests me I think I will
research some more of this idea by
talking to different individuals by
reading your books by watching your
films doing whatever it is you feel is
your creative way to allow yourself to
know whatever it is you think you need
to know I okay this is kind of different
but what I do believe is
[Music] in Jesus Christ what does that mean what
in Jesus Christ what does that mean what
does that mean yes when you say you
believe in Jesus Christ what does that
mean that means that I believe in a God
who created the universe
yes including all of us
yes that because we are one
moment all right you believe you are a
sinner what is a sinner will you define
this for me since it is outside the
concept of my
Society you never
heard we understand your Concept in this
way we have not heard the concept from
you however and you are a unique facet
of all that is expressing it in your own
way therefore if you would Define for me
your concept of the idea you call sinner
as it relates to how you see
yourself sin for
me is anything that I would do
think that go
against something God want what does God
want God wants I guess very simply
simply
Gods need to show unconditional love all
sit One Moment One Moment One Moment did you
One Moment One Moment One Moment did you
say
unconditional love
love
unconditional do you understand what
that
means I understand it to me
that as far as
people love for example the people in
here who they are and what they've done
who they are and what they've done
yes as far as I'm concerned I love them
because God loves no right to overrule
mean God loves everybody in here I have
no right to overrule that all right now
you know that you can create the reality
of overruling it but we understand what
you mean when you say you have no right
you do have a right because you can do
it but that does not mean that it's
something you want to do you follow
me anything you can do you have a right
to do in the sense that you can do it
because you are also the Creator now
again we are not suggesting this is what
you want to do nor we are suggesting
that this is something which would
create Harmony upon your world no but in
this way simply take yourself literally
it is not a matter of whether you not
have the right to do it you can do it
because you know people have done it
people have very blatantly judged other
people is this not so all right now
because they can do it it is not a
matter of whether or not they have the
right to do it is it WR there is no
right and wrong it is a matter of
whether you choose to create a
positively manifesting reality or a
negatively manifesting reality which
would you suggest I would suggest the
positive one because in this way choosing the
one because in this way choosing the
positively manifesting reality will be
integrating yourself with all that is
and therefore knowing yourself as the
Creator and allowing the Creator to know
you in that way whereas a negatively
manifesting reality is to separate the
idea of yourself from all that is to
isolate to create an idea of isolation
that does not allow you to feel your
connection to all that is and in this
way leads to what you call the need to
dominate for that will be when you
separate yourself from all that is the
only way that you will feel you can
collect what you see around you to you
to dominate and control it thus in this
way you create many ideas out of
separation and negative manifestation
that are in your your terms
unpleasant disease and many other ideas that you
disease and many other ideas that you
say you do not like this is why we would
suggest positive
manifestation however recognize that we
perceive the idea in and of itself that
you call judgment to be of the negative
manifestation thus we do not say
anything is right or wrong because that
to us is to judge all that is you follow
me to us even the idea of judgment is
the choosing of the
negative now you can know what you
prefer to know what you prefer does not
mean that you have to judge or
invalidate anyone
else in terms of the way they chose to
explore their own God
good to relate to themselves as their
portion of all that is now if they have
chosen separation negative reality
limitation judgment then it will be less likely
judgment then it will be less likely
that they will perceive their connection
to all that
is in this way however one who is
integrated has chosen the idea of
unconditional love will recognize that there is no
love will recognize that there is no
need to judge those who have not chosen
unconditional love for unconditional
love is the granting of validity to
everything within creation for its own
sake because that portion of creation
has se fit to learn about itself in the
way it has chosen then you in choosing
unconditional love then generate the
faith and the trust to know that in an
ultimate sense they are always going to
be all right because ultimately every
idea is still contained within the
overall idea of all that is and cannot
become lost there is nowhere to lose anything
lost there is nowhere to lose anything
too until you create that type of
Separation there is nowhere to lose
anything to until you you in choosing
negativity and limitation and separation
from yourself as all that is choose to
create a
dimension in which you can remove
yourself from the rest of
everything you follow
me yes you
do any
idea that you call a lost soul
is a contradiction in
terms a soul always knows where it
is the idea we are ascribing to many
individuals who are
expressing simply simply
that
specific ritualized
ritualized
Expressions through which they channel
the idea of their
love many times even even though they
express it to be unconditional still
comes with
conditions now we are not saying this is
your case we are simply saying that we
are relating to the
terminology that you are using by being
so
specific about what you have described
to be the way you believe and what you
have called the idea of being a sinner
which by your ultimate definition
means someone who is outside has placed
themselves outside their recognition of themselves
outside their recognition of themselves
as God
God
yes of course now understand this is
what we are talking about many of what
you call upon your planet your beliefs
or your religions so to speak speak of
the idea of God or what we call all that
is as being omnipotent everywhere
omnicient all knowing allseeing
everything everywhere now if God by your definition
everywhere now if God by your definition
is everything how can you be outside of
it you must also be God God must also be
you now God knows that you are God why
do you not know that you are
God so say I make a model I create a
model of of
what all
right not me yes it
is understand that what you experience
as your physical
reality is all a symbol if you wish to
use the term illusion all right that may
clarify it for you that illusion or
symbol
it is a representation of an
idea IDE
yes are that IDE you understand that
everything in your universe is a matter
physically of vibration you cannot
perceive anything that you are not the
vibration that you are makes what you
perceive the physical reality to be thus
if you have created this this idea of a
model airplane in front of you you are
extending a portion of the idea of
yourself and reflecting it back to
yourself as the ability to do that
outside yourself
seemingly but everything that you
perceive every individual in the room is
your creation you have to create your
version of them in order to perceive
them you follow me
all right guess
one if I am dedicating my life to
following Jesus Christ why would you
want to do that he did not want you to
do that he did not want me to do that no
he does not want you to follow him he
wants you to be like him that's kind
what I mean well say what you
mean understand that your terminology is
what we were discussing that upon your
planet many times the terminology that
you choose does reflect how you go about
relating to the ideas you think you
believe in and in this case you are
saying that by following someone you are
separating yourself and making yourself
less than rather than being equal to
which is what he wanted you to know that
all of you are Christ Consciousness like
he is and in this way the idea the
idea of what you have referred to in
your Society of Second Coming is not the
coming of of an individual it is the
recognition within each individual upon
your planet of the Christ that you are
and living like
it that is your second coming when
Jus said I don't know if he [Music]
said but he said I am the way the trth
and the life no one comes to the father
but through me what do you mean by that
the idea is
this he was saying to paraphrase in your
terminology as you understand your
language now what you perceive in me is the
now what you perceive in me is the
vibration of integration wherein I know
myself to be on the same level equal to
God all that
is the only way that you will know
yourself to be that idea is to be like
me be of the equal vibration of
recognizing yourself as all that
is that is why he said I am the way he
did not mean I know the only thing that
will get you there he simply meant that
you in allowing yourself to know that
everything you do is valid in the
overall sense are granting support and
service and validity to the ultimate
idea of the creation itself
and recognizing your own quality to
godhood that is being the way you said
something and people kind of laugh and
you go he didn't say I know the only way
but he said way truth
no understand this as well what you are
calling your biblical
literature contains less than 10 % of
what that individual ever said in his
life and what was even written down is
very much misinterpreted according to
the understanding of When It Was
Written recognize that what you call
your Bible was not written to record
history it was written to
convert follow
me it is in this way true for those
individuals that wrote it in the way
they understand stod
it but recognize that there is still
much misinterpretation of what was actually
misinterpretation of what was actually
said in this way we are sensing into the
mass Consciousness your higher levels of
consciousness we cannot expect to take
us at our word it is up to you to
believe what you want as we have said
but we will discuss with you what we
perceive to exist within your own higher
consciousness which knows itself to be equal to the
which knows itself to be equal to the
idea of the Christ Consciousness we can
talk to it and so can
you we are simply here to let you know
that you can talk to your own higher
Consciousness and once you allow
yourself to do so you will find that it
will tell you exactly what I am telling
you now is I guess
now is I guess
what that's what I believe all right
okay it gets you where
one moment it makes you
everything understand this it is not the
idea of what you are perceiving to be a
removal of
validity to us big deal does not mean
the removal of validity it means the
equalizing of everything as equally
valid the granting of every past that be
valid no matter what you in other words
no one thing no one belief is any more
of a big deal than any other belief they
are all equal
IDE are valid including the idea that no
other IDE
is very
good cre yes because that person would
not have created it for themselves if
they did not need to look at that idea
was Jesus Christ the only son of God you
are all children of
God now
recognize that the idea as it was
translated into your
language is usually interpreted this way
the idea of what you call Jesus Christ
referring to himself was as the son of
man call himself the son of
man call himself the Son of God look in
your own Bible he calls himself the son
of
man 2000 years ago that word God I don't
believe was written in the
read the Bible understand first of all
that in this way as you say the writings
of what was verbalized were not even
begun to be committed to paper until
approximately 57 years after the death
of the physical
Jesus so you talked about the B
being every
single written idea
contains some misinterpretation where it
regards the idea of placing ritual
around the idea of what
happened God couldn't watched over why
should he because it was his word no no
no understand it was a
reflection an offering a
gift unconditional remember that term
unconditional love God is unconditional
love and will not force you to interpret
something in any way shape or for it is
up to you that is why you are
here so the word of God the
Bible not word of God yes all of it is
is
people simply understand than this it is
all relative the word of God is all relative
relative the word of God is all relative
to itself God contains every
Paradox every
parad every
dichotomy every
blending God is all that is there is
nothing
outside you are all that is
is your space in which you
live your time which you spend much of
wondering who and what you
are all of those things are
Creations from your idea of who you
think you
are you are one
idea of
God every being in creation
are all the different ways God has of
looking at
itself that is what it means to be all
that is every Dimension every being
is every Dimension every being
everything every thought it is all
God and many of those things come into
creation simply because for no other
reason than they can under understand
this many times when you
ascribe more importance to this passage
or this literature than some other
passage or literature seeking for some
ultimate idea of
Truth you
are in that way at that
moment diversifying focusing and
fixating a portion of all that is and
not looking at the whole which always
sees itself as
whole the
idea of knowing yourself to be
God is simply allowing
yourself the broadest possible
definition of that
concept and knowing that for God that is
real God knows itself to be its own being but
God knows itself to be its own being but
also knows itself to be the compilation
of every being within it and knows every
being within it to contain the totality
of the whole for in that way as you say
nothing is impossible to all that
is and if you can conceive of it it is
real to all that is and on some level
some Dimension some aspect of
Consciousness it is exists if you can
conceive of it it exists and it is a
reality within all that is now when you
do this separating out and searching
through and analyzing all of the
different passages in literature many
times you go doing this because you are
looking for this ultimate
purpose recognize this existence is all
that is is always was is now always will
be existence does not have its existence
with in time time exists within all that
is therefore it is
eternal one moment recognize therefore
that the concept and any concept that is
created within all that is is in a sense
subordinate to it therefore ultimate
truth as a concept purpose as a concept
are things that exist Within existence
and existence existed before there was
the concept of purpose and that which
exists before the concept of purpose
does not need a purpose to keep on
existing thus all that is will be all
that is in all the ways it can be simply
for no other reason no other purpose
other than it
can because it is the creator
and the creator
creates simply because it
can now your symbols are valid for you
you have changed your mind before and
you will change your mind again about
what symbols are relevant in the
understanding of who and what you are
and it does not matter in the overall
sense what you choose to
believe if you know
that you are believing what you are
believing out of unconditional love for
all that is and also equally important
unconditional love for
yourself then there is no need to worry about
then there is no need to worry about
what you believe there is no need to
worry about what anyone believes because
you know that whatever you believe is
going to create the type of reality that
you will
experience and experience that you
will the only
if that's what you
believe what you're
missing is relationship with the God who
made you
why understand again you are missing
yourself the idea that I perceive both
ideas I contain the totality of the
dichotomy of the polarity of the seeming
opposites I know myself to be all that
is and I also know all that is relates
to me as a higher Consciousness I can
create the idea of knowing I have a
relationship with all that is at the
same time I can also see myself as the
one creating that relationship and
therefore being all that is to me this
is not something which is mutually
exclusive I can create whatever sense of
relationship I wish and I know that
whatever sense of relationship I create
is still going to be add as real as any
other sense of relationship that I
choose to create and for me all of it is
valid and all of it is being created out
of joy and ecstasy and unconditional
love and the expression of the same
unconditional love that the Creator
created us to
be that is how I perceive the
relationship I am always in the
relationship with all that is within Joy
love and
ecstasy for us and our civilization the
feeling of this ecstasy
is the expression and the experience of
what you are defining as the sense of
that relationship why is that happen
here because for the past 25,000 years
approximately of your time you have
chosen as a group Consciousness to
explore the idea of separating yourself
from your memory of being all that is
and now you are turning over a new idea
you are through with the separation and
that is why you are creating this idea
you call a new age of understanding a
new age of awareness in light and
love you all
are the entire planet or you would not
be on it because that is the idea of
this planet that you are on to create
the transformation to begin to recognize
yourselves as all that is and create
because now you know you are the Creator
peace Harmony light and love understand
you do not get Peace by hating War you
get Peace by loving peace now you are
through simply with a tool of separation
and within the next span as you count
time of approximately 30 to 50 of your
years all of your civilization will also
recognize this for when you create
separation you create the experience of
more time and thus that is why the
experience of experiencing all the
limitation and separation has taken
25,000 years when you now choose to
create the idea of integration of
knowing yourself to be all that is then
this experience can be played out upon
your planet in a mere 2 to 3,000 years
and after that point you will not need
to reincarnate upon this planet again
for it will have served its purpose for
you you will move on to something
else back um to when you were talking
about when I said big deal yes and
everybody I guess agreed with that they
simply recognized that you were quoting
something we had said many times okay um
now this is my first time yes and for
what you're saying I could leave
here knowing that whatever I chose to
knowing that whatever I chose to
do would be all right
precisely and now what I want to know why would
and now what I want to know why would
anybody want to come back if that's what
they know
maybe simply because they enjoy the
situation recognize they do not have to
come back and many do
not why you come back why didn't I come
back talk about a lot of times I come
here I don't think about specific
questions but when I around this group
of people step out me that I W answer
well what you already know is simply
what you choose to do is okay so why do
you need a question answer it is not so
much that they need question answer
there can also be the equality of
sharing when you know what you know you
can share because you have created
yourselves to be a physical planet and
you have created the idea that you are
separate beings and you have created the
idea that you can communicate different
ideas that might seem like fun because
you may not have considered it from the
specific point of view that someone else
has considered it from so this is an
opportunity for sharing for blending for
appreciating all the different ways that
all that is has of expressing itself
through all the different people that
you are each and every one of you is a
different path is a different way if
there was only one way to do something
there would only be one person therefore
many individuals are simply taking
advantage of the richness of the
experience of all that is expressing
itself through all the different beings
that you are and they enjoy the sharing
in that way it shows and reflects to
each individual different portions of
themselves they may not have been
willing to consider in exactly that way
and for them it is a joyful experience
of integration that is why they choose
to come back but understand it is not
the original person who comes back every
being that comes back again and again
and again is a new complete being a new
complete idea of themselves him or her
and a new complete Universe it is not
the same person no one comes back
everyone here is new even if they have
been here for,
times what happens when you die many
different things you will first of all obviously
things you will first of all obviously
no longer consider yourself to be
physical as you now understand
physicality many different things we
come back here you can you
not there can be in that state of being
when you remove yourself from the idea
of the physical reality as you have
created to be a limiting one when you
remove yourself from that physical state
of
limitation then you will know that you
chose everything that you experienced in
that life and that you can create any
other type of reality on this planet or
any other planet or not reincarnate at
all you can choose to know in that level
and see very obviously that you are in
fact the Creator so then I would no
longer be reincarnated you do not have
to be it is always a
choice now since you are here I will
assume that you chose to reincarnate at
least one more
time why you that since you are here
this time not one more time after this
this time since you are here I will assume
time since you are here I will assume
you chose to
reincarnate this this time into this
lifetime yes yes yes it's not my first
one no there is upon the average as you say
no there is upon the average as you say
two to 3,000 lives for every individual
in the room with regard to the
particular Earth cycle you are now
involved in during the last 50,000 of
your years or
so why why
not because you chose to because you
chose to explore the idea of limitation
as it is being expressed on this planet
and to do so you chose to manifest
yourself in many different lives to
explore all the different ideas that you
can explore in being in this Society you
have been everything there is to be in
this Society one time or another
sometimes more than one
time everything because this is now the
transformational life and this life can
be the last physical life you may choose
in this cycle since the cycle is now
over and turning into another cycle
cycle
yes um I've been reading a lot on the
Lost Years of Jesus and I want to know
um uh the period in time when this the
the Bible uh that that information that
was erased from it um where he went did
he go to India instead that's why came
back into there was the idea of travel
to the area you call India what
age now we perceive that there was
connection at what you call age
17 also what you call
age 30 approximately
30 approximately
also the area you call
Egypt also the
idea of many what you call outof body
experiences to travel many different
places other than that recognize
that recognize
simply that what that being was allowing
himself to recognize was his own godhood
his own Christ consciousness
and in this way we simply reflecting to
you we can do it too yes right
right
yes um just when you when you repeat
exactly what he said that it reveals the
whole thing I am the way the truth and
the life you repeat that but very good
yes if you repeat it and mean it for
yourself that's it there's no debate
there no big mystery yeah it's
self-evidence yes you see that is why we are saying do
yes you see that is why we are saying do
what he did not follow for if you follow
then you wind up saying he said this he
said that rather than simply repeating
what he said and feeling the vibration
within yourself for what it gives you we
are the way to Al
yes briefly briefly okay um so far
everything you've been saying um is I've
never been to one of these sessions
before but so far everything you've been
saying is perfectly understandable to me
I understand exactly what you're talking
about right does that mean that I've
spent more lifetimes working on these
answers is that why it's clear to me and
maybe unar to other people can be does
not have to be understand simply that
whatever purpose you created this life
to be will delegate what type of
understanding you have about anything in
it does not have to be connected to the
idea you call past life because you are
creating your past and your future from
the present since the present is always
the only time in which you exist all
times are existing at one time yes is
all simultaneous and any idea you call
past and future lives all exist right
now okay this is um recently I've had a
feeling that there have been visitors
from the outside maybe from
you're four or of them and under
hypnosis and re and I haven't been able
to get through to these the other night
I had
and I have a lot of blockage a lot of
resistance to this but I had these light
forces visit me there different
colors but they were trying to give me
some sort of message and no matter how
hard I concentrated on the message I
couldn't I could not figure out what it
was is because you were concentrating I
think so I think so how do I get this
message first of all simply assume that
you have it on whatever level you need
to have it then relax go about to your
business live your life understand that
you chose to experience a certain number
of ideas in this physical life and you
will experience every single one of them
you will not miss any of them it's just
a matter of time you make your own
timing you make your own idea of Destiny
than with Destiny are always on
TI there is no need for for
anxiousness understand that anxiousness
is the negative view of the same energy
that causes
excitement be excited know that your
opening up to the ideas that you are
creating in your reality and simply
follow your joy follow your excitement
do whatever excites you because what
excites you represents the vibration
that reflects the path you chose to be
that is what excitement
is fight
you all right the two and then we will
take your
break why
choose not know why we came this and
we if we also have memory childood why
do we stop all right now again recognize
that what you are still doing is what we
call a habitual ritual out of all of the
lives and times that you have separated
yourself from knowing who and what you
are you are now learning to reintegrate
this idea and you will find that you are
creating the type of society that will
allow the children that are being born
into it now to
remember yes now do not be surprised
therefore if these children tell you
what's going
on they will remind you of the
agreements you have made with them to be
here
now there are overall themes if you wish
but again you have been everything there
is to be even within any particular
overall theme you may choose to create
but that is also a choice and you have
many parallel existences and Alternate
dimensions of reality in which you have
different themes follow Mees that
Mees that
enter in a sense but do forget again
that what is being described are the
themes that are congruent with this
particular reality you have alternate
dimensional portions of yourself that
are experiencing different
themes as well as the ones that you are
now referring
to you follow me
mhm well this have answered your
question than than
you
yes go
on for or is it just this civilization
and other civilization such as yours
that is not you speak to us going for do
do the densities just go on forever
yes and
not there is one whole everything and
within one one unbroken homogeneous all
that is there is no need for the idea of
diversifying into different separate
density levels yet because it can within
all that is is created an infinite
number of densities simply because you
can imagine it so this basically bottom
line is
excise thank you it is
creation it is creation
no you may all take a short break right
break right
now as we [Music]
[Music]
continue diverge for a moment of your
time
to go create an
i which we know you will
enjoy Erica are you ready yeah all right
now before we
begin allow
me to tell
you this is not being done so that you
may have more opportunities to judge
yourself you already have enough of
those
recognize that this is simply being
offered to you as a
co-creation so that you can see how very
creative you are even when you choose to
limit yourselves even when you choose to feel
yourselves even when you choose to feel
that you do not deserve to know that you
are happy that you do not feel you deserve
happy that you do not feel you deserve
to have whatever you wish without
struggle with without
strike this for you
also may serve to give you some idea and
again we are not meaning to judge you
nor to as you say call you
down but simply recognize this may give
you some
sense of how many times when we
communicate with you you sound to
us for we see you as a total
conglomerate of all that you are and we
understand that you are at any given
moment of time as you create those
moments to exist different ideas of
yourself you become different ideas from
moment to moment to moment to moment
many times you exemplify this in your
speech and what to you sounds like a
coherent statement to us sounds like
three different people talking about
three different ways of
life you think
well what about so and so and this
relating to such and such and that and
then again how about
this and you think it all is one idea
when it is actually free or
more and with every time you state those
different ideas you become a different
person the person that only relates to
the idea and exemplifies the idea you
are stating at the moment and when you
put the butt and or whatever in between
those statements and create for yourself a
statements and create for yourself a
polarity a contradiction a
dichotomy then you become a different
person that has now unto yourself saying
a specific
idea recogn ize that when you are the
person that creates the
question and then become the person that
knows you have the
answer you may create what you have
judged upon your Society up to this
point to be a negative habit you call it
absent mindedness but recognize that that is
mindedness but recognize that that is
why you usually ascribe because in your
knowingness you know that the idea
behind mind absent mindedness more often
than not is something that puts you in
touch with who you are the center of
yourself where you know the answers are
and that is why you usually ascribe the
term absent-mindedness to someone you
think is smart you follow
me recognize that you say absentminded
Professor Geniuses are
absentminded they tend to lose track in
what you turn to be the Practical ideas
of day-to-day living but this is only
because they begin to listen to
themselves Now understand you would act
the same way and it is not necessarily a
negative way to act if you went from a
person who separates the answer from
yourself and formed a question to a
person who listened to the answer or
discovered that you had the answer it
could go something like this well Bashar
what about so and so and such and such
now recognize as we have said that as
you speak something you are on the level
of that idea or you could not conceive
of it therefore when you say something
when you imagine something if you all of
a sudden in mids sentence recognized
that you became that if you let yourself
recognize that you became what you are
conceiving then you would just be so and
it would be well Bashar what about such
and uh oh I see what what did you have a
question what what are you talking
talking to me no I did not have a
question I know my answer well somebody
asked a question well yes but that must
have been the me I was
before now I allowed myself to become
the me that has the answer and I the me
that I am now never ask a question
because the me I am now does not need to
ask questions to separate the answer
from myself therefore I forgot what I was
myself therefore I forgot what I was
saying because I am now another me that
does not contain
that idea you follow
idea you follow
me no however we
will generate for your
enjoyment a I'll say
condensation in a way
of many times and again not to judge you
how you sound to my
civilization in all the ways that you
have created to hold yourself back from being
created to hold yourself back from being
willing to be who and what you
are take it away right I'm trying I hope
I wish I can't I don't know how I don't
understand I want to achieve I want to
become I'm lost it got away from me
easier said than done it's difficult
it's hard it's hopeless I don't deserve
it make it happen I'm working on it
that's in the future it's a goal I'm
pursuing an idea I'll get around to it
it's the me it's the me it's above me
it's beyond me it's out of my reach it's
out of my grasp hang in there have
patience things take time be persistent
work hard earn a living I expect to I
guess I suppose maybe perhaps possibly
we'll see I can't see how I can't
imagine I can't cope I'm afraid I'm
going to get hurt I'm going to fall flat
on my face I'll be ruined but however
look before you leave have a plan think
about what you're doing analyze the
situation I can't help it it's a habit
it's not my problem it is a problem why
how it's always been this way you can't
teach an old dog new trick I'm setting
my ways you're a dreamer it isn't real
it's not valid it's stupid it's silly
it's ridiculous it'll never get you
anywhere it won't work it won't succeed
you failed you made a mistake you're
being naive you're inadequate who do you
think you are you think you know it all
you're not an
expert you're wasting your time you're
fooling yourself you're being taken for
for a ride stop pulling the wool over
your eyes wake up and smell the
coffee prove it face reality you don't
know what you're talking about grow up
you've got your head in the cloud stop
acting like a child you're nuts you're a
looney you're insane give it up you're
acting like a fool I'm Hess I'm
powerless it's out of my hands what can
I do what difference does it make you
can't change things overnight you can't
fight City Hall I can't handle it it's
too much for me I'm in way for my head
I've bitten off more than I can chew I
don't have time I'm too busy I'm pushing
myself I'm holding myself back the rug
was pulled out from underneath me I'm
out of control I don't want to get
involved leave me out of it you can't
have your cake and eat it too M you made
your bed now sleep in it leave well
enough alone don't make ways don't stir
up trouble don't ask you're gullible um
you're fall into a trap nobody's perfect
it can be done don't expect miracles be
practical that's not normal what's your
problem give me a break it's driving me
crazy it's making me uptight it's a
tense situation Hammer the idea home
follow in their footsteps disaster
catastrophe accident task I've got a
long way to go it's a long journey what
if evil no good bad rotten Wicked
spiteful vengeful hateful determined
stubborn judgment good for nothing out
of place awkward embarrassment secret
hidden out of sight out of mind we'll
never know I haven't the faintest idea
God only knows I'm only human that's the
way it is you can't have everything you
want be happy with what you have don't
upset the apple cart Don't Rock the Boat
I'll sell for that that mind your p's
and q's don't be selfish I know what's
best for you it's too much trouble don't
bother I'm beat I'm sorry misery loves
company you don't know your ass from a
hole in the
ground you should you better you have to
this is killing me walk before you run I
don't have a leg to stand on kind of
sort of almost and who cares
cares
now do you wonder
understand yeah that many times in the
course of a communication and a
conversation to us what you think is one
statement many times sounds like a
series of
those when you think you are being
positive you are finding any excuse not
to be you even think that the idea in
and of itself of thinking
positive is not something that is
practical in the overall sense well yes well I'll
in the overall sense well yes well I'll
feel better well so what what will
thinking positively get
me now in this way when we speak of the
idea of
conviction when we say that your words
are vibrations and vibrations are ideas
and ideas are your reality well is it
any wonder the reality that you create for
wonder the reality that you create for
yourself you always create the symbols
that go with it to reflect that idea and
all of these ideas that what just read
to you are a product of the habitual
ritual that you have created of
Separation now recognizing and giving yourself the
now recognizing and giving yourself the
opportunity to make all of that equal to
everything that you possibly could
experience you now know that this was
not read to you so that you will have to
be careful about what you say no you
don't not have to step on your words
you do not have to control your language
oh well if I say this well he's going to
jump down my
throat I have already jump down enough appro
recognize in this way it is simply an
opportunity for us to assist in
reflecting to you another Viewpoint of
yourselves that you may previously not
have considered to be one that carried
so much weight as you have given
it now in this way
therefore recognize that you can if you
choose to Simply lighten up on
yourselves and by lightening up on
yourselves you will find yourselves to
be enen
that is all it takes it is all very
simple you and
creation though ultimately infinitely
Diversified is completely simple the
idea is
simple and you can
create anything out of it and that is
why you can create anything out of it
because the basic idea of existence is
so
simple if it were in of itself a complex
thing then you would find yourselves
rigidly structured and not able to
structured and not able to
create infinitely diverse
situations but because creation is in
and of itself Simplicity itself totally
homogeneous one thing
then out of the
Oneness can come
anything anything you
wish you have but to see to know to
believe to feel to think yourself into
that idea to know you are any idea that you
idea to know you are any idea that you
have you are any idea that you
have and the then there will be no
separation between you and the
idea there will not even be the concept
of
between you follow me
me
no we thank you for your willingness to
enjoy yourselves we
yourselves we
will take sharing for a time and then
discuss some of the suggestions we spoke of
some of the suggestions we spoke of
earlier sharing yeah you V you uh last
week we had an
opp and I had asked you
about to communicate with colon
Kad I would like to know is there a life
connection with
this in our perception and in your
terminology is somewhat as you say
bifurcated in other
words not directly
but there was an
involvement with the energy of that
being though at that time you found it
in your terms prudent to not physically
interact though you were aware of each
other in the sense of your influence in
what you call world affairs even then
and in this way you
interacted by being of the same Nature
by being involved in the same types of
activities but you were not directly
involved now you can give yourself the
opportunity to bring this idea full
circle and
recognize the
polarity that has has been created again
and this time the willingness to act
from the point of view of knowing that
all polarity is contained on one whole
unbroken idea within the self then you
can know that you can attract and create
and co-create with other individuals
that type of interaction to be of
service in this way to allow there to be
an equalizing of the IES and a
sothing of the separation that is being
created by that individual upon your
planet for
himself wonderful um that answers a lot
of questions for me that answers why um
I am so attracted to the energy although
um his
daily functioning in this physical form
is totally 180 de from where my beliefs
are yet there is a very C understanding
and a very clear need to communicate
with him the idea of the image of Peace
in Christ all right and once again
recognize it is through
unconditional love
absolutely without the expectation that
he need listen to you absolutely then
you will be speaking the clearest
wonderful thank you thank you
yes given all been talking I have
question
how manifest physical energy in our body
and the concept of pain all right
um specifically in my body I've
had a history stomach
Al and
I I hadn't had a diagnosis over many
times it's been chronic curring period
of
time and I've looked at
it not separating my body from
my what does it do for
you having an
what does it cause you to look
at uh caus to look
at as a result
of Now understand while you are quote
unquote pondering that idea that all
disease and all
pain results from separation the idea of
loss of
something limitation of the idea of
yourself as being connected to your own
godhood all pain is created out of
separation from yourself as all that is
is
now can you
allow the idea of the pain to serve that
purpose for you do you think there may
be some other specific things that the
pain allows you to look at that you may
not be considering if you did not create
that for
yourself well I'm very aware when I have
of Separation in this in the sense
that I feel like there's a block uh
block my blocking the energy
why do you feel you are blocking
energy what is the idea to block energy
what does that mean to
you does it mean that you are not
willing to accept and allow a portion of
your personality to be
valid yes what
portion well when I have the pain I feel
like if I want to breathe through it or
let go or something of that
nature uh all right let us in this
way I'll say not chiding you but simply
speaking for
myself let us cut the method physical
Jaron what is it about yourself you
cannot
stomach what is it about your reality
you cannot stomach what is it about life
you cannot
stomach what upset you
bottom line that
se why do you imagine that you create a
feeling of
Separation what do you feel separated
from well I see you know I I see my let
go uh but what does all this
mean what is it you
think that you should be doing that you
are not or that you are doing that you
think you should not be
doing speak physically about your life
what are you doing in your
life and is what you are doing in your
life representative of who you know yourself
representative of who you know yourself
to
be then understand that as you create
the vision so-called vision of yourself
being this complete individual you
understand that that vision is of an
individual that does not contain an
ulcer yes then why not simply be that
individual now rather rather than assume
that you have to try to achieve to
become that individual in the
future well I I I do fine if that
my then simply ask yourself if you know
that you are a complete
individual then if there is a reason for
a complete individual to have an uler
then talk to yourself ask yourself what
the reason is
but not from the idea that you are not a
complete individual with a
problem you are a complete individual
with a particular type of symbol a
particular type of experience that is
telling you
something what is it telling you that
you are not listening
to go
within speak to your body Consciousness
listen to your body
Consciousness if you are a complete
person with the idea of an
uler because there is no such thing as
being a less complete portion of
something else every idea is in and of
itself perfect for what it is therefore
you are a perfectly complete person with
a perfect manifestation of an
un why have you created yourself to be a
complete idea that contains the notion
of an un speak to yourself what do you
get what image what feeling no matter
how silly do not judge it do not think
about it what do you get what is the
first impression I'm
impression I'm
not all right very good very
good now what in your
now what in your
life as you go through life as you
examine the idea of your interaction
with white what
white what
becomes nothing for
you what is it that you think needs to
be
unraveled untied What secrets do you believe are
untied What secrets do you believe are
hidden from
you well um
I guess the I iimp something don't don't
glimpses of what and what is there
possibly that you could get glimpses of
that you need to feel you should
maintain as I said What secrets do you
think are being kept and why do you feel
that anything can be kept from
you why why do you feel you need to try
so hard to hold on to something when its
natural inclination is to come and
go and in coming and going serve the
purpose you chose to create that event
for in that
way why do you think you are being
Steed why do you think there are things
that are hidden from you do you not
understand that everything that you need
to know is obvious in your
life if you will but treat your reality
as valid and everything in it then you
will always see how everything that
concerns you in the moment is right
there for you to look at and anything
that comes and goes does so because the
coming and the going serves the purpose
of the moment there is nothing you have
to sink Your Hooks into and hold on to
or it will get away from
you nothing away from you you are
creating it
all it is all within
you do you think you might be able to
relax into the idea that your life is
not being
interrupted that you can never be off
your path because a path is not
something you are on a path is what you
are and you cannot be off of
yourself do you think
that you would enjoy the idea of
relaxing into
life of knowing that you deserve the
ease of
creation of knowing that you did not
have to do anything to deserve to
exist and therefore anything within
existence you do not have to need to do
anything to prove that you deserve
anything within existence
all you need
do is act upon the knowingness of the
self that you already are and all that
means is acting upon the opportunities
you give to yourself you create for
yourself in your reality exactly in the
way you create them and not hoping
expecting wishing them to be something
else for it is only in allowing the way
you created to be all right that it gets
you to something else you follow
you follow
me now take your hands and open them
wide all your fingers
displayed out in front of you like this
all right
right
now can you feel the idea that you can
embrace the love of Creation in your
arms can you feel this idea this Warth
this unconditional love that has all
always for you present from all that
is can you imagine this
idea then if you will do me a
favor take that
love and hold it within yourself and
embrace yourself and love
yourself and treat yourself with the
same preservability
and the same resp expect that all that
is has for
you because all that is thinks you
deserve it so why don't
you love yourself hold yourself cuddle
yourself cherish and nurture
yourself and in this cherishing and in
this nurturing it is not a
weakness it is a strength
for you are then pulling yourself into
the center of your being which is
exactly where you know that you are all
that is and everything you
create is a tool to show yourself
another idea of all that you can be and
that you can transform your tools from
negative into positive manifestation
once you allow the tool you create in
the manner you have created it to serve
the purpose and not reject it for it
always comes to you in the manner which
you chose to have it come to show you
what you chose to do
about when you accept what you create
the first time it does not ever have to
come back in the same
way let it do its
job by not being something that you
cannot imagine has anything to do with
your life and the instant that you allow
yourself to recognize that everything
that occurs to you happens because of
you and that it has everything to do
with your life exactly as you have
conceived of yourself then any reason
for pain will vanish you will accept the
idea of the message being sent not
create separation from the path that you
are and not need to experience that loss
or separation of yourself in terms of
disease or pain that come to you in
symbolic ways to shake you up and remind
you what you are
doing you follow
me then relax I do yes the
yes the
pain um when your energy ENT
like I experiencing excruciating pain my
ey is starting to di now and it's really
so
painful all right once again we have
discussed this idea simply recognize you
are still creating the idea is no big
deal that you are still
comparing Where You Think You Are now to
where you think you are going to be and
when you receive or create for yourself
these surges of
knowingness and you are filtering them
through those comparisons well then the
idea of the slower vibration of where
you are now and the supposed faster
vibration of where you think you are
going rub up against each other and
cause friction which causes pain it will
dissipate as you acclimate and shift and
merge and blend and become one vibration
with that idea by allowing yourself to
know you are becoming the future self in
the
present in a sense yes of
course it is all the same idea why
separate it
out you know what total idea you are so
why say well does it have to do with
that does it have to do with this does
it have to do with what I a for
breakfast this
morning it is all everything everything
in your reality is a symbol of the total
idea that you are
being thus you have simply to look at
what you know you are being and every
symbol that relates to it that you are
creating will make
sense under the hypnosis um the hypn
took us into a cottage where we exam
which is same symbology I use when I us
people but uh one of the doors I
approached was a black door with no
handle and I knew I wasn't supposed to
go in it uh so I stood there in front of
it it was a wooden door painted black I
put my hand on the door and I put my
hand on the door and I understand what
that's represen to me do you what
well I assume it to me that something in
the past for like no no it was an
exemplification of the idea of what you
do to yourself to Splinter to
fractionate yourself when you come up
with this idea that there is something
you are not supposed to
do therefore you get what you put out I
am not supposed to go through that
door ouch I showed
me I don't know
that's that is what I mean yes I didn't
me I wasn't supposed to go through I
could have gone through if I wanted to
but then why didn't you I felt like it
wasn't necessarily something need to see
and when I told
Hypno my
fingered and I didn't even realize I
could do it but to take the splinter out
so I reached over and I pulled the
splinter out and this huge long black
Splinter was really pointy and I
dissolved it with white light and I put
blue light around my good but understand
simply again that was learning the idea
after the
fact you do not have to get the splitter
in the first place if you recognize that
there is not anything you are not
supposed to do so it wasn't related to
anything it is all
related it is all related why create
more SE why need to your microscope and put
SE why need to your microscope and put
labels on a specific
idea that you can then take your
responsibility and put over there well
this happened because of this
over not because of me now because of
disob you follow me that is the idea of
why you reminded yourself to come back
to the now with the Splinter and
sometimes times you will find that this
is why you think you need to create the
idea of pain it is a very focusing
concept and let me tell you when you are
in pain you are nowhere else but
here there was this tunnel of pain when
my third eye was all right then make the
association between what we are saying
it is all symbolic of the idea it is the
separation the drifting off into the ne
lands of your past and future lives and
then not watching what you are doing in
the present that causes you to get the
pain that snaps you back right where you
know you want to
be I think that I want I I you
understand and then when you understand
then you say all right thank you
Splinter I know what purpose you served
I am now here and in the present thank
you and goodbye
there one of the door it is very
creative on your part I thought so oh I
think so too oh thank you there's a one
of the door I came to which was really
really beautiful it was a crystal door
living a block of Ice and there was no
way physically there was no knob or
anything but I just stood back and I put
white light around and it vanished and I
walked through very good and um my first
impression was the C because it was uh
it was very green and there was lots of
Crystal Sparkles and the vibration was
very very high and I felt like I I
shouldn't go to another
should I
know you know you're you're reflecting
something to me that I haven't noticed
about this whole experience oh yes what
is that
do well the should because the other
door I went through was the golden door
and I know I visited my higher self and
I asked if I could keep the door open
and I heard no and and now I'm thinking
I shouldn't keep the door open I
shouldn't shouldn't
shouldn't why not get experimental and
see what happens if you
do that's a good
idea anyway this
Vision want to make sure ask you
about make sure um did you write that
one
down I'm usually more aware of my
grammar since when I have a headache the
words reverberate my head um then why
not listen to them in there and go into
your meditation and Center yourself and
get your answers there rather than
creating an echo out
here thank you thank
you enjoy
yourself I will huh I will I promise you
what you
what I will you what I promise you want
I will are you here and now yes what is
your present tense I am I am thank you I
will
someday I am thank
you guys um I was I was married um to
Bruce Chapman and I he died
and I wanted to know why he died why
because he was through with his
life well what was what then was my
purpose with this life I guess I just
don't understand well what did you share
with each other what have you learned
and what are you still learning any
relationship once created always goes on
you are not through with the
relationship for you are still creating
your idea of that being and that being
is still reflecting to you ideas that
you are now putting into your life and
allowing yourself to assimilate so the
relationship goes on so what it is not
physical it is still a relationship now
what are you learning about this idea
and what service has he provided for you
by your cocreation of him leaving
physical reality before you have what is
it you are benefiting from by staying in
physical reality while he goes through
and does something
else well I know that I know that answer
well thank you so you wish to share it
yeah um what what I'm learning basically
is a lot about myself and very good just
really expanding in myself I thought May
there was something oh something more
important than knowing all of yourself
oh what could that be I ask one more
question point out that there are
various dimensions do you know where he
dimensions do you know where he
is all we can say is that he is not
physically
reincarnated now a portion of his
Consciousness is going to be in a sense
with you for a
while recognize that sometimes
individuals choose to be perfectly I'll
say pragmatic about your terminology to
become non-physical so that they can act
in the function of Spirit guides for
those that are still physical yeah I
feel him around a lot of the time and
and he died 12 years ago but I can still
I mean I really focus on something then
understand simply it is an opportunity
for you to continue whatever aspects of
the relationship can be continued
outside of physicality and for you to
look at yourself and use that as a
loving gift as a
reflection honor his gift by loving
yourself enough to make
it but thank you I have done
nothing oh thank
[Music]
you right did you have good
di are you still having a good
di or you really sound
exciting well I am excited I
very being
being
yeah um I had it was a very uh spiritual
experience very censoring upon myself
and got very much in touch with loving
myself which I
know idea for me to experience thank you
I very much all right anytime you choose
to love yourself I will choose to take
that as a gift thank
you that goes for all of
you continue I had a very connection and
toward the
planet
and connection didn't
[Music]
connection of course because you are
creating the connection or you would not
perceive it okay I know there's a connection
maybe I will say
[Music] this you are allowing yourself to
this you are allowing yourself to
connect to that energy though it is not
something that you associate with
directly in terms of the idea of origin
you're allowing yourself to connect to
that energy because you you believe that
the way in which you wish to be of
assistance to your Society in this
transformational life will best be
served by connecting into that energy by
utilizing what it is offering you and
also because you have so many other
acquaintances that are in this way
connected directly to that energy so you
are surrounding yourself and acting in
this way as an earth server and forming
an
association with the energy that you
perceive to be in your terminology the
one that you can I'll say identify with
the most in terms of what you want to
do do you follow me yes I
don't thank you all right now understand
also that as you simply continue with
your life if any specifics are necessary
they will be there automatically and all
you need to do to find them is keep on
mov
M all right transformation and change
transformation and change transformation
and change life life
life thank you you
question about not being judgmental
right but as far as I'm concerned judging is
but as far as I'm concerned judging is
US I've been using judging in order to
because I do not know how else to be a
responsible human being Now understand
that there is a difference between
judging and
preferring preference is not an
invalidation it is simply knowing what
vibrates more harmoniously
with what it is you want to do this does
not mean that you invalidate everything
else it simply means you choose what
reflects more accurately the ideas you
want to reflect you can prefer something
without judging everything else you
follow me I follow you but I think I uh
I think I
uh I expressed myself think correctly
because you don't understand what I'm
what I'm talking about is
simply put I
have I have to take care of several
other people in my life I support three
four other people so the weight of the
responsibility is present with me very
often why do you create it to be a
weight why is it not a
joy you have co-created the situation
with them why are you not enjoying
sharing with them why do you feel them
to be a
burden I can't enjoy it at all time it
would be why not I don't know all right
that's a
start would you like to I then go ahead
thank you it is as simple as that when
you say well I would love to in that
moment you are capable of doing so
because you recog ize the vibration that
it takes to do so and then in the very
next second you say
but which separates you from where you
were a moment ago when you said why not
I doubt sometimes my ability all right
very good you are judging yourself right
now let me ask you
this if you do not choose to believe
that you you know what you are
doing do you think that they might have
known what they were doing when they
chose to be with you I think they do
well then why doubt yourself obviously
they think they're with the perfect
person or they wouldn't be with you so
why doubt that you have the ability to
interact with them in whatever way you
both agreed or all agreed
to you don't have to try simply by being
who and what you are you fulfill your
part of the bargain
and if you have any doubts then that at
the time you create them is also part of
the bargain and allows them to see
reflected in you back to them some of
the ideas they also chose to explore and
understand about the reality into which
they were
born then in allowing everything in the
relationship to serve the purpose of the
relationship and not feel that somehow
you are of disservice to the agreement
that you made you will allow yourself to
automatically see how everything is of
service and then you will take the
weight off yourself you will not push
yourself you not have to try so hard you
don't not have to try to be who you are
it is the simplest thing in creation it
is all you actually can be you are never
not who you are no matter what you are
doing therefore recognize simply that you you
therefore recognize simply that you you
knew what you were doing when you chose
to form this relationship they all knew
what they were doing when they chose to
form the relationship and together you
all know what you are doing when you
begin to take that for granted you can
enjoy the relationship for what it is
and not what you think it should be and
then when you stop judging the
relationship it will become what you
wanted to
be you follow me
mhm now it is
that simple unless you choose to look at
it as
otherwise that is up to you but anything
you do will still be part and parcel of
the overall ideas that you chose to
examine by creating that relationship
and they know it
too otherwise you would not be
together these things are simply not
accidental
follow me I am thank you thank you guys
okay um the Triad of the association yes I
um the Triad of the association yes I
assume there are other associations of
other planets and other yes in the
universe yes are they all Tri
orles they are whatever their idea of
symbology makes fit and once once they
are totally Blended like out is totally
planet do they then combine with others
yes um once your the planet that are
existing in force density I assume once
you're in for density there's no more
war disease all that no matter where you
are no thank you I mean not just
necessarily but in other on other
planets too there is to some degree
still the ability in fourth density or
at least in what I will call the very
beginnings of it to still create some
idea of that separation but beyond that
no okay now are there planets that are
in third densities in thir density whose
technology has advanced to the extent
that they actually have space whatever
where they can C where they can go
beyond um you
um you
know light use yes and do they are there
planets that actually come to other
planets in a
in a
sense recognize again that though it may
symbolically seem like planets are being
conquered no one can be conquered if
they do not vibrate to the idea that
they can be and thus you will find that
the so-called best Safeguard to that
idea is to Simply know that you are not
of that vibration of that idea and they
not being of the same reality will never
f find
you they come to what represents your
planet to them it will not be inhabited
to them right yeah well I'm just asking
to see you know how much of science
fiction stories we read uh a lot of it
seems very plausible in a sense but you
are making many metaphors which you are
taking literally and it is not the case
you are using that as a symbol to allow
yourself to
know that what is offered to
you as the idea of their negativity you
can simply accept as that as an offering
of a gift of a way of life and you can
say well no thanks you can offer them
back the idea of your
positivity you will not exist in the
same vibration if they do not exist well
I'm going to play it for myself I'm just
curious in general all right but again
understand there is no such thing as
idal curiosity and what you are
examining has purpose within you or you
would not even have considered the idea
yes I'm understanding oh let them know
what the purpose is can you tell me it
is only your willingness to reflect at
this time the idea so that it could be
realized in the totality of the group as
it
exists okay thank you oh thank you now very
now very
briefly the can you explain a little bit
the advantages of aligning the energies
in the body in the morning by either
doing sit-ups or arching and pping the
back by standing on your hands and knees
now you can create again like anything
any kind of a tool any kind of a ritual
if it has validity for you it will do
for you whatever your imagination tells
you it is doing for you are creating
that idea to do so now in a mass
conscious sense because many of you are
connected in that way you can say what
you are doing is forming an idea of the
alignment of all your chakra points so
that the idea of that overall energy in
your spine can go to all the branches of
your body and filter out into your oric
field so that you in the breathing
pattern are harmonizing and
synchronizing yourself with what you
perceive to be the foundation vibration
of all that is you follow
me
no recognize that many of you have
discussed with us the
idea of the interaction of your Society
with our society physically and the
interactions that have taken place with
other societies are taking place now and can
societies are taking place now and can
take place physically upon your planet
and in this way we have discussed many
times the odd idea that you know that
your governments and your media in many
areas are very well aware of our
existence but because you have created
your governments do take responsibility
of your lives for you then you have said
yes we want to be kept in the dark
therefore it is now your
opportunity not your
order only a
suggestion that you can begin in your
imagination to create conversations
which you may memorize you may write
them down you may take them however you
wish and you may go to the people in
your media now recognize there are many
media now recognize there are many
sightings of spacecraft from many
different civilizations all the time on
your planet and they are aware of a
large majority of these
pigh they choose
not to print them in this way they are
told not to print
them in this way since you know that
these things are ongoing without
Force without without
condemning Without
accusing but only from unconditional
love and a willingness to understand and
share and cocreate and let them know
that you support them and that they
would be appreciated on your level by
supporting you in that way that you can
go to your media and you can ask them
the reasons for why they have chosen to
suppress the
information involve them in conversation
of a loving nature letting them know
that the more of you that already know
the less reason for them to not print
what they know
will be something you want to read which
is after all why they are in that
business therefore you understand the
idea of public
opinion if you all are willing to
express to them that you know this is
occurring and that they do not have to
hide these ideas then they will be more
eager to be aware of these interactions
and print them for you so that it is
forming a
co-creation of conviction from both
polarities that you have created in your
Society making you the media and making
the media you making you the government
and the government you which is what the
original idea we assume was to be to
begin with mean
with mean
now all it takes is
conviction and unconditional
love that is it willingness to be who
you are to speak about what you know is
in your heart Without accusing without
condemning without expecting them to
listen but just letting them know who
and what you are and where you stand and
what reality you believe in then if they
choose to share that reality with you
then you will have given them an
opportunity to do so otherwise how will
they know
they will feed you what they think you
want to
read Because you tell them no
different you follow me
me
therefore if you
wish only again as a suggestion but
because you are in your terms more than
one in
number allow yourself to know that
because you think of it that way
if each and every one of you went to the
same media Source at different times
they would begin to understand that
something's going
on and that there is an
interest and that all these individuals
that have come to them have not come
waving their fingers have not come
condemning them and accusing them but
have come seeking sharing loving
suggesting creative ways
that they may allow themselves to print
what they know is going on and let it be
all right to do
so do you follow
me by doing that it will be one way that
you can equalize yourselves so that we
may physically interact with
you not that that should be a goal
understand that not that that should be
a goal for your world is your own you do
not need
us but we can
share if you are
willing that is up to
you and if you do not do
this it will not make me love you any
less understand
understand
yourselves support yourselves and
recognize that there are no accidents as
you create your ecstatic explosions of
coincidence all synchronicity in your
lives occurs for a reason and that
reason is your
reason everything is Reve for
you when you recognize yourself as all
that is nothing is hidden love
hidden love
yourselves with the totality the same
totality that all that is loves you and
you will know you are the same
vibration you will become the knowing
you that is equal and capable of
carrying on
conversations with any being or entity
or level or Dimension or
Consciousness that you may have
previously considered to be somewhere
above you out of your grasp beyond your understanding you
understanding you
are the Christ
Consciousness you are
children of God and you are your own
parents as
well it does not matter how you choose
to know
this but know it you
do and it is for the reason that you do
know you are
God that you do everything that you do
for ultimately you know you are
indestructible and ultimately it does not matter in
and ultimately it does not matter in
what way you explore the idea that you
are as all
values for exist you
do and exist you always
will and that is why I say that your
civilization and our civilization is the
sharing that continues forever
we thank you for your loving gift of
expressing each unique facet of your
being and sharing that with us for then
for us it grants us the ability to be
aware of that much more of all that is
for all beings to partake of in Joy love
and light we thank you all we bid you all
light we thank you all we bid you all
good night