Oh my. How are you all this evening of
your time as you create time to exist?
In this way, we will begin this evening
interaction with the idea of
transformation. In this way, you can all begin to
In this way, you can all begin to
recognize that the cycles you have
created in your physiological reality
will invoke patterns in the material
day-to-day experiences that you are
creating your lives to be. And now can
be seen for many of you are exploring
the idea of the blending of different
levels of your conscious senses to take
place and reflect to you these patterns
in the forms of
transformations in the ideas, the
habits, the patterns, the day-to-day
experiences you have lived for so long.
You will now understand that many ideas
you're experiencing may seem to be being
uprooted in your lives and in this way
destabilizing what has always been for
you seemingly a foundation upon which
you could rely. In this way recognize it
is not so much that you are becoming
unstable but that you are simply
recognizing that change is becoming your
stability. Because in this way, the idea
of the fourth density transformation,
the blending of your consciousness will
invoke and create you to be an
individual being who always will allow
themselves to transform into whatever it
is they need to be to allow themselves
to be the idea that they chose to be in
this physical material world in which
you have chosen to live. Thus, change
being the only constant in the universe
will become your staple, will become
your foundation. You may find at first
that because of simply the ideas you are
holding on to, the things you have made
attachments to. The way you you're used
to thinking of things that it may seem
at first to be unsettling, upsetting,
upside downing in this way,
disorientating in this way, confusing.
But again, simply recognize that these
ideas are only part and parcel of your
ability to now consciously realize that
you are unlocking from one viewpoint one
reality, one idea of what you think life
is all about and allowing yourself to
reorient into new modes of perceiving
the idea of what it is to even be a
being in physical materiality. All of
these concepts in this way, what you
have for so long considered the idea of
being physically real to be now you are
beginning to understand are all based on
assumptions and that that is only one
way that you can exist in a physical
materiality. All of the ideas that you
have for so long held to be the
cherished laws of your universe are now
being seen to be the agreed upon ideas
that you have all decided to experience
to create the illusion for the idea that
you have all agreed upon in physical
reality because you made the choice to
experience limitation. You made the
choice to experience the idea of
forgetting that you are the creator of
your reality so that you could explore
that particular corner, I shall say, of
all that is because limitation is one of
the ways you can experience creation.
Now you are at the end of the cycle of
limitation and begin to create the idea
of the recognizing of integration, the
blending of all levels of your existence
in the embodiment that you now consider
yourself to be. this aspect of your soul
self upon what you call your physical
planet Earth. As you allow yourself to
do so, all of the previously
preconceived notions about what reality
should be, what you have experienced
reality to be are all finding themselves
dissolving like what you call your
proverbial house of cards. In this way,
laying down a new understanding that
everything in your physical materiality
is and is becoming as malleable as the
reality you perceive in what you call
your dream state. Because your physical
reality is the product of your dream
state. Only you have created it in your
belief structure to seemingly be a more
solidified one. You are dreaming right
now. There is no difference between this
reality you call physical and any
reality you call the i.e. of your
non-physical dream state reality except
that you give yourself the opportunity
to create the difference in the
definition physical non-physical that
definition is the only thing that
creates there to be a difference. And
now many of you are finding that as you
are blending and redefining the terms of
your reality, recognizing that reality,
your physical reality is not something
that exists without you, but is only the
product of what you believe your reality
to be. You are now allowing yourself to
gather to your conscious realization the
notion that your physical reality can
become anything you desire it to be,
anything you imagine it to be. And as
such, when you allow yourself to begin
to blend, the cognition that your dream
reality and your physical reality can
both come to terms, can be meeting on
equal levels within the dimension of
your imagination. Then many of the ideas
you have here to for considered only to
be dreams will become more solid. Many
of the ideas you have here only decided
to be physical reality and solid will
become more dreamlike, more surreal as
you use that terminology until you allow
yourself to know in your conscious
awareness that they will both blend
within the dimension of your
imagination. And in that dimension,
everything in your reality that you have
for so long desired to be possible is
possible. And you can allow yourself to
avail yourself of all the probable
realities. You will then consciously
allow yourself to recognize you are as a
being by definition. In this way, in
what you call your literature, when it
is said in your own words that you are
made in the image of the creator, do not
forget that the creator that all that is
is a
multi-dimensional idea. And in this way,
you are and every being in creation is
made in the image of the creator in that
way. And therefore, every being exists
on every level, every dimension, every
parallelity that there is. And in this
way you are simply understanding that
all that you are learning about
yourselves in the blending of the
transformations now taking place is not
so much learning anything new but only
remembering more and more and more of
all that you already are existing at all
these different levels. You are
discovering more of yourself integrating
owning all of these ideas and therefore
allowing yourself even while you have
created an aspect to exist in physical
reality. In owning that cognition, then
even the aspect of you that exists in
physical reality will create a
harmonious synchronous reflection of
that cognition of the knowledge that you
exist on every level. And therefore,
even in physical reality, you will be
able to know that you can live your
dreams and create the phrase in your
terminology, heaven upon earth. Are you
all following along? Yes. In this way,
therefore, recognize that all of the
transformations you may now see
accelerating around you in this way are
all symptomatic, so to speak, all part
and parcel of the idea of the path you
have always desired to be. Do not fear
in this way. But should you find
yourself fearing, then simply recognize
that any fear that comes up for you is
simply a message and a messenger
bringing you one more piece of the self
you have forgotten. so that you can know
the totality of your consciousness.
Treat your fear as a friend bringing you
more and more and more awareness of all
the different portions you have for so
long shut out of your reality. Now when
you accept the different pieces that
your fear brings to you, then you will
no longer fear in that way in a negative
sense and you will allow all the
transformations in your life to take
place in a positive effect. You will
allow every incident, every situation,
every relationship, every opportunity in
your life to be representative of the
path you chose to be and not an
interruption in it. Since you will
understand that there is no such thing
as an interruption and that you are not
on a path that can be interrupted. You
are the path that you are on. You are
the path that you are living. You cannot
be off of yourself. Everything that you
experience in your life is, if you are
willing to view it in that way, a part
of the path you chose to be. Should you
decide to view the situation as
negative, then that will automatically
bring with it the inability to recognize
that the situation is a part of the
path. Because viewing it from a negative
point of view automatically brings with
it the definition of forgetting, of
limitation, of not allowing yourself to
know you are connected, that you are
creating every single situation in your
lives. And that it all is there for the
purpose of serving you. To let you know,
to allow you to realize you are the
multi-dimensional creators of the
reality that you experience. That you
are self-empowered. That you have the
control. That your lives are what you
wish them to be in this way. And you can
partake in ecstasy and joy. All of the
ideas you have held in your hearts and
desire to experience for so long. For
now, the tens of thousands of your years
of counting, of the cycle of limitation,
are at an end, and you are beginning the
adventure into yourselves, the
recognition and the fruition of all you
have ever imagined or dreamed to be
possible within this physical reality.
For this is, in a sense, the purpose for
which you began the exploration and
limitation in this physical reality you
call your planet Earth. And now you have
arrived once again in your
reincarnational state, to participate in
a most joyous reunion. That reunion
being the reunion of all portions of
yourself. You follow me?
Sure. Yes. Um, just the other night we
had a home and
afterwards and the last part of the
difference there was very faint a bunch
of
very large
And we were wondering if
you found only at this time once again
we will remind you what we have said
about the idea of the combination of the
red and green vibration being the
connection of your heart and the
connection of the recognition of the
transformation of your planet earth
which is represented by the emerald ray
vibration. At this time you are simply
seeing within your own consciousness the
alteration of your perceptions and
looking through gateways into other
dimensions or levels of yourself.
Volir. It is also connected to some
degree to some of the ideas we discussed
about Polaris and Volir. In this way, do
Polaris and Volir. In this way, do
recognize that because you have created
the notion of the ideal patterns and
cycles, you will now find in this way
that at least in a generalized sense,
what you now call your eighth, your
ninth, and your 10th months will see the
idea of much upheaval in terms of
lifestyle, much change in the idea of
individuals of yourselves and
individuals that you know. Allow
yourselves to be of service to any
individual who now finds themselves
interacting with you and expressing to
you their confusion or the idea that
everything in their lives seems to be
changing, unhinging, unlocking, falling
apart. For allow yourself to recognize
that these three months following in
this way. 8 9 and 10 are your mass
consciousness recognition patterns and
the unlocking of the energy that will
take place followed by the idea of 11 12
and 1 and the transformation through a
large energy gate into what you call the
idea 1,987 which shall be a year of
realization and manifestation on many
different levels. The spring bringing
with it one of the largest
transformational doorways upon your
planet altogether. All right.
You have created this
momentum. Feel the pulse of your own
self empowerment.
It is the pilgrim
briefly. Um, we have a sphere in our
house and recently I heard some information
and recently I heard some information
regarding that which
um I was told
from the um the area secret
in this way. First of all, recognize it
is not so much the idea of a
physiological representation from
somewhere else but an identification to
somewhere else through a representative
symbol on your own pilot.
So when I was actually
only in the form of energy
identification no it
the blending of the green and the white
again your planetary energy of the
emerald ray mixed with the idea of the
white light vibration of transformation. No.
Okay. Then the last thing is um I'm
happy with my my
for rejuvenating.
And what does it ask?
First of all, of course, understand that
like any physiological symbol, it works
because you believe in it. If you do not
believe in it, it does not work.
It is simply one more manifestation to
some degree of a recognition on one of
the individuals in your planetary sphere
of influence's part to recognize that
there are a blending or a combination of
idea of liquid forms in that way and
energy forms that might represent a mass
consciousness understanding of alignment
within the body and revitalization to
some degree. It is a stimulation of
certain cellular structures in this way.
But once again to understand that more
and more many of these things may come
about but more and more you will also
find that many of the things that are
being created by different individuals
in your planet may have relevance to
those individuals but not necessarily to
the masses for they are all valid for the
masses for they are all valid for the
individual who allowed their imagination
to cocreate that idea to some degree
although once again in the idea of the
timing taking place. There will also be
many individuals who have formed within
themselves the idea of a negative
confusion about what all of these
symbols mean and in this way may be
reading more into a symbol than they are
willing to take responsibility for the
action themselves.
following in this way he was going to
find that it is one more thing you can
feel so inclined to experiment with our
perception in this way is that the idea
once again of unlocking the crystallin
energy in purified water will be just as
beneficial forward the idea of simply
imparting your blue white
electromagnetic oric field into purified
water knowing that you have crystized
ize that idea as an externalized symbol
of the master crystal you are. And then
in that way ingesting the water and
feeling the alignment of your oric field
and the imbument and the radiation of
your blue white energy will perform the
same type of
symbological centering and clearing and
crystallizing as any other idea invented
so to speak out of the imagination of
any individual upon your planet. It all
in a sense boils down to that archetypal
symbol of the water anywhere. No matter
what the concoction
following simply what you would refer to
in your language as purified water in
water in
rather than telling information in this
way. Do recognize of course that by
definition any other level of
consciousness from yourself or anywhere
else so to speak that is going to be
connecting with you by definition must
have an interest in you. I mean it
speaks a lot about it it you know caring
for me and what it seems to me. Do
recognize that what you are allowing
yourself to do right now is form an
identification with many portions of
your own higher consciousness which in
turn will reflect back to you your
worthiness and validity and ability for
unconditional love and respect towards
yourself so that you can make other
connections. You are going to be in
touch and are in touch with different
levels of other consciousness. But
primarily what you are now perceiving
are different levels of your own higher
consciousness that are being reflected
back to you in ways to allow you to
validate yourself. That is why it seems
to be so interested in you because you
are interested in validating yourself.
You follow me? Thus, it will always, as
any guide will do, reflect to you those
portions of the ideas that you most
need, so that you know that the interest
that is there is an indication of your
willingness now to show the same
interest for you from yourself. You
follow me? Oh yeah, I feel awful lot of
the love that speaks up towards me from
myself while I'm channeling a You are
acclimating just fine. Again, it is not
so much the need for the idea of
labeling anything, but in this way,
allow yourself to simply participate in
whatever type of interaction seems to be
taking place. Allow the emotions to come
through. It will all be for the purpose
of the idea of blending and accelerating
yourself into more of your being. Do you
know anything of this particular entity?
Other than what we have just shared with
you, now is not the time.
For in this way, it would only be
imposing more labels, right? and causing
more separation. There will be an
opportunity later for more clarification
in that way. But you will find in this
sense that the more you simply trust
whatever interaction you have chosen to
be a part of, the less you will need to
label it. It will simply come in
whatever manner it needs to and will
simply fit into whatever interactions
need to occur for whom it must interact
with. All right.
Find it. Nice. You talked earlier in
your introduction about parallel
parallel lives. Am I at this time
experiencing parallel lives? If so, can
you describe? You are not experiencing
parallel lives. The oversoul has many
aspects and fragments that are parallel
to the fragment you are here. You follow
me? Yes. So, does that make sense to
you? What impact does that have on me in this
What impact does that have on me in this
mindset? You allow yourself the idea of
what you call bleed through to some
degree to allow yourself to simply feel
connections in many different levels in
many different experiences that you may
require to allow yourself to draw from
the knowledge bank of the total you so
that you can simply act in this life
instinctively as you can also do in
other lives instinctively as they draw
from your experiences here. Can you give
me an example of a parallel life that my
over soul is experiencing in addition to
mine? The idea that you call
surgeon more than that
too. Why do you need to know more?
Because I at this point I'm interested.
Why? Because things are influencing me.
No, no, no, no,
no. Influences you but you. You choose
to be influenced. All right. I'm I
choosing to be influenced. Why? Because
what knowledge? All right. Then in that
way, allow yourself to trust that your
imagination is your tunnel, is your
conduit. Go through it and explore
freely. You are not looking for
accuracy. There is no one background
against which to measure anything that
you discover in your imagination as
being more valid than something else.
Anything you form a connection to has
validity for what you need to know. Now
follow your excitement. I do. Oh, uh,
another question is what are the
functions of the pituitary gland in the
human body and do you have that? There
are many ideas of function. In this way,
we have a representation to some degree.
Yes. In this way, you will find that
along with other portions of the brain
and other glandular systems in your
body, it will form an energy foundation
to allow there to be a balancing of
electromagnetic energy that you partake
of on your planetary sphere to create
from consciousness. The idea you call
mentality or mind in physical reality.
Mind is the physical reality's version
of non-physical consciousness and it is
created through the balancing effects of
those glandular systems.
How do you stimulate your pituitary
gland to be more active? Your imagination. Is
to be more active? Your imagination. Is
that the only way? No, but it is the
simplest. Are there other ways? Whatever
your imagination comes up
with. Again, understand the idea is that
if you find yourself attracted to
certain substances in your reality, such
as
leithm, such
leotril, such
as what you call f human
You will find that many of these ideas
along with what you call some mineral
ideas saying iron, copper, magnesium,
small amounts will form some association to
amounts will form some association to
stimulation of certain ideas in that
area. So will certain forms of
magnetism. So will certain forms of
electricity. In this way, so will
certain crystallin forms in that sense.
But in this way, recognize that each and
every one of those
symbiological ideas are only an
externalized reflection of your
imagination's ability to cohesively come
up with an external representation of
what your imagination is doing. Anyway,
the vibration of your imagination is the
conduit to your so-called higher self
itself. And in this way, if you simply
allow the energy through directly, you
will not need to have it rrooted into an
external symbol and then back to you.
You follow me? Is that why people use
crystals? Yes. At this time, it is a more rarified
Yes. At this time, it is a more rarified
external symbol than many you have been
using because it is almost an energy
state itself. Thus, though it is still a
itself. Thus, though it is still a
symbol, it is to some degree more
rarified than many of the ideas you have
been experiencing upon our planet. such
as the ingestion of medications and
other ideas, but it is still an external
ideas, but it is still an external
symbol. You are your own master crystal.
Always understand that in this way the
so-called foundation or entry point of
your consciousness while it is supported
by the idea of the pineal and the pituitary the
hypothalamus are all supporting
balancing systems for the idea that your
consciousness first creates connection
to what you call your physiological
brain through the very center the
membrane brain you call the corpusc
colossum. For in this way you will find
that there is a whole different
understanding and structure in your
brain that you have yet to discover. The
idea of all the separating membranes
that so to speak sectionalize the brain
are in and of themselves the actual
supporting framework through which the
consciousness is first routed before it
differentiates into the cellular
clusters that represent what you think
are the actual actuating mechanisms of
mentality but are not. Sure. One
Sure. One
moment. Will I have been of assistance
to you? I think I got confused.
I I I understand what you said. I
understand the words, but I have to
think about All right. Enjoy. Thank you.
Could you say something about
in this way you will find that it will
be a balancing to a certain
type of mineralized electromagnetic
balance within your system and supply
some electrolytic balance within your
system. It is a
regulator of a type that has to do with
the idea
of r-rooting of offflow of
resonance. In a sense though the idea of
the tonsils may be more representative
of a different type of switching
mechanism whereas the appendix in this
way will be more of an assimilating
mechanism. Now the
idea for a moment again of what we have
been discussing as the foundation of the
brain structure the seeming separations in the
structure the seeming separations in the
clusters actually being the foundation
will have a degree of similarity to the
recognition your society scientifically
is beginning to understand with what it
calls strings. You follow me?
your idea in what you call
physics, astrophysics. Strings being the
astrophysics. Strings being the
representation of the
primal conduits that give validity to
the clusters that you call solid
space-time reality, but that within
themselves are not representative of any
space and time at
all. More on that later. just the
hypobatic because there is a correlation
between the way your physical brain is
set up and the way strings interact
within the physiological universe
supplying connections and conduits from
many other universes at the same time
like the black holes but differ
I have a baby who experienced oxygen
deprivation at birth consequently
suffered brain damage uh she has what's
called cerebal palsy
Um, I'm trying to understand for one
thing why it is that supposedly anyway
the brain is the only structure in the
body that once the cells die they're
dead. This is not so. It's not so. No.
Can you tell me anything? You are
beginning in your own society to begin
to understand this idea. more of what
you call oxygen and more of what you
call silicon and
silicon and
more of some electro magnetic and
electrical activity along with with
nitrogen and
carbon can
be manufactured in this way to
provide more of the building blocks that
are required for the recomposition of
the cellular structure of your brain.
In this way, you will find that it is
simply that you have not yet supplied
the proper soil, so to speak, for the
proper soil, so to speak, for the
idea of what you consider to be the
rarified cellular structure of your
brain to take advantage of within your
mass consciousness to allow itself to
draw from the mass consciousness energy
pool to restructure
itself. In this way you can also
understand that every thought that
exists, every thought that you
have rewires physically rewires the
neuronic pathways in your
brain. Allow yourself first of all to
recognize that the individual you call
your child has chosen a form of
limitation to allow other individuals
around himself to also reach further
into their own understanding of
communication within themselves. and you
can recognize that you can be in
communication with that individual on
other levels. Doing so may in and of
itself create a type of electromagnetic
atmosphere wherein that individual may
not require any longer that particular
manifestation in physical reality and
can rewire the entire pattern to
function in whatever form it needs to.
for do recognize that your physicists
and your medicinal practitioners have
already discovered in many cases that
you do not require all of the
physiological brain in order to simply
have full capacity.
Yeah, I did see a thing on television
about uh people they discovered from CAT
scans that were only a small portion of
their brain was actually in use and yet
they had total motor control and and had
high IQs and it was this total puzzle.
That is simply because it has not been
understood completely yet that the idea
of the brain is by nature holographic
and that is every portion contains the
whole. All you need to do is rearrange
your ideas about this. You can
communicate with that being and allow
them to come out of the shell they have
created for the purpose of allowing you
to delve further into your shell. All right. All right.
Okay.
What is the harmonic resonance of the
brain? Can you um you're painting a
model for me of the harmonic resonance
of the molecular structure of the brain.
Can you go on? It will to some degree be
attached to the 7 and 1/2 cycle per
second idea of the earth vibration.
Although there will be variations within
this to allow it to manifest some
differences. In this way the
sub frequency modulations will be
approximately around eight or nine. That
is why you will find that the general
ideas of when you approached 10 cycles
per second in what you call your delta
frequency will put you almost out of
your body because you are now forming a
harmonic resonance with the very
intrusion or introduction of
consciousness into physical reality at
all. So you would agree then uh that learning
So you would agree then uh that learning
harmonics and how
harmonics say in music are it is one way
to unlock the very essence of your
physical reality. Thank you. Thank you.
Yes. One more time. Continue with child.
Oh, I'm sorry. Yes, I can.
Um, oh, on your planet, do you have ways
technologically, so to speak, of dealing
with brain damage? We do not have brain
damage. Oh, it never occurs.
In this way, simply recognize it is a
tool we do not need. So, it does not
occur. So, it never occurs. No. Do you
foresee um uh I think so anyway. I kind
of see it the idea of science as you're
developing actual physical handling it.
Oh yes. But do understand. Yes. Soon as
soon as you wish. Sure. One moment. Do
understand that anything that occurs in
your physical reality as a socalled
medical cure is only an external
reflection for the fact that you now
believe that it is possible to do that.
And thus the cure itself isn't even
necessary if you would realize that
medically speaking. You follow me? Yes.
It
just this is is real to me on a certain
level. It's just you still hear so much
so much agreement or beliefs the idea
understand it is simply a matter of
priorities in your system the system you
have created your society to be and also
understand that if it is real in your
reality you can experience this idea far
and away before the majority of your
civilization does it is up to you. You
will simply attract yourself to the
situations that are necessary for you to
participate in whatever type of
experience you can be willing to
co-create. You've all Yes. There's a
lady uh named Margaret Eric who works
with people that have brain damage
in doing real work. Do you mean that you
have attracted yourself to information
back? that you coincidentally allowed
yourself and yourself to interact with
individuals around you that have all the
information you need thereby allowing
you to know you are not isolated in your
situation that you can gain all the
information that you require in your
life simply through all the individuals
that you interact with because they are
representative of all the different
portions of yourself you are willing to
look at yeah I thought it was kind of
neat when you started talking about the
brain and I come here to ask these
questions and all of a sudden we were
talking about the brain and I went all
right thank Thank you very much for your
willingness. Thank you. Heart stood.
Yes. Energy gates representations of the
crystallization of certain portions of
your mass conscious self-consciousness.
We're expected to have a big one in
research. You are who expected? I don't
know. That's what I heard. Ah, what you
I don't never expected. Thank you. then
it is not in your reality and you will
not experience it no matter who else
does. Recognize in out of perception
this is your opportunity to decide what
you prefer to be your reality and not to
create the idea of the reinforcement of
what you might perceive to be the
release in negative ways through your
feelings. In this way, to some
degree also through many of the
individuals in your society, we can from
time to time assimilate some of the
information and quote unquote keep you
posted. But in this way, do recognize
that any recognition in that sense is
only a sensing of the energy that
is in existence at the time the
so-called prediction is made and does
not in any way, shape, or form mean it
cannot change according to your desire
to change it.
Relax. Do understand that many of you
have chosen to live where you do
geographically upon your planet because
you like living on the edge. Therefore,
you will use the energy and channel it
through yourselves in constructive ways
and will allow yourselves to rroot that
energy into creativity. Now we will at
this time share with you a physiological
time share with you a physiological
symbol
of you may find it
enjoyable if we take what you call a
spirit ical quartz
crystal and what you call a tube of
steel and around that sleeving that on
the outside jacketing it a tube of
copper.
Place the quartz crystal in the end of
the tube so that it is attached
snugly. Drive the tube into the ground near what
Drive the tube into the ground near what
you call a
fault. It can be a radiator for much of
the energy and release it in positive
ways. Right? You follow me? You may also
find that there are many other devices
that have existed upon your planet and
have been utilized in many civilizations
that take advantage of the harmonic
resonances of your electromagnetic
field. Such as what you
might view as stone wells that have a
bottom that do not seem to be for any
purpose sunken into the ground. These
are resonating cavity chambers which you
can also duplicate out of what you call
bricks round 6 ft in diameter 10 ft 12
ft in
diameter approximately the idea again 6
or 12 ft deep whatever the diameter that
is the depth and in this way sunken into
the ground with a little bit of a wall
up around it perhaps no more than 3 ft
high these brick Pits can also be
resonating chambers to allow there to be
the capturing so to speak of the energy
in that way of the earth vibrations and
placed in the middle of that chamber.
The two poles with the crystal sunken
into the ground at least 6 ft into the
ground at least 3 ft above the ground or
above the bottom of the pit.
These can function as energy release
valves. Yes. Sound energy. Vibrational energy.
Yes. Sound energy. Vibrational energy.
Sure. This is happening now. Are people
actually taking advantage of this at
this point of the energy? Yes. Many.
Yes. Yeah. In a specific way of a
crystal ball in the uh cylinder. No.
This is our sharing to you as our
perception of what your mass
consciousness can take advantage of as a
symbol to reflect how it is willing to
now allow some of the energy to be
rechanled in positive ways. Let's do it.
Is wonderful enough.
It will depend upon what you think of
the fault. In this way you will find
that the idea can simply
be in one
area. Any area along what you consider
to be a major fault. Any area that you
feel intimate with in terms of its
proximity to you. You can
place along one
side or both
sides anywhere from three to seven
pips in whatever arrangement seems
appropriate. Always there being more on
one side than another. How long are
supposed the the tubing supposed to be
at least in your terms? Once again 9 ft
for there to be 6 ft in the earth and 3
ft above. And how how large of a ball?
In this way it will suffice for the idea
of 6 ft in diameter though you can do 12
ft in diameter. The ball the sphere.
Yes. The crystal the crystal crystal in
this way can simply be the
idea. What you call six of your inches
to 1 ft.
anywhere in that
range. Preferably either the six or the
12. Sure.
Um would you be willing to
suggest some means by which I could even
out some of the um energy that I'm
experiencing? Even out blended in. Well,
I feel that it's mostly Yes. Yes.
Sit up straight. Right Right
now. All
right. Inhale. Exhale. Feel the
inhalation of energy in your solar
plexus. Exhale it through your
mouth in your imagination at this time.
Allow yourself to invoke the balancing
of your energy field. Your blue white
electromagnetic energy field. See it as
a sphere around you, completely around
you. Allow it to contain shades of what you
Allow it to contain shades of what you
would
call polished granite
gray, shiny, thin, shiny, thin,
crystallin,
luminescent, but
solid. Feel the balancing of the
earth. Understand that you are an
extension of your planet.
and that any energy in your terms that
you feel to be overwhelming for the
extension that you are is safely
absorbed by the majority of the crystal
of your
world. Always and only
always do you, as a crystallin extension
of your world, ever receive only just
enough to allow you to function in a
comfortable state of existence to form
one of the
poles that extends from the surface of
your planet skyward that connects up to
all the other poles on your planet that
you call all the individual beings upon
it. You are a terminal in that way.
You receive only your own
share. Allow the rest to be balanced in
all the other individuals on your world
through the opaces of the planet
itself. Know that you are a harmonious
crystallin form of love and
form of love and
light. And
breathe. Breathe.
Breathe. Move. Breathe.
Relax. Breathe. Love. The love of your
world. In and out. Feel
it. Always connected, never
separated. Thank you. How do you feel?
As you move through life, understand
that whether you take steps and remove
one foot at a time from the surface, you
are always still
connected. There is always a
pulse, a shaft of energy from you to the
planet, from the planet to
you, an unbreakable and unbendable rod.
What happens if you jump in here? It is
still there. For the atmosphere is also
only an extension of your
planet. You are extended from the planet
into the air so that there can be the
radiance of the charge from the planet
into the air through the terminal that
you
are. You follow me? Yeah.
Thank you. Nice. We've talked about
levitation before, physical levitation.
I see that if you can consciously
unbalance the say the etheric flux
around you, you can levitate your
body. Um if if consciousness is
connected to the primordial field we're
talking about um then that means that
the force vectors involved in this field
can be modulated by your thought. Nice.
And if that can be done those are
probably imagine longitudinal waves with
frequencies that aren't electromagnetic
in nature at all but say
electrogravitational nature which is one
way. Okay. That implies that there's
also magneto gravitational waves in a
sense. Can you I've never I don't know
any of the manifestations in a real
world. Can you can you describe
something uh how would that manifest
itself in a real world magnet
[Music]
gravitational to some degree what you
refer to rarely as ball
lightning? Spherical lightning that
floats. It is in your world rare because
it is an interaction of certain forced
vectors that do not need a high degree
of consistency in your world.
Yes. But they will from time to time
form apex points that will allow such a
manifestation to take place.
Is this something weird
in a sense? Although again the idea from
time to time you will find may have a
spontaneous action in this way in what
you call some of your cases of
combustion. In this sense simply
recognize that the idea is that you will
connect into whatever buffering zones
are necessary to allow you to interact
with it in a non-destructive way.
Levitation may be one manifestation of
that, but it carries with it the idea of
a buffering zone in a sense, though that
may or may not be consciously in the
belief system of the idea of the
individual doing it.
Thank you. You sure? Yes. Um I was doing
the exercise that you were giving
Barnett and so I'm also experiencing a
quite a bit of pain in my solar plexus
or since the earthquake. Nice. One of
the questions that I wanted to explore
with you though in terms of the Orion
energy coming through. I was given the
message or what came through was
something about I shall no longer carry
the burden of my people when a
so do you feel lighter?
No. Uh well I've been uh having like
high fever and and acceleration fourth
density symptoms extremely since the
earthquake and I do experience them
though as as pain. It will level
out. Relax. It will level
Relax. It will level
out. It is simply that now that that
energy has been crystallized and that
burden has been removed, since you have
been straining for so long, you simply
are now surprised that you shot ahead
that fast because there's nothing
holding you
back. It was what we had referred to as
some of the elastic effect. You have
crashed through a barrier. Nothing
restrains you. You follow me? Mhm. You
will modulate your frequency.
Relax. Did this come for judgment?
Remnants. Yes. Remnants of judgment. A
shark. Has that been of assistance? Yes.
Thank you.
Cool. Blue dreams to you.
Nurse. Good. Wait. Um could you go on
about released mechanisms and how they
work to release us from uh those
stresses that we feel so much? Simply in
this way do recognize that you have as a
mass consciousness created many
different situations to occur in your
lives that will reflect when you are all
in agreement as to making let us say a
jump to another level. You increase your
energy level and therefore in a sense
transport yourself into another
dimensional aspect of yourself. You are
not the same you you used to be. All it
is is simply redefining the idea that
you are as a personality to allow the
personality to now exhibit whatever new
idea your consciousness is. Because your
personality is not who or what you are.
It is an artificial construct that acts
as your representative in physical
reality. However your consciousness now
decides to define itself can allow the
shift to occur and the release to occur
in the physiological personality
structure to be able to exemplify or
represent the new idea your
consciousness has become. All it takes
is trust, allowance, and following. Yes.
Thank you. Nice. Yes. Um yeah, I wanted
to say that
um you know, it seems that during the
summer I'm always hot and like
frequently during the our winter time
too. It's like I can never get you know
like really cool enough like to be
comfortable. And uh someone during this that uh well
And uh someone during this that uh well
one thing that may like relate to to uh
that is that I eat like I eat extremely
large amounts of hot tub constantly and
I'm wondering if that has something to
do with you know the fact that it is to
some degree a reflection as in this way
it is simply a reflection
on your part that you think you need to
move faster, faster, and faster. Oh
no. Uhhuh.
Wait a
second. So, so, so is the implications
of that to move faster or is the
implication to slow down? you know like
in a sense to slow down because the idea
is that when you super cool yourself you
become more conductive of the type of
acceleration you actually
desire. So when you cool down and
crystallize is when the energy can move
through you without creating
friction. Before me you are simply
attempting to believe that the energy
must go through you as you are faster
and faster and faster than it is
naturally inclined to do.
Sure. Wouldn't a fast also be
beneficial? Are you making a joke?
Well, like a fruit totally under.
In this way, you can recognize that it
may in your terms be of reflective
benefit for that individual. But what
does that individual think?
Oh, well, you know, sometimes I do fast,
but uh but uh but like it's really
interesting that you said that because I
tend to go real fast. I you know, it's
like I drive
uh as I think fast, move fast. I see.
I'm just very fast. You are eternal.
What's your hurry? Heat. Heat.
It was an accident that he was born
there. Uh
so I'm trying to understand what you're
saying. Is it about you know like where
do you live
now? Slow town here.
But the thing that I'm trying thing I'm
trying to ask is uh when you talk
thinking about you know uh you
about you know uh you
know you know like has less
molecular activity or you know like or
movement than uh just in a regular but
it allows energy to go through it faster
because it is crystallized in a lattice
work structure that does not create a
difficulty for the energy to find a
path. It is the paths that are
aligned. And it is not the structure
that must do the moving. It is the
energy through it that makes the
difference.
This is like a super fluid. Okay. Super
conductivity. Uhhuh.
Uhhuh.
Uh so like your recommendation is to
simply slow down.
What is your mind? You are eternal. It's
a great question, but it's like
understand again the paradox is that
when you do in fact balance out and stop
trying to push yourself, you will
experience the sensation of
acceleration. That is the
paradox. Do recognize it is not that
things speed up. That is not what
acceleration is. Things do not speed up.
You are living in the moment. And though
therefore you may have the perception
that things are speeding up by living in
the moment, it is simply that things are
not taking as much time. You are not
creating as much time
experientially. That is what makes
things seem to be speeding up. But that
is simply your bias point of view. From
the way you have always looked at things
in your physical reality. You think
acceleration is the speeding up of
something. It is the ceasing of the
creation of as much time.
You follow me? Yeah, I think I do. Live
in the moment. Enjoy every moment.
You know what you say happens when you
are having fun.
You know what I say? Time flies.
That is why because you are living in
the now and not creating as much time.
It is not that time is going by and you
just haven't noticed it. It is not that
time has sped up. You haven't created as
much in your reality. So you simply
reinsert yourself along the agreed upon
time track wherever you need
to. You skip over intervening moments.
You don't create them. Whereas others
do you follow me?
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. You v
you. How can we increase the moment?
Increase the moment. Live in it fully
live. Now expand those pools and expand.
uh can we do it by the mechanisms of the
pit in the crystal and your uh you can
do it in whatever way your imagination
is excited about doing it but once again
in that sense simply recognize if you
are doing it to try to get somewhere
better than where you think you are you
are not living in the
moment you follow
me allowing whatever it is you are doing
at any given moment to be just as
perfect as anything else you will ever
do just different is living in the
moment. You are not trying to get
anywhere. You never go
anywhere. You follow me? You simply
expand in a sense. But even that is a notion of
in a sense. But even that is a notion of
going
somewhere. It is all an idea. It is all
a shifting of perspective. What is the
movement of the moment? That is in mind.
The movement of the moment is in
recognizing that when you live in the
now, then you are infinitely
accelerated. Being infinitely
accelerated is the same thing as being
everywhere at once. Being everywhere at
once is the same thing as standing
perfectly still. You follow me? That is the
still. You follow me? That is the
movement of the moment. No movement at
all. It is the
understanding of yourself as all that is
and acting like it.
Thank you. Yes. Um, this morning when I
woke up, I woke up with incredible pain
on my right side. Incredible.
I don't know. Obviously pretty credible.
I don't know where it came from.
Where it came from. Yeah. The deal is is
that it's it's difficult. It's been
difficult to breathe all day. Whenever I
take I've been breathing every single
position when you lie down, when you
stand up, when you sit, are they all
Yeah. quote unquote difficult. Well,
uncomfortable. All right. Uncomfortable.
And so all day long I've been breathing
shallow because it's like a stabbing
pain to breathe really deep or breathe
regular. I
see. One moment.
Will you do me a favor? I'll try. Yes.
You'll what?
Yes or no? I will. Yeah. Thank you.
In your imagination right now, in your
what you call mind's
eye, will you imagine a picture of a
long, bright, gleaming, shining, sharp
blade of steel?
Okay. Do you see it? Yes. Is it
surrounded by darkness? Yes, it is.
Is there a face behind it?
No.
Can you allow yourself to imagine a face
behind it? How does it make you feel when you
it? How does it make you feel when you
do?
Okay. Neutral. All right.
Can you feel that you can communicate
with the face behind the steel?
Yeah. Kind of like communicating with
myself. All right. Do not
All right. Do not
rationalize. All right. Simply allow it
to say something to you.
What has it said?
All right. What feeling comes up in you when
right. What feeling comes up in you when
it says
so? Not what do you think you should
feel? What feeling does in fact
occur? The first feeling, the feeling
that the pain that's there or what what
is sitting there is okay. Why? Natural. Why? Natural.
Natural.
In what way?
How did such a pain become natural?
Part of me? Yes. Do you prefer it? No.
Then why have you allowed it to be a
natural part of you?
Because all day long I was just
accepting that it was there. All right.
What are you feeling?
I don't know. I feel emotional. I don't
Yes. Yes. Go ahead. Release it. Release
it. It is all right. You feel emotional
because you are using your energy
motion, your emotion. You are now
centering from the place you have now
allowed yourself to
face. It is all right to feel the energy
flow through you. It will not deplete
you. It will not drain you as you were
drained of your life's blood. blood.
Forgive
yourself and anyone else you think needs
forgiving.
You are only passing through a doorway
of yourself and creating a memory in the
present of things that you wish to
forgive and equalize.
You may now
find that relationship and interaction
with individuals in your life and
individuals not yet in your life but
soon to be will now take on a new kind
of crystallin quality and brightness.
And there may not be the
apprehension of getting involved in
those types of relationships, be it the
idea you call social and or
business for fear of being stabbed.
How are you?
That was a big relief. Thank you.
Thank you for forgiving
yourself. For knowing that you deserve
the same unconditional love that all
that is thinks you deserve.
that anything you have ever experienced
has been for the purpose of allowing you
to integrate now and find joy and
ecstasy in your life. You are no longer
under the
knife. It shadow does not fall upon you
anymore.
I thank you for your willingness to
shift your perspective into a different
facet of the multi-dimensional crystal
that you are to reenter yourself and
glow from within the life force that
sustains you forever and ever and ever
and ever.
Thank you my
child. Our love to
you, the love of the universe to you and
through you. Sure.
Nice. Also the graphs, the greens and
the blues and
the squiggles and the
squiggles and the
nets, the strings you're talking
about to some degree. In this way, they
can be representative
of the matrices that represent the
connection points of all different
universes. You may interpret them in
that way. We also simply were
specifically referring to something that
is a notation in your physicists
understanding the idea that there is a
compaction of reality along lines called
strings. They do not understand so much
exactly what they represent. Yet from
outer perspective they are the lines
that define the
interaction and interplay and intersease
and supporting framework of all the
physicalized universes. They can be
perceived in a sense as a matrices of
graphs and geometrics from time to time
in an energy sense.
So that would then explain the the
motion of moving through and past
the grass swivel into what seems to be
right now anyway it seems to be just a
yes. Now you can also understand that
many times the idea is that when you
begin to render your external
symbols more and more simplified than
they may simply become the first level
of introduction in physical reality
which is simply the simple
geometrics rather than having to take on
such complexities of form in order to
represent something to you. You are
simply dealing at a very rarified
crystallin level in that way and
converting all of your symbology into
simplicity. You follow me? Yes. Thank
you. Oh, fine. You you sure? You uh I'd
like to share that if anybody's uh
experiencing a difficulty in breeding, I
can help them in rebooting um at the
break if you want to breathe and I can
help you. Jackie. Yes. Thank you dear
for expressing the love of your unique
facet and sharing
you I have fallen in love with um a
three acres of
land I have three months to come up with
oh a time limit how exciting
you do enjoy these games do you know
time limits only so much time. Hurry,
hurry, hurry, hurry. Everything will
fall apart otherwise. Nothing will be as
it is supposed to be.
I don't know if it's going to be there.
I'm expecting it to. But money? Yeah. Is
that the only way that the land may be
the idea you can share? This particular
piece of land that I fell in love with,
the feelings I have for it is quite a
bit of money. Yes. Why? Not that money
is not necessarily going to be the way
that will manifest. But why does it have
to be the only way? As far as I know in
um as far as you know California.
Ah I see. So what you are saying is that
is the way it is and thereby defining
the only reality you will allow to be
valid. Well you may need the million for
you. Could be.
Is that even remotely possible for you?
Of course. Oh of course. Oh, of
course. Oh, first it was I've got to
have that money and now of course it
could. Is it not also just as possible that you
Is it not also just as possible that you
may run into somebody who already
has the land? The land. Some land that
you may discover to be even more
appropriate than the one you were
thinking of getting. Well, I have money
on this property already. All right. But
again, so what?
I felt very close to this particular
piece. All right. Then simply recognize,
however, we are not saying it cannot in
your terms come into your reality that
way. However, let us plant the seed
within you. That the idea many times is
not so much the so-called quote unquote
achievement of the
goal, but the idea of the interaction of
getting there itself. That is all you
need. before. Uhhuh.
before. Uhhuh.
Relax. If you know that the idea you are
being in life requires that land, that
that land is the simplest and the
easiest way for nature for all that is
to support you in being the idea you are
willing to be 100% in trust. then take
it for granted that if that is what is
necessary, it will be there. However,
you need to acquire it, it will be
there. You don't have to worry about the
methodologies. All you have to know is
that you are being the idea 100% that
excites you the most. And if the land is
part of that, then you will have it. If
you don't, you don't need
it. You follow me? Mhm. Relax. Trust. Be
the idea. You do not have to worry or
analyze the mechanisms of being the
idea. That is
automatic. All ideas come with all the
ingredients necessary to continue to
support you in being the idea you are.
Automatically, synchronistically,
coincidentally, not accidentally.
Relax. If that land truly is a part of
you being an idea, there is no way it
will not be yours. No way.
Well, that's what I figured. I just
wanted to make sure.
Wanting to make sure is the shest way to
not be the idea that represents that the
land is yours. You follow me?
Are you sure?
Yeah. What exciting idea are you going to do
What exciting idea are you going to do
with that?
Um, build a house. A house.
How beautiful. Will it be a reflection
of your spirit? Mhm.
All right. What else?
[Music] And why do you feel the need to build a
And why do you feel the need to build a
house on that land? That's what I was
wondering.
Maybe maybe maybe
they're in another line. though. And I
fell in love with a piece of dirt on
your It loves you too.
Allow yourself to go and
live. Whether the house is there or not,
you are your own
house. Experience the relationship as
you will. Proceed as opportunities allow
themselves in this way. as you allow
opportunities to manifest to you, but do
not put expectations that they have to
manifest in a certain way or you will
still not feel the
relationship. You follow me? Mhm. Allow
yourself to allow whatever opportunities
do occur to be the opportunities that
need to
occur for what you expect this
relationship to mean may not be what it
actually is.
Live the relationship for what it is,
not the expectations you think it should
be. All right. Mhm. Yes. Thank you. You
may Oh, take a short
break. Oh, I don't say sharing. Hey,
Hey,
someone told me of a uh incident of a a
jet reconnaissance plane that
disappeared over the week over
California somewhere that hasn't been
found. Would you have any comment on
that? That's all the information that I
have that was told to me. Our perception
is that the idea you are
discussing in this way is the reference
to what you call your military craft,
right? Or it has been found. or has been
in this way simply recognize that the
idea is that your military does not want
most of the public to know anything
about it. So it has been according with
the idea of what you call once again
secrecy as it is representative of one
of their designs that is not generally
publicly known for what you call stealth
reconnaissance.
You follow me? Yes, I do. Thank you.
Sure. face. Does the government have any
um anti-gravity devices or spacecraft?
They have spacecraft. They have not
completely been able to make sense out
of the operation. They have spacecraft,
but it's solid propellant or no no not
their own. Oh, recovered.
Oh, recovered.
from the idea you would call
crashers. In this way, at an early stage
of
interaction between other civilizations
and your
own, you find that certain types of
craft were able to be in your terms
interfered with in their navigational
systems with the idea of what you call
your radar.
This created the idea of
crash. These ships have been
recovered are still in the possession of
your governments.
How about the beings that were in the
class at this time? The idea most of the
original beings in this way of course in
your terms physically dead.
You did say
most. There were others alive for a time
in other incidents.
Oh, and what kind of substances were the
spacecraft made out of? In this way, you
will find combination copper, magnesium
hole, very thin,
multi-layered. Again, at this time, for
the most
part, though they have made some quote
unquote progress, much of the idea of
the manufacturing and the actual
material eludes your scientists.
Where are these aircraft stored?
They have been moved many places from
time to time. Our perception of one of
the main areas still is in the area that you
main areas still is in the area that you
call New Mexico. Is that where they put
what about the hospitality?
It it seems like copper would conduct
heat if if they're trying. It is not
copper as you understand it. Nor is
there friction as you understand it.
Right. um in the field that this ship would
um in the field that this ship would
generate. It would be inertia free and
free. I'm interested in building a
craft. Go ahead. Have a good time.
There is much information and literature
to avail yourself of of the ideas that
already exist in your society. And there
are individuals that are present with
you tonight of your time that are aware
of some of that information and have
already begun the procedures of their
own experimentation. they can make
themselves known to you. I'm I'm one of
the guys that helped with that device.
Well, then yeah, we're working on it.
We're we're going for it. There are
still other individuals.
Yeah, I'm sure they'll we'll get
together on it. All right. I'm I'm just,
you know, fishing fishing. Fishing
fishing. What bait are you doing?
What bait are you doing?
I don't I don't want to get pulled in by
my catch. I see.
Then you'd better let your line out.
I don't know. I'm just I wouldn't have a
good time.
From this point forward.
As the so-called experiment
[Music] stands, only one comment is
stands, only one comment is
necessary. The fastening of the two
aluminum hemispheres needs to be more solid.
hemispheres needs to be more solid.
Yeah, just that way. Yeah,
just making sure.
While we're on the subject, can we
discuss a few other things about it? The
only comment necessary. All right. How
about on the uh the control mechanism?
The only
at this time. You have taken it to a
point of doing. No more is necessary
from us now.
Thank you very much. Thank you. Very
excited. You still are. Thank you. Thank you.
Y
I've been going through a phase very
much like what you were describing in
the beginning discussion. Oh, how
unusual.
Nice. Um I also was going feeling going
through periods of depression and
understanding that that was a lot to do
with integrating going inside. Nice.
Around the same time about a month ago,
my father became really depressed in New
Jersey. Nice.
after some major surgery
and I felt the rope pulling go and visit
him. Oh,
I I had a strong feeling he was
mirroring back to me saying and you to
him. Yeah. May I thank you for this
Yeah. May I thank you for this
opportunity to create a little bit more
of an analogy definition of the idea
once again of depression. As we have
already discussed, the idea is that it's
not negative. You are going within when
you know the answers you need are not
outside of you. You go to where you know
they are within. It is meditation.
Judgment makes it negative. Judgment
that there is something wrong with you.
That you have to go within to find the
answers. That is why depression becomes
depression in a negative sense. Look at
it this way. If you
will consider it
depression in your own
terminology, a board meeting of all your
parts. You get together and decide to redefine
You get together and decide to redefine
what you are as a company
so that when you emerge from the meeting
you have a new
identity that that basic concept back
it's not necessarily negative but more
balanced perspective you might utilize
this particular analogy
with his energy it might be something he
can relate too.
All right. Um, and he I'm wondering what
he was showing me. He when he gets
depressed, he's extremely
simply a lot of judgment. Yeah, it was
very very painful.
I I felt like it was real.
Of course, it is no accident. Okay, let
me ask you this. Um, I had
felt in a way my father's part of me was
was depressed to take care of me and and
depressed to take care of me and and
faces experiences and that part was
depressed and I found it interesting
that my
father sometimes family members mirror
almost like architecture. Yes. Yes. Yes.
Very good. Thank you for being so
insightful.
But I always get a job.
Sure. Sure. Hey, uh there's a new friend
of mine called Carolina that I was
talking to last night. And uh she had a
very disturbing dream last night. Oh,
disturbing. Yes. And uh she said that
she was uh married and had a few
children uh and that she felt herself
able to look at her house and the house
would change according to how she wanted
it to change just by thought. That's a
good part. How unusual.
Um then she had some painters come to
paint the house and they were very
negative, hostile, angry people. They
began painting the walls and she noticed
that the walls began absorbing light,
taking the light from her and the light
from objects and this disturbed her
quite a bit and she kind of woke up and
she was here earlier but she's still a
little upset. She's out taking a walk.
All right. So that is what that
individual desires to do is reconnect to
those portions of himself. And remember
that the idea of enacting those dreams
out means you are integrating those
pieces that they represent. Right? It is
not an indication that there is
something yet to do. It is an indication
that the integration has occurred.
Remember the idea of the habit that when
you have an experience, you still think
a process is necessary beyond having the
experience itself in order to feel
integrated. Having the experience is the
integration. Right.
Well, what I thought of on the symbolism
of that is that she had parts of herself
that were polarized to light and that
she had made a decision or eventually
she told the guys to leave, the painters
to leave and they finally left. So, she
had made a decision to be a being of
love and light. Thank you. It caused a
little disorientation in her. Of course.
Well, thank you.
By you.
Ace. Um, I had I've been having dreams
for the past six months of a person that
I knew well 16 years ago, but I haven't
seen that person since. And now you just
contradicted yourself.
Oh, you mean physically?
Oh, yeah. That's right. That's my point.
Did I see that person? I mean, okay. Did
that did that person have the same
experience that I was having on some
level of their consciousness perhaps on
a remembered level to some extent
although there may be different
interpretation but understand that in
that way when you experience some of
those ideas it is generally indicative
that you are communicating with some
level of the consciousness of that
individual whether they are aware of it
or not although it is likely that on
some level they are particularly if it
has been going on for that long it's
been going on a lot and I can't figure
figure out why why this well what do
they represent to you I it's always
great I enjoy it very much then have a
good time you are learning you are
growing and you are sharing on many
different levels being asleep and being
out of your body is not the ending of
doing things it is a very busy time you are
things it is a very busy time you are
very interactive paying many visits
having many interactions doing many
things you follow me yes I do follow
you. Allow the representations to be
whatever they are to you at this time.
It is not necessarily so that the
physiological return of this individual
is necessary, but it might occur and in
this way is only indicative that you are
now allowing yourselves to reflect to
each other what you each represent to
each other so that you can utilize it in
your own life. that particular aspect of
you. I'm always having very visual. You also
I'm always having very visual. You also
were twins at one time. Me and the
person I'm dreaming of. Ace. That's
interesting. I'm having very visual uh
dreams of what this person looks like
today because this was 16 years ago. Ace
where I can see them up close. I mean
completely the twin energy is still very
very strong.
Wow. Pleasant dreams
Pleasant dreams
Frankie you venue venue over the years
I've possibly had maybe 30 dreams I was
a professional baseball player for 14
years and in my dreams I'm always like
with Dodgers Angels or whatever club and
I never can get up the bat I'm coming up
the bat I can't find my bat I'm outside the
I have a funny
feeling that most of the individuals
present tonight think they can interpret
that.
Are you having a good time in your life
now? Uh, pretty good. Yeah, pretty.
Baseball was my love was. Well, it still
is, but I mean as a player. All right.
What excites you now?
My business
as much. No. Why not? Quite a bit. It's
lately it's getting close because but I
really love baseball. When you allow
yourself to simply know that you can
utilize all you have learned from your
excitement in another idea in many
different ways. There will not only be one way to
ways. There will not only be one way to
circumn the basis.
You will create your turn at bath by
allowing yourself to reapply the same
energy in a number of
ways. Be all of the perspective. be all
of the
players. Look at the entire game from
every point of view. All the players.
All of what you call the
spectators. Be the field of play
itself. Be the sky overhead. Be the
atmosphere of interaction.
Apply the excitement knowing that if you
are willing to recognize that you have
created in your life a timing of
shifting of what it is you are doing,
you have not lost anything. You are
still the same 100% entity and energy
and you are simply choosing where to
apply different portions of that 100%.
You have not lost anything. It is simply
up to you to determine whether or not
you wish to be conscious of where all of
that 100%
is. You may be allowing some of it to
remain in the so-called past, but it is
still there. Do recognize that as soon
as you allow yourself to know that you
are fully in the now and everything in
your life can be just as exciting in a
different way. You will then be playing
with all of your
ability in other ways and you will hit
home runs all the time. I used to
in other
ways. You simply set yourself up to show
yourself that you have that type of
energy manifestation capability and you
can apply it in whatever way you now
find your life to be manifesting. The
way your life is manifesting is no
accident and no loss. I can say
something. Uh when I was a boy, my idol
was Babe Ruth because he was, you know,
way before me. But I wanted to have two
things in my life. I wanted to achieve
the power of Babe Ruth and I wanted to
break his home run record. Okay. I
achieved his power and it, you know, was
well known in baseball. But I had bad
luck. I mean it just uh I never achieved
luck. Well, it wasn't meant to be right.
Okay. It wasn't meant to be right. You
chose it not to be necessary. That is
what it was not meant to be means. You
chose it to not be necessary for you are
simply recognizing that you will quote
unquote break other types of
records. You simply now have the
opportunity to take all that energy that
was not utilized in that manifestation
and apply it in other ways. You will
feel just as fulfilled when you allow
yourself to know that you have not
missed your
time. But your time is always now.
Thank you very much. By the
way, there is an
aspect an aspect whether you understand
the term or not is not necessary. But
there is an aspect of the consciousness
you have referred
to around for
you. You understand? Yeah, it on some
level some portions does function as a
guide.
Um, there are some things you said at
the beginning that I trying to sit with
and I need a little clarification
maybe. Oh, one more
message coming through.
You you point where you want to go and
that's where you will go.
Continue. Just like B. [Music]
[Music]
Thank you. Um,
one of the things as you were saying
that there's going to be like a lot of
of sort of changing of like jobs is
already that's what I was going to say
is that a lot myself as well as almost
everybody I know is having major major
major changes in their lives [Laughter]
[Laughter]
where I am paying attention.
simply reflecting that there is an
opportunity for an individual here to
recognize that what you are saying may
apply. [Music]
[Music]
Oh, not only are you listening, you are
doing something else that you can do. Continue.
Continue.
Um, at any rate, it one of the things is
that I'm finding that that um I'm
helping to reflect or whatever basically
that I'm getting the phone calls of, you
know, oh my god, this is happening to
me. And you were saying that there might
be ways that we might be able to help
people get through them through that.
You will attract those individuals when
you find them discussing with you, well,
I can't understand what's going on.
Everything seems to be coming apart. you
will say ah I can give you an idea as to
why that may be. So just to share that
kind of information. Nice. Um, one also
one of the individuals said that in
one of the individuals said that um all
all of the planets continue
planets continue
all of the planets right now are in
retrograde and that is also reflecting
to us that that um that change that
around September and October they're
going to start coming back. Yes. And so
the two doorways
not better different. Okay. The other
question well let's put it this way. I
think things will start integrating.
They are integrating now. They are
simply unlocking first. Right. And but
the thing that the what I'm experiencing
is that they're unlocking and all the
energy is just lying around. Yes. Yes.
It's just precursor to integration.
That's right. Okay. Um very
uncomfortable. Everybody say everybody
when it's happening. Okay. Um the other
thing was that you were saying something
about when when you're feeling the
disorientation and all and the
instability and everything that fears
will come up and I didn't quite
understand what you said. He said that
when the fear portions of yourself may
come up to the surface that you have for
a long time kept in your so-called
subconscious and because that you may
have habits of judgment in you. These
portions coming up may come up in the
form of fears. Simply we are saying that
it is not something you really have to
fear that it is only another portion of
yourself coming to the surface of your
consciousness. Okay. So you're not
saying the fears are the things that
we've forgotten but the things that we
have forgotten may cause fear. Yes.
Okay. I They do not have to, but they
may. Okay. I'm just trying to clarify.
Oh, thank you. Thank you. Yes. Um, then
you physiologically the the change from
third to fourth density, how does it
affect alignment of your cellular
structure? You may later on or even now
from time to time find that the
physiological things in your world may
seem to be a bit brighter, more
colorful, actually glowing.
What about individual body types and
like will there be changes in to some
degree there will be a type of evolution
you will find that you will once again
rely less and less upon your ideas of
internal organs and more upon your
glandular system. So the idea is that
many of your internal organs according
to the idea of the passage of time may
cease to function.
When you sustain yourself more and more
on energy, you will not need to process
the idea of digestion of fiber or fabric
in that way. I've noticed my eye colors
sort of changing. That will be one of
the reflections as well.
Is there any other um what about newer
the idea is that you may find as some of
you may have already found that you will
either perceive in yourself or in
others. Now, I will use your
terminology. The strangest sensation
that their skin is no longer made out of
the things you used to think it was
made, but carries with it a little bit
more of
a
silicon like
quality. Your cellular structures will
also contain more
silicon as you become more crystallized.
Crystal I
got you. Will kids be born new kids that are
you. Will kids be born new kids that are
being born will they be born with
slightly different body types or you may
notice a general pattern occurring in
this way to some degree. There may be again
way to some degree. There may be again
something within the eyes mostly for now
it will be mostly within what you call
the demeanor. Mhm.
Um, and the openness.
Amanda is a is a little girl to me. But
who what's special significance or where
have we met before? I can't really many
places, many
times. Explore and discover for us at
this time. No comment is necessary.
You will find out.
We do not want to spoil the surprise.
That's fine. Thank you. Nice.
There are a couple of things. Um All
right. All right. Um the first is this
sensation um this impression that um
I've been experiencing which is and this
is not judgmental or has any negative
attachment to it but the idea of saying
goodbye. Hey, I feel like um I've been
saying goodbye to a lot of people. Well,
as you become a different vibration and
other individuals may choose to be
another vibration, then you will simply
not find yourself interacting so much in
the reality into which you are
solidifying. That is all. You're only
allowing a cognition to come of how you
are changing based upon what you see
reflected in other individuals and your
proximity to them. I feel as if it's a
clearing of space. in a sense
in a very positive way. Oh yeah. As if
the and again I I don't know the the
solitude identification
is is welcome. Okay. Okay. And the on
the other side of that, what I've also
been experiencing and I wanted to share
this because I haven't heard if anyone
else had is the sensation of looking
around at people all the time and not
and seeing not so much the physical
seeing the physical but seeing something
inside the physical that's constantly
moving. Yay. Anyone else?
Yeah. And it's been really kind of fun.
Um kind of it's been fun. Not on a kind
of a more um smaller portion of that. Um
I've noticed that that has also been
expressing itself in things like
deciding to not have my bank card uh
work for me and so 5 minutes later it
doesn't. All right. Car accidents. I I
mean the little things are as we were
talking car
interaction. Oh, can I ask you about
that car interaction please?
Um that was that car interaction was
coincidentally with someone who
reflected just what I had been thinking
about all day about what I wanted as a
reflection for myself.
Coincidence. Was that all the significance that was
Was that all the significance that was
attached to that interaction? Not all in
a in a demeaning way, but was that there
are a couple of more things? There are
Oh, good. Okay. Thank you. Oh, thank
you.
Um, I have a couple of questions I want
to ask you. One is you had what
happened? All right.
All right.
Um, one is an individual in my life that
I've uh stopped seeing and communicating
with, and I was just wondering if you
could give me some information as to um
what relationships we may have had.
No, do not mean to be stubborn, but you
are in the middle of something and we
find that we will be in your terms
interfering. Take your power back. You will
Take your power back. You will
understand. Just take your power back.
Okay. The second question is uh relating
to my career which I feel um a great
deal of lack of
motivation and your career. Is your
career the most exciting thing you could
be doing in your life?
It could be. But is it?
Not at the moment. What is
pursuing my own self-discovery? Have a
good time.
Do what is the most exciting thing and
it will unexpectedly lead you exactly
where it is you have desired to be. You
are simply assuming that there is only
one path and that path is only
represented by certain symbols you will
allow to be representative of that.
follow it. Then you will always be in
synchronous conscious harmony with the
path you chose to do. Whether it seems
as if where you are going is taking you
where you think you should be or not
doesn't make a certain follow your
excitement and you will unexpectedly
wind up where you thought you would
never get by following it. I understand
that a lot of people in my life a lot of
people in your
life are are acting negatively. So what
this is your opportunity to decide
whether you believe it is true for you
or not by surrounding yourself with
reflection that will give you the
opportunity to decide whether you are
going to exercise your own
self-empowerment or give it away to all
of
them. This is your
opportunity. This is it. Take it.
Um two practices. Uh the first is
Um so our belief system is a template
upon which our um our reality becomes
manifest. If um there's something in our
reality that um we choose not to prefer
and we come to a point where we choose
not to prefer it any longer and um we
get in touch with a belief that might be
assisting that manifestation. We want to
change the belief. So how does one All
right. All right. You are putting an
extra step in there that does not need
to be. Again, it is the understanding or
the belief that you think you need a
process beyond cognition.
Oh, okay.
Simply preferring the change knowing
there is something to prefer is the
changing of the belief. Otherwise, you
wouldn't have the protection that
there's something else to prefer. Oh, I
see. There is no extra step necessary.
I got on that
but it does not find itself to be that
restrictive. No
the group consciousness. Now the
idea of again perhaps preferring as we
have suggested to be the color blue with
six arms may be your preference and it
is not that you cannot create that but
if it is not the group consciousness
then if you do create it you will no
longer be in the group conscious
physical reality. You follow it is not so much
reality. You follow it is not so much
that you cannot create what you desire.
you will simply find yourself
associating with whatever reality needs
that manifestation to be of service to
them.
Oh, great. Okay, let's open it up.
And the other thing is that last week I
spoke with Anthony who informed me that
there's a little boy around me named
Egar and that in my dream state I've
been uh assisting him and protecting him
and um that he wanted to come to me at
this time and thank me and send me love
and I just I didn't ask and I wanted to
ask now what did I protect him from and what
now what did I protect him from and what
is my relationship to him? I mean it's
very interesting. It's the first time
when it all we are allowed to share at
this time is that there are some
connections in what you would call past
lives in a love sort of way.
Been loving an eager little boy. [Music] [Music]
You're spontaneous.
Thank you. Thank you.
I thank you for joining me in the
now and allowing yourselves more and
more spontaneity of interaction,
willingness to share of all that you
are. Yes. More importantly, I was wondering
Yes. More importantly, I was wondering
why I co-created him to interact with me
and be via this entity. what he seems
like for me and that could be it you
know but I was wondering
it is a reflection of what we have
already discussed that many times you
still feel that there has to be an
intermediary process between two ideas
rather than simply recognizing the
connection as one event
thank you
um I have a father that um I really have
difficulty communicating with I can get
right into a phone conversation with him
the idea of having a nice convers ation
and so on and and then all of a sudden
you know it starts to get really strange
between us and strange yeah strange um I
feel like well I I feel like he just from my
like well I I feel like he just from my
viewpoint anyway I feel like he doesn't
allow me to just you know to be who I am
and say what I want to say and I see and
do you do the same for him
I try but maybe I don't want to do it
try I
mean I I have judged them a lot in the
past. True. I've been working on not
doing it so much. All right. Do remember
that you chose each other. Yeah. And do
remember therefore that whatever that
individual chose to be, you recognize
that that is what you would need to
become the type of personality you
desire to be in this
life. So he has by being who he is been
of service to you to allow you to become
who you are as a personality. Right. But
is it possible to really get into any
real good level of communication with
him? I'm You are in a perfect level of
communication. You
You
simply for whatever you are
communicating reinforces your beliefs
about each other and your beliefs about
yourself. But when you change the idea
of who and what you are, the
communication will change. When I change
the idea of who and what I am,
yes. having to do with him or just other than
having to do with him or just other than
that or both rather than creating
yourself to be who you are as you
measure up against him. Simply know who
you are and radiate that so that you
will give him an opportunity to talk to
you. What do I do instead of that when I
talk to him? Maybe I'm not aware of you.
Who are you?
Just a simple enough question. Yeah. A
being. Ah, a being. Very good. Very
good. A being. A being. What does that
mean? What does that imply?
Define past that.
Um, one who exists is ah, one who
exists. Thank you. That was not so
difficult, was it? No, I guess not. All
right. You recognize that you have
created a scenario in which there seems
to be aside from yourself other beings.
Others who exist. Yes. No. Maybe. Yes.
All right. You are a being. He is a being.
right. You are a being. He is a being.
You exist. He exists. Now, on one level,
you are the same. All is the same. One
being. But you have created a
differentiation. Start from
Start from
zero. Go into your meditations and
explore from zero when you created the
first differentiation between the first
differentiation that allowed you to know
you were you and he was he and
re-examine through your meditations the
agreements you have made.
Then you may create in your particular
way of understanding a particular
perception of the beliefs that you have
created about each other that may allow
you some
insight into the interactions taking
place. Go back and reread the contract.
Are we talking about this lifetime?
Because I know that I've experienced
some other things. Simply give it a zero
point. It does not have to represent any
particular lifetime. It will be a
general representation that has been
themes throughout many
lives. It will do. You sure? You follow
me? Yes. For you, our perception at this
time is simply that this type of
internal dialogue is what will allow you
to create external dialogues that will
reflect your understanding of yourself.
All right. Thank you. Yes. That that
would apply the same thing with my older
son. Yes,
Yes,
with the inclusion of the idea of also
feeling out some of the ideas rather
than just the dialogues and beliefs.
How can I open up the communication with
him and get closer? Again, by opening up
communication within
yourself and what portion of you he
represents. get in touch with that
portion of herself that he reflects and
you will be talking with him and he will
be talking with you. Thank you. Does it
help just to realize that you're
running the communication is a good way
to if you believe that that is something
that will serve you then yes if you
don't let your imagination tell you what
will that is what it is
for. Your imagination is tuned
specifically to the vibration of the
being that you are and therefore is
completely capable of supplying you with
what methodologies work for you.
Otherwise, it would be someone else's
imagination.
any any relationship of people that you
have anything everything you are all the
relationships that you
have you are all the relationships that
you have follow me
have follow me
the
shark do you have any information on a
planet called Andromeda
is not recognized in this way as a
planet is recognized as what you call a galaxy
is recognized as what you call a galaxy
and is recognized as a level of
consciousness, an organizational
consciousness matrix, what you would refer to
matrix, what you would refer to
colloquially as a council, but not
exactly. It is an association of energy,
an association of
awareness. And it represents to some
degree a pulse of energy
interaction between
itself as representative of an
overview of a particular energy
consciousness matrix that represents
many different
galaxies surrounding that one.
Does that make some sense to you? Thank
you very much. Thank you. Yes. Yeah.
Understanding that all relationships are
an aspect of ourselves. I had an an
event happen with my sister last night.
Do share that I'm curious about. I was
going into a deep meditation and I
believed that I was connecting many
aspects of myself and especially what I
call my higher self. I was talking to it
and getting information back and it was
around 3:00 in the morning and my sister
was in another area of the city and uh
picked it up uh called me on the phone
and what I was curious about was I had
no idea that I was sending it out to
anything other than my higher self.
Well, that is simply sometimes the only
way you will allow that to happen when
you are not aware of it. Otherwise,
sometimes you can try hard to make it
happen.
Many times you will connect up to other
individuals when you are not trying to
because being unconscious of the
connection is the way you will allow
yourself to accomplish the
connection. Whereas if you are trying to
do that then you may restrict
yourself. It is also an indication for
you that you are both connected to the
same soul energy.
the oversold.
Okay. Next question was separation. I've
been working on a lot of issues
concerning separation and you and
several others.
I seem to plug in extremely dramatically
to the idea of abandonment. Oh, yes. And
um I'm
not I've been doing a lot a lot of work
with it and I a lot a lot. Yeah.
And I feel like there's still some kind
of a plug in my solar plexus that
isn't moving. Isn't moving? Where do you
suppose it would go?
Just sort of dissipate and allow more of
a Can you imagine what that would be
like if it did?
I can imagine it.
I don't feel like not believe that your
imagination is real. Yes, I do. Well
then in the visuals though there seems
to be an absence of connection with the
feeling. You are putting expectations on
the way you think it should feel and
again you still do not believe that it
is
real. If you believed it is real then
you would know that no matter what
feeling you have the feeling you have is
a reflection of the blending not
something that reflects that the
blending has not occurred.
Then is when you will allow your
physical reality to show it to you in
its own good
timing. You follow me? You are waiting
for a reaction before you will allow
yourself to believe that a reaction has
occurred.
I I'm not quite sure how to apply that.
The point is you already
have. The point is you do not have to be
sure of how to apply it. If you are
simply sure that you believe that to be
true, then you will allow your physical
reality to show you that you believe it
to be true. The point is is that if you
know it is true, you will not make a
demand that your physical reality show
you in a way that you think represents a
change. You will simply allow the change
to occur to whatever way it needs to.
Living your life with the assumption
that a change has happened.
So if I don't that I don't prefer to
feel the the feeling anymore, the
intensity of abandonment that way, then
you're saying if I use my imagination to
feel what it would feel like not to have
that, then you are being someone who
does not have that.
You are being an idea that does not
contain abandonment.
All you need to do is believe that you
are that idea and once again not believe
that there is some intermediary process
necessary to manifest that idea that you
are now being that conceiving the idea
is the birthing of the idea at the same
time even though the feelings are kind of
even though the feelings are kind of
disassociated from disassociated is
fine simply trust that you are feeling
your knowledge in the way you need to to
make sense out of it for
you. Many of the definitions of the
feelings you have been used to
experiencing in the way you have been
used to experience them in your life no
longer apply. Every physical symbol is up for
apply. Every physical symbol is up for
grabs and redefinition.
Therefore, if you are simply feeling
something that you have always
interpreted as this, therefore it means
that, do not put that definition on it
anymore. Simply assume that however it
is you are feeling is the way you feel
after having made the change. Since you
know that the change has been
made, it is up to you to simply know the
change has been made. Whatever feeling
is there is whatever feeling needs to be
there after the change has been made.
You follow me? I think so. You think so?
All right.
And see what feelings happen. Yes. And
let the feelings that happen be the
feelings that need to be there. Do not
label them as well. That feeling used to
mean I used to feel that way. Therefore,
I do not assume a change made since I'm
still feeling that feeling and
interpreting it the way I used to
interpret it. Just let it be the
feeling. You can recognize the preference in that
You can recognize the preference in that
way. But once again recognize how very
quickly you create your reality from
your and putting the pressure on
yourself to have a feeling that you
think should be in itself can be what
maintains the old
feeling. Follow me. When you allow
yourself to come to that fine line
balance when you do not have that many
more symbols in that way, then you may
find yourself teetering very very
quickly from one side to the other. And
simply the slightest belief in one
direction or the other is what manifests
that reality and makes it seem so solid.
You are right on the edge many times
more than you ever think of
transformation. So our symbols have been our buffers in
So our symbols have been our buffers in
a way. Yes,
that's really interesting.
So, as soon as the tools stop um having
their effect on you, as soon as the
tools are not made to be so much more
important than what you know to be true,
they will stop having a greater effect
than your own knowledge of
yourself. For then the knowledge will be
within you and not in the tool.
Emotion is a tool.
What kind of people are we going to be
if we don't have normal emotions? You
will be centered beings of infinite
compassion and
knowledge that do not need to express
the polarity of the idea you usually think
polarity of the idea you usually think
is emotion but will express the
vibration of unconditional love which in
a sense is really the only emotion there
is. Everything else is a variation of
it.
Um, several years ago, I started out uh
uh gambling out of greed and it turned
into a tizzy of uh tizzy. Yeah. Yeah. As
a as a method of of discovering myself.
I first I first heard about choppers and
I went up to the slot machine. I float
some energy out and I hit $2,300.
And then another time and then every
time has a special lesson. And then
another time another time I I went
through the whole casino and I I said,
"Hey, this machine's going to hit
tonight and there was a guy flying it.
It was six $6,000 jackpot." And I I sat
down next to him and I says, "Can can I
have that machine as soon as you're
done?" And he had a couple quarters left
and he hit the son of a And and
it was irritating because I wanted to
see a jackpot get hit that night and I
did.
You won as well since you knew that that
was there. Yeah, but I this you did not
need the money. All right. So So do
that. I didn't need the money.
So we needed to know that you knew what
you knew. Okay. There is that is what
made you abundant beyond measure. Yeah.
There's part of me that doesn't have
that gratitude.
May I stop you right there for one
moment? One moment. And thank you very
much for pointing out the idea that we
have been discussing of allowing
yourselves to listen to what you say and
how many times what you say is an
immediate reflection of how you believe
your reality to be and so create it to
be. The moment you allow yourself to
believe that you can even with any
degree of solidity and reality say
yourself there is a part of me that
etc. You create the separations
like giving sound to fears. Yes.
Manifest. When you say there is a part
of me you create the part.
instead of the old. All
right. Okay.
And it also in creating that part
creates the opportunity for you to no
longer own it and no longer take
responsibility for the effect that part
creates. The saying of it or the actual
believing of it. Believing it. Which
usually means that is why you say it.
Yeah. Okay. So, so what I've been in
pursuit of pursuit. Yeah. Is that this
million if there's a $2 million jackpot
is up there
and I and it's funny because I keep I
keep uh I go in there and I I swear it's
so clear that I've already won the thing
and I I dreamt about it and it's
actually happened and there was one time
I blinked. I swear to God all the all
the all the things were lined up there
on the bottom line just like they were
supposed to be and then I looked again
it disappeared. And I go back to the
room and all all pissed off my hotel
room and then I restudy my tapes and I
read over my notes and everything and uh
Did you not learn anything from that?
That's the whole thing. I keep I keep
every time I get angry that I didn't win
but I but I But you did win. Yeah, I
keep it forces me to keep studying my
notes and stuff and stuff. But
understand when you saw what you saw,
you were at that moment in the
reality in the parallel universe in
which you did win but then didn't
believe it. So you snapped back.
You did win.
Allow yourself to continue to explore in
whatever way is exciting for you.
Any way and any method is valid. learn
from it.
Um the certain whispers tell me well the
physical that's too much therefore the
physical universe can't deliver that. Oh
it delivers that all the time and
more. Many times when we say that you
are exploring abundance we say that
money is not always necessary to allow
you to know that you are abundant.
However, if that idea that you are
exploring is what excites you the most
then in all probability that is the way
the universe will deliver the idea to
you.
There is nothing that says it can't.
Nothing at all except
you. Now all we would request is that
you examine why you are doing this. For
you may find that what you are learning
by going about the
idea is far more enriching than getting
the learning. Yeah, I agree. Therefore,
not that it cannot happen, but simply
recognize that you are always getting
something out of it that makes you rich
beyond measure. When you blend the two
attitudes is when you will allow either
possibility to happen because either
possibility would be equal and not
something more than what you are already
getting. Okay. This notion that um
one I shouldn't say I agree with this,
but I guess I do. Yeah, I admit that I
do. Who said you should not say
um that uh putting too much demand in
and such on on the environment. All
right. All the demand is only upon
yourself. You know, someone this guy is a magic
You know, someone this guy is a magic
man one time.
Mic mom. Magic man. And and some and and
someone asked him one time why he could
lift a girl's dress up and not get an
objection. And his answer was because I
didn't put an addiction there. All
right. And in a sense, I guess that's
what I've been doing. In a sense, um
I've been putting but again recognize it
is not necessarily for negativity. You
are learning what you need to be
learning. So if any objections are being
put there, it is for the purpose of
enriching you in the way you think you
need to be enriched. So what are you
saying? The barrier to getting things to
manifest is the service to you itself.
Oh, I see. Yeah. I haven't I have but I
haven't believed that it could be
possible or viable. Well, I thought the
the I thought the limitation was greater
than the greater than you know is more
of a limitation as it more than it was a
function. Depends on what you are
learning. Okay.
Thank you very much.
[Music]
Can you tell me about the moon changing
from yellow to orange to red? Well,
simply in this way recognizes the
aberration of your atmosphere and the
bending of
light. It is not an uncommon phenomena.
You see it in your sun as well and in
any stellar body in this way that
proceeds to the horizon when you have a
certain amount of particlets in your
atmosphere to bend the light in that
way. Now it may have some symbolic
interpretation for you in that sense.
The one that we would simply observe
symbolically is that the idea of red
being a physiological vibration allows
you to know that you are solidifying the
unconscious into your consciousness. As
the moon has been for a long time
representative of the unconsciousness
and the instability in your
lives, now you are allowing it to become
something more physical, something more
touchable, something closer, something
real. Yeah, sure. I've noticed the moon
Yeah, sure. I've noticed the moon
looking a lot larger. Is that real or it
is perceptible in this way in what you
call your own self-created illusions. If
you were in your terms to quote unquote
technologically measure the diameter,
you would find it to be absolutely no
bigger. Well, I've looked at it and it's
I thought I know, but it is not.
It is also a perceptual phenomena based
upon the fact that now it is closer to
the horizon and therefore you are
comparing it to objects that you are
familiar with. When it is in the sky,
you have no such comparison. It is the
same size. I know a few months ago it
happened to me. It was so big. the case.
In this way, we will once again thank
you for
solidifying the idea of your dream
reality and allowing your physical
reality to become like a
dream. The blending that is taking place
within each and every one of
you allows us
the opportunity to begin to
experience the portions of the all that
is that you are willing to consciously
recognize yourselves to be. We thank you
for sharing the beauty of your soul
collectively and
individually. And in this way we bid you
and send you our unconditional love and
that of the blended consciousness of all
the association in contact with you.
In this manner we will once
again speak with you, share with you in the
speak with you, share with you in the
dream reality and dimension of
imagination that we are becoming
together with
you. We bid you exciting dream life and
life dreams for they are one and the
same in the dimension of your soul. We
bid you a fall and loving good evening.