All right, I'll say. How are you all
listening to your time as you create
time to exist?
Now, in this way, as we continue the
idea of the interaction of your
consciousness with our own, allow us to
illuminate some of the ideas.
First of all, in this way, we have said
many times of late in your time frame, the
times of late in your time frame, the
idea that that which you consider to be
your personality is an artificial
construct and is not nor what you
are. Therefore, allow us to address some
of the ideas about what you are.
In this way recognize that though you
have created for many thousands of your
years of time as you count time as you
create time the idea that you are a
human existence. Understand in this
existence. Understand in this
way that the idea of your
humanity, the
essence of what you are in this
way is not restricted to what you call
your human form existence.
Now begin to allow yourselves to
recognize that in a nonphysical
state you are not
human. You are quite something
else. and that something else, that
essence, that primal idea of your energy
consciousness, your being, your soul, if
you will, is the
is the
idea of all that it can be and can
project itself
as basically any form, any symbol, any
idea it wishes to. Now we know that your
civilization at this time does recognize
to some degree at least intellectually
as you say the idea that you are not
non-physically human and that humanity
is only the idea of the physical
reflection of the soul. But in this way
also realize that many of you because of
the habit of being human many
times may not realize that when you
think of the
idea of the disembodied soul you still
find yourself making the analogy that it
is a human soul. You follow me?
Understand the soul, the energy essence,
the consciousness, the being is not
intrinsically human. Now you may find in this
human. Now you may find in this
way that the idea of many different
civilizations within the third fourth
density reality that you are
experiencing do have similar human form
or what you would call
humanoid appearance. In this way recognize also
appearance. In this way recognize also
that from our perspective in considering
ourselves to be our own form of human to
us you are
humanoid. But recognize in this way our
souless your
souless is not
humanoid. It is an
essence that is above and beyond and
transcends that limited definition.
Therefore, begin to understand that one
of the reasons as you make the shift
from third to fourth density and
recognize more of your consciousness to
be what it is. One of the reasons you
are beginning to experience many
ideas that disorient you and confuse you
and do not seem to fit in to the
structure you are used to is because you
are beginning to view from time to time
from a point of view that is not
strictly human.
It is the essential viewpoint of the
beingness, the
consciousness that you are, which can be
human and many other
things. Recognize in this way that you
can begin to understand
begin to understand
yourselves in this homogeneous
sense as everything and nothing. at the
same height as a principle, as an idea, as an
essence. Now, in this way, by simply
allowing yourself to view from the
viewpoint of this essentialness of your
existence, many of the things that are
now beginning to occur to you in your
transformation from third to fourth
density may carry a new clarity if you
allow yourselves the opportunity
to discontinue the limitation of
expecting everything to make sense in
human terms. For in this way, the idea of the
terms. For in this way, the idea of the
projection of your
humanity has been a definition which has
served you and in a sense will continue
to serve you even through the idea of
your fourth density experience. Although
the type of humanity that you will be in
fourth density is not the same type that
you were in third, you are in your terms
evolving once
again. And you will find in a sense to
speak linearly that further
linearly that further
on in the middle let us
say and very much so towards the end of
your fourth density
cycle you will not be so to speak human
form in the way you have considered
yourselves to be at all.
In this way, as you progress
from quasi plain out of physical reality
to non-physical existence by going from
fourth to fifth
density, you will in this way allow
yourselves the opportunity to
experientially become the energy
matrix of focused consciousness within
the homogeneous energy field of all that
is that you actually are. And in this
way, the idea of expressing yourself as
humanity, will be a
tool no longer necessary for your
experience. The idea of
The idea of
humanity, though well it has served you
in this way, is again yet but another
tool you have clothed yourself
within to suit the
purposes that you chose to explore and
experience. Do Do
recognize
that as you all exist on many different
plains of reality
simultaneously there are many other
guises that you also exist
within that are
humanoid and not human at all.
In this
way, by simply shifting the perspective
of your
consciousness, you may even as you make
your transformation from third to fourth
density, begin to understand that from
time to time as it suits you. In the
creation of your transformation, there
may be opportunities to look even
through the eyes of the aspects of
yourself that have nothing at all to do
with humanity.
For it will broaden your perspective in
many different ways. Though you will
remain focused for the most part in the
idea of your humanor density existence
as long as that suits the purpose of
this fragment of your consciousness that
is channeling through the prism of this
artificial personality construct that
you call your human
body. You all follow along. Yes.
Sharky. You're sharp. Yes. Um lately I
feel lighter. I feel my body less. I
feel lighter and lighter. Yes. And uh
I'm fascinated with the non-physical
stuff. Um now I from time to time I'm in
touch with the fifth density aspect of
myself that I uh that is non-physical.
And yet I see I I feel a female energy
and I see her physically because I
because like you just said, I'm we're
used to seeing the what other way
um what was more truer to what that
non-physical would look like? Anything
at all?
In a sense, if you wish, you may in your
imagination simply form the idea of an
energy sphere, a sphere of light, if you
will. that carries with it, though it is still
that carries with it, though it is still
a
symbol. Symbols which are in your terms
perhaps more of an accurate reflection
of the way or the manner in which that
form of consciousness seeks to
consolidate itself or identify itself
within the homogeneous energy matrix of
all that is relative to the way you
choose to do so for yourself. Okay. Now,
but actually would
non-physicalness look like anything in
particular? I know you just said that.
Not really.
Now understand again anything that you
perceive in this way you are going to
create a symbol so that you can
understand it from the perspective in
which you are existing including the
idea that it has a quote unquote
feminine aspect. For the idea of
masculine feminine are again simply the
idea of energy polarities manifesting in
ways that make sense to you in physical
dimensionality. The soul is
fundamentally not exactly truly
masculine or feminine or really even
both. The idea of masculinity and
femininity in the way you experience
them emotionally is a physiological
emotionally is a physiological
manifestation. And the same energy when
viewed from a non-physical
reality does not carry the same type of
effect or impact. It is felt in a
totally different way altogether.
Also I I wanted to share with you that
today I was playing with the idea of
channeling and um what happened is I
started channeling a male person named
Arnold. And Arnold said uh it was funny
because I didn't expect a name like that
Arnold. And he said uh that he uh he
said you're not he said I'm not what you
expected am I? And that he I asked
mentally he was from the 1900s and and u
I mean I asked him what time track and
he said early 1900s and that in his
society he was considered to be quite
insane only he knew that he wasn't and
that he was very wise and just had a
different perspective of life and that
he was we were making communication
happened at that point because uh we
were vibrating together that I totally
understood. All right. How does this
serve you?
Oh, I just he was so happy and so joyous
and you Oh, I just it was wonderful and
I really uh it is I'm viewing the world
differently now. Yes. And um allow me to
extend our appreciation and in this
sense congratulations for forming your
ability to form in a sense with that
other consciousness the idea of a
grounding for yourself. In this way,
understand it is, I will say, quite
paradoxically clever in the sense that
your ability to make sure that you are
comfortable with the type of insanity
you are creating for yourself is
grounded within the communication of
another individual of the same ilk. All
right. Yes. Yes. And that also he even changed
Yes. Yes. And that also he even changed
into a quote sane or person in a way.
The voice changed because I was I was
voicing that loud and then he said uh
first he was talking like I am white
insane and then he stopped and he said
yes he said I am I I I put up a front
for the society but actually you know he
started talking differently but actually
you know it's just so that uh you can
blend with society and act up. All right
now very good. Now you have touched upon
an
aspect that in this way shows the timing
of the arising of this concept and you
can now begin to realize one idea. Many
of the individuals throughout your
so-called history that you have
considered to be the idea of insane
allow themselves to remain so because
they are rewarded by forming contacts in
the other realities they are perceiving.
And as you have just
discovered, many of the contacts that
allow them to maintain what is described
as their insanity happen to be dialogues
with their future selves.
You follow me.
Yeah. No, I don't know. I got
no think about it.
Understand in this way that as we have
said many times the idea you call
insanity is simply that an individual
does not share the mass agreed upon
reality and is perceiving other
realities that are no less real than the
one that is massag agreed upon. Right?
What allows them to
maintain the connection to the other
realities they are perceiving is that
they are rewarded by finding out that
there is someone they do communicate
with. You follow me? Yeah. Many of those
individuals and consciousnesses that
they find that they are communicating
with are their own future selves. Just
as now you are grounding the idea in
your own past self and allowing that
past self to ground itself in its own
future which is you.
Okay. You are now closing a cycle begun
then in that life and in this way
allowing yourself to utilize the
completion of that cycle now in this
life to ground you so that you can
proceed. Oh, so you're saying that
switch in the voice is kind of was more
moving into that future self
as you also will form connections to the
past self in that way and completing the
cycle. You allow the completion of that
connection to extend to form the
connection to your own future self from
here as well which is talking back to
you now as well. And when you get there
you will find you will be talking back
to you
very creative. We all got along real
good. Sure.
Sure.
For you. Yes. I'd like to share
something that happened last night. Um a
dream experience that was quite
wonderful. Oh, right. It started out
with um meeting an
alien called that turned into
uh a young humanoid man. And as the
group that I was with met to welcome
this person, they seemed to take on a
more feminine aspect. Um and later um I
was talking to this being and explained
that I had come back to to that dream to
meet her and indicated that um I I
realized that I
was covered part of my shoulder was
covered by my down comforter under which
I was actually sleeping at the time. And
I I said to her, "Do you know what this
is?" and she didn't want me to talk
about it because I think she felt I
would be pulled back to my body. And I
said, "This is actually the comforter
I'm sleeping under." I came back to this
dream to meet you
again. And later when I was writing it
down, so many possibilities occurred to
me and I would like some feedback from
you on it. I What are they? Well, I
thought this can be my future self. This
can be the male female within me. This
can be
um myself in a parallel universe.
Now may I ask you a question? Yes, of
course. In this way recognize that your
society because of the habitual rituals
it has created for itself has created a
prediliction for the idea that the terms
it finds to define its reality must
always be mutually exclusive of each
other. always being well. It is either
this or that. Yeah. Why can it not be
this and that? Well, that occurred to
me. All right. Then understand that all
of those
ideas in your terminology are true.
Absolutely. Yes. Or you would not have
conceived of them. Understand what it
means. What it truly means to be a
multi-dimensional being.
All of the aspects future alternate
parallel aspect are all real and all
true. For you are interaction itself.
You are the very concept of interaction
and you will interact on every level
there is to interact upon. So as you as
I shall say turn the dial to make the
connections to create the validity for
each interaction, you find that there is
actually something on each and every
frequency that does exist and they all
blend and they are all part and parcel
of your communication to yourself from
yourself. Whether you are interacting
with what you term to be other
consciousness or not does not make it
any different. Other
consciousness still can only be
perceived by you when you create your
own version of it to experience in your
own universe that you are. You follow
me? Yes, that's quite true. And I've
been experiencing more and more of that.
And obviously this is just another
indication. has been. It is also an
indication of the reality that each and
every one of you are very very very busy
while you are
asleep. You do not stop by any means
doing things. You are quite
involved when you are out of your body.
Yes, I know that. And I've been
exploring more of it and it's getting
more exciting. I can feel myself
contacting other um how should I
say fragments of myself so to speak. I'm
I'm becoming more and more holistically
like parts of the puzzle all coming
together and I understand more of my my
total being. Thank you very much. Thank
you for helping so much.
Thank you for allowing us to reflect to
you your ability to help yourself.
Thank you. You sure? Yes. Good evening.
Besides having uh this week I had four
consecutive vivid dreams in a row since
Steve gave me a crystal and coming here
the first real dream lives I've had that
were so exciting and four nights in a
row. It's the first time in many years
I've vivid dreams. I wanted to ask you a
question of it's known that a lot of
famous thinkers when they were tackling
a very difficult problem would take a
catnap. Yes. And going through I guess
what the alpha frequencies and the earth
resonant frequencies and the theta
frequencies. Then coming back out they'd
have they were able to remember things
that they didn't know they knew. Yes.
Where is it exactly that dialogue with
the higher self? Okay. Is there a
particular frequency or set of
frequencies where the physical body is
able to communicate best? In this way,
the idea of that so-called tap although
do understand that it is only you that
is creating the idea that there is a
separation to go through. It is all one
homogeneous knowingness. But in this way the tap
knowingness. But in this way the tap
usually will occur more often than not
in that way at the theta level as you
have described it in this sense
approximately what you call in terms of
brain wave frequency 10 to 12 cycles per
second. Mhm. Very good. Thank you. Can I ask you
Mhm. Very good. Thank you. Can I ask you
one more question then? Uh when you were
talking about communicating with our
higher selves, when people pray, Yes. do
they pray to their higher selves or be
all that is or what kind of
communication is going on?
The idea of the activation mechanism of
what you call faith in this way, not
being a nebulous term, but an actual
description of the activation energy
that gives rise to the physicalization
of your belief structure. You are in
this sense forming a link with the all
that is. Therefore, it automatically includes
is. Therefore, it automatically includes
your higher self and everything in
between. You follow me? Sure. Thank you.
Oh, thank you. Sure.
You done you? I uh couple things. One is
I have had a dream recently myself that
normally does not take place. It's uh it
concerned a woman with uh two sets of
legs and and her daughter and some sort
of a palace or mansion. And
um I look at
this as some sort of a sexual thing. And
as much as I am presently
aligning my uh second and fourth chakra
basically and I thought perhaps there
was some symbolic some symbolism there.
Would you have an opinion on that?
Simply in this way, our perception of
the energy at this time will describe
the coming to terms with certain ideas
of your own feminine aspects. And in
this way, an indication symbolically to
you that there is within this
identification of your own feminine
aspect, a bifurcation of choices, a
bifurcation of paths you take. You can
walk one or the other way.
Could you say a little bit more on that?
I'm not sure that I'm saying
Allow us to ask you a question as well
then. Okay.
Do you feel in this way that the idea of
coming to terms with your own feminine
energy can allow
you to blend with your own masculine
energy in a way that allows both the
masculine and feminine aspects within
yourself to
operate freely?
I'm not totally sure yet. Uh I do have
this overwhelming love for women. It
just does not matter.
Uh on the other hand, I do or on the
other. Thank you very
much. Uh I do feel this desire to you
know to be with or to just deal with
women as opposed to men. On the other
hand, uh I have been integrating my
beliefs and feelings about men at least
changing them somewhat. All right.
Instead of being the I should have
handled. So I'm not sure if I have at
this point really made some sort of All
right. You are in the middle of a
process in this way that you have
created for yourself to give yourself
the opportunity to strengthen the idea
of the way you can relate both to
females and to males both from your
feminine and masculine aspects to each
so that you can allow them to be equal
on their own terms. And in this way,
feel the blending that will allow you
the freedom to communicate with either
masculine or feminine aspects of energy
within other individuals when you may
find them to be unbalanced so as to
allow them the opportunity to see the
blending within you so they may choose
the balance for themselves if they wish.
Oh, great.
Okay. The other thing is I I want to
finish uh I notice sometimes that I have
come here and I have asked you a
question and you have immediately come
back as if giving me an answer as
if I felt like you've said well Jesus I
just gave you that answer a few hours
ago or something. Has it been any time
that that I will have been with you on
your ship or in some sort of
communication with you and gotten an
answer in in aic form and come here and
ask you a question
physically and you have come back with
with Jesus. I've just given you the
answer or something on that order.
It is not literally in that fashion the
idea but simply in this sense many
times understand this when we speak so
to speak to
you the idea is that we are not only
communicating with your physiological
personality but with your higher self as
well and in this sense many times you
will find that the higher self will hear
the idea and your physiological self
will
Okay, that's so that's the apparent
exasperation that I feel that you
perhaps may be reflecting back to me.
Thank you. Okay, for myself, I am never
exasperated with you. I enjoy you
immensely. Yeah, that's why I said the
reflection. Yes, thank you. Thank you
for being a student enough to allow
yourself to reflect the totality of your
own process to yourself.
Now simply what was said in this way was
the idea that the particular type of
formation or blending that is taking
place within this individual of his own
male and female aspects will be being
undertaken for the purpose of the types
of communication he will be creating and
co-creating with other individuals who
may find themselves to be out of balance
with the ivy of their own masculine
feminine energy. So that the type of
formation of blending he is creating for
himself will allow those individuals in
that interaction to see reflected in him
the ideas of the blending of the
masculine and feminine energies that
they may choose to be able to allow
themselves to partake of if they desire.
Does that clarify the idea? Thank you.
Yes. Um I'm studying American Sign Language
Um I'm studying American Sign Language
recently and I want to know if there's
any significance today.
That's great. You've been using your
hands. I haven't seen you for a while or
felt you for a while and you've been
using your hands more. Is this an
indication of something? It is an
indication of the blending of the
consciousness of my own in this way with
the physiological channel and an
understanding in the idea that all of
the energy and the communication that we
are sending is not being translated into
physiological words. Some of it is
translating through the bodily form and
reinforcing itself with communication to
your higher consciousness because the
higher consciousness does understand and
pick up on the ideas that are channeled
in this way. Not only through the vocal
communication but also through the
physiological communication and also the
energy essence of the idea being
exemplified and channeled through the
physiological medium. In this way you
will understand that to some degree it
will be in terms of your signing perhaps
symbolically representative of the idea
that you are going to in your terms lose
the need for the vocalization even as
our civilization has done so so that you
will be able to feel totally feel with
all parts of your being the
communication that is coming
through. You follow me? Now in this way
you will find simply that although in
this way no accident it is the idea of
coincidence that allows us to create the
idea of the formation of the energy
channels through the physiological
medium. In this way you will find that
the reason for the manifestation of the
signature you find within the channel
hands will be the idea that we are
forming a loop closing a circuit so that
the energy will process in a circular
fashion and in this way complete the
circuit from my consciousness to the
physiological channels and through. In
this way again it is not so much the
idea of accident in this way but it is
in this sense let us say serendipity in
the idea of the symbol for and within
your own sign language to mean I love
you also um again I have a energetic pattern
also um again I have a energetic pattern
of a being in my house um it's not so
humanoid this time it is more of an
alien and I've been drawing pictures of
Yes, I don't know if they're male or
female or it matters. Your description
of it as an energetic pattern is most
astute. Thank you. Um, can you give me any
Thank you. Um, can you give me any
information about this energetic
pattern? How does it allow you to feel?
Do you allow yourself to create in your
mentality the sense of a next step or
level for yourself in terms of the
recognition of what patterns of energy
in general mean to you symbolically in
your society? Yes, that does occur. But
then there is I have this fear that one
evening it is going to manifest like
blocks in my soul and I probably think I
think I'm going to be afraid. All right.
Then understand that you have created
the invitation and in this way that being
invitation and in this way that being
that consciousness that reflection that
idea will only invite itself so far as
the definition on your invitation had
allowed. You follow me? Therefore, when
you are willing to throw a bigger party.
Yes. Um, can you give me any information
about a planet or a soldier?
Those labels do not apply at this time.
Oh,
you think we are keeping something from
you. I know you understand it is not
even the idea to apply a limiting label
at this time for what that energy
actually represents would be doing you a
disservice for it would not allow you
the broadness of focus that will allow you
broadness of focus that will allow you
to interact most
acutely follow
all right along the same lines I have a
sense that there
activity in my home also, but I'm not
real sure. I have a uh
overhead fire alarm that beeps on
occasion and it seems that every time I
uh get a really great awareness or even
think about God, it beeps. And sometimes
it beeps at 5 in the morning and I find
myself asking you to let me go back to
sleep. All right. Understand in this
case what you are allowing yourself to
create for your own symbology is an
extension of what you normally refer to
as poltergeist phenomena. In this way,
recognize that 99.9% of that which you
refer to as Hobberg's phenomena is
simply extensions of your own energy not
contained within your physiological form
and create for you the idea of so-called
disturbances or in this way symbols or
landmarks or the idea of expressions of
energy of the being that is the fuller
you in this way that you may at this
time not consciously be willing
willing to be responsible for you.
Follow me. I I'm halfway through. All
right. Recognize the symbology of what
you are creating in this way. As soon as
you begin as soon as you begin to extend
your senses into more of the being that
you are, you are creating an
alarm. You follow me? Yes. Now recognize
you are simply showing yourself that you
are always perfectly
safe. And in this way you always have
the ability should the fear arise to
create a limitation that allows you to
go no farther than you are comfortable
with. But it is your own energy in this
sense giving you an opportunity to tease
yourself to entice yourself to be in
communication with your higher self and
all that is in a trusting mode. There is
no cause for alarm.
alarm.
Um I I have naturally I feel
um I do feel the heat. I there there's a
part of me that
really becomes a child and is frightened
of the unknown. And there's a part one
moment. Your definition of a child in this way
Your definition of a child in this way
is not something that is fundamentally
basic to the concept of childhood.
Children do not fear the unknown. This
one did. All right. But understand that
that is a learned idea. It is not
fundamental simply to the idea of being
a
child. You learn that from the society
into which you chose to be born. I agree
with that. All right. Then simply
recognize first and foremost that you
can be a child without
fear. You follow me? Yeah.
That is what will allow you to step
beyond the limitations you have imposed.
Trust as a child trusts for it was the
trust of the child that chose to buy
into the belief of the
society to have the fear. Allow the same
trust to allow you to buy out of it into
another belief. All right. Okay. And when I do
belief. All right. Okay. And when I do
that then I have created
um the ability I guess I want to say or
the energy that I know I have asked and
have invited into my
invited into my
home to maybe not that all right is that
and again yes in a sense and again
understand this with the same faith and
the same trust and the same knowingness
by which you are creating any reality
you experience, any reality that you
experience. You can know that what will
be there will only be as much as you are
comfortable with and you will never give
yourself more than you can handle. You
follow me? Yes. Otherwise, it would not
serve your purpose. Yes.
Is there anything that you can suggest
that I try to do or not do to assist
myself? Simply in this way, allow
yourself to recognize that as you create
the idea in a belief for the need for
defense, you will create the reason for
the need. You follow it? Yes, I do.
need. You follow it? Yes, I do.
That is the only thing. The only thing
that creates the reason
is the need itself. Thank you.
Now, tonight of your time, as you drift
off to
sleep, what may assist you is the
image of a bright blue crystallin energy
sphere. Allow yourself to become that
sphere and allow whatever leaks back
into your conscious
awareness come the
morning be the
recognition of your own
self-empowerment and your own
creatorhood and your own link to all
that is and your own birthight. birthright of birthright of
ecstatic
creativity. All right.
Thank you very much.
You sure? Uh I have a couple questions a
couple friends of mine. Um easier asking
questions from friend asking questions I
wanted at present. They are much in the
same. You will find for in this way your
willingness to share on any level at all
always concerns you as well. Thank you.
Uh first question are there people
living in different dimensions on earth?
In different dimensions. Yes.
Also parallel dimensions.
And parallel. Yes. alternate and
parallel. Okay. And they're similar to us some.
Okay. And they're similar to us some.
Okay. And um the second question is
uh is God a someone or something?
Is there a difference? Yes. Is there a
difference? Not
really. All that is is all that is.
Therefore, all that is contains both
concepts, someone,
something. You follow me? Yes. All that
is simply is all that is. And to us,
that is our definition of God.
All right. Thank you. It can recognize
itself as its own being and also
recognize itself as the combination of
all creations that it is. Yes. Yes.
Thank you.
Yes. What is the difference between the
terms alternate and parallel dimensions?
Thank you.
In this way, the definition most
ascribed to parallel dimensionality will
be those that let us
say you might
recognize in this way as similar to your
own experience of Earth with minor
differences or major differences to
varying degrees.
alternate will be something that is
another scenario altogether that does
not seem to have anything at all to do
with your earth. I see.
Each and every civilization has its own
alternate and parallel dimensional
expressions. Now in other words let us say you are
Now in other words let us say you are
just for the sake of being arbitrary
earth number
342. All the other earths to you are
parallel earths. However to earth number
343 you are a parallel earth. One of the
options in which earth can express
itself as the idea of earth.
You hold it. Yes. such that alternate
dimensions would would have maybe no
earth in it at all. Would not be the
concept of earth, but would be the
expression perhaps of the same soul
entities experiencing another type of
civilization altogether that is not
founded on the principles of earthness
including not.
Oh, to some degree. Yes.
Okay. Thank you. Uh, while I've got your
attention, uh, have a couple of personal
questions. All right. Uh, quite some
time ago, my car started, I guess you
would say, sputtering. And I asked you
about that. You suggested that I clean
my filters. All right. And I did that.
It didn't change the condition of my
car. And it's been doing it. And I just
thought I'd better continue and observe
it and find out what happens to it. And
it's still doing it. All right.
has been doing it for quite some time of
your time. Yes. Are you still getting
places? I'm getting around. Yeah. All
right. I was just wondering if you had maybe a
I was just wondering if you had maybe a
revised perception of
Thank you. Every moment of time that
exists will always bring with it a
revised, so to speak, perception. For
every moment is a new now with a new
definition of what that now
represents. One moment. This moment's
This moment's
perception is simply the idea that the
symbology of allowing you to create an
effect with your own filters now enables
you to
understand that you now have the type of
filter filter that can in this way find itself
filter that can in this way find itself
adaptable to many different conditions
and still keep
moving. You follow me? All right. The
idea you are discussing in and of itself
of parallelity and alternate
dimensionality. Each one of those is in
a sense a filter. You follow me?
In this way, you are simply finding that
you are allowing it to be all right to
let your
f in my
mouth. Can you comment on that? You will
find in this way it is a sensitivity to
the idea of the magnetite in your spinal
cavities. In this sense, it is being
activated quite often in this way along
with your heart chakras in this way as a
sensitivity to the electromagnetic
fluctuations upon your planet. And this
may also be another reason for why you
sense that there is let us say more of a
continuity with the idea of your filter
and its electric connection or
electromagnetic connection. You may find
that the fluctuation is actually more
electromagnetic than specifically
electric. Right. Thank you.
For sure.
You would you say that uh possibly your hand
would you say that uh possibly your hand
motions are an indication of you're
becoming more Italian. Now
understand that first of all they are
not my hand motions.
In this way again it is simply a
reflection through the phys theological
channel of what you may term to be the
extra energy that is felt in the
physical body that does not get
translated into words. You follow me?
Yes. That was done for humor. Yes.
Yeah. What do you think? What do you
think of the purpose of existing for the
purpose of having fun and creating fun
for people?
Like anything else is an idea. You enjoy
it? Yes, very much. Thank you. Well, then
Yes, very much. Thank you. Well, then
you may continue to do so. Thank you. I
would have anyway. Thank you. The idea
of creation in and of itself in a sense
is that creation was created out of
ecstasy to begin with. Beautiful. Nice.
One more question. Bashar. I noticed
that for myself the physical existence
has a much greater clarity of perception
than any other universe. Can you uh give
me some insight in how to develop as
clear perception of other universes as I
seem to have of this one? Use your
imagination as we have told you. M now
again at the same
time stop judging the way you are
perceiving your reality for many times
you actually do get the opportunity to
experience something else and because of
your judgment you don't even know you're
doing it
because you are so focused on attempting
to not see this physical universe that
is what keeps you focused within
You follow me to a degree. A little more
clarification simply again what you focus on whether
simply again what you focus on whether
it is from focusing on wanting or not
wanting is still a focus upon the
idea. And in this way it is the
expression as you have just shared it
with us. The idea that you do not want
to focus so strongly on this one that
allows you to maintain such a strong
focus on this one. I got you. The
resistance. Yes. Okay.
Resistance is maintenance.
Mhm. You follow me? Yes, I do. It is
support of that which you do not prefer.
That's wonderful. One moment.
On Friday night at my home in Malibu, um
it appeared that an event took place.
Nice. Extraterrestrial activity. Nice.
In which many patterns and um signs were
left. Can you give me any input on that
situation? Simply in this way you will
understand that a particular type of
energy field being a quasi density
energy field round and about the craft
and also the beings in this way created
a change in the molecular structure of
the vegetation that was in this way come
into contact with that energy field.
Mhm. And in this sense you can also
understand that you are not now in the
same universe you were in before that
event. Yeah. I felt a shift or now
understand it is simply part and parcel
in your terms of the
acceleration of the
interaction of your level of
consciousness with many others in this
way. Particularly as we have said that
particular area in which you reside
let's say is prone to that to begin with
because of the energy vortex of your
planet residing in that local
particularly that household I think what
is it so special about that particular
house that's where my watch was taken
again understand that those things that
exist within the energy vortexes which
represent dimensional doorways are prone
to exist in many plains of reality at
once from time to time and so things can
pop in and pop out.
I would say
the material the electromagnetic fluid that
material the electromagnetic fluid that
defines one reality from another is let
us say sketchy in those
local malleable [Music]
[Music]
malleable. Therefore, simply recognize
that you are giving yourself the
opportunity to know that your senses are
becoming accustomed to existing within
that type of zone of activity and
therefore you are becoming more aware of
activity that takes place within such a
zone. Uh-huh. In other words, you may
find that you can get used
to living in Grand Central Station.
I love it. This
is I had asked about 3 or 4 days before
that to make another physical contact as
I had in September.
Um, woke up Saturday morning to that
wonderful um, then you must have bought
the proper ticket. I must answer. I have
another question.
Um and it may be tied to other things
but when I come to see you Bashar now um
such as this evening and a few other
times I've been
here upon the journey here and after
arriving
um I find that I seem to get very
agitated internally and it feels as if
my shoulder and neck starts to shut
down which thank you for laughing
So can you can you give me some
enlightenment on that? Again understand
in this way as you form your connection
your ease of existence within those
energy fluctuations you will find that
the idea of being able to communicate
with your own higher self in this way
will also be something that opens up and
that what you call the area in between
your shoulder blades the base of your
neck your spine the top of your spine in
this way at the base of your neck will
represent the main connection point of
channeling in this sense that's what it
that's been occurring.
Um, you are acclimating to the energy
and the frequency therein.
And and I've been also needing to sleep
or rest a lot more lately like for the
purpose of forming communication to ease
yourself into the reality physically. Is
there something I can do to assist that?
You are doing just fine. Thank you.
I'm having similar experiences where the
Did you get ask
um I'm having similar experiences where
my um the area from above my rib on up
it seems to be like
a almost like a thorax yes of an insect
that was feeling very heavy last week
and I was needing a lot of rest as well
and was having a lot of the summer is
that the same thing to a degree each and
every one of you will feel the
transformation in your own way.
Understand that not because it is us but
simply the idea that you are all
together in this type of interaction is
an indication that you are all utilizing
similar energy. You follow me? And in
this way you're all becoming sensitive
to the types of energies that can
become experientially perceived in your
new definition of your daytoday reality.
All of the ideas of your physiological
symbols are being now seen to be the
energy symbols and the energy and
physical matter are now taking turns
being equally real in this way. So you
are experiencing energy many times in
the same way you experience physical
form. And thus when you give yourself
energy bursts in that way through your
energy matrix your chakra points you may
actually feel it to be a physical
encasement. You follow me?
You follow me?
Again, it is all part and parcel of
simply acclimatizing to a new frequency
which is a new definition of the idea
that you ought to becoming.
Thank you. Also the
uh my awaken life has also been very
much more fluid. Yes. And I've been
feeling much more. You are beginning to
live your dreams.
Live the dream state. Recognize that
your physical state and the dream state
are losing their separate definitions
and becoming one homogeneous
experience. That is why you will be able
to do anything you desire upon your
planet in fourth density because you
will be living a living dream.
and my dreams I haven't been remembering
very much at all of my dreams or that is
because you are beginning to live them.
Understand again that the idea you call
a dream in this way. Now this does not
mean that if you are having vivid dreams
you are not doing this. But more often
than not, you will simply find that the
idea of creating a dream is only
necessary as long as you continue to
make a separation between physical
reality and dream reality. For then you
create a symbol by which you can
remember the experience you had in the
dream state because you are still
separating that the dream state is
different than the physical state. When
you blend the two and begin to live your
dreams, there is no need for a symbol to
make the bridge and the link because in
a sense you never stop dreaming. You
follow me? You never wake up into
physical reality. It becomes one
experience. And therefore, you are
already linked. You are already bridged.
And you do not need the symbol to remind
you that you did have a real experience
in the dream reality for you are still
having it. Follow me. Yes, I do. Oh, you
also um there's a drug called ecstasy.
Yes. And every time you say living an
ecstatic moment, I think of the drug
ecstasy. Um can you tell me a little bit
about what that drug does? Thank you. In
this way, you will find that it does
have an effect upon what you call to be
the heart chakra. In this sense, also
understand that like anything else, it
is but a tool. And in this way you will
also understand that it can because of
what your mentality has made any idea of
synthetic creation in drug form to be
have side effects. And in this way you
will simply find that it can serve you
to allow yourself to come into contact
like any tool with certain aspects of
yourself. And in this way you can also
recognize that you have the capability
of recreating that for yourself without
the tool. You follow me?
understand that whether you use a
so-called symbolic tool or not, you are
still creating the
experience. You follow me? Only by your
belief in the so-called drug do you
allow yourself to think the drug is
doing the creating. You are doing the
creating of the experience anyway. That
is all the tool is there to show you
that you have the capability of creating
this type of an experience. If you
prefer it, create it again for yourself.
You do not need the drug or the tool to
create it. You may have used the drug as
a tool to show you that you can create
it. It shows you what may be possible.
Therefore, if you like it, do it
for yourself by yourself. For you are
doing it by yourself anyway.
You follow me? Sure. [Music] [Music]
There
was question here as well. Is there
still I know from a female me? No.
All right then. We will go here. We will
go there. We will go
there. My great.
Um, is there a way that I in meditation
or whatever I could assist my physical self
self
as there lately I have been doing a lot
of meditation
and it's paying off paying off all right
if I may use that term of course but I
do feel a distinct
slowness in my physical comprehension.
In what way?
Um, it's it's not as alive as it would
be. Jesus is a hell of a way. I can't
even explain it. It's a feeling
but it is not the same type
of all that isness I guess that exists
when I am say meditation in meditate uh
while meditating are you beginning to
meditate right now
[Laughter] feel like
feel like
that okay the thing is wake up
okay That's precisely what I'm talking
about that particular there is a gap
in the
physicalness and then get up and do
something with the energy that you
create from your meditation. [Music]
[Music]
Uh I'm not far.
Why not take me literally get up and do
[Music] something? Change the definition of the
something? Change the definition of the
idea of your physical
state. Get
up, feel the energy you have created
within yourself. Open the doors of your
imagination and go and physically do
something with the
energy that is creative. That is
Joyful that is enjoyable. Yes.
Does not sound convincing.
It's not a matter of convincing.
It's I felt like I was doing that on
some level. Some level. On one level or
another. I don't I don't know. What
about the physical level?
since that is what you are talking
about. Well,
okay. I guess is there any other way
that you could assist me? Uh, you can
give me a little more
clarity. Yes, you can. Stand
up. You want me to stand up now? Is
there any other time? Okay, you
got Okay.
Stand up very straight and tall.
Okay, we've done this before.
[Music] Yes, turn around.
Now, open your arms and hold them out in
front of you as if to embrace all the
possibilities in the world.
Now, what is one thing that your
imagination can allow you to create that
you would find enjoyable to go and
physically do?
Um, the type of things that I was doing
in the winter. Um, reaching a lot of
people. All right. What else? Doing my
my talks. What else? Anything else at
all? spending a lot of time out in the world,
spending a lot of time out in the world,
I guess. All
right. Anything more specific?
Well, I I I I Are you still standing up
straight? I want to be instrumental in And do you
I want to be instrumental in And do you
hear how much more bold you are when you
stand up straight?
Yeah. But I don't perhaps Okay. Perhaps
you think I lose that when when I'm not
here, but I don't necessarily lose that.
I did not say you lost it. Okay.
However, you may choose to not be that
idea from time to time. In a
In a
sense, in a sense, because of what you
are asking, it is my perception that you
are choosing to not be that right now.
You might say that. Yes. Oh, I did. Yes.
Now, may I ask you why you choose to
choose to not be that same degree of
bold activity right now as opposed to
any other time that you may be doing
that you could assist me? But why do you
need assistance when you can simply
choose to be boldly active?
Where can I possibly assist you if you
know how to perhaps perhaps just what
you had have said has put some flare to
you. Perhaps you tell me. Has it? Yes,
it has. How?
Well, I guess it's the reflection of it.
Reflection of the boldness. Yes. And the
activity. Yes. oftentimes when I'm when
when I'm here, you know, like months
ago, we we'd get into it and you just
sit up and we go through this whole
scenario and
the next week, I mean, I'd go through
several days of it and next week I'll
come back and I'm sort of in some sort
of phase of contemplation or or probably
working at listening to you instead of
just relaxing. You mean listening to
yourself? Okay. Well, as you talk. All
right. And you'll sit well sit up and
very [Music]
[Music]
good. And uh do that again. Would
you sit up one more time? Up.
One more time. Set
up. Very good.
Now, how come you do not choose to
communicate like that all the time?
Uh actually what just came to my mind is
people can't have it. Oh, who says
and and so what are you you or are you
creating you to be the judgment from
them [Music] [Music]
[Applause]
cuz I have I have literally trained
myself to be that way with people to to
deal with the dark skin or the to not be
able to to deal with me
as not being overpowering or All right.
All right. So they could have it and I
have actually molded myself in that and
that's all just been reflected. So give
birth to the true essence that you are
in this way. This does not mean that you
have to be accosting. No, no, no. Thank
you. For in this way, simply understand
that your
willingness to be bold about your own
convictions in this way will be what the
other individuals will truly pick up
on. Otherwise, they are going to look at
you and say he doesn't believe in
himself.
I got it. Thank
you. Sure.
[Applause] One moment. Tag. Tag.
[Music]
I have several questions. I'd like to
short, right?
One is, are chakras actual in the same
way that our bodies are actual or are
they merely the thought held by some
people? Does that question make sense?
Yes. And yes. They are actual. Yes.
Okay. In your terminology, yes, they do
represent in your physiological terms
the energy formation of the energy being
that you are projecting itself into
physical materiality.
So they are really doorways and
connection points in that sense. Yes.
But there actually are vortexes of
energy that help define the physical
body in a sense. Yes. Now again of
course all of this is product of your
creation and in that overall sense to
the higher self is quite arbitrary but
as a physical reality they are there
they are measurable. Well
do do your I mean are do do people in
your civilization have chakras?
Yes. Okay. Next question.
Last time you made the remark that
Hubard and other people and his
followers are from Orion. And I'm
curious if each of us is simply a part
of the all that is existing in the
eternal now. Yes. What sense can be made
of the concept of a person being from
I've discussed this. This idea simply is
arbitrary to the life you have created
it. In this way you may find that origin
point is simply a reflection of
attachments to ideas that are made. Now
this does not mean
again understand that any confusion in
this discussion will stem from the fact
that we are talking linearly and also
nonlinearly at the same time. Okay. So
understand in this way that while the so
to speak lives actually do exist in that
system and you can say in linear sense
that individuals can come from there to
this system. You will also understand
that for each and every light you can
have a different origin point. For an
origin point is simply an attachment to
an idea that serves the purposes of the
particular life in which you are forming
the origin point. Okay. Does that
clarify it to some degree? Somewhat. But
I have a correlary. Oh, right. J were um was
um was
Hubard present here on Earth or was what
we know of as him merely a thought
projection from another system?
In this way, in your terms, there is a
physical materiality. Yes. In the same
way that you have a physical
materiality. But when you say that he was from
But when you say that he was from
someplace else, you are all from
someplace else in that sense. You are
all from nowhere at the same time. And
so is he of course. Yes. And in this
way, many of you are forming the idea of
the connection of an origin point to
that system to serve the purposes of
this life and perhaps many other lives
as
well. And they have the same degree of
physical materiality that you do in that
sense in serving the purpose of being in
your civilization of earth at this time.
But was he you have said that Christ was
a fifth
density being that chose to be here to
do whatever he was doing. Was hovered a
fifth or sixth density being that chose
to in the term that you mean it?
No. In the idea that you all exist on
all levels and all density
simultaneously. Yes. Yes. But there Yes.
But in this way as to the specifics of
the mechanics of the formation of the
mechanics of the formation of the
identity in that sense not really. Okay.
So a few days after he dropped his body
or whatever
um it was my reality that the hea being
was called before a tribunal composed of
the council of sacrament to evaluate
his creation on earth which people refer
to as Scientology or the church sort of.
I say sort of only
because that the idea of councils,
tribunals and hierarchies is a third
density perspective. Within the
so-called hierarchy, there is no
hierarchy. Well, there is something that's been
Well, there is something that's been
referred to as the council of Saturn.
from your third density perspective.
Yes, it is a recognition of the portion
of the extension of your higher
consciousness as in this way that
perceives the balance of the system that
you call your own solar system. Yes. And
then are sort of guardians for the
system sort of. How would you describe
it then?
as I just did. It is an extension of a
portion of your overall consciousness
that in in a sense embodies itself not
in physical form but embodies itself to
be able to recognize itself as the
creation as that fragment of the overall
mass consciousness of your system that
perceives and recognizes the balances of
energy within the system.
This may not make sense to you in third
density perspective terminology but in
this way that is our definition. I
understand. Okay. One one other question
simply this. Yeah.
From the higher density perspective
councils, tribunals and
hierarchies do not judge anything.
No. Not in the sense of right or wrong
but do they
not collect information or sense or
perspectives in a sense yes and that is
what we are saying they are the
perspective of the balance of all the
energy that goes into making the mass
consciousness of your system and so was
my perception that there was an uh
evaluative not necessarily judgmental
yes in a sense that is why I said sort
of well how would you describe it other
than what I describe it. In other words,
simply as you are saying the whole idea
at the point it is now created itself to
be is taken into account within the
balance of the energy of the entire
system and the recognition of all the
purposes that it served in this way are
taken into account and added to the
balance of the energy in the system.
Good. Thank you. I have one other
question. All right. It has been my
experience over the last x number of
years this lifetime first of all I came
upon the awareness of multi-dimensional
personality and then began meeting
different people who it seemed to me
were extensions of the same oversoul in
a
sense counterparts
um not of my own necessarily but I would
meet say five or six people and I
thought and it my experience was that
all of those five or six people were
extensions of the same oversoul. Pardon
me. Now, Leah on a tape says that each
of us as an oversoul may be operating
two or three thousand personalities.
Yes. Was that similar to your
perception? Yes.
Okay. Um I wanted to ask you your
perception of the connection between a
few different personalities that I'm
aware of to see if your perception of
their connection is similar to mine.
that uh no okay thank you for in this
way understand again the perceptions
that you have serve you as you have them
in the way you have them my opinion in
this sense means absolutely nothing very
good thank you thank you female and then
we will take short break um several
weeks ago you mentioned that the eyes of
March 15th of March would be a
particularly good time for activities
with extraterrestrials. An opportunity
opportunity. Okay. No guarantees. So, I
decided to have a party. Well, whether
whether whether you decide to come or
not, that's up to you. All right. Um, so
I'm having a party and I think Pam went
out the last time and I have naps which
I left out the car, but I will go with
them and hand them out. All right, each
and every one of you have a good time.
And also I'm very excited to hear that
other people are I mean this is
something I didn't even think about but
then to come here and hear other people
talking about it makes me aware of the
fact that yes this is really happening
to me too because lately I've been
hearing voices. I've been
hearing someone calling my name and
there's no one around and I just you
know I just go okay. Now you have
brought up a very interesting
point. Understand not that the
experiences as you are having them
specifically are not valid for they are
but what you can allow yourself to
recognize is the main point of all of
those specific experiences that you are
having is to recognize the
synchronicity with which you are having
them with other individuals.
That is the main point, not the specific
labeling of the way you are specifically
experiencing them. It is the recognition
that you are functioning and beginning
to recognize yourselves consciously in
one pulse, one
pulse, one
heartbeat. You may all take a short
break after All right.
All right.
All continue. Okay. Several weeks ago,
Kim was helping me to explore
uh to understand some things about
myself. Um, in July I had been attacked and my I
Um, in July I had been attacked and my I
had hit my head uh getting a confusion,
I guess. And he says that I probably
allowed that to happen so that I would
have a a reason
to an understanding of why I was having
so many headaches and being dizzy and a
lot of other things so I could so that
sounds good to me. But um now recently
I've fallen down the steps at my house
for the second time and I'm wondering if
I'm creating that for a similar reason.
What are your feelings at this point
about the idea? I don't know. I Well, I
haven't. Do you feel in this way that
certain scenarios you are creating in
your life in this way are causing you to
feel that you have to start all over
from the bottom?
I don't know. Does not have to be the
case. Just simply a suggestion. What do
you feel? Well, I don't know. Things are
still really kind of up in the air for
me. If you remember, I up in the
air somewhere. If you remember when I
first started coming here, I was looking
for a place to live in Malibu and I
ended up finding this place in the
Panga. Now, the place that I moved to
has been sold and so I'm still going to
be looking for a place in Malibu. All
right. Um, and so there's a lot of
change happening. Very good.
But, um, I also have this doctor that I
go to who's a chiropractor that I really
like a lot. Maybe I was maybe I I feel
that maybe I'm allowed myself to fall
down again so that I can make sure
coffee
can. So do you have any other You are
not finished yet. I'm not. Okay. Um and
also uh I'm suing the owner of the house
uh I'm suing the owner of the house
because there's no handrail. There's no
lights and the house has been really
bad. as far as things that should be
done to it that haven't been done to it.
So that's that's probably I don't know.
Yeah, I guess that's another reason. All
right. Anything else you wish to throw
in?
Uh yeah, I guess I feel that
might as well put it all on the table.
Okay. Um we've also talked about my
hearing problem. You're hearing what?
Didn't hear
that in my left ear.
And so what have you been told about
that so far? Well, from your medical
personnel? Um, nothing from him. From
another person that I had seen
previously. They had said that it was a
blockage in my middle ear and they tried
to fix it, but they couldn't fix it. And
why? Uh, I don't know. The things that they
Uh, I don't know. The things that they
they tried to do didn't didn't fix it.
And then I didn't have any more money,
so I quit going. All right.
So So now I guess it's a matter of if
somebody else is paying for it, then
maybe it can get fixed. Maybe, maybe
not. Maybe in this way you can simply allow
Maybe in this way you can simply allow
yourself when you begin listening to
yourself to fix it
yourself and stop
distrusting the constant state of motion
that can give you the stability you are
seeking. So you will not find yourself
falling down on the job.
down on the job.
of life. Now
life. Now
I'm going to stand in this way as we
have said the greatest degree of stability. Erica
stability. Erica
pay attention for Mark as well.
The greatest degree of stability is when
you keep moving and do not attempt to
put all your weight on one foot.
Okay? And in this way you will find that
if you attempt to do that the pressure
may be too much to
bear. And in this sense you can
understand that the idea of constant
motion is what will allow you to be the
most stable for change is the only
stable for change is the only
constant and in this sense
also the degree to which you are willing
to be
adaptable. Do you catch that connotation
also Erica for your friend?
So allowing the idea of of adaptability
to change different places. Yes.
Understand? It was the very essence of
the symbol of
adaptability that allowed him to make
the change from the place he thought he
was going to
begin. Do you follow me? Yeah. Are you
sure? I think so.
what you call the
cockroaches adaptability which is their
essential symbology. Oh
okay constants constants
constants constant
existence through complete adaptability.
Understand the reason they have not
changed is because they always are
changing. They are always adapting. Now
I am not calling you a
cockroach but in that sense you might
allow yourself to adapt a lesson from
them in that way. And also
Mark, the idea
that as you allow adaptability and
change to be all
right, then you will constantly form for
yourself situations that when they occur, no
situations that when they occur, no
matter how often they change, are always
stable situations
and not unstable
situations where you find yourself
falling. all around about
yourself. So, you follow me.
Well, I'm sure you're not telling me
that I have to move every four or five
months. Why not? Why are you so sure? I
am not saying you have to do anything.
One moment. I am not saying you have to
do anything. But allow me to illuminate
that if you happen to be creating the
type of reality where you find yourself
doing so then that is the type of
reality that is serving
you. Do it with joy and you will see why
you are creating it and at the same time
you will allow the way it is manifesting
to serve you. So it will not be a
burden. You will enjoy the
You will enjoy the
motion. And in enjoying the motion, you
may find yourself becoming more stable
than you have ever been.
That sounds good. I would prefer to
enjoy it. Then by all means do so. No
one is standing in your own way but you.
Allow the reality you are experiencing
as you are experiencing it to be the
reality you chose to experience so that
it can become another
reality. Only by allowing a purpose to
be served can you create other
purposes, other events, other
situations. Do not turn a deaf ear upon
yourself. Listen to what you actually are, not
Listen to what you actually are, not
what you think you should
be, not what others think you should
be, evolving.
[Music] Well, I don't know. I have a pretty
Well, I don't know. I have a pretty
clear idea what I am. You think so?
That's always changing. Of course. Yeah.
You said that's good. So, so that's
okay. Yes.
So there is no need to pin yourself
down in that sense.
Allow yourself to be
fluid for the new fourth density reality
in that way is the very essence of
adaptability and fluidity.
I feel that
understand that you may simply be
creating in a physically symbolic
terminology the idea that your
recognition of fourth density may be
showing you that if no one particular
place is your home then everywhere is
your home. You are at home anywhere that
you are.
That perhaps is the strongest reason for
the symbol you are creating as I
perceive it. Okay. I kind of feel that
that what you're telling me on another
level is that maybe I'm preparing myself
for um moving around a lot having to do with
um moving around a lot having to do with
the performance that I've spoken to you.
There are in this timing other beings that
are in this timing other beings that
have now revealed themselves to us that
are beginning to
recognize that an acceptable, stable
form of
life is to be a nomad.
Where's my motor home?
Right here.
Now thank you very much for your sharing
and Erica also recognize and to each and
every one of you also similarly
connected. Okay
Okay
that the energy of the serious
consciousness is already present.
Can you feel it? Yes. Now recognize in
this way the manifestation
at the level it exists right now is for
you to make use of as you
will for you are now in the time of the
transformation and are entering and
emerging into the
doorway. And in this sense to recognize
that while in this sense your friends
are here with us with
you, the opportunity to make their
energy to allow their energy to
manifest is
now. Thank you very much. Allow me
also to tell each and every one of
you that commencing in the time
frame that you call your April
month. Let us say though we will
continue to some degree in the manner in
which we are now interacting. You will
also find there will be an additional
format if you
will. It will
be activity.
Now we will we will we will make
underline this word suggestions
for activities. It is up to you willing or
activities. It is up to you willing or
not in whatever form your imagination
allows you to co-create the idea. But
suggestions we will suggest, activities
we will suggest that can allow you if
you are willing again in whatever way
your imagination be reflective of your
own vibration to partake of these
activities to allow you to physically
sense and experience in direct terms the
acceleration of your willingness to be
more sensitive.
Sounds great. Would you be interested in
stopping by a party at
this weekend? The activity will be for you to
weekend? The activity will be for you to
do.
Would you be interested in popping by?
Yes and no. All right. Each of you will
be attending your own party no matter
where you are.
I want to talk to you about my eyesight
a little bit. Most of my life has been
very good. The last year seems to be
getting worse and worse. All right. I
was wondering if you
the first and fundamental primary idea
which we have shared many times with
your civilization which is a fundamental
civilization which is a fundamental
underlying idea for many of you because
you are all connected in the same way in
the transformation is to recognize that
because of your old habits I say many of
you are now defocusing from the
structure you have been in so that you
can attune to an inner
sight before
me. It is as simple as that. Thank you.
Oh, really?
Then begin to trust what you are feeling
for yourself.
I was actually get I was actually
wondering also how bad it gets cuz I
hold my 18
in is neither good nor bad.
It is valid to the degree that you are
willing to explore certain ideas within
yourself. Now understand that because
you have now created the conviction of
the interaction of the recognition of
one of the ideas, one of the purposes
behind that, it will now also begin to
change in other
ways. Therefore, it is not so much that
it will continue linearly, although it
may a little bit, but it will also begin
to expand volutrically in different
ways. Shelly.
I for the last 20 years have had pain in
different parts of my body specifically
my shoulders both left and right side at
different times and
my lower and um middle back
and just recently I'm getting into more
and more understanding what the parts of
the body mean. All right. Um, are you
carrying any unnecessary burdens?
I honestly have to say I don't feel that
I am. All right. At this point, did you
before you felt those temptations?
Yes, I'm sure. You sure? Yes, I'm sure I
do because I know I've heard go a lot.
All right, very good. Then summing, you
are giving yourself a physiological
representation of many of the processing
that you are doing. So that you know
that when you have the effect of the
feeling in your body, you are already at
the end of the
process for you are channeling it
through you and out. Yes.
Yes.
And I I understand what you're saying.
Um I still don't understand why my body
is um so resisting. It feels like
resisting because there is still
ingrained within the overall habit of
the understanding of yourself in a
physical society. The idea that your
physical body as you have it now is
somehow different from the idea you will
be when you finally make the
transformation. And so in this way you
are still seeing the physical body at a
slower vibration. So that when higher
vibrations go through it there will be
friction which causes the
idea because of the different rates of
vibrations coming into contact with one
another through the specific energy
vortices in your body. You follow me?
Yes. It is simply remnants of the
habitual way you think of yourself as a
physical being compared to how you are beginning
being compared to how you are beginning
to think of yourself as a slightly less
physical being.
It will acclimate.
Okay. Um more and more I find myself saying
Um more and more I find myself saying
that I raising my mind and body to a
higher vibration. Is that helping in any
way? What does it do for you?
What does it do for you?
Sometimes I feel
like all right now understand that if
you find that to raise yourself is an
effort then don't do it that
way. If you simply feel the idea of your
expansion, the number span is not really
so much the idea that you are literally
raising anything. That in and of itself
is only a perspective. You are simply
expanding into more of the self that
already exists without ever.
exists without ever.
Yeah. So that you will not have to
sprain yourself.
Um when I think of expanding my
body, it's as
though I think of expanding and I really
see things in my mind. So when I get
into feeling physically, I find myself
gaining weight. All right. And I don't
want to do that. All right. Again,
simply part and powerful of the idea
that you are channeling the energy
through your physical body in terms that
are symbolic to the way you habitually
think the physical body to be. Again,
you will acclimate and the energy will
not add mass in a very short time. Oh,
thank you.
I did not do anything. Well, answered my
question. Oh, I do. Allow yourself also
to begin to recognize beginning this
night of your time that dialogues with
your dream consciousness can allow you
to assimilate that energy in a manner
that is less
than I started doing last night. All
right. Thank you. Thank you. One step
ahead of me.
for you.
and we also in this way revise the idea
that you had rechanled some of that
energy into the interaction that
occurred within what you call your
Philippines and in this sense recognize
that you did it in an extremely symbolic
manner for in this way the energy of
that area is contained within the heart
chakra of your planet. and the
individual involved is named after the
heart. For in this way also recognize
this has changed to some degree some of
the idea of your interaction with what
you call the Soviet Union. Although the
overall interaction is now remaining, it
is spreading itself out in many
different interactions that are varying
between the idea of negative and
positive effects. You are finding
yourselves recently, very quickly, more
and more forming different kinds of
interactions with that country and they
with you in a very blatant way.
you in a very blatant way.
So the
stated United States and Russia
it is one of the
ideas coming down. I heard something on
the news. The wind had come down.
That had what you call nuclear engine.
derived power source from nuclear means
and in this way form the same dispersion
of the idea of the nuclear contaminants
in the atmosphere as it burned up as you
say as the nuclear batteries aboard some
of the instruments aboard your shuttle
also provided into the atmosphere.
So it was match for match.
Do you mean your Soviet craft? In this
way, it will have dispersed itself over
wide range of what you call your oceans.
And you said it was
nuclear. What happened to Florida?
in this way. Now understand again and
pay strict
attention. We are not saying this will
occur but there is the probability for
certain individuals if they are still of
a mine tube as they are of a mine tube
right now to perhaps
exhibit some diseased effect from having
inhaled those particles along what you
call your eastern seabboard.
How many? How many individuals? This is
not determined.
The decisions are made in the moment
they are made. And they are not all
made and they are constantly shifting.
They are constantly connected to all the
other ideas that are going on between
you and every other being on your planet
as to whether it will serve a purpose or
not for them to become
deceived. It may
not. If the lines of communication
continue to open as they are now
doing, it may not serve a purpose.
You will find at this time that there
are many of
you that are finding yourselves all of a
sudden taking trips to the Soviet
Union. And in this way you will also
find there are many of them visiting you
and that the lines of communication are
opening more and more and more with and
without the interaction of what you call
the government.
For you are now beginning to get the
idea that you are your own government.
Um NASA this week discovered the remains
of the seem to be a little secretive
about it.
Simply in this way they are doing it out
of consideration.
nothing like they didn't
die. I would be devastating people.
You will find in this way that it is our
perception that they were in your terms
either physically dead or nearly so upon
the contact with the water. And in this
way if you will find that what you call
your autopsy may show that there was
water entering into the lung cavity. It
will be the idea that they were
unconscious. True.
There's a current theory in new physics
that there's a a concept called ether.
And this ether is it is an old theory as
well. Revive. Sure. Well, it's a web of
what they say pure massless charge that
underlies all the physical universe.
Okay. Does that have anything to do with
what you want to follow?
Okay. Pure massless charge.
Okay. If you take away all the matter
that there is there there instead of
pure vacuum was once believed there is a
web of mass with charge underneath.
There is something else. There is a
potentiality of creation that fills all
that seems to be empty. In other words,
now what I wanted to know uh you
mentioned that gravity gravity as we
perceive it is the interaction between
the physical world and the template
universe. Does this does this web fit in
any anywhere in that? Yikes. It is the
representation. It is the first
physicalized manifestation of the
template. Okay, we're going to go deeper into that
Okay, we're going to go deeper into that
event.
other manifestations.
Well, they become more and more physical
from that point.
In other words, that is the simplest
physicalized manifestation of a
non-physical template.
It is the homogeneous energy out of
which all physical reality is
differentiated. They call it hand energy. Nice. Um, is
They call it hand energy. Nice. Um, is
there is there you mentioned earlier
that the device you had us experiment
with the rotating copper disc in the
electromagnetic field.
Now I' I've envisioned that experiment
in my head and it seems that either it's
going to translate from place to place
or it may rise up. Uh that means that
somehow you're blocking what we call a
gravitational field, the transmission of
this field. Channeling it, not blocking
it. against itself or more through the
against itself or more through the
device. In other words, rather than let
us use a simple analogy rather than the
idea, let us say you have what you call
a tube, a short tube if you wish, the
analogy you call a can with no covers.
You follow me? Sure. And in this way, if
you wish to propel it from place to
place, what you are doing now with your
technology is giving it a good swift
kick. before age. Now, if you can
understand that you can place what you
call a rope through the can and lift one
end, the can will simply slide from
place to
place. The rope can be analogous to the
idea of the gravity field in this way
and it defines the course that the can
will take depending upon how you channel
the rope through the can. Rather than
needing to keep the rope still and kick
the can along the rope, you can move the
rope and move the can simultaneously. Is
that what they call high and
low pale electromagnetic potential? To
some degree that is one manifestation of
that idea but only one manifestation. You divine. Malaysia,
Malaysia,
they are culture. Yes.
much like what you call American Indian recommen in the
in the
dream go after the gift no matter what
go after the gift. All right. What about
giving them a gift?
All
right. Once they have the gift to
defend, they work out to work out their anger
they work out to work out their anger
and violence.
So do you. Many times
you simply have your own symbol for it.
Some of them you call nightmares.
In this way though, they they had They
would dream their anger through to a positive
dream their anger through to a positive
outcome. Yeah. And then they would wake
up in the morning always have the
children with all right and vice versa.
And then they would manifest
in some way during the day. They would
create um I a long time ago about well four
um I a long time ago about well four
years ago or so tried this process did
the process.
and found that
I was able to look through a lot of all
right then at the tool observed you did and
then at the tool observed you did and
then I got scared about it all right
because I thought perhaps you are not
being Malaysian enough
I am being serious
if you are the vibration of the idea of
those Malaysians then you will allow it
to serve you in the way it serves them.
What I got scared about was the idea
that I had so much violence or anger in
me that I wondered if I
was creating more.
Now in a sense understand one idea that
anger in of itself in its natural state
is not negative.
You can choose to make it negative. But
in this way, anger is simply the
aligning energy that allows you to
synchronize with what you know
represents the reality you
are. You follow me? That is all anger
actually is for. And when you allow it
to be natural, it will usually last no
longer than 10 to 15 of your will be
aligned with regard to what you are
seeing. You will simply know what
represents the reality you are and you
will simply know that that is what you
have preferred. Or you can at least give
yourself the opportunity to prefer
something else if you find that your
anger has shown you that you do prefer
something else.
else.
Yes. When you allow it to seem to be the
natural anger. Now if you continue to judge
anger. Now if you continue to judge
it then it can turn into judgment,
guilt, frustration, hate, violence and
all those different ideas. Very good.
Yeah. As soon as you started to judge
yourself, find yourself coming up short
in your own
self-empowerment, then in this way you
extend the experience of violence. Then what?
Well, at the time
I read process in that I got
clear of my own what I
right but now I'm where I'm concerned with
but now I'm where I'm concerned with
this is if I'm living my dream right now
will I
I
be violence it is your
choice understand we may once again use
if you wish the library
analogy it is all right for you to read
any book in the library that you are,
positive and or
negative. What your reality is is the
book you choose to check
out. You follow me? Therefore, make your
choice consciously. You can know it is
all right to experience all the violence
you want, for it is one idea you can
experience, for you are all that is. And
it will always be a potential that you
can have within you as long as you are
physical in a dimension which you can
experience it in that way. So let it be
equal to everything else. And then you
will not think that the reality the idea
of a violent reality has any more power
than the reality of a nonviolent
reality. And you will choose from equal
choices what you prefer to experience.
You are able right now to simply
understand that if
you already understand the
situation, if you can perceive the
situation you think you are in, you are
not in it
anymore You follow me? Yeah. Yes.
Therefore, you are automatically by
definition already outside of it.
Otherwise, you would not be able to see
it. You follow me? The analogy was put
forth by one of your individuals upon
your planet that as long as you are on
an island, you may not know it is an
island. When you know it is an island,
you are off of it. to be able to see all
at once in one glance that it is an
island. So when you know it is an
island, the question, how do I get off
this island is already meaningless. For
to be able to even ask the question, you
are already off of it. For you know it
is an
island. You follow me?
Therefore, recognize that many times the
questions that you ask are not the
beginning of a necessary process, but
the
end. Unless you choose to believe that
it is not real and you believe you must
create a series of steps in order to
achieve the idea that you have rather
than simply recognizing that that idea
that you have is the idea that you
are and that is all there is to it.
Thank you. For sure.
Friday, I was feeling all this energy
coming into my space and in the evening
I got this real strong energy as though
someone was trying to get it. When I got
that there was a disaster or
something upset and but I couldn't get
what it was. I don't know if
somebody running a body in the middle of
a disaster
or I don't know whatever
only that we will once again ask you
what do you choose to do with that
effect and that information in the form
in which you created it.
Well I at the time does it peak your
curiosity? I'm speaking to warn people. Warn them?
I'm speaking to warn people. Warn them?
Yeah. Of what? What? You don't have
anything to warn them about, do you? No,
I didn't. Good.
Yes. For in this way, you would be
running, as you say, hither and yawn,
warning people about things that may
have only to do with you.
Did it only have something to do with a
sense? What was it?
Understand that one of the ideas within
you that has been within you for some
time is that when you allow the energy
of your higher self to come through.
You many times believe that the
information will be of a dire nature.
And this is giving you an opportunity to
come to terms with the idea that you can
have that feeling and yet have nothing
to talk
about. So that you can let the feeling
through and know that it is serving you
by getting used to it, getting over it,
and not necessarily in this way
reinforcing the so-called dire
circumstances. you think have to be
connected to the feeling which is not.
You follow me? Yeah. It is for you one
way to practice the methodology of
delivering the channeling of your higher
self, not so much the information.
It has to do with you getting used to
the methodology. So you will balance
your system. So you will be clear for
the information and not put such dire
information and not put such dire
meaning upon it.
I was wondering
um I have these hearts. Yes. And one
time most
Yes. You are very sensitive to the
electromagnetic fluctuations of your
planet as many individuals are. You will
find that your heart chakra will be
sensitive to those fluctuations and
individuals will from time to time
experience what you call
palpitations that will be reflective of
the intensity and sometimes even the
local of what you call your earthquake
or volcanic activity. Recognize that
many times when you have your
palpitations there may be another
portion of your body that also exhibits
the idea of pain. the other portion of
your body can give you a clue as to the
local, the intensity of the palipotation
to the intensity of the quake or the
volcanic activity. And in this way, even
the type of palpitation as to whether it
is or not earthquake or
volcano. Simply the more you experience
different tremors and quakes, pay
attention, for it is in itself its own
symbology and carries with it its own
symbolic language. Do not worry, there is nothing
language. Do not worry, there is nothing
wrong with you. You are sensitive to
those electromagnetic fluctuations in
your heart and in the sinus area where
you have a high degree of
magnetite. You follow me?
Thank you.
Yes. to the subject of poetry. Poetry.
What would you have me say?
Particular in relation to the
transformation to the new age. The
function of poetry of the new age
can be the allowance by you of the
recognition in new
terminology of that which you may call
synchronicities. The idea that as things
The idea that as things
rhyme, that is a reflection of events in
time. And with regard to the
idea of your
experience in this way, you can
simply trust that each and every day that you
trust that each and every day that you
create for yourself to
live as
life, you
you
will absorb and replace all notions.
of
strife. It is in your
terms the use of your language to paint
a
picture. And in this way you can give
yourself a
sense of the music, the tonality and the
harmony that goes into forming the
realities that you experience, the
patterns, the tempos, the
pace. You follow me? You will
You will
find that in fourth density life
itself is the literal expression poetry
in motion.
Thank you for your sharing. Yes. My
question about being on that island and
not really possibly not knowing what
you're
on in the middle of one, not really
knowing the way out or even sure that
the way out of what? Out. Out of what?
What predicament?
I teach.
Is that ridiculous? Science.
Just lightening things up a bit.
All right. Thank you.
Continue. Problem situation. Situation is that I'm
Problem situation. Situation is that I'm
in an inner city and I'm very sensitive
to emotions around me. And what I'm
experiencing is a lot of anger and rage
in my environment. And I find myself
picking up on it. Yes. And sometimes
being almost out of control with it. All
right. How does that feel?
Feels awful. Awful. Awful. I and I'm not
unacustomed to expressing anger but I am
in a situation where
um it could present a problem
situation a situation
prefer
so uh and I also have been at
times in the habit of carrying a lesson
further than I need to.
Yes. And I'm wondering perhaps the
situation I'm in right now. I'm staying
longer than I need to. What is a
teacher? Yeah. Someone
and also someone that learns
that the students are also teachers.
What are they teaching you?
Patience. Why do you need
patience? Patience is only the result of
impatience. If you are enjoying every
moment of your life as you are creating
it, you do not need patience. You are
too busy having fun.
Now they are teaching you that you as
well contain the idea of
rage. You follow me? So they are giving
you an opportunity to first of all
identify with their
reality so that you can come to equal
sharing. First of all,
all right.
If they do not believe that you
understand their
reality, they will not feel that they
can interact with you
equally. Therefore, you are now first of all
Therefore, you are now first of all
allowing yourself to tap into the
understanding that you can
identify with the level of emotional
energy in the way they express
it. so that you become like unto them.
You follow me?
Now that is the first step in the
process you have created. You allow
yourself to become equal to
them according to their
understanding of
reality. When you let that be the lesson
they have to show you, when you let it
be equal to all the other lessons you
think you are
teaching, then you will truly begin to
teach. For in this way you will find
that once you are equal to them, you
will not have to allow them to create
the idea that you only teach them and
they only learn from you. But that you
are learning from them. They are
learning from you. You are teaching each
other and therefore you are sharing
equally and you understand each other
equally. Then once everything is
equal, you can then offer them the
opportunity to view that your
understanding of reality can also be
their understanding of reality and they
can then choose another reality besides
rage. Then you will have taught them.
But the first step in your process is to
allow them to know that you do in fact
identify with them. So by all
means, by all means tell
them tell them that they have taught you
what it is like to feel rage and you
know therefore what their own rage feels
like and you can understand
them. And then
hint hint that they can
hint that they can
know they can
know that the opportunity they have
created by attracting you to
them and them to
you is that you know you
know even though they may not you know
that they are
selfmpowered and can do anything that
they wish to do without needing to hurt
anyone else to do it. That's how
powerful they really are. And you know
they are that powerful. They are only
creating their rage because they don't
believe in their own power.
They have not felt it. Allow them to
feel their true
power by teaching them that you believe
in
them. Now understand
this. This is something we have
discussed recently of your time. One of
the reasons again not that you need us
in any way, shape, or form, but simply
that you have recognized that your
co-creation of interaction with us many
times has allowed you to see aspects of
yourself you may not have been willing
to see
beforehand. But simply the reason that
that occurs at
all is because that well while we do
believe that you are creating certain
scenarios for yourself that may or may
not impose certain
limitations fundamentally fundamentally when you
fundamentally fundamentally when you
tell us of your struggles and your
strife we don't believe you.
We believe that you are
basically perfect that you are as powerful as you
perfect that you are as powerful as you
need to be to create all that you are
experiencing. So when you say I am this
and I am that and it is negative and
this and that. I don't believe you and
that is the only reason you can allow me
to assist you. is because you know that
when you come to me telling me how
terrible you are, I won't believe you
because I know that you are love
it and that everything you do is an act
of love because you are created from
love. That is what you are made of.
So if you are willing to share with them
that they have taught you
rage and you can then teach them that
that rage that they have taught you to
feel is in no way, shape or form as
powerful an
expression in their own terms as the
true power that they have as the creator
of that
rage. Then they can begin to relax
within their own power and understand
that the world is already
theirs and that they do not have to
control it in order to have it. And in
point of fact, they lose it when they
attempt to do so. that they are
already already as powerful as they will
ever be. And if they simply are willing to
be. And if they simply are willing to
recognize
that, they can have anything they
desire without
[Music] needing to attack anyone
needing to attack anyone
else or in very many ways even involve
anyone else or to have that.
believe in them and let them know you
believe in
them and that they have a
choice. Understand they have been born into
Understand they have been born into
belief
systems that are in your
terms strong
habits. But that is also only an idea.
It does not have to be a
barrier. Their culture is your
culture. You are the earth's
culture. You have understood rage in
your lifetimes. And so they are expressing it
lifetimes. And so they are expressing it
in this
lifetime. But now you know they are
something more than their rage. They are
something more than their rage. Let them
know that so they can begin to single.
In this way, through the connections
that I form in your civilization, I give
myself the opportunity to have those
experiences, but they do not create a
manifestable effect in my society.
Yes.
Thank you for the opportunity.
Yes. solar system
not in your solar system in the galaxy. Thank you.
Thank you.
um in the galaxy by the name of a
density there.
Sir, beyond Pluto.
Yes, in a sense. Do you mind if I
interject? Was the one planet that was
destroyed now represented by the
asteroid belt? Yes. Okay. That is the
reference. Mald.
What's the name of the other one?
There is none. At this point in our
perception, we do not find anything in
your terms lower than fifth.
Are you referring to Mal?
Okay. Yes or no?
One of the two
in a sense
one as we have said that was in your
terms destroyed and one as yet
undiscovered. Do you know the view of all of it of
Do you know the view of all of it of
what of the other
plan? Third beyond Pluto.
Yes. In a sense. Do you mind if I
interject? Was the one planet that was
destroyed now represented by the
asteroid belt? Yes. Okay. That is the
reference. Mald.
What's the name of the other one?
There is none.
If it's transdimensional, there are two
transdimensional. One. One destroyed, right?
One. One destroyed, right?
One destroyed, two
transdimensional, one as yet
undiscovered in your own dimension.
Okay. The transdimensional we wouldn't
proceed with our telescope. No.
Any of the ancients pictured 12 planets.
Is that where that fits in? Yes. So, do
you know the density level of any of
those planets? The transdimensional
1/4. What is transdimensional? They do
not exist in your dimension. But as you
proceed into the next dimensionality,
you will begin to perceive it.
But you're saying that there is an
additional planet in our dimension that
yes, we could actually land on if you
would, but we haven't discovered. Yes.
Where is the light? We are scient
within the
next you call decade.
Where is the one beyond? It is not in
this way in what you call precisely the
plane of the ecliptic
as is also not Pluto.
Does the sun have a a binary? Yes. How
distant is it from the sun?
the
translations into your terminology. Some
of them are not contained in the
physiological channel. One moment.
Let us say in a
sense what you would call one3 Third
approximately there will be some
discrepancy in this approximately
between what you call 16 to 1/3 the
distance to your next nearest star.
Okay. Which is approximately 4.1 years.
Yes. Approximately between 2/3 and one light.
Not that far.
If the binary is closer, then it is a
dark star.
It is the one you have recently labeled
Nemesis.
And yet ours to our planet. Yeah. The
other one is so distant it doesn't
really affect our orbit. We can notice
it. Oh, it does when it comes into the
system. And does that and has many
times. Okay. Does Nemesis have planets
revolving around it?
There is one trailing it.
What is the period of the Nemesis?
Approximately in your terms again there
will be some discrepancy in translation
but between what you call 20 to 33
million of your years.
Yes. It is as you have surmised to some
degree what is responsible for the
periodic extinctions upon your planet.
That's the theory in the book.
extinction. What you call life yet?
How did you find a dark star? In this
way, you will find it to be a dense mass
that does not radiate light in
your visible spectrum. more it will be
infrared and below
almost what you would
call neutronic
very old. Yes. And in a sense originally
from another system
like neutroneum you call it very
dense. You understand the term uh
vaguely in the sense that what you call
the idea for analogy one cubic
foot would weigh as much as many of your
mountains
other words uh it
is collapsed yes and therefore does not
radiate in the higher frequencies there will
there will
brief period of time remaining for
listening her accent.
Um, often times I'm pointing out
different uh stars uh which I perceive
are spacecraft and uh rarely
spacecraft and uh rarely
rarely. Okay. Well, often times I have
seen and you have mentioned on the
nights that uh you know people can't
sleep those are usually the nights that
I'm pointing out. All right. There can
be the perceptions of energies in this
way simply they do not always manifest
in the term you call spacecraft. Okay.
Well, will you tell me then? I see often
starlike uh light that rotate colors
uh light that rotate colors
uh specifically red, green,
blue, some yellow, orange maybe. And uh
some of these are simply your stars
aberated by your atmosphere.
Some are not. Some are energy doorways.
Yeah. What does that mean? Dimensional
doorways. Does that clarify the idea?
Doorways or tunnels to other dimensions
of
existence. Does that clarify the idea?
Through these doorways, many of
so-called spacecraft emerge.
Well, the the color the I mean the the
color is real vivid. I mean and they
they do tend to move with the flow of
the stars. Yes. Again, understand that
when it is for the most part the idea of
atmospheric aberration, your atmosphere
will simply act like a prism and take
and bend the starike. So it will have
the entire range of the spectrum.
Yes. Understand that above your
atmosphere, the stars do not twinkle, as
you say. The atmosphere is a lens that
distorts. That's what bothers me because
there is a distinct difference in these
and twinkling. It's it's like a
rotation. What you say? It's a
rotation. That may appear to be the
case. But again, your atmospheric
aberration can also cause that. Now, we
are not saying that that is the case in
every case, but it is the case in the
majority. And how would you know if you were
And how would you know if you were
seeing a spacecraft?
You would not
necessarily now understand
this. There is in a sense to be
practical for a
moment, let us say a rule of thumb that
you may use in this way that many
individuals have found to be convenient
for them. Unless it is obviously a
them. Unless it is obviously a
spacecraft, then it is not one, even if
it
is. For what purpose does it serve? If
you have to
guess. Mhm. Therefore, if you see
something and you are not sure, go on
about your business.
When you are sure, you will be sure.
There will be no mistake.
You follow me. Thank you. You sure?
briefly, right? The other night we went up. The
right? The other night we went up. The
other night we went up to the um
observatory and they had Orion
um on the scope
and I went up to view it and in doing so
I got extremely dizzy as if I were being
lifted and I couldn't feel the floor or
the stairway and felt as if I was going
to tumble or fall over. Took me quite
some time to get my equilibrium back.
All right.
simple identification with times past.
identification with times past.
That is all we can say for now in the
time frame that we have. Okay. Briefly,
a man named Bellacovsky on our planet
said that the reason for our frequent
catastrophes or at least one that
happened uh 15 20,000 years ago is that
Venus had a near collision with the
Earth and that's the reason why it spins
the opposite direction to all of the
planets. Is there a truth to that?
To some degree there was a shifting in
that way to some
degree of that
idea. This is something we can
delineate a little bit later your time
in more
detail. For now there have been many
more than you think. Shiftings and
balancings and rebalancings of the
orbits of your planets much more than
you think for various reasons.
Now understand this
idea. Just as you have in a sense the
idea of a magnetic axis shift within
your own
planet, so also does the solar system.
So also does every
galaxy have in a sense magnetic axis
shifts.
This is another phase of understanding
of a new set of dynamics and in this way
we can discuss them later. But to be
brief, some of that shifting idea of the
solar systems magnetic flux was the
cause in this way of some near
interactions in the various orbits of
different planets at that time.
and the cause of some of what you now
experience to be some ideas of
retrograde motion.
He was close. Yes. But there are a few
principles as yet undiscovered that were
not in the
equations at the time. Understanding
magnetic flu. Yes.
Quickly quickly. We did see one night
about six weeks
ago the same thing that I just described
to you. You saw a starlike object moving
away from us
specifically. Do could do
you see anything in
that? I just think you six weeks ago as
if it was a shuttle leaving the mother
ship. Yeah.
This is what I will share with you at
this time.
Understand that you are witnessing the
idea of emotion as you describe it, but
not in your
dimension. And this leads to many other
ideas and depends upon your willingness
to extend your senses
farther. What you see many times is not
physical sight, though you do not know it.
sight, though you do not know it.
You follow me? Yeah. Go with that for
now. And here is a
suggestion. When you see something in
your sky, sky,
extend
imagination. Extend your senses to that
point in
space and simply see what you pick up.
You will always pick up some form of
consciousness for everything is
conscious. But see what you
get. That is one of the reasons you are
being in a sense
lured into extending your senses into
what you are
seeing. But you have not yet begun to
extend yourself in the manner of the
invitation being offered. And so we
cannot discuss what you yourself will
create yourself to find.
Yet when you begin to interact a little
more, there will be the cocreation of
the delineation of some of that
interaction. That is what we can share
for now.
Of course can be. It is up to you. Thank
you very much. One moment.
One moment.
Was there female? Yes. All right. You
then you that is all. My understanding
of the planet most deck is that located
in the serious system. Can you check
that out? Understand
Understand
this. There is an identification
counterpart within the serious system.
But because of the idea of its
extradimensional aspect in your
own that is why there is a
connection just as our planet in our
system is a connection to
you and the serious planet sustain in
their system is a connection to us and
to you.
There are other planets in your system
that have counterparts in our system and
in theirs and that is one of them in
that way though it also exists in your
own in another dimensional plane.
Yes. By what criteria do do you choose
to uh leave for any evening?
In this way, simply the sense of the
timing of what has been created, the
amount of momentum
generated, the idea of our own endeavors
making themselves known to us in this
timing which lets us know that we have
created all that needs to be created
within this particular now moment. I see
sort of like a seasoning of activity
here and energizing on your side. Yes,
in a sense. Thank you.
through you.
In this way, we extend once again the
idea of the
sharing in the eternal now of
unconditional love which creates
all there
is. We thank you for your
cocreation, for your sharing, for your
love, for your gift.
We bid you exciting dream
lives. We bid you fun.