How are you all time is time to
we willing time this intera with the
idea that each and every of you is architect a
desire you have
created your idea of ​​yourself in this physiological
your idea of ​​yourself in this physiological
life you have come into
this physiological life with the tools
that you need that we have discussed
many times with you your
imagination to enable you and you to
become the planner the designer the
architects of the lives you are
living in this
way that you have infinite store of blind
in your dream in your initiation
and you call upon
many of them and them man them intoity
all as we  haveed that it takes
is your willingness to have the
conviction to truly set up sh to take
the action to
know to feel that you are truly that not
to
as you can be many of you go through
your lives thinking you are not very creative
you constantly compare
yourselves against other individuals
whom you feel to be more creative simply
because of the specific way in which
they exibit their creativity and by
having been t that only certain ways of
expression in your society are those that represent creativity do
you then
think you are that
faulty do not
forle that in ஆக்சன்ஸ்
All your as you are
do to the depth and the
bread of tools that you have access to
that you have available to you to draw
Allow your
tr that you are lerallyators
with creation
in a you cann do anything but create
so recogn and allow
yourself to and become familiarized with
and comfortable with the fact that you
are always in the act of creation are the hand
that paint the you as
yoursical life  and you always have the
option and
ortunity to create your to be a new canvely
any given and another masterp you your are masterp
are masterp
you can always
recogn your as you wish to imagine as
you wish to desire your lives to be now
lead to the understanding and more and
more cognition that your physical lives
are in fact let say not to be the
meaning but to use your language in
explanatory manner and analy manner your
physical lives as we have said are truly
nothing more than let us say
exceptionally lucid
dreams solidified dreams [music] able time and
time and
you recogn that  is
only dream and as you blend the dream reality
dream and as you blend the dream reality
more and more with the physical and versa
you will then recognize that every
stroke you
paint will truly really alter actually alter
the physical reality that you
experience as you allow there to be
andar dreaming and what you
callicalysicality only ever been your
specifically design dream in to
the pain you call
you have
painted many
paintings under the same title.
new free for at any given you have never
been anything but free to allow yourself
to the pi you desire to experience as
the life you are living you are you
created by cre
you but expential that
you perceive is your
architecture for creation has beeped
unto all beings with creation the
ability to
beesigners so each un manpril and
manpril and
more and
more ways methodologies so in that way
allow your to and to
believe that regardless of what your
talent is of what your creativity is
You are all creative
in your own unique way by and
for there is and never  has been and
never will again ever be anyone like
you.  Even though as we have said there is a
youess as reincarnation the you you
are now does
in fact only have one life to
live it knowing that you do fit in or you
it knowing that you do fit in or you
would not be a part of the overall painting
each and every one of you is a
brush stroke in the painting of your
civilization in the painting of the
universe.
andan to the stroke of your
existence so that you can support the
big picture.
[music]
The title can be designer
dreams.  You strawberry.  How are you?
Perfect.  How are you?  Perfect.  Thank
you. as
as
you first let
me my admiration for the eloquence of
the painting that we call
tonight paint me if you will a picture
of what we would turn a day in the life of I
of I
will explore
expand my interests into what you would
call the advancement of our technology
to explore other dimensions of
existence I have in my capacity to be the architect
of those new methodologies
of exploration now have begun to
experience excursions into dimensions of reality
that our
civilization are available
time to time
will commic otherivations
[applause] aslean
aslean
understanding  consci and i will act with
them as
asivations in there may be
as you would call the idea of
physiological sculpture for enjoy that a
great deal var [music ] make
make
the before 2000
will undergo radical
changes in in climate and earth vol all
right stop stop stop stop stop perception
enercrect however it is a perception of
momentum behind certain ideas with your
civilization that is changing the way it
is changing is this there will be
transformations and there may be to some deree tic
changes energy changes
electromagnetic changes may  localized
expressions as have already been to some
deree of what you call shiftings in your
planetary structure however recogniz
that within the last what you call 30 of
your years and very specifically with the
last end of years many of what you call
the old predicted events no longer have to
manifest to the deree that happ happ
[applause] fire fire
enerpressions
enerpression you
There is no such thing as a prediction
of the future.  There is only a sensing
of the energy that is the most probable energy
that may manifest in your reality
at the time the prediction is made.
that your awareness of any so prediction
in itself changes the energy and the
prediction is your opportunity to decide
well I have now been told where a great
deal of momentum lies in our society.  Do
I wish to put stock in that or do I
prefer another reality now that I am
aware of what direction and behind which idea
the energy is going.  If you find
that you do in fact prefer another way to manifest that reality
then take the so-
called prediction as your opportunity to
change that reality at least for
yourself.  So
that if there will be certain individual
who still believe they must go through
the transformation in catastrophic ways you do not
need to be present in those areas you
the more and more and more of you
that choose to believe you can go through
the transformation in
transformation in
noncatastric ways will then by blending
and combining enery
a vast majority of your will need
to go through catastrophic
transformations and cans to undergo
transformation in beneficial and
positive ways you follow me yes that ass you
yes [music]
[music]
I'm unclear as
to how if  there was a major point
earthquake in Los Angeles and as they
will be destroyed
how do we that
energy first that some has already g to be reach
and the sucession of smaller someer
put others are
you will simply comes with knowing
will simply comes with knowing
whatity you vibrate accord to by knowing
you do not need to a transformation in
that way you will automatically automatically
be functioning on a
vibratory level that will allow you to
take have potentially catastrophic
energy and channel it through you in
positive way.  It is not that you have to have
a conscious analytical methodology
of how to do it.  Simply, if you know you do not
need that experience and if you
exist in an area where you think that
potential exists, then you will
release through your body.  You will act
as a safety vow simply by being in that
area and knowing that that reality is not true
for you.  You will then live
your life in a manner in a style that
will allow that energy that is always coming to
you to be transformed in you
and expanded outward into your reality
and allow your reality, the reality you
experience in a daytoday event to become a
reflection of the use of that energy
in a positive way as opposed to a
negative way.  Are you catching this?
Yes.  Does that yes it does you thank you
very much. harvesting harvesting Yes. 51
in first of all we would su you we would su
that in your terminology you call
harvest perhs you might wish toly stick
to transformation for harvest implies en
would be transformed at the same
time.  Yes, but that is doing in the
sense of your desire to express that
fourth state.  Now there will be perhaps
a few entities that will remain in third
density.  That's their chic.  It is our
perception that the majority of the
individuals upon your planet will as you
say kick over into denity when they need to.
At this time everyone has a
different rate of acceleration into that
idea of ​​service but in general the
overall average rate will seem to
project that within the span of
approximately the next 27 of your years
the majority of your planet will all thatity
state.  Are you following me?  Yes, that
is our perception of the energy.
Generally speaking yes in a sense 51% by
definition in your terms is required but
it is not something that is difficult to
do for you are at any given time
100% of an overall idea that you are being
and if you simply being the idea
of ​​service in that way knowing that by
being of service you are automatically served you
are 100% in that If
If
they third can be many different
occurrences that can be perceived the
idea can simply be that they will in
their own time physically die out and
simply not be reincarnated in your
fourth density world but reincarnate in
a third density version or parallel earth
or they can literally
physiologically
that oh yes how
would he dire he dire
you
by recognizing that a healer recognizes that
the healer assists others to heal
themselves.  Are you following me?  Yes.  Then
secondly that you cannot force anything on
anyone else nor do they have to choose
your point of view.  The way let
us best is to first of all and
fundamentally recogn that whatever it is
they are doing whether you label itth or
third density or otherwise is at that
moment obviously what they believe they
need to explore to understand that
portion of themselves.  So first of all
trust in the fundamental
indestructibility of that being. har et all
et all
right then from that attitude and point of view
you can take the
pressure the situation in terms of
needing them to change needing them to
become other than what they are you will
under any idea is
something you can ass them by asking
them how does the situation serve them how does it
you how does it have what does
this situation allow them now to face
that perhaps they were not
willing to face before the creation of the
disease for many times that is why
your society creates disease because it has been
taught to not face certain
portions of its wholeness  and in not
being willing to face its wholeness it
will then create situations where it is forced to Now
Now
if there is
nothing they can discover
about themselves that they need to fear
then they will not necessarily have to take
such drastic measures in order to force
themselves to look at a certain
portion that they have buried with
their conscious to bring it to the
surface through the drastic idea you
call disease.  If they are willing to
face and integrate every portion of
their being that they could ever discover
, then they will not need a
disease in order to discover those ideas
and they can allow themselves to accept
another perhaps a more positive delivery
service for the message that they are
attempting to show themselves.  Are you
following me?  I do.  How do you
in as we have already sued ask them what
they are getting out of it by having it
in the first place let them to explore
that there is just poss
a positive reason for why they have
it let them to explore how it might be
positive and then they can allow
themselves to expand to their awareness Yes, thank Yes, thank
[music]
you. You have something that I want to share
You have something that I want to share
with all right up.  Thank you.
a few weeks ago, several weeks ago,
almost couple months ago, after I
started coming here and listening to
you, talk to the group and the group
share with you and several times, many
many times I heard you say follow your
excitement. that
that
was very for
to and it took weeks before I was even
willing to let go and
around but the thing that I toare with the
group here is that I finally
did to experent right and to very
lightly just of my
of my
excit and little
little
of and if that didn't kill me then
maybe and so I did and son of a gun some
amazing things opened up and so I
started to think oh maybe this isn't
quite so dangerous as I had imagined it
could [music] more more
[music]
contr contr thates to outs go
outs go
all by
only areas of
life coming here
So what has
resulted from that
experiment is that I have developed a
business where I help myself and other
people follow their excit
what it has all
to all
your and it's the most amazing things have
been coming into my space and the
most amazing
Do you mean to tell
me that life works you
it?  I am so
shocked by the truth and the people and the
quality of the of the realities that
I've been creating and of the people who have been
creating with me just keeps [applause]
doubling and it's like a game now to find let's
find another piece of
excitement very exciting game.  Yes, it
is.  And I want to thank you.  very
very like to thank you for being willing
toess the unique facet of the
multidimensional that you are for every
individual makes a differ to the entiation
every individual's willingness to
function in that way allows the
entire civilization that much more
opportunity to also choose to function
likewise. Yes, that's true.  And I've been seeing
Yes, that's true.  And I've been seeing
that with people around me.  What
a follow my excitement, those around me that
are picking up on the excitement
are starting to go, "Oh, hey, she's
having fun."  And then they start to
possibly step out a little bit and then they
get into some excited.
excited.
Marvelously wonderful.  Thank you very
much. Thank Thank
you.
Hi.  I haven't seen you for you been on
vacation and I was on vacation.
So I am always
on vacation right
now.  So we vacation in the same
location.
I have two questions.  One developed as a
result of the last one you had with the
gentlemen.  You mentioned the phrase of
when a key portion of self is presented to
view guys by another delivery service
other than a catastrophic uh
you know my uh when that
occurs say I in the dream state et all
right how best effectively does one handle uh I
mean okay so you know here is
a negative portion of self All
All
right.  All right.  Comes up
dream.  Now, now what do you do?  What's
the best thing to do other than you can do
many things.  One thing you can do is
allow yourself to recogn that if you
already with your dream reality, it is over
and there is no need to assume that is a
necessary process.
Ass integrated act like and you will fr
of the integration you have some other
things you can suffer over [laughter] it Now you [laughter] [music]
can I you on behalf of
all my question I came with tonight
Yes.  Did you have it in a little?
little?
Yes.  My
husband my husband sends mother call to say
that she has been having quite a
time with him. things
things
unsa up you know on and
oned about the sit
anded to know what we could do to
help those w her words but that's what
you think so
well that's my re to i see all
So I would to may I rewrite the end of
the very much the happy ending.  What is the
happy going on forever?  Well, at least
years at least.  All right.  Then exactly
years from now everything will go
catastrophic.  So actually my real is
what can we what can you learn?
What can we learn?  What can we all right
the man to learn?  All
right.  Basically and fundamentally in a
general sense what you can allow
yourself to begin to teach that
individual is that first of all they have not
necessarily consciously.  We do
not wish to imply blame on anyone for
there is no blame but there is
responsibility. toeves toeves
powered
sy that as individual to they are as
powerful as they need to be to have to as to and that
and that
any that anyone
has from any tool including what you
call a drug which is isable you
believe that ites you in ae
where you have ag to by what you callys
are taking you
create to that
you are creating the experience
then you can recogn that perhaps the
drug as a tool can be utilized to show
you what you are able of but now that you
know what you are able of since you are
doing it anyway you  no longer need the
tool in order to recreate it you can recreate the
sensation on your own any
time you wish creativity for awareness
insight in this way you canare the
idea that there is nothing are
willical par hand chemicalsable
you haveb [music ] are powerful life
a tool and a tool as tool and not need
toely on the tool for the
source that
that
addic they do not believe that and and
can
you [music] guys I
[music] guys I
have a situation I started taking care
of a friend's dog about a week and
a half ago and  it's at their house.
We're sharing we're sitting at their
house and this dog is an Australian.
very frisy.  He's about six weeks old a
beautiful dog.  I've raised dogs before
and I thought, well, I could I could
work with her uh six months.  Six months
and uh the dog is kept outside.  I let
the dog may I interrupt you for one
more? Yes.  Feel free to jump in where you know
Yes.  Feel free to jump in where you know
you can be assistance.
[laughter] The dog the dog they keep the dog
The dog the dog they keep the dog
outside I the dog inside I play with the
dog I changed the dog's diet uh there
are two little children.  The dog is
overwhelming to the children.  I thought
maybe the dog is reflecting the
situation of the household.  The
household has changed.  Very likely the
household has now changed.  We give the
dog a lot of love.  I devise games when
it jumps up.  I go with it.  Just as
fast as I do it the dog says I'll go further
and just
more if I if outside because she choose
on the furniture she eats toys outside
the water cooler
cover like it's increasing.  It's
increasing.  And I even called on my dog
who passed away a year ago to talk to
her.  He did.  He came back.  He said she
wants to move on.  She wants to go to a
farm because she hurts all day and I I
guess I'm asking you what can I do
to you can speak to the family?  I well I
could but and I guess I'm sort of
looking forward because I was instructed
to the fact that the dog was sent to
obedient school and I didn't agree with
most of the stuff that was told because
supposed to hit it with a chain.  I'm not
going to do that.  I'm not going to by
any of the stuff I heard really.  So, uh
I was just trying to calm the dog so
when they came back things would be
different.  I really don't know what to do
anymore with this dog.
syven basically represents in your
society symbol of service and that
expansion the rate of expansion ener anying
anying
to the sitation exps to meev enery with limitations more sit
now with the arang
as well and quite
more since you are unqu outsider
but not really since you
are involved to some extent you are being
asked to be of service in a
certain way perhaps you might be let
say a reflection a tangential
reflection that they may benefit accent
knowing that if they believe
necessary to restrict theal in your to
beat theal into submission
perhaps it is only  indication
of their willingness to suppress in
similar fions their own desires their
own urges
They would never do that.  They did that
but there were just some things with the
yank on the chain.  It didn't go to
beatings or anything like that.  I I
really I guess I just want to do some
wonder in a couple of weeks in ease
things.  You can ease things by sharing the point of
view that you are and allow
them to do the easing for themselves if they
choose to.
So
share and see what they may or may not make
in what you have to tell them what
you have learned by youration with
the right have another week
so I all you canel quite
aort with
theal use your able as able as
to
the I try so fast try is very fast
there is no need to again try what do you
think you have to
your heart is everyg could poss up cann outrun
outrun
you the letting go of any need to change the
dog in any
specific things than because
you love each other right we
love each other and to get this so
that he would have his own power not the
responsibility FR you
you
and later on dream I got
the right it is to be a of nothing and
to beasy in everything you and that is I
feel about where I'm you mean where you
are where I [
music] Yeah.  Thank you for
Yeah.  Thank you for
your Thank you.  I would also like to
share and ask you to explore this with
me.  The other
night all night I was in Green State and
it was like I was working with a planet
holding with several quite a few others
being a planet in place.  And when I w up I
did and I
anything else you [laughter]
could this thank you for you are able to nurture and cradle
the planet even as it
nurtures and cradles you.  You support
it, it supports
you.  Thank you.
Next I have a physical situation I ask
you about wonder if there's some other
symbated to in the summer
to in the summer
time over the last couple years
occasionally I get these little blotches
on my arm and then they sort of turn
into little things little rashes this
year I got some on my face first I had one
now I have five now I have Have you
you
referred to what you call your medical
practitioners?  Yeah.  What did they tell
you? Theyve correctly diagnosed it and if I
Theyve correctly diagnosed it and if I
wait a couple weeks it may clear up kind
why there and I think medical
practitioners always see holistic view
even inysical terms if you could give
any ins
that do they
believe or have they shared with you the
notion that it may be connected to what
you would the
idea
of ​​fungal substance Yeah. What is the carbohydrate and
carbohydrate and
vegetable?  Are you at this time
parpa in contain what
you callult?
Not much that I'm aware of.
of.
Cheese bread a little cheese bread not
bread not
much.  What about sugar?
for in this way at this time we would suggest
that for a little while you maintain
the idea more strictly of
vegetable intake and or what you would
call fruit juices that are all
transparent in that way although you can
also include the idea of ​​juice of transparent transparent
in
your perhs a week may more from
that contain the idea of ​​the
cultures in any way shape or form in
that sense of
fermentation allow yourself
also a lot of
pure cool lot
of energiz it with your imagination your
blue white electromagnetic field drink
it and
refesh.  You may find that in your
culture there are certain ideas of what
you call topical applications that may
or may not be assistance to you with
regard to the potency of
removing the fungal rash but in this way
it is something that can work itself
through your system and alleviate itself
if you simply for a while allow to be
aarification of the system
in terms of your
Good view I was interest hearing that
you we don't typically hear from our
medical doctors.  I would also like to
ask you about my mother similar to what
we were talking about helping with this
other gentlem I
realized that I can perhaps maybe
a vehicle to her transformation
you are being one other you would not be in contact
with her and not with you it
seems to be kind
of cris point cris in
in the view of the family and in her
eyes getting worse getting worse worse
you can begin to explore again once what does
each member of the get out of the
situation the way is all your toore
other communication
and you canare
inacusory  theollowing
ence they do not believe
you comm to as sole
in recogn that some the expressions may
only be a reflection of the fear
that aord and agreement might lead
I don't understand
that the idea
of
being energy
the idea of ​​not being interactive
in other words you may all
be sucumbing to the belief that the only
way you can feel you can be interactive is
to be abrac
you
individuals will also find because of
the way you have created your
you ask questions about well
why is there so much dotomy between
myself and mine  parents but recognize you
chose them  they chose you and in many situations
the idea because of the way
your society is created
itself in the fion that you
find it to be
being would give you something toush against
to ensure that you would become
the ideology you desire to be by opposing the ideology
they are now it
does not have to continue to work that
way in your society but that is usually
the way it has worked simply because you have
been exploring separation judg
invalidation and limitation of each other
each other
and growth not have
come from sharing and unity unity
can be the product of the granting of
validity and  equality to the infin
diversity any Thank you Thank you
[laughter]
you.  All we can say because we do not
quote unquote neither recommend nor condemn
nor evaluate the worth of
anyone but simply we will put it this
way if you as an
individual find that there are things
that another individual has to say has to
share that strike accord within
you then recognize that those particular
ideas to you find and use this is not to
to you find and use this is not to
might be other things that
individuales that do not fit into
yourity they do not have to and again what we
will say is simply that
you are always only driven to that
which you believe is necessary for your
own understanding and  reflection of and
another to
be for certains of your own identity to
allow you to make discoveries within
yourself and you can change your mind
now in changing your mind about whether
an individual may have things to say
that are relevant for you or not that does not
have anything to do with having to
discount that individual you are the
one that is changing so if you find your
and listening to different individuals
at different times it is only because
you yourself are changing and finding
that different ideas are now more valid
for you more true for you than other
ideas that used to be this is the
process of your  own grow your own
reflections and it  does not invalidate
anyone else for all have been where they
needed to be to interact with you
exactly when you needed to act with them
in whatever way you needed that
interaction.  Allow us toind you of one
thing you are your
you are your
own
master.  Do you
follow this sister?  Yes.  Thank you.
Thank you very
much.  I wonder if you could explore some
dreams been having lately with crystals.
I'll tell you some of the ideas that
I've had so far.  Oh, that's
right.  I was with some friends very
close friends of mine and I found the
box full of the rocks and I wanted to keep
them all.  I thought how sish when
we can all have them.  And then the next
dream was last night and I was shoeing
somewhere and the first thing I saw some
shoes that I really like.  They were
silver shoes and they had three
turquoise stones on the top and then the
soul was in with turquoise and green
some other kinds of stones and I love
them.  I don't understand the shoes part
but I really love the shoes.  So I walked
out the store and I thought I'll come
back and look at them later.  And
somebody said something about cstals and
I didn't look where the cstal was.  I
kept on going and I saw a lady break the
cstal up into lots of pieces and it was
a smoky amethy cstal.  And I thought,
well, I'll let everyone else take some
and I'll come back later and if there's a
piece that I like, I'll take it.  And I
was wondering if the two dreams I have a
smoke amstal maybe I didn't take that one
because I already have one.  So, let
everyone else have one.  But when I have
the pink cstal, I didn't want to give it
up.  All right, thank you.  It also brings
energy to cool weeks
agots of a lot of fun. [music] I thought
anyone is not fun
but after I like there is
much that happens with silence I
know a lot Yes
, of course.  I wanted it to pick up
again.  It is.  It has never st only your
assumption that it has allows you to
feel as if it has.  I had more fun in
dreams than I did during the day.  But
recogniz that it is your opportunity to allow
yourself to recognize that the same
degree of ecstasy exists in your
physiological reality.  And the idea as
we perceive it of the cstal and dreams
is exemplification of that which you
will discover to be true about your
physicality.  The idea of ​​the pink stone
with the stone can be viewed as a type
of prenatal condition. bir stone
bir stone
about you in
about your idea of ​​the shoes with the turtist
your idea of ​​the shoes with the turtist
reflecting the idea of ​​the blue
green eneries of your planet earth as
you will walk and be of service as you
learn to follow in your as
you walk as you are as you
will then create that for yourself
and the shoes are simply symbolic of maturity to
take your way
of the heavens and of the earth the
silver and the turquise in that is maturation maturity
with you all need and
isinkstal matured into the am idea the violet
matured into the am idea the violet
light  of your knowing when you recognize
that whereas previously the feeling that
came with it was i must gather them all
up or i will have now that you have
matured into the am you There is more
than enough to if there any left well
I'll get to it.  I already my ownstal
any it is three
stages of maturation and with
that idea of ​​maturation will come the
understanding that when you are
infinitely accelerated it is the same
thing as being everywh at once and being everywh
at once is the same feeling
Stillness can you
are bad when broke
upstal habit ritual with
you it
thinking you are losing
ancient beginnings of the separations
which occurred on your planet to allow you
to experience the degree of
diversity that you experience.  It was let
us say a melanchy point of view
about the idea of ​​that which you already
know was
once becoming fragmented but it is still
one thing.
And you can recogn it as one thing and
in the
silence you can hear
one thing still [music
still [music
] growstal
um I detected a
more it is a combined blending of many
different changes that are taking place
with energies much change occurred with the
energies much change occurred with the
idea you call the haan
vortex that is still
present I have a
question speak I find in
myself that there is [music ] ]
I had
a newish
homeet and now I
feel very much like aish it is
your to choose the direction that you
can look at the situation from  you can
come on back and feel confined or you
can come back and still be the idea of
where you were and allow the idea of
where you were to begin to be the idea where
you are and expand idea out
instead of feeling that environment you
are now in hems you in that
way to the experience all
right in the Hawaiian experience
that I would that I prefer to have more
grounded sense of
myself personally and as I experience myself more more
here willve
my all right you to some back there is
not much that need to be said perception
at this time except that the  idea of
being grounded I was
thinking  that
Everything excites that excite you?  Yes.  Do
it.  Thank
you.  Perhaps also of benefit as a moving
meditation is to simply walk through
your city and observe and share and
radiate walk and give and receive all
Yes.  When you were talking to this about
the ameth
something you said made me rec a
ring that I had that was made by someone I
love very much and given to me for
Christmas years ago and it was stolen
from me about years ago of all the things
was taken that was the one that I had the
most difficulty letting go of
because of
the emoalic
thought it many times and when you Ied
that I was able to have that taken
because I really need it anymore reached
a certain amount of maturity and the
although the now to me eternal
yes eternal fabulous because
eternal fabulous because
the  marvelous
aborts well keeps
expanding and shared about that before
but to
now about and that
about and that
is
never you are Thank
you.  I speak up I have a question
concerning one of my housemates.  Yes.
goes through very strong m swings
attributes to
PMS and I have a question in terms
of I suppose how
to for myself how to deal with her
incred mamings and also there is
something that could do I don't know in
terms of meditation or something to do
you think that would trust her
imagination to give her what needs [music]
doing what she in
lifeh any frra that has may from thates
thates
you will to herenate her i inationer breaking inationer breaking
all
and perhaps
when you do not impose so many
limitations then the walls and the
objects  in
yourity will not be
withingance need to
without everything fragile
you are simply recognizing the
interconnect of everything but you are
still recognizing it with some deree of
fear negativity you think that because
everything is close at hand and
inconnect that that means that one and
and
then broken energy another in that but
you recogn that the interconnectedness
of everything is what allows it to be strong
then you can expand it to
infinite willen will never th will never break it will never uncohesive
never uncohesive
you do not need to have
everything so to speak right in  front of
your analytical  examination in to you have handle
because then there is so much focus so
much pressure that you are you have have
others
thating netivity
some it can be if you are
willing to all thele as however you need not
in the idea can be liked unto what
some individuals will do what you call what you call polterist phenomen
where there are the flying
around ofs and the breaking
ofs 99.9% ener
all the breaking
things one
more enerying
that go into the down breaking sy
in this can
you can breakingunder of the  sys toan
you do not need so many symbs so you do not have to
look for so many symbs in analytical
sense in order to understand
each other you can have direct knowing direct feeling
of each other you don't not have to
act through many symbs which
are only your illusionary projections
and may not be strong enough to contain the energy that you are they will
If you sy aroundowing you understand
you are for
the understanding must always come back to
you the sys around you breaking an
inherent belief you have within yourself
that to take all that power  with
yourself would droy
you but you do not have to fear that you
are infinite you are
indestructible and will not feel like
pressure if you are willing to accept
the reflections with each other as
positive messages positive sharing positive interaction
and be willing to be willing to
state who you are without having to accuse
the other individual be
willing to state who you are strengthen
yourself stand up for yourself share with
them your viewpoints as to how they are
able to their own self their own
strength allow them to know that they
can do what excites them and you can do what excites
you and then together you
will reflect and parallel each other's
strength in your excitement in your excitement in your sharing you Thank
you very much.  You may all take a
break.
that our physical environment around us
was a
projection where the light of our
consciousness through the ideas and
agreement patterns that we had projected
into existir in the same way that our
existir in the same way that our
projectors project through film tonight
you touched on the
concept of energies that were
transmitted through our physical b alter
the physical environment
Is our consci and our body
theing view in these energies are
translated through the body and inse now
do remember and recognize that we
areingal terms in your language the idea
of ​​course is that you actually are the event
you are experiencing and even the
idea of  projecting the energy out is in of s illusion
concept that another question completely
different a friend of
m has fallen in love has a great desire
and excitement and love for a woman who
is married and has two children and he's
married to another wife and they have
two children and he wishes to bring this
about he concerned with the fact that other
people our su would the andy of commic
all concern sharing
theings attractions andowing all recogn
that if they are connected to each other
then the connection of one of those
individuals to another individual in
another group  that is connected to
itself is a reflection of  the idea that
perhaps all of those individuals are
more closely connected than they
think if it is an opportunity for
everyone to be as you say out in the
open with their feelings and share and
know and trust that they can get
reflections from each other without
feeling threatened without feeling cheated
threatened without feeling cheated
uponed in that way then perhaps they can
all learn much about their individual
abilities for the expression of
unconditional love to each other and can
explore the idea of ​​the boundaries that
your society has set and perhaps allow
them in whatever way will maintain how weak how weak
[applause]
initial  inclination may not be what
follows through it may simply be for the
purpose of allowing certain forms of communication to open up and
once those communications have been opened up the original intentions may no longer be necessary
and struggling with
smoking and what you said earlier about
the  drugs to somebody else and also
about dreams seems to
someh how to apply I drank last night
that I kept putting out my cigarette and
then I'd look in the asd be another
little cigarette waiting for A How can
I in this way first of all you sy
that it mayle a way that you definitely the
in life to unfold as
well do you feel that you are victimized by circumstance
all is there any reason you
All Very good.  Then you can begin by not
invalidating your
invalidations.  So if you find that you
are creating something you deem to be
negative, do not judge it any further
than you already have to create
it.  Go easy on yourself.  First of all,
do not chastize yourself for the
creation to begin with of what youce to be a
negative chain or sequence of
events then you will at least remove the
first layer of pressure upon yourself.
Now as you have experiences in your
dream reality you can first of all
recognize that it is just as real as any reality you will
ever experience.
And in this way you can allow yourself
to know that you areowing yourself
something in plain terms, symbolic terms symbolic terms
that will allow you to
simply recognize the idea as it fits into
your life.  The idea of ​​what you feel to be
repetitiveness lack of ability to have control
over a situation that seems seems to be
repeating.
no matter what it appears to be is
always a new thing if only that you recogn
it is not exactly the same thing
happening exactly the way it did the
first time because you are making
comparison that it is happening
again so in this way you can first of
all treat every apparent reoccurrence as
something new.  Do not assume it is the
same old
thing.  Assume it is a different new
thing.  It may come in the same
guys.  But that is simply because you are
using symbs you are familiar with the
carhs.  You do not have to attribute to
the apparent reappearance of the
cigarette.  The same meaning you usually
attribute to it.  Give it a new meaning.
Every time it seems to resurvey it a new
meaning, not the same meaning.  It is
only by bequeing the same meaning on an
apparently similar symbol that you create
the effect that the symbol seems to
carry only the same meaning over and
over again.  All symbs are blank,
neutral.  No symbol and no situation
comes with built meaning.  You supply the
meaning.  The meaning you supply is the
effect you get. Whatever
Whatever
symbogy isle to you in the idea of ​​the
cigarette start to give it new meaning.
As soon as you start to give the
cigarette new meaning you will then
allow the cigarette to transform from
the symbol that it is into another type
of symbol that will then be reflective
of the new meaning you have instilled
within it.  Stilling new meaning in an
old symbol is what changes the old
symbol into a new one.  Because the
meaning of a symbol is the soul of the
symbol.  The symbol, the outward symbol
is only an illusion, a cloak, a
guys.  When you change its meaning then
the symbol will transform to accommodate
the new meaning.  You follow me.  So first
and foremost you can remove the idea
that you are only doing something
repetitively.  you are not everything is
sometimes you may use what appears to
be the same symb toent that you are momentuming momentum
let reappearance of apparently same symb
is actually a new opportunity to look at
a similar idea from a different point of
view giving it the new meanings at
Now you can also understand you have to
force yourself to become more
spiritual you can recognize that you not
need to demand that you change in that
way and that when you making a demand upon
yourself that you change from what
you perceive to be old
habits then that will be one less  habit
right there is ceasing to demand
Let me finish.
The idea of ​​what you desire can come
most easily when you do
notand as a prerequis for the change with
you.  When you simply know you are
different when you allow yourself to
assume and take it for granted that you are different
then you will change.  And it
is not that you have to force
yourself to stop smoking.  By being a
different being you will simply not have the ge
it will not be in the definition of the being
you will now be.  Now may I ask
you a
question?  Are you sure I may ask you a
question?  Thank you very
much.  Using your imagination right now
can you in any way form ever imagine
yourself not smoking?
Yes, you
can.  Are you sure you
can?  Yeah.  All right.  Very
good. Then in your willingness to have the
Then in your willingness to have the
vision of yourself as someone who simply does not
smoke.  Now wait before we go on
let me clarify your definition.  Are you
actually saying you can imagine
yourself as someone who simply does not
smoke or are you envisioning yourself as
someone who has to fight the smoke? ener all
ener all
right and someone who does not the ge to smoke canion it smutting
my enery all right all right we
understand but for now never mind
that all then let meind you of something
all then let meind you of something
right now as we have said bring
me and here drainage
all you maketin that is
not when you to know that what you imagine what you
envision you can be
just as real as anything you are in your
physical reality then when you have the
vision of yourself a nonoker you will
not to some necessary process order you to become
to some necessary process order you to become
the  nonsoker you recogn that if
you can envision it you must at that
moment actually be that person because
you can only conceive of what you
contain you can only imagine what the vibratory
in that however long you are willing to thatity that initiation
you are that a nonoker
but you make the assumption that
the imagination is not as real as the physical reality
and so you think there
must be something you need to do in
order to
real your imagination
[music] toble asoker
means that that is the process
and not of a process then all you need  to do
not of a process then all you need  to do
is trust that  your ability to imagine
yourself as a nonsoker is the same thing
as beinger and all you have act
likening to be is real right now then
your body will automatically act like
non body and won't have the
you will what
all now do
it now.  If you are saying I'll wait
till I have ge
you are implying that there will be a
time when you will no longer be a nonsoker
and then you have to fight it if
you are a nonsoker you will never have
the earth peri
now if you find that you do have
the earth do not prti yourself and do not struggle reimagine
yourself as the
nonsoker you may want because of the
society you are in to give yourself an
opportunity to yourself that you are in
control and you have the power does not have to
be  a struggle if you find
yourself creating the urge first of all
do recogniz that if you do find yourself
creating the urge then the one the you
that creates thege is not the you you
are when you
Nonoker nonokeres
nonokeres
by yourself creating uroker
.  All you need to do is become the
nonsoker once again and there won't be an urge
.  It is not a matter of having to
fight the earth.  It is becoming the
individual once again who doesn't have
the all.  You are either the smoker or
you are not.  It is not matter of
fighting to become you either are you are not
or you are to those are
one to the other you
than you One moment all you
all you
are with some of you
now understand you enjoy that do not
and as longer need to you will lose the ge that is
all there can
be it can be that you do not It can be
in but this is not a given.  It
may be very specific with the
individuals that are being born and the
relationship that they actually have
with the individual that is bearing
them.  Trust your own instincts in this
matter always your imagination always provides
you with the proper
understanding of
yourself that is
what it cannot provide you with
understanding on the same level of
someone else because it is you it is your imagination
if it could give you
more understanding of someone else it
would be someone else imagination and
not I
Indian culture looking.
two people get together
and physiologically another body to be
physiologically another body to be
[laughter] [music
]
cre if we will a unit unit yes and no do not
for that we are always connect no
matter where we are well but you said
that a child will take AC biological
par of may physiologically present to
ass and aid thatult is
parent of the child the
children of all and in this way we once
again will always tr the timing of the
interactions that occur when and with that
with that
because we are
never understand what I'm last focusing my
understand what I'm last focusing my
attention on over those few days
and  what I was hoping to get
some I don't know feedb on is this whole
area of ​​relationship somebody else
brought up a
at least agreement they
need
selfs there isly also differ our understand your
as to the you will
always be you need to be
You still however are always being where
you need to be when you need to be
there.   person
says I love you to another un to
them there is outfow there is outfow
but inside the
outflow is a kind of a sucking back into
them and what they really say when they
say I love you what they really saying is I
need you to love me very often that
is the case on And
And
that winds up making things
and the connection is more often
well maybe parallel the connection when
somebody says I love you to somebody
else in strawber man the husband and the
wife two different
families in my perception often not being
the high self channeling through
the physical but one  of the lesser lives that that
is
because you
haveation that my to be connected to the
lesser life other person and then the
relationship between the two
physiological cells dissolves and then
you go on a little bit longer and a
different lesser life falls in love with
a different person's lesser life and
kind of goes on
like in the process I mean it is process
by which one can it's one of the many
processes we can use on this planet to achieve
greater integration
I don't know
where we in
this generally speaking the phenomen you
are describing basically comes
describing basically comes
from lack of belief that as it is serves
rather than what you think it should be noting you
specifically and also that
the idea of ​​needing someone else to love
them is lack of willingness of having self
to with
right regardless of whatever symbology
of what you call lesser lives or not are
involved that may be the fundamental
for the idea as it on the
world how what
is in what place does se play in your
civilization what is Ribed is a
part of the relationship as
the relationship define timing of interaction
physiologically but we simply allow the
relationship to be what it is and therefore foundation recognizez
imately when  there is
and is not timing for  the idea of ​​okay
but in this broad trans
trans
back well don'tity take ah describe
differenou more enery
identified that that
particular becomes important to their
ownership to be centered and feel selfed that's what
I mean when I said
for those people
exemely part of their lives whereas I
gather not equal Thank you [music]
[music]
you.  Yes.
[laughter] Last Last
been
tremendously dreams killing bombs
shooting stabbings. Excitingly interesting. em
em
good in becing [laughter] unreasonably
you can to recogn that as you form
more and more let us up in up in
those
more compassionate
compassionate
with that you have become
emally involved through attachments of judg thanks you yes
I'm curious as to mying in thising yesell there
there
another all right what excites you
theing with several different art form
all you find exciting iind exciter that the
you to be.
So if you follow what excit you will be in synchronous harmony
with youring no matter what form it takes if excit
to you know you are in with the
path you chose to be thank
you so what does it you now my
painting and my acting I
I
just I I would hope that
hope implies despair.  Well, do you know
or do you
not? I don't know.  Trust trust trust trust.
I don't know.  Trust trust trust trust.
I
know that perhaps in some way I can
serve.  I know
that [music]
[music]
another I know
may su I know I know I
can I know I you how do youve yes
youve yes
validation for many other people who see
you that is someone conviction willing
to the joy and asy they with themselves
so you can act as active reflection for
them and allow them to
become
inspired inspiration breathing
with thank you for for
since last week
um I've been experiencing it
's hard to exp all
right you are doing just
fine everything you have to is a
gift and so everyone else can
take they see themselves with you
andly do notar
to thank you thank
you last week when I experienced the
pain and I had the
sense that enties were trying to channel
through
me in this
I have been more
more
struggling with back and do I want this
in my life and do not want it is your
decision you are in full control
they know that
yes I coming more aware of
my of my contr over this over
over just confused because
good confusion fusion with
confusion fusion with
confusion fusion with more of your your
thinks confusion to be
are oneity previty and reorienting to a
broad spectrum of
newabil that is what you generally call
confusion but it can be positive you are
reorienting I know it may feel like a limbo stat i
know it may feel like you
are being floating but in this way that is
your natural state
.  So allow yourself to recogn that
all you are doing is now floating, relaxing
,
considering reorienting yourself that is
all your
confusion is.
I have some memory that is all
right and the very next moment the next
moment I say I don't want this in my
life I want to go back to normal so you
are exploring
polar both sides of the spectrum
negative positive positive
negative that is part of the process
again do not
forg yes yes but do not forg the only
that is causing the seeming lack of
peace of mind is that you are
invalidating the experience you are
believing that the experience is intrally netive that
is why you are creating the
scenario to as if is unsling that
created to  netive the
experience does not contain intrins
negativity once
again all sit yes all sit you underine that
as many as you to neutral neutral
bler zip
you supply the meaning now because
of the way
your t to
automatically instantly supply nean to
many neutral situations and so you sitation intring now
intring now
all you are out
ofits and you can see you are doing it
and to prer to catch yourself when you do
it and that is
and you are
not.  So all of this go into allowing you to
actually become the person that will be the you that will be the channel
.  This is all a part of your own
process.  You are learning what you need
to learn.
If you
toar what you need to learn you can
become excit about the process and not
an excited anxiety same enery one
positive one negative which do you
prefer if you become excited about
everything that occurs urs in the
process then the symbs in the process
willase to feel negative and start to
feel positive and the symbols that
actually occur will only be seen by you
to be positive symbols.  You will allow
them to transform that will allow you to
know that your transformation can be an ease of transformation struggle
.  Are you following me?  Yes, I follow
you.  What I think has been occurring is that
in my process to find out more about
this and find out more about people who have
done this and and their experiences I've been getting
this and and their experiences I've been getting
mixed feedback some being
positive and some being negative and so
whoever I'm speaking to you know if it's positive I
say okay I'm going to do this
and then if I speak to somebody and
their experience was negative I say no I don't want
that I but understand what
does allow you to
it allows you
to what portions of the feedb you choose to
believe are true for  you because the
only possible thing anyone can ever tell
you is what was true for
them and what was for them in no way
shape or
you have given yourself to communicate
with someone who may be that possible
and when if it comes up with you you
will have something toate to but no one no
one no one can ever ever ever tell
you what is true for [music]
So is up to you to well all right I
prefer that bit of feedb and this bit of
feedb and though I do not prefer this
bit of feedback I know I will integrate that
bit of feedback  because not
preferring this bit of feedback  allows
me a clearer perspective on the feedback I do
you so blending all that together allows
you to become polarized balan
you will your to flow
more as if you find any time to use analy
on
your in
so bec you desire to [music
] B you
need to do is remember that you
are the game
and then you will adopt that will
enjoy the mo
of rather than you
contr adopt a
different changes
literally on how
can thank
you point one
you are doing just fine [music]
tof you desire to be
thank you
you
point  tr your own instincts your
ownagination let youragination construct
the methodologies you think you require
it can do so that is what is design to do
.  So if you feel you need a process or a
method, relax into your meditative
state of imagination and invent
one.  What you will
recognize is perhaps two things.  One, you
can begin to trust your imagination and
two, in inventing the process you have
already channel something.
any access to your own higher
consciousness and always are channeling
that through to form the physical life
you are experiencing yourself to be so
channeling is not something you are not
used to doing you are just talking about doing
it in a different way so it needs
not be something that you have to get
used to from scratch As you follow me I do
you all any other consciousness with you
all any other consciousness with you
have made agreement will always trust
yourace you can ask for assistance it will be provided
but it will never do
anything for you it will always allow
you to get to the point where you know
you  are selfempowered enough to do it
and make the decision on your own behalf
for without allowing
No one and nothing can ever control you
if it appears that that is happening it
is you believing in the reality that you
can be controlled but then you are controlling
that situation There
is in our perception an energy
connection of six density
consciousness that may now may not
always necessarily have to follow this
particular configuration but may be
liken unto what you in general and
in general upon aselective consciousness
you call raw r a raw you following s the
the
idea at first will be to put you  in
touch with different levels of your
consciousness  since you have created
yourself to be a multievel consciousness
so the
ener time you are you will
you will
blend the idea of ​​channeling in
anyent is never actually lally
that
you are as consci you form your own comfort zone your understanding and
understanding and
method of moding the energy with which
you are in contact so that what you are
doing in channeling some other
consciousness you
is up ener altered awowsion other
you do points ass you very much thank
you very much we thank
you i have a coule of all i went to ha a little
ahad of
I did not
[music]
go understand your meaning we
to any I came back really high and
feeling very powerful and time I got
very sick and I having time throwing it
How do you feel
now?  Not quite myself
yet.  Which s are you?  Strong s
strong yes yes yes yes many times you
will find in your civilization because of the
way you think of yourself that when
you do all your to access another level
of your enery then if there are remnant
habit ways of thinking of yourself that ex
they create little ofary ande
again no need to
appear to pay attention an old symb
with old
meaning you follow me
now the old symbol of disase does not
have to mean you are doing something
Oh, [laughter]
[laughter]
good.  All right.  can you are
you process you think you need others who you estivation
on
And I would if you
see that I don't
know I feel very connected to
her that I just
perhaps let me put it this our
perception at this time is
that you may ass
later this parallel tangential
direcover at first whatever is about
your discover to become more later. as you
are again always trust your own
instincts in this understanding and follow what excites you
the most whether what excites you
the most appears to be
connected to what you think it might be connected
to or not has anything to do
with it the excitement is What lets you
know it is connected
.  It doesn't always look like
it's connected because you don't want to be to obvious
.  You don't want to bore
yourself. You trust and follow the excitement. Yes Yes
for our
sonukeloped a a
[music]
severe thr situation and he also developed
a severe lim along with it and
is any I know that he going through
transformation what information could
youare by the system to ease
Now comes a time of interactive
reflection in terms of the agreement you have made
as a family from when you have
all come now comes a time when there are
come now comes a time when there are
many portions of the self and the
consciousness that are being faced and
interacted with very early on in the
life so they will not be necessary to are
you are now
some traveling and field  trips together
to the desert area may be of concern as
you are planning to do you
these may bring up
recollections of what you would
scenari that will allow to be
integration and connection and
communication between the portions of the triad in
between the portions of the triad in
your immediate
family and allow certain things to be
alleviated. are things need to
are things need to
be are need to be trav [music ]
]
to may indicationsyological sym
indications of the inherited learned
reluctance to perhs deal with the things
that need to be said and go to the
places that need to be gone
will not forgotten how to that
few things
you than Thank you.
gre shiny smooth polished white
fled stones may be of
stones may be of
assance
to as a sy that can be focused upon
toent the are
sy that
cannent the enery so have passing
passing
together in lives where there was also
much syological
there were times
together in scenarios that
you would call in your judg terms
bitter and
foul and fr with
disease thated and struck down the
living it is simply now that the energy
of the collective
family is passing through a parallel
time frame relevant to some other time
frames you have lived in and  so certain
symbs are being reflected in this life
but not to any great extent but they are
there to be integrated to be faced to be
lived it will pass in the waters of sharing the
waters of sharing the
waters of
sharing you will what we me
when you come to that
The minerals in the waters of
sharing.  It may play a larger part in
your future than you are
aware we will also send enery gift. small white
small white
cube that may at times
transparent becomely blue and may at as black
and après BR Brahmašara شديد ت
mother of aram rabram
Thank you.  Have a good time. [laughter] will
will
be a few moments for this
you have [music ] back
] back
all and I would to I do
want to sin
you for your su
some have
comeent quite exposive you to me some
and one being lightened up.  Thank you. ocur little
ocur little
butterfly might also like to
also mention the Steve gave me a couple
days ago in achieving
things that I had questioned
back and forth that I have with the help of Steveing your
your
information it has occurred like
100% I think you know what thank
you since I knew come tonight first
of all been a great research no longer hesck
you and I think you understand why I
'm not but that is density right the
fourth density is there actually it
actually it
's but any on
all day to day because I get such incred
delight over  your answers have been trying to
think of a question all day and sitting here
trying to think of question that I
could get one
of you
knoww I can't think of questions so ask
you can you think of an
[laughter] [music] [music]
answer yes
I do you want to hear
it?  May I start with a question?
Do you need to hear it?  No, I don't
need to hear it.  I just know that
there's a lot of excitement and adorable and
everything has been going so
fantastic that roll as you
say that's just what I was going to what a
coincidence.
the words right out [laughter] [laughter]
of
perhaps still like I said sort of feel you got you got
answer question that
maybe I haven’t quite conceived yet
usually one step or
few really well it appears to be a little bit late some late
some late
never always perfectly timed always
everything that occurs always occurs in perfect
timing by
definition a thing cann occur outside of
timing how that [music] [music]
[laughter]
Thank you for
your understanding of the awareness.
Thank you.
Yes.  You know talking earlier about
following your
excit on this planet when like there's a
sexual attra to somebody there is well
at least in my universe.  Oh, thank you
very much.
this
excited a lot didn't you?  Yes, I learned that is
why the excitement is there
understand that every relationship is
there for a reason and that
unconditional love is what is used to create
the relationship
to regardless of what it is you are
going to experience in the relationship
you do create the excitement that is
necessary to attract you into it in the
first place so that you will have the
experience you need to if there is
a situation there is that does not
mean that the theoryship has to be experienced
negatively right hope not there is no
hing about you can still learn from the
about you can still learn from the
negative
experience so there is no  reason to fear
it m
Everything you have ever done has
gotten you to where you are now.  So it
has all served a purpose in a positive
way.  All you need to do is know that if
you are willing to allow a relationship to be what it is
and not what you expect it should
be, then it will be
just
always and no relationship was ever
invalid. Correct.  One last thing.
Correct.  One last thing.
So if like I understand what you're
saying about if you view if you view it negative
then it can
be negative because you ne but it's not
necessarily automatically negative
neutral zero even though the apparent no you are
you are
missing when you even though it
apparently that's still a product of
your judg that's what I'm saying
everything is a neutral situation right
and even though I'mbing in that it could
be that it looks netive yes right okay
so what you're saying to me is okay
you'rebing in the negative
it's not it's
sit integrity and you can
recognivity when you see it in terms of
the format but that does not mean that
the overall experience has to have a
negative effect in terms of how you connect into it m
effect in terms of how you connect into it m
the following I missed the very
first part of that if you wouldn't mind giving it to
You may be able to be a situation are
experiencing individuals of integrity
and that can be translated in your
language as a negative scenario but in
this way you can recogn that yoursation
someone else of integrity doesn't have to
wind up having  a netive
outcome right when you ack of integrity
do you mean something that they still inger inger
integration is
still not being
powerful as to have without havingur anyone
else to get [music] [laughter
[music] [laughter
] Thank
you for your gift all we
all we
Let you in on a
little I am now about to undergo what
you would call an alteration or shift in
consciousness or perspective in my imagination
I will now be communicative in
much the same manner in their own terms
as I have been communicative with you with
another civilization you may refer to
in there is the timing of the
journey in the shif  with that individual
and cstalation
has for the tri of
your in that cognition and recognition
there is a reflection sent and a
reflection given and the gift has been
received and will now begin to activate the irural
if you in your langageity transal Perhaps
Perhaps
some when you space you will meet them
and they will meet
you at this time therefore all us to
you once again our unconditional love
and appreciation us us
more by you
by you
are the
dream as and
as and
will trans
dream and life
dreams we a f and unconditionally loving [music] [music]
[applause]
good than you all for being inv