I now say how are you all this evening
of your time as you create time to
exist in this way allow us to proceed
and continue with the idea of the
interaction we have been sharing with
you of late that being the idea of
putting into your physicalized awareness
the ideas you are willing to be in life
and allowing yourself to live them
actively in that way
knowingly allowing yourself the freedom
to understand that that which occurs
your own imagination that which occurs
within your own feeling that which
occurs within your own mentality is a
reflection of the ideas you chose to be
in that way by being physical this
lifetime and in that sense give
yourselves Grant yourselves the freedom
the same freedom to be the idea you
perceive yourselves to be as creation
has granted you in the idea of your
existence to begin with now we have
discussed and described the idea of this
specific time frame as your mass
Consciousness has chosen to create it of
being one of activity and active you
have been in this way allow us to say
understand that as the actions that are
occurring in your Society in your
civilization upon your planet are
becoming in your terms more blatant
rising to the surface in this way and
not in this way existing so much
underground any longer it is giving you
all an opportunity to understand the
different scenarios you have all been
allowing to exist and creating to exist
for so many years in your Society in
this way granting you an opportunity to
see whether or not the ideas that are
now occurring more blatantly as you
would call it in that way upon the
surface in your civilization are ideas
that you feel Express the reality you
would like to experience in your world
in this way giving yourselves an
opportunity to act upon the scenarios
you see not out of malice not out of
accus ation not out of judgment but out
of willingness and unconditional love to
respond to the scenarios you are
witnessing going on in your world in
this day and age and in that way
allowing you the opportunity to reflect
to the individuals who are involved in
some of the scenarios you may feel to be
negative in your terms the opportunity
to know that you exist and in your
existence you prefer a positive scenario
you prefer the idea of peace in your
world of Harmony in that way and that
you are not cut off not separated from
those incidents that you yourselves are
your governments are your sociological
institutions are your Economic
Institutions are your religious
institutions as well as your political
institutions you are equal to these
ideas and the idea of many interactions
which have been in your terms covert now
coming to the surface has giving you an
opportunity to recognize that you are
now willing to look at all of these
things and less willing to as you would
say push them under the rug turn your
back not take responsibility for the the
ideas you are co-creating in your
reality but now that you know they are
coming to the surface let that be a
symbol to each and every one of you that
you are now strong enough to look at
these ideas you do not have to run in
fear feel that your world is falling
apart because you are witnessing what
you I'll say refer to as negative
scenarios in your life and time it is an
opportunity for you to know that if you
can witness these ideas it is an
indication that you are strong enough in
this way to choose use that which is
more of a representation of the reality
you do desire to exist within
individually and collectively are you
following along yes in this way as you
give yourselves your own barometer if
you will to use that terminology your
own Arrow your own sign post pointing
the way more and more of what has been
bubbling in your subconscious in your
unconscious is going to be coming to the
surface but understand them never never
at a rate greater than you can
understand than you can do something
with otherwise there would be no point
recognize life and creation is not
pointless in that way you will never be
allowing yourself to perceive something
that is not there for a reason you can
make sense of you can understand if you
could not understand it it would have no
reason being there in that way and it
would serve nothing in terms of your
purpose of growth and spiritual
awakening are you following me yes in
this way the therefore allow yourselves
not to run from fear but to joyously
accept the opportunity to now witness
all of the ideas that have been
perpetuated through judgment through
fear through negativity as they rise to
the surface not feeling like they are
going to overwhelm you but greet them
with joy because now that you are
meeting them on the surface it is an
indication to each and every one of you
that you are ready and willing to look
at them in the hard light of your
self-illuminated creative reality and to choose whether
creative reality and to choose whether
or not these ideas that have been held
underground for so long are ideas you
wish to continue to experience in your
world or not you follow
me we will thank you for your
willingness to be so bold in your life
to allow yourselves the opportunity to
recognize that change in positive ways
has been your desire and is now becoming
manifest in your world within each and
every one of you that allows yourself to
continue to know that that the idea of
peace and Harmony is the reality you
feel most deeply most strongly with the
most excitement and ecstasy then you
yourself are calling forth all of these
negative scenarios all of the
forgetfulness all of the suppressed
ideas so that you can operate and
function within Clarity Clairvoyance
within your own life and the freedom to
know that the choice is yours to make
you have complete and total
self-empowerment to choose the lives you
wish to lead you are now in our
perspective from our point of view in
what you are now creating allowing
yourselves to be willing to take the
responsibility upon yourselves not the
responsibility in the notion of blame
but responsibility in the notion of that
you are the creators of your
reality we extend our
appreciation to you for your willingness
to be exactly who you have chosen to be
and we continue this night of your time
within the idea of the sharing
sharing
sharing yes do you have all right how did
how did
Rob how did Rob School gos get ripped
off do you mean how or why how how in
this way do you find that you have
discussed this idea with your brother
and that he has some Notions yeah what
did he
say understand he is intimately
connected to any scenario he is going to
create in his life in that way does he
have a his own feelings on how and why
he thinks he co-created that incident
what are his attitudes toward the idea
of his education of the limiting the
bracketing the jacketing that he may
feel his education may be putting him
within does Rob care to answer
answer
no do you really feel it is any big
mystery in this way that you would
choose to remove the symbols of
something you feel to be such a rigid
structure in your
life in this
way understand that you are simply part
and parcel one more idea in that way of
a co-creation of allowing yourself to
explore all the different symbols though
it does not have to happen in that way
that your our educational system is
going through the changes that are
taking place within the educational
system will create many simp within the
system that will seem to be a breakdown
so to speak if you wish to put that in
quotes a breakdown of authority in that
way of rules in that way the ability for
individuals to come and go and to so to
speak let us say
penetrate the barriers of others to
violate others in that way but recognize
the idea simply is is that within your
educational system has also been created
individuals who have chosen to allow
themselves not to know their own power
and are in their own terms weak enough
to be attracted to someone who wishes
them to remove those symbols for them so
that they will not feel they have to do
it themselves will have an excuse to say
that they do not have to fit into the
structure rather than simply allowing
themselves to know that in that way they
are creating their own understanding of
that structure and not have to have
someone else do their dirty
work now I am not
chastising but we are picking the
symbols and the words that will make the
most sense at this time you follow me
yeah can you in that way on your own
time in your own words and with the love
that we perceive to be within your heart
share these ideas with your brother and
explain the notion yeah thank you will
that be all right d thank d thank
you
Shing I got a question uh I don't know
much about your planet but you said that
you don't use money as I understand we
don't know how the need for the tool
when every individual is being of
service to every other individual and
finds themselves to be in exactly the
right place and the right time to be of
service and find themselves being served
by the individual that they are serving
there is no need for an artificial
symbol of the exchange The Exchange is
immediate all right well I was looking
at our situation and we use money and
I've just kind of had a different
perspective of it lately and that is
that all right it's a very useful tool
for for me to show what I do want to
support of course in your Society since
you have creative tool you might as well
use it in that way understand it will
change in time as your understanding of
yourselves changes as you pull back all
the symbology within yourself then the
tools one by one will
vanish okay well what I'm curious about
is for example if I was going to buy a
new car I realized that that I am
choosing to to support that group of
Engineers and designers and salespeople
and service people that have turned out
a top quality job so I picked one out of
a 100 that I want to support with oh
right that is not to say that your tool
of money is necessary for you to acquire
a car in that way but it is one way no
but I mean it's also a nice way to show
support to a particular team of course
and I'm curious about how how you can
show support to a team like that for
example in this in my case halfway
across the world because they're in
Japan and they're designing and they're
doing their thing and so I want to
support them because I really think
they're doing a great job well go and
tell them well that I am by buying their
product well all right you can also go
and tell them right understand they will
appreciate that type of support as well
and that is more reflective of what we
do in our civilization we interact
directly with the individuals that are
responsible for any particular creation
that we happen to find being of service
to us and support
them allowing them to share the services
that each individual finding Merit in
their service wishes to share
back you follow me we go and perform
service for their service oh I see okay
that that makes a little more sense all
right it is an action rather than a
symbolic idea in The Exchange in that
way we simply find ourselves creating
the time to interact with those
individuals directly but doesn't money
allow allow the possibility to support a
lot more people in a lot of different
ways rather than going to all those
different people to support them not
necessarily okay it is dependent upon
the synchronicity involved and the type
of schedule so to speak that that
creates in your life understand that you
would probably have the time if you did
not have to work so hard for your money
that all works
out you follow me okay one thing
replaces the other in that way since you
have created the idea that many of you
must work to get the money in that way
then that is what takes up the time in
our situation The Exchange is simply
more immediate but isn't it you know I I
realize that but it allows me the
opportunity to do what I enjoy doing in
one particular then that is why you are
here okay in this type of a society that
has that type of symbol and you are
using it in that way there is nothing
wrong with it so when you go someplace
else you can vary the type of service
that you provide is that of course okay
understand that when each every
individual is acting in the now each and
every individual will find themselves
able to provide many different
Services thank you recognize in this way
we are not saying that your system your
monetary symbolic system and many other
systems in your Society are something
that is negative
intrinsically we are not saying that you
cannot and do not derive benefit from
them simply recognize that they are all
basically neutral symbols and you decide
what to make of them so for you you have
decided you will utilize it in a
positive way and so it gives you
pleasure and you find yourself creating
pleasure with the interaction with those
individuals who have provided service
for you by supporting them through that
symbol like it
Shing OT do um during my class um the
last class when I went into meditation
and um Thomas led us to this Lake and um
I had an interaction with
you um when I came out of it so to speak
I didn't actually feel like I really had
an interaction with you correct and it
was only when Dale brought it
up that he too had the same kind of
experience somewhat acknowledge it that
I thought oh maybe it was Bashar oh and
maybe it was real so I thought well I go
into meditation again and I go back to
the lake and again I had an interaction with
lake and again I had an interaction with
you but I don't feel all the reality of
it understand the idea as we have always
described it to you is that our energy
our signature vibration is always being
sent to you now if you find that you
wish to form an identification an
association with what you are doing with us then
with what you are doing with us then
many times you will find that an
individual in your Society will form a
simol acum a model to represent our
energy to themselves so that they
understand they are dealing with that
portion of themselves mhm so when I have
telepathic communication with you at the
lake is that just me imagining your
responses that's what I'm asking in a
sense yes but that does not make it any
less real of an interaction again your
imagination is a dimension of reality
simply on a different level and in this
way you are interacting with us you are
interacting with another portion of
yourself understand again simply that
your Society has the prediliction that
it has to be this or that whereas the
idea is that it is this and that and
both are real and both are true and the
truth is composed of all truths MH the
interaction is as real as is valid for
you on whatever level it is valid for
you because that is how it serves you to
get you where you are going there is no
need to pick it apart and say well was
it real in this way was it real in that
way there is no need for the labeling in
that sense our energy is being offered
for you in that way to make use of in
whatever way you so desire your energy
is always available to you you do not
need our energy but you from time to
time each and every one of you will pick
the symbols to represent the
conversations you are having with
yourself as you need them to let know
that you are having the conversations
with yourself on that level
Now understand again it is always coming
back to you even the idea of what you
call Spirit guides are always luring you
to yourself and interaction with
yourself they do their job the best when
they remain more or less unobtrusive in
that way so that they are not living
your life for you allowing you to feel
that you have to have them or have to
have me or us or someone else to get
your answers but that you allow us
through your willingness to form and
utilize us as a symbol you allow us to
gently remind you that you are in a
communication with the same level of
yourself that you perceive us to be on
you follow me mhm therefore it allows
you to understand you do not have to
continue to make a differentiation
between where you are and where you
perceive we might be mhm for in this way
we are no better than you we are simply
different and it is our pleasure to
allow you to utilize us as a symbol in
that way as long as you know there is no
need to rely upon us to live your life
and in this way the interaction is both
an interaction with you and an
interaction with us and both are real
and within our overall Consciousness the
interaction you have when you utilize us
as a symbol is stored and
registered okay another question I'm I'm
kind of confused about the
relationship between um different
personalities of the same overso I'm not
quite clear on how you are a future self
of Daryl all right again there are many
different ways to look at it and in many
ways all of them are real you can
consider the idea from your linear time
Dimension point of view to Simply Be the
idea that let us say darl will
physically die and be
reborn in your future in my society as
me and my Society having the capability
of going back and forth through time
will Dain to speak through my own past
self to
you did you catch that mhm um that is
one way of looking at the idea there are
many other
ways understand that also the idea of
time though it is real while you are in
it is from the oversold point of view
you an illusion and all of the different
lives in that sense are all simultaneous
as you already understand mhm and so in
that way you can also look at it as a
parallelity okay I understand so why
when someone asks you have you ever had
um a life or an experience on Earth you
say no I say except for the physical
being sitting before you
now which you consider just as much a
part of your experience as of course
so this is Daryl's only Incarnation no
no
no understand the physical channel has
his own series of lives I have my own
series of lives this is the one in which
we are connected and
overlap and for both of us in that way
therefore while I have my own so to
speak past he is a part of it while he
has his own so to speak future I am a
part of that that because you created
now yes because it serves the purpose of the
yes because it serves the purpose of the
interaction now okay so your
relationship with uh Daryl parallels
car's relationship with her
great-grandmother uh if Carrie were to
have a past life
regression could she possibly regress to
see the experiences of her
great-grandmother in a sense she could
but understand it is not quite the same
idea for in this way there is much more
for in this way there is much more
intertwining by herself in that way she
can allow herself the opportunity to do
so but recognize that she is creating
this particular manifestation to be
within the same time track whereas the
inter relationship just to form the
definition in specifics that you are
looking for between myself and the
physical Channel takes place in two
different time tracks
altogether MH mhm so it is similar in
that way and she could do that
I and understand in a sense she is doing
that and the idea of her grandmother's
experiences throughout life did contain
a few opportunities to experience
certain cognitions that were not understood at
cognitions that were not understood at
that time to be Communications from her
own future self now sitting next to you
you follow me can you repeat that side I
say all right it's the last sentence the
idea many times I will put it in general
terms of when you are living your life
and sometimes when you get cognitions of
something that you think is going to
happen in that way perhaps sometimes the
ID the experience you call
deju will be Communications from your
future self back to you and in that way
when you then arrive at the time that
you experience it you will have an
overlap Sensation that you call a Deja
Vu uhhuh I see okay you spoke with uh a
friend of mine darthy Bo the other day
and she is exploring a her past life as
King Solomon anding not really not
really we describe the idea of the
identification to your friend in that
way it is not so much a literal idea as
it is an identification with a
particular type of energy she is
exploring within herself and also
connected to life in that time and also
connected to the energy of what you knew
to be that individual but it was not an
individual that you could say any one
one individual now was totally but
rather many individuals now were
together and she's one of those
individuals so why does she have to work
through that past life why that she
doesn't it's just something she's
creating because she wants to confront
understand that any connections you make
in that way are being made in the
present now they do serve you at the
time they are made but recognize you
always have the opportunity to know that
if you can recognize as we also
discussed with your friend the IDE IDE
that you are so to speak working through
something from a past life recognize
that you are doing it from a point of
view that is already beyond the
connection for you are in a sense
looking back and in this way you can
recognize that simply by being where you
are means in a sense you have already
worked it through if you are willing to
look at it that way you can actually
have that effect in the present it is
not like you have to create a process so
to speak although again and any process
your imagination creates is valid for
you and a part of the idea you chose to
be but you can also at the same time if
you wish to Simply recognize that by
having allowed yourself to create the
life you are now in in containing the
idea of everything you have ever been
and simply acting as the being you find
yourself to be now just by living the
life you are you will automatically work
everything through mhm you do not have
to stop yourself from living to do it in
a mode that feels like suffering exactly
you can simply live and draw from the
knowledge and the experience of
everything you have gained and in that
way as you live in the moment you will
tap what you need to of the totality of
yourself mhm and apply it where
necessary you follow me mhm thank you
sure nice
um I'd like to just point out an idea
when you were talking about that there's
not one individual you could say that
has that was the Incarnation of King
Solomon that um many people are
receiving that energy that in in the
idea of time going backwards that um
everyone uh experiencing that energy
actually is going backwards to the
Incarnation of King Solomon being able
to be in that idea and understand also
if I may interrupt you for one moment
that each and every individual who
traces themselves back in that way will
find themselves being their own aspect
their own version of that individual
understanding that even at that time
because that individual was a multiple
aspect personality Consciousness there
was more than one of him overlapping not
that any particular reality experienced
more than one but there was a
simultaneous psychic interaction on many
different parallel worlds of the same
individual in that way and many
individuals because each individual is
their own reality is their own parallel
world is their own universe will Trace
themselves back only to their own
version of that entity not anyone else's
you follow me one other idea that um I
wanted to share with you was at the at
the pond my experience was of the energy
of your civilization or your planet and
I could not distinguish if it was you
specifically but I knew the vibration
was of your civilization that's all I
could determine another thing that I I
can't seem to figure out and I'd like to
explore with you if you would care to is
that the being that I was contacting or
that I was in communication with his
ribs were vibrating and there was some
something in the communication that I
can't figure out can you tell me what
that meant or what that symbology is all
we can share with you at this time is
that the idea of the energy that you
will allow through yourself when you are
with willing to do so will feel a very
supportive energy in that way and as it
manifests through your solar plexus will
embrace you in a very loving band of
energy around your rib area and make you
feel uplifted you follow me yes it is a
uplifted you follow me yes it is a
symbolic identification with the type of
energy that when you allow it through
yourself will feel very
supportive okay thank you thank you
sharing sure question um I spoke with
you with regard to March 15th um this
extreme pain in my solar plexus and that
had to do with pushing myself my next
stage well I had it again is this me
resisting uh Progressive Movement only
in a fundamental sense but do not judge
yourself for having remnants of judgment
within you otherwise you are compounding
the idea because consciously I don't
feel like I'm resisting it so why am I
getting this pain understand in this way
again you are still viewing yourself as
highly accelerated in that way and this
is as we have said during what you call
your April month one more highly
accelerated activity time and in this
way since you are still making the
association to exist within a physical
reality that still does have separation
and judgment you will from time to time
as you feel the acceleration energy
going through yourself still feel some
of the pain in that way it will
lessen as you acclimate but you are
still utilizing it as a barometer for
your own progress so to
speak so do not judge
yourself allow it to flow you can ease
it it does not have to be experienced as
pain remind yourself of that idea that
you have a choice to Simply understand
the reason for why the energy is going
through you and allow yourself to
understand it does not have to manifest
as a separation in that way as pain
okay also um once a lot of people speak
about um opening their chakras when
they're meditating how does one open their
meditating how does one open their
chakras Envision them open that is one
way if that works for you it will do
nicely mhm what's another way that you
can suggest I can suggest many different
ways but understand the way that your
imagination says is yours is the way
that will work for you MH you can do
anything at all in that way if you are
applying what you are doing to the idea
of opening your chakras in that way also
understand in a sense it can be just as
simple as allowing yourself to know they
are open
exactly
uhhuh yes it will have as many layers as
you care to give it each will be valid
since you have chosen to do it in that
way and will represent the path you
chose to
be and if you change your mind about how
you wish to do it then that is a part of
the flow Go With It mhm
Now understand if you still request a
suggestion you can view yourself as an
electromagnetic being made of electromagnetic fluid
being made of electromagnetic fluid
immersed in electromagnetic fluid you
can see the lines of electromagnetic
force around you through you that create
you to be an energy pattern interwoven
intertwining interacting and in this way
allow yourself to see that all of these
lines of so-called force of movement of
action of activity of creation are
flowing unimpeded through you in a continuous
unimpeded through you in a continuous
cyclic motion of ease and
creativity allow yourself to see
yourself imbued with blue white
electromagnetic energy and know that
every single line of energy that courses
through you that forms the pattern of
the being you happen to be mhm is always
drawing from the central source of all
that is for its own
revitalization and it brings that
revitalization to you from that Source
every moment of time that you create to
exist and that you are constantly
revitalized constantly accelerated and
constantly balanced allowing the
material idea of yourself and the oric
etheric idea of yourself the astral and
all the other levels of your existence
to all be in harmonious synchronization
through these lines of activity knowing
that the lines of communication which is
what they are are functioning perfectly
between all the different levels you
have created yourself to be so that you
can sense consciously physically the
blending that is taking place and allow
yourself not to create the idea of there
being a stop up or a block in any
particular direction hold and in this way also
direction hold and in this way also
remember that that which you perceive to
be a block is not really a block it is a
sign that points in an unexpected
Direction when you judge that this
unexpected direction is not something
that represents a part of your path then
it becomes a block mhm when you go as
the sign points left or right then that
will be the way to go straight
ahead when you find yourself giving
yourself a wall in that way okay simply
understand it is not there for you to
beat your head against but it is there
to indicate that now is the time to turn
to go with the flow of yourself left or
right and that turning paradoxically
will be the way to go straight ahead
most quickly mhm so allow the idea to
flow and you will not have to experience
the unexpected as separation and pain
but you can experience it as integration
and ecstasy it can be the same energy
ecstasy it can be the same energy
anxiety and the pain of anxiety and
separation is the same as the energy of
ecstasy except with a judgment put upon
it
mhm thank
you yes I've been told that I have
guides or that most of us have Guides of
what good is knowing that me or what
would I do with that information you
tell me has it served you
and as we have already said that guides
are doing their job best when they lure
you to yourself so it is not like they
have to be blatantly in your
life so if you find that you have the
ability to have access to all the
information that you require in your
life and all the answers for every given
situation that you are living then in a
sense you are functioning as those
guides would wish you to function as
your own best guide you follow me that
is their Prim
purpose to allow you to function as your
own best guide so if you are doing that
already there is not necessarily any
need that you should symbolically
recognize the fact that you have guides
in physical terms you follow me is a
guide something uh that I've known in a
past life oh can be can be yes sometimes
individuals will take turns being other
individuals guides one being
non-physical one being physical taking
turns living lives in that way
thank you well Fu
you there was a um movie on TV the other
night about a boy who had epilepsy and
they did a laser like split in the
center of his brain to stop the
epileptic seizures can you explain that in terms
seizures can you explain that in terms
of how that same epileptic
energy is experienced the way you were
describing with the
channel in this way recognize
that because the idea of epilepsy as we
have said to some degree is similar to
the channeling energy turned Inward and
not outward it is allowing your
scientists and medical personnel to
focus on the idea of that energy in the
brain it is luring them to research the
idea of how your brain works and
translates your Consciousness into
physical terms it is responsible for the
idea of now the separation of different
functions within the brain but now will
be responsible for the idea of the
integration of the brain in that way it
is leading your scientists to begin to
explore the idea of the neural Pathways
that are active within all portions of
the brain as opposed to going to the
understanding of having to isolate a
particular section though isolation will
have been their first step simply
because isolation is the Habit your
civilization progresses on most usually
in this way you will find it will come
roundabout full circle and the idea of
the exploration of epilepsy will allow
individuals to know that the idea of the
splitting of the brain will draw their
attention to the idea of the center of
the brain in that way not so much that
they are then splitting it and looking
at either half but that if they
reintegrate it and look at the interface
between it they will understand that
that area called the coras scum is the
interface and the source through which
and the net through which and the Matrix
through which all is channeled into your
physical reality from the non-physical
they will find the idea in the very
Center they have chosen to draw as the
splitting line itself not thinking that
it carries within it the actual idea
they are looking for you follow me yes
so is the split medically through the
Corpus kosum is that where the split is
taking place more often than not yes it
will be the separation the unplugging of
the communication from what has been
described as the left and right
hemisphere although those are arbitrary
labels and you are beginning to
understand that many things take place
throughout the entirety of the brain and
are not really isolated so to speak
exactly in left and right
hemispheres okay so so if they're going
through the black hole in the brain are
they doing a reversal in that black hole
procedure in a sense but what they are
allowing themselves to understand is
that is where they need to focus but
they are simply assuming that that line
represents what will give them the
opportunity to isolate the idea in one
side or another and are not yet
realizing that it is that line in itself
that represents the interaction that
must take place between the two sides
that will give them the source that they
are seeking in other words it is again
an example of the idea of attempting to
stop a process in order to understand it
rather than allowing the interface the
line to function as an interface so that
they can see how the energy is
translating into both sides of the
brain and other words they are assuming
like what you call a Diamond
Cutter that the idea of cleaving a
diamond the idea of the line upon which
the diamond is cleaved is only good for
the purpose of
Separation those cleaving lines in and
of themselves are the definitive Matrix
of the existence of that diamond and can
lead them back to the template the
non-physical template upon which the
idea of the structure is based they are
simply assuming that the only good the
line represents is one of
Separation they do not understand that
lines are interfaces are ideas and areas
of
interaction you follow me yes is this
just a matter of timing before they yes
and some of your scientists have begun
to move in that direction there can be
an entirely new study based upon not so
much the sections into which they find
or create the brain to be divided but
the divisions themselves that they have
divisions themselves that they have
created you follow me the divisions the
line that they have only been using as
conveniences to say well look at section
A and look at section B will in and of
themselves begin to take on the aspect
that it is the dividing line that gives
birth to section A and birth to section
B and therefore all that they are
looking for in the isolated sections can
be found Blended in the dividing line
itself you follow me that's fascinating
thank you recognize that as you create
these black hole cellular structures you
will find that if you were to remove all
the sections you have now categorized
there would be the idea of a very thin
lais work shell like paper like
structure that in and of itself is the
extension of that Central dividing
Corpus colossum line that membrane is in
and of itself an entirely different type
of an approach a different understanding
of how information is processed in the
brain and you will then find that there
will be people in your Society who will
begin to explore that portion of the
brain almost as if they are actually
exploring the bones of the brain so to
speak rather than the body of the brain
you follow me so they're exploring more
like the blueprint
yes it
yes as if it would
be that someone living in a house as you
call them would begin to explore the
idea that much goes on in the walls that
divide the
rooms everything that supports the house
goes on in the walls that divide the
rooms in which you live you follow me
and yet we never see between between
those walls
until you have to go in digging after it
because the room you are living in is
too hot or too cold or something is not
to your
liking understand that these ideas of
epilepsy and many related diseases in
that way are giving you the opportunity
to dig further and further until you
come to the very structure out of which
those ideas manifest it is not so much
within the body of the brain but within
the structure that supports the
body thank you thank you would that be a
physical structure of the brain Bashar
yes it has a physiological counterpart
and then the step from that will be to
understand it has a non-physiological
counterpart a template yeah just as your
house has a
blueprint how does that relate to uh my
dad's a neurosurgeon and he said for
quite a few years a lot of the Leading
Edge um neurosurgeons have understood
that there are no as far as they can
tell local areas of the brain uh that
you can describe left and right Behavior
to that uh feelings are located in one
area and if you just erase that it will
STP a trimor or feelings and he said
it's really holographic yes exactly and
he said exploring in the way that you're
talking about about trying to cut off
certain areas of the brain is like
trying to determine why is the light
working walking over to the light switch
and knocking it out with a a
sledgehammer saying look we've located
the cause of the light and completely
overlooking the fact that the light is
tied into the whole electrical system
and that all the way back to the water
system it is in your terms sistic yeah
and he said there's no way you can that
it is holographic and they also have a
lot of studies that show people have
lost up to 90% of their uh neocortex and
have still been able to retain all the
language and motor functionings of the
brain what can begin to understand is
that the central dividing structure will
be what we refer to an society as a
flash Matrix it will be something that
acts as a
translation membrane permeable to any portion of the
membrane permeable to any portion of the
brain and allows certain ideas to
manifest in certain sections according
to the purposes being
served so it is not so much that an idea
that is discovered to be functioning
within a particular portion of the body
of the brain in one instance has to
function there all the time if the
purpose is different right The Matrix
can allow it to function whatever it
needs to function to serve the purpose
being served so I'm I am kind of on the edge
served so I'm I am kind of on the edge
here I'm not quite sure what would be
explored to take the next step to
understand this I'm not sure if it's
actual physical structure or you can
begin that way if you wish but you can
also understand it as an energy
relationship there can be in your terms
mathematics and equations to Define that
idea okay
the idea of how the membrane what you
call the Corpus kosom acts as a
permeable membrane allowing both
hemispheres to interface can be a step
okay and would it be biochemical or
electrical it will be all of them okay
understand as you create your
Consciousness to exist in physical
reality you will create all the
physiological symbols to go along with
it so that from any particular Point can
you trace it back whether you are
biochemically oriented or electrically
oriented or whatever Avenue you have
taken upon yourself to be your point of
view yes uh one more question does the
uh I don't quite how to say this the
word does the brain actually create its
own structure from its own
template yes and no
understand that it is a self-feeding
system to some degree and that once your
Consciousness interjects the template
into physical reality there will be an
automatic growth in that way that in
your terms controls the way the cells
move and structure themselves there is a
type of physiological Consciousness that
also in your terms takes a hand in the
patterning of that idea and once it is
formed does lend a hand in continuing to
support that idea and recreate itself
let us say as an electromagnetic
Consciousness yes but it is always
supported from the non-physical
Consciousness that you are
yes I have another question um that
relates to the 14th and 15th February
Leia was talking about an idea about
that when we open up and I don't know
why she put it in either or terms she
said you either learn to love and accept
more and more and more of all that is ni
uh or you learn to love yourself more
than anything else and that is called
service to the self and could you expand
on that please simply in this way what
was being defined is that if you
recognize that being of service to all
that is is
automatically allowing yourself to be
taken care of then you have a blending
that will accelerate you to the
understanding of your higher existence
within forc density taking the approach
of feeling like you need to serve
yourself first is actually paradoxical
to truly loving yourself in that way
right for if you know that you love
yourself unconditionally then you take
it for granted that you are taken care
of in that way and can simply be of
service to all that is right and isn't
also really understanding all of
yourself is understanding that
everything that you think see perceive
and feel is yourself in that way yes
simply what was being being said is that
to be overly concerned with the idea of
feeling like you must protect yourself
in that way is not really allowing
yourself to be supported by all that is
because you are not supporting
it you follow me I I think so I'm not I
don't know why it's not jelling in my
brain simply the idea of service to self
in that way is being overly concerned
that you by being of service to all that
is are not automatically
supported okay here's here's my
confusion as as I understand self is
seeing myself as this here what's
sitting here talking right now and at my
full understanding is understanding I'm
connected to everyone in this room all
right okay so when I hear someone saying
that you'll love yourself more than
anything else is an immediate creation
of separation of understanding no not in
that way it is a description of how you
apply that understanding in other words
if you know that you do love yourself
unconditionally as all that is loves you
in that way then you are no longer
concerned with focusing the attention of
how to apply that towards you but
outwardly got it does that clarify the
idea yes it does thank you thank you I'm
the you venue um just recently I went to
a seminar of creativity where
neurosurgeon was talking about the bra
right as a gland and this is a new in a
sense it is in sense some master
gland it is not so much an organ in the
same sense as what you would call your
bodily organs are
processing let us say on a secondary
level the IDE is that support your
existence whereas your glandular system
will be more closely connected to the
actual electrochemical activity and not
so much the biochemical
activity um another idea that I'm
working on today is um can you comment a
little bit more about the events that
occurred today in
Libya not really so much more than what
we have already shared with you about
the idea of allowing such interactions
to come to the surface rather than being
covert to give yourselves the
opportunity to now interact with your
governments as a portion of the
government and not as something
ostracized from that idea so that you can tell them
from that idea so that you can tell them
without judging them Without accusing
them but with your unconditional love
you can share with them that you prefer
peace and have faith that the idea of
Peace will be what will allow you to
function within strength and not the
idea in that way of needing to function
on the same level as somebody you are
saying robs other individuals of their
power by doing the same
thing you follow me in that way
understand that if you truly find that
an idea is worth believing in you do not
have to defend it in that way otherwise
you are saying that you do not believe
it is strong enough to manifest upon the
Earth for its own sake
you follow me you're referring to PE
yes the idea that you find that someone
in your
world might be playing the
idea of forcing their point of view on
someone else you can understand that you do not
else you can understand that you do not
prefer in your terms to condone that
particular type of action but
recognize that by reacting in the same
manner you are only perpetuating the
same idea in other terms in other
clothes if you truly in this way say
that you believe in the idea of Peace
then acting in a peaceful manner in that
way if you truly believed in it would
have far more effect and far more
power than all of the Weaponry that
exists upon your
planet and you would be able to actually
see that power in effect if you truly
believed that it had power and did not
need to be
defended by forcing the idea of other
people into the subjugation of your
point of
view understand that as long as you as a
society find that you are choosing to in
your terms Fight Fire with Fire to those
whose point of view you do not agree
with you will only be continuing to
attach yourselves to them
in the way that you say you do not want
to be
attached you follow me that's definitely
in this way also as we have
said it is not even a matter of
judging for again you do not get Peace
by hating War you get Peace by loving
Peace by acting by being peaceful
fulfilled of peace and taking it upon
yourselves the initiative to act
individually and or
collectively to
allow all the governments upon your
planet which are only extensions of you
to
know that there are many ways you can
share and that anyone who feels they
must push their point of view no matter
who it is upon someone else obviously
does not truly believe in the power of
their point of
view if you share this with the
individuals that are fighting they may
begin to let it sink in that if they
feel they must defend their point of
view then in this way perhaps they
themselves can come to some
understanding about how much they really
do believe or don't believe in what they
themselves are
saying you follow me yes
there will still continue as we perceive
it at this time to be an acceleration of
some of this interaction many other
factors will come into play before this
month is
out the more quickly you allow
yourselves to become a part of the
action in a peaceful Way by
communicating not only with your own
governments but with all governments
this is your world you have to stop at
your borders they are arbitrary
designations the more you communicate
with all of the governments that you
are that you prefer peace the more and
the sooner you will let them know they
do not have to maintain the
Shad you follow
me for in this way they are only
thinking that they are reflecting what
they think you
want they think you want to be protected
you are putting them in the position of
believing they have to act as your
protectors because you have given
responsibility for the creations of your
lives over to them take the
responsibility back and you will relieve
them of that burden and allow them to be
natural you follow me they will when you
allow them to wake up into their own
self empowerment be eternally grateful
does that clarify the idea to some
degree for now yes it does thank you
thank you
yes oh you know that you just
answer my all right sure you venue she first if
my all right sure you venue she first if
you say so well I was just continuing
what her question was about liia um I
feel a little confused as far as um the
IDE I know a lot of people are thinking
this might be a prerequisite to war and
I'm confused as far as what you're
saying is to far as that
idea do you believe that the interaction
between what you call your country and
their country must lead to war or do you
believe that some understanding can come
from this I I definitely believe that an
this I I definitely believe that an
understanding can come from that then
within your own imagination as you
conceive of what that understanding
might be of what shape it might take act
upon it and you will make a
difference we cannot stress enough that
each and every single one of you make a
difference act as the full being you
have been created to be and you will see
that difference in your reality
you follow me well have you stated um
from your perspective if you felt this
was just um another idea being Express
or if it was something having to do with
war or was something just you are not
going to in our perception have what you
call nuclear Annihilation if that is
what you are talking about right well to
me Annihilation doesn't necess mean the
same thing as War you may understand
that in your strictest technical
terminology you have already had had war
with them you are having a war right
[Music] now it is not something that is going to
now it is not something that is going to
happen you are in the middle of it now
war is also only one type of
exchange transmute and transform the
exchange into a positive one by your
willingness to act in a positive manner
now that the lines of communication are
open no matter if they be
negative utilize them in a positive way
send your thoughts send your love not
only to them but to your own governments
because you are your
governments act like a being who exists
in a world where communication will make
a
difference then it
will all
right sure um what you mentioned earlier
about uh serving all that is is serving
serving oneself
serving all that is is doing what
excites one could you CL being true to
yourself right doing what excites you in
service to other individuals in that way
allowing them to partake of the gift
that you are and allowing them to serve
you in return automatically how could
you do anything else well understand
intrinsically you can you are always
serving other people the idea is to
allow yourself to consciously know that
so that you will not feel that the
service has to be in negative
manifestation uh negative manifestation
being judgment and separation I see I
see I see I see um let's see I had
another question
question
um I can't remember it I'll come up
later you sure yes um I have some
confusion here oh that is all right
understand again the ideas of what you
call depression and confusion are not
necessarily Negative they are simply
cusing and withdrawing to the center of
yourself where you know the answers lie
cusing confusion allows you to unlock
disorient from one reality so that you
can reorient to a new understanding of
yourself nothing necessarily negative
about confusion right I feel that way so
maybe together we can explore and get to
my center and Clarity maybe maybe um
firstly when when uh we at the beginning
of this month when you started we all
started discussing all doing something
and taking action and making a
difference I did some things and I
explored I did some things doing things
and also went did some uh inward things
exploring my own fears and feelings and
angers which might be contributing to
war now my feeling today was when I
heard that there was an attack I felt
okay I'm exploring Maybe there's some
places I haven't found in me but I find
it hard to believe that there's not one
person that loves the idea of Peace
enough to have created peace because I
from what I understand it will only take
one it only needs one and I can't
believe not one of us now understand
this idea each and every one of you is
your own complete
reality right now the definition of the
reality that you are sharing you are
agreeing to
share because this is let us say in the
middle of the transformation is one that
allows you to still be able to perceive
all of the different ways people are
perceiving their world to be the further
you accelerate towards fourth density
reality the more specialized your
particular Viewpoint will create your
reality to be and all the individuals
you will experience in your reality will
will all be reflections of what you
choose to
be understand as many individuals so to
speak not to be contradictory but in
your language it may not make much sense
all the individuals on your world every
single one of them the countless
billions in that way all each and every
one of them is right now their own
complete potential true quote unquote
reality future possible probable
future each and every one of them will
experience the future they choose to
be every single one of
them now let us say
hypothetically if every single
individual upon your planet chose to
experience a different future you all
would the idea however is that many of you
the idea however is that many of you
will choose to have different Futures
that share similar
qualities and so you will agree to
interact within a certain range of
experience that will allow all of you to
feel you are in the same future but you
are not by strictest definition you are all
not by strictest definition you are all
in your own future your own present
Bashar was something you're just saying
um being at peace and at
War I feel peaceful I me I don't feel
I'm at war with all right is that then
you are not getting blown up are you no
not all and I mean the idea being that
most of us in the room I assume we not
at war with Libya during degrees of
Peace KFI can have my dinner at my house
anytime all right perhaps someday we
shall so if if you accept the fact that
others might feel that they're at War
with with a a country or allow them and
allow yourself to know that there is no
need to judge that they have that point
of view and by your willingness to
unconditionally love them as they are
and reflect that to them that is what
will allow them the opportunity to look
at you and see reflected in you the
opportunity to choose peace all for
themselves as
well are you saying that the the
limitations of the mass Consciousness
are being um expanded in a sense so that
there there are more opportunities
for as creative as you are willing to be
within integrity and unconditional love
the opportunity is open to you act on it
if you can imagine it do it if it serves
all that is and allows you to be a
reflection of the peace you know exists
in your particular
world has this has this unlimited um has
this capacity for unlimited action
always been there of
course then why hasn't why hasn't anyone
moved in the direction understand you
are and understand that your unlimited
capacity for creation is what has
allowed you to create a reality in which
you can experience
limitation understand that you are
always using
100% of yourself even if you are using
90% to create the illusion that only 10%
of you is
functional you follow me therefore
possible is it therefore possible for
all the billions of beings that exist on
this planet to theoretically choose Futures
planet to theoretically choose Futures
that are so wildly Divergent that in
fact there are there's no commonality
between it it is possible yes however
your energy your Mass Consciousness and
the purposes for which you generally all
agreed to be on earth to begin with make
it let us say
unlikely you can change the scenario if
you wish but you have a great deal of
energy and momentum behind the idea that
you will generally move together in a
general way towards the idea of higher
understanding peace and
Harmony you went said that we could
choose to create um by virtue of our
belief uh anything anything that we
still desire providing it felt
within within the limitations of the
general agreement consens yes um so now
it's just a broader consensus more is
possible yes more is
possible
now each and every one of you
may allow yourselves the
opportunity during your break to feel
within yourselves the
yourselves the
potential for all that takes place in
your world to be felt within yourself
immediately and for what you feel within
yourself to have an effect on all that
takes place within your world in
instantaneously would you repeat
that no oh all
no oh all
right during your break as you quote
unquote refresh
yourselves allow the refreshment you are
taking in to
in to
also expand outward from each and every
one of you and fill the world with
refreshment so that you know that what you feel
so that you know that what you feel
personally as you view yourself in your
own personal relationship to all that
you see taking place in your world you
can also
extend your
your
beingness your Consciousness outward so
that the whole world you are in contact
with also feels the
individuality of your reality and can
choose that for themselves to share that
with you to refresh themselves if they
desire all right thank you mhm thank you
all you may all take a short
break all right say
sharing you then
you um I I still have questions about
Libya and this this situation I feel
when um I'm in this room with this group
of people that um we can talk to each
other about how we
see uh how we see the situation on our
planet how we would prefer it to be and
yet um I can just talk to anyone on my
acquaintances in my business and
um their point of view makes a lot of
sense of course it is valid for them
understand the idea is not to convince
someone of your point of view nor that
they have to adopt it simply that you
are sharing it as your point of
view I was wondering if you could
um suggest just to say um that we prefer
peace and peaceful Solutions just seems
to elicit responses of well that's naive
because if you just sit around and be
peaceful then they're going to go on
being terrorists and why should we sit
around while they blow up people around
the planet we have to do
something and I I don't know how I feel
what is
naive um you
think that one isn't aware of political
realities Now understand that it may be
that many
individuals in that
way are
choosing to view an
individual in your case in this way let
us say such as yourself as being naive
because they have their own definition
of what they think reality is and they
think everyone agrees with
it they are formulating that there
is a real background that is the same
for everyone against which all
viewpoints can be
measured you can allow them to
understand understand that in a sense
according to
what your own physicists now know to
assume that there is a definitive solid
background against which all viewpoints
can be measured is a naive point of
view but in this way
recognize that
simply again not meaning to attack in
that way but that you can allow them to
know that not everyone thinks as they do
about what reality
means yes yes share the
idea that it is because they
believe that there is a
steadfast so-called background
reality that they think
their
situation needs to
be
reactive instead of
active that they
feel that the structure of physical
reality is something rigid out of which
they cannot break Beyond a certain
point and that is what allows them to
experience the situation as they are
again and again and
again in this specific incident is there
a specific way we could see it
differently so that we could act instead
of react I mean in the sense this do you
have any examples in your history at all
of individuals who were willing to act
as peace more than willing to react as
word yes all
right all
right then in this way if you know that
all it takes is one individual to make a
difference in the reality you perceive
then act like that
individual choose your model to
determine the reflection of the reality
you experience
MH if a model is what you need
understand that their Viewpoint that you
are naive is only because they are
choosing models to pattern themselves
after that do not have a belief in the
option in other
realities yes I mean I'm not talking to
people who believe that you create your
own reality all right but again
understand the purpose is not to
convince them otherwise mhm if they
choose to view in their opinion that you
are naive so what it is an opportunity
for you to decide whether you truly
believe what you are saying or
not and to stick with it or change it
yes that is the purpose they are serving
for you are you truly experiencing
you are you truly experiencing
conviction in your beliefs or do you
choose to doubt what you know to be true
for you
uh I choose to doubt when I'm talking to
them all right then since you know
you're making that choice you can choose
something else if you prefer it thank
you for sure one moment guys um then you
for sure my sister was supposed to come
here this evening and she could supposed
to well I mean she was planning oning
all right and she she's an alha singer
and she's very talented she's very good
but she gets sick all the time she
always gets these sinus infections that
then it blocks off her nasal passage and
she can't sing high out or anything and
she's here in Long Beach doing a job and
she's already missed a week of rehear
cuz she's s a well and I was wondering
if you could enlighten me on anything to
advise her as to why she's getting [Applause]
me does she have anything blue anything yes
yes something that she can look at as a
color and allow herself to imagine that
blue as being
energy yes then suggest this tonight of her
yes then suggest this tonight of her
time before in that way
communicate this right now as well as
contacting her later all right through
your own Consciousness visualize her
receiving the
information look at that
blue color feel
color feel
herself to be immersed in that
energy allow her to see a doorway
in the middle of her sinus cavities a
doorway from the sinus into the brain
allow it to be
open allow there to be
no door that can close but allow it to
be an open conduit with a
tunnel to the very center of her
brain and then down through the
throat to the very center of her solar
plexus up through the heart up through
the throat into the center of the
brain deflecting into the sinus cavity
allow there to be an open
pathway see herself as she is immersed
in that blue energy breathing it in
through her nose through her
mouth into that tunnel into the brain
down through to her solar plexus up
again and out into her oric field into
her electromagnetic field of allowing
there to be a balance of the vibration
she knows herself to be
becoming allow her also to allow a
doorway and a tunnel to go from the
center of the brain connecting into this
tunnel we have already described up to
the top of her head and out so that
there is a releasing of the pressure in
the internal systems within her so there
is an equalization of the pressure of
her oric field in which she is immersed
and the internal pressures of her body
and all the different chakra points all
right allow her to breathe freely as she
is going to sleep of this energy and to
relieve herself of the
difference in the pressure that she has
created in the outside and the inside
worlds allow her to balance the pressure
systems much the same way that what you
call one of
your air V
vehicles in this way can allow there to
be the balancing of external and
internal pressures in this way to allow
there not to be a
strain against the skin that holds
everything in and keeps everything out
so there is an
equalization and a smoothness of
flowing that will allow her to attain
any height any depth in any liquid any
medium any
atmosphere dense or total
vacuum this is
allegorical but will
suffice thank you allow also her to
understand that there is a
stream a level of energy which she may
tap into in Her Dream starting tonight
of her time
and she may begin starting tonight of
her time to have
cognizance of the interactions taking
place within those levels and allow them
to become her physical reality and not
to create such a separation between her
dream self and her physical self
equalize the pressure of the differences
between the dream reality and the
physical reality as well she will find
herself becoming very very
active very
active she will accept accelerate in
ways that will allow her to expend that
energy and utilize that energy in many
different ways and it will all equalize
and balance so that no matter at what level
balance so that no matter at what level
so to speak she finds herself to be she
will already find The major portion of
herself to exist there
already so she will have assistance as
she needs it to exist on any level and
will not have to struggle to reach or
attain a particular height or a
particular depth equalizing the
depth equalizing the
pressure all
right repeat this idea
verbatim wait I have a question Connie
uh her sister was doing a particular
yoga stance and was looking at her third
eye in the mirror and saw herself
disappear oh right can you explain that
at all any particular way not off hand
other than she was con not concent I
guess allowing herself all right
to um to completely become one with her
whole environment and and she didn't see
herself as a separate entity from it and
as it
and and what and become transparent to
herself allowing the inside and the
outside to be the same
thing the idea of the sinus connected to
the third eye activity in that way
becoming Clairvoyant about your own life
allowing the path to be clear to become
transparent to yourself allowing the
inner and the outer to
blend that is the symbol
yes thank you yes
you yes
um well all this evening this analogy
that you shared with me uh I wanted to
express to the people here and it has to
do with uh well I want to start by
saying when when I was a child my
parents would always say to me like when
it when when I was just old enough to
vote they would say go out and vote
because it makes a difference and then I
would sit at home and you know the polls
it would be a landslide for one
president and I would say now if I went
out it would make a difference there was
millions of those differ but yes it
would make a difference okay just
is I
know and I am not ching him no you're
not you're not and and that's what I
realized that was what was so wonderful
was when you had when you had said to me
that if you take a cube and you change
one side of that Cube it is a different
Cube it is not the same CU with another
color correct it is a different Cuban
and it literally is a different world if
you make that choice for yourself yes
and that is how it counts right um one
other thing I I'm living my life and I just
thing I I'm living my life and I just
want I want to share one small aspect
with with everyone here I was a couple
days ago I was driving on the freeway uh
about 5:30 in the morning and I'm
listening to a wonderful tape of a
medium and I look in the rearview mirror
and there's this motorcycle cop with his
red lights
blinking and this is like one of the
first times that I didn't like seeing
him coming up he was right there you
know and I didn't even realize I was
feeding I was so engrossed in what I was
doing and I wasn't identified I didn't
get an adrenaline rush this is the first
time I didn't get an adrenaline rush and
uh the freeway off wamp was about an
eighth mile away so I just drove until
the offramp and I get off and the the
and I was really loving with this
officer and he comes up to me and he
wanted to kill me he literally he was he
was very negative and he was upset that
I got off the freeway he says what nerve
do you have getting off the freeway who
do you think you are and uh and then he
says I'm riding you up for going 80 mil
an hour and I felt like a victim I
really did because I felt like I said
why are you mad at me and that's when he
said because I was going 80 and and so
anyways I left there and I said to
myself what is this symbol for me and I
realize that I'm accelerating at a pace
that I'm unaware
of
good so anyways um bading from that I I
just want to say that my life literally
changed from that ticket from what I
learned from it I don't want to go into
that now but because I was willing to
explore what my higher self is teaching
me in everything in my life that I'm
getting a lot of mileage out of
it very good thank you what are you
sharing a most arresting
tale speeding right along than
you sh all right all right
sh all right all right
um I had a very interesting dream last
night it was a very strange UFO dream
and um I was in this house and um all of
a sudden I felt this really strong
vibrating energy and it was like I knew
all of a sudden I went outside and there
was this UFO but it was a very funny
looking UFO it was like around it was
like a round ball and it had a big
funnel sticking out of it all right was
kind of moving around and that final
part was kind of moving around and there
was lots of silvery balloon not bigger
than the UFO things all behind it and as
I looked at it I I felt the energy again
and I said darl come here quick I was
like going on the side of my mouth
because I was afraid that I was going to
make it go and he wouldn't see it and so
he came out and we looked at it and that
was about the end of the
dream um and the thing that's most
unusual is the the shape of the very
unexpected to think but I knew that's
what it was I just didn't know what purp
was doing it you knew that's what it
was are you sure yes absolutely 100%
positive positive where did it come
from I don't know where it came from I
can make a guess all right go ahead make
again but it doesn't make any sense for
it to come from there okay yes that's
correct
then what is your next
guess that's not a
guess okay my next guess would be uh
uh
Now understand this way the idea was
your perception of what some individuals
have per perceived as UFO but in this
way is actually a projection of
Consciousness and it was your
Consciousness it was your overs soul and
all the silver bubbles were all your
different lives what's the funnel business your
lives what's the funnel business your
channeling into the different lives from
the overs Soul big ball funneling into
the little B yes the extension of the
over soul that blows and creates out of
that extension all the silver bubbles of
the life that you experience and
surround yourself with and do the dance
so that was why when I felt the energy
was it was a very vibrating energy
yes in this way recognize that many UFOs
are projections of exactly that type of
Consciousness into your physical reality
and are perceived as glowing spheres of
light not what Young the what isn't that
s j with that
yes that it is projection of
Consciousness now there are all types
right I just yes um Can two uh portions
of the same overso exist at in the same
time frame yes they are called
counterparts and so would they wouldn't
necessarily be twins or anything no you
may never meet them
when you meet them you may not like
them or you may is up to you Erica
yeah that answer yes good thank you very
much there will
there will
be that we perceive the
idea tomorrow being the day of the
halfway mark of your month of April in
what you call the second half more
acceleration and in this way more
regular appearances by your
appearances by your
friend you're you yes [Music]
[Music]
yes not tonight though huh no it is
before the halfway mark guess you're
have to show
tomorrow there will be first opportunity
no guarantee in what you call Wednesday
night of your time and then also next
Monday night of your
time for the
communication in that way that will
represent the acceleration of your
energy and pay
attention the
idea of allowing for that communication
bridge to come through will be directly
proportional to the degree you are
willing to act as the beings you know
yourselves to be be
[Laughter]
okay guys to pop haven't heard that in a
sense you may View it as my own higher
self is consciousness from that
Civilization you would call the star
serious you follow me that's higher self
not future self can be same thing you
channeled your higher self once that was
a different experience it was a
different aspect of the whole idea it was the
aspect of the whole idea it was the
crystallin consciousness
you may refer to it as a future self if
you wish understand that from
wish understand that from
its point of view it is all quite
arbitrary doesn't matter
no why
um is there a reason why it's deciding
to channel through you rather than just
you Channel Through
Us in this way what you are always
experiencing you will experience perhaps
in that way as simply CHP through the
physiological channel of darl in the
same way you experience my Consciousness
but recognize it is always coming
through me in that sense because of the
terminology that you have made it to be
my future self and myself being Daryl's
future self there will always be the
manifestation of the Third identity that
you will perceive in that way on all the
different levels simultaneously and then
the creation of the construction of the
fourth identity inwardly and also the
fifth manifestation the one you
create for yourselves to experience did
you get that is
that wait wait a minute
wait could you repeat that please simply
that there
is would you like to explain it he's
saying it's like he the chath has to
come through him for of all because of
the the energy exchange and then you
understand the idea about when when he
comes through Daryl and they make a
third personality so that made the
fourth personality is that interaction
what's the fifth thing our creation our
perception of that personality guys the
fourth is the one that is experienced in
a sense inwardly by the channel right
exactly the fifth is the one you choose
to create of the Third
identity now
okay yeah you said that uh you've made a
connection with Daryl that that being
your only past life on Earth even though
Daryl has his own past Liv now is chop
does he have a connection with Daryl or
is there no connection except through
you then in that way is that what you're
saying that Daryl is not one of Chop's
past lives it is not connected in
exactly the same way no
mhm so it' be the higher self like when
I think I'm talking to my higher self
when I'm asking myself questions it's
kind of like
more I guess in a way the over picture
of your complete self in a sense rather
than but in a specific way that is what
was referred to as the future self which
is a specific version of the idea of the
higher self so are you conscious of what
this higher self quote is saying to us
while it's coming out oh yes
yeah do you interact both you twoo I
mean can you change and you start
talking and then [\h__\h] start talking
yes now also understand in that way that
there are many dimensions of the
experience going on quote unquote On My
Level as well at the same
time and for me there is also the idea
of the different variations of the
interactions that create a whole
scenario one of which one aspect of
which is what you are experiencing as
your entire
scenario did that come through I didn't
all right my inward experience what we have
right my inward experience what we have
described as the fourth
identity the one that occurs inside the
channel you follow me that total
experience Within Me
is
what is my interaction with you to me MH
what it represents for
you the entire interaction that you
perceive to be taking place between us
is that one inward bubble of experience
for me while I am in communication with
my future
self Now understand that what that means
is
the interaction that is channeling
inward to the physical channel
darl is penetrating into another
dimension of experience and
communicating with other entities as
well in other
words as a
Consciousness Daryl is
also speaking through someone somewhere
else as I am speaking through him to you
as chupop is speaking through me to
us because the fourth identity inward is
the one that penetrates through the
doorway within each of us down so to
speak not in a derogatory manner to the
next level that requires that type of
interaction in their own terms so for
each and every one of us that is in that
way the channel the inward experience
also becomes the outward experience for
another group of entities in some other
dimension of experience would darl be
channeling to the Bernard
Star oh very good M well thank
you there and other places can uh
someone be channeling such as
myself in other U places yes without being uh
in other U places yes without being uh
aware of it yes yes mhm yeah [Music]
[Music]
it we just told
him now in the idea of the dream reality
yes you are all aware of
it now it is a new understanding the way
the levels interact the way the doorways
interpenetrate each other and it is one
more understanding of the
multi-dimensional aspect of each and
every one of you for understand this is
partly partly an analogy for why it has
been said that what you perceive to be
stars are manifestations of other levels
of consciousness leaking so to speak
into your
reality your
thoughts your emotion ions and your
Consciousness in that way to other
entities in a sense can also be their
stars perceiving energy yes is astral
projection um to the idea of channeling
as far as you said how you can Channel
yourself somewhere
else not by your definitions in this way
it is mostly the idea of the projection
of your consciousness without
relationship to what you call your
physiological form in time and
space it is what seems to be the
personality you consider yourself to be
existing without your body but
perceiving in the same manner so to
speak that you would perceive if you
were physically present at the location
your senses now
occupy you follow me
when when so when
chupop comes through you and then down
through Daryl is that
interacting because you're connected to chupop or
because you're connected to chupop or
that interaction because simply because
it's it's serious energy and because
it's well both my particular
manifestation of my cognizance is
connected to the idea of the particular
manifestation of
chipal I am making a definition in the
same way to some degree that you make
your definitions and I am making them for you
definitions and I am making them for you
in those terms so that you understand it
as an
identity I guess I'm wondering is then
it's not every just because po Pop's
connected with Sirius that he needs a a
go between you understand what I'm
saying oh there is no need for the go
between in that way but that is what
serves the idea I have of myself and the
idea the channel has of himself and the
idea you all have of
yourselves understand there is direct
communication as well many times
although it is not perceived many times
as communication but it is perceived as
your imagination as Visions as emotions as
imagination as Visions as emotions as
attitudes you follow me who decides when
jaop comes through is it toil to jaop or
is that it is up to the idea of the
combined timing of the interaction of
all of us together including you for
when it best serves
you you stars are are um Consciousness
is coming through from other levels to
us everything is consciousness there is
a physiological in your terms reason for
the existence of a star that you do not
perceive to be connected to
Consciousness but it is also a
reflection of different levels of
consciousness penetrating into your
system there are consciousnesses in that
way attached to those phom
you follow me yes did did we at one time
on this planet know that and as how the
system of astrology started that we
think that the Stars it is one of the
aspects that makes that connection in an
archetypal manner yes very good yes
you're talking about um as you were
talking about feelings and attitudes I
was wondering about something that
occurred to me a couple of days ago do
we generate thought or are we processing
um vibrations of
that thoughts are
vibration in physiological
electromagnetic terms they are the
vibrations that are reflections of
patterns of Consciousness in physical
terms so we're not creating them yes you
are we're choosing them or creating what
is the
difference well you are the Creator as
you choose so you create you have
created the idea of a medium the
electromagnetic atmosphere in which a
Consciousness can have a model of itself
represented by what you call a thought
it is a model a thought is a model for
Consciousness in physical terms is that
something we become sympathetic to it's
already since it's already a part of all
that is we just become sympathetic to
that vibration and then appreciate it it
is not that the vibration exists without
you you create it but because you think
you do not then you feel you have to
become sympathetic with it as a
reflection but understand you create the
vibration to begin with and if you do
not recognize that you created it to
begin with then in order to associate
with it you might see it as an echo
bouncing back to you outside so that
your senses can pick it up and develop a
sympathy with it is that what we're all
doing this room right now yes is it a
creation or as much as a an acceptance
or a tuning into right is everything's
existing at once we're not we're not
adding anything to it we're just
perceiving other parts of it as a needle
on a record but the perception is the
creation is the creation
right I understand point of view is a
creation and we're also the event yes
but it's not an addition it's the
creation but we're not it's not an
addition it's just a perception of
something which is isn't that what
you're saying in a sense yes it is not
so much an addition as you mean it and
yet because each and every one of you is
unique the way you are perceiving in
this now moment is a new now moment
uhhuh and creating there to be a new now
moment which in a sense can be looked at
as an addition but paradoxically the
total volume of all that is does not
change right got thank you yes is there
an analogy to theologically to the
sympathetic nervous system and and what
we're talking about
like yes there is although we will find
that as we are scanning the majority of
the terminology necessary to describe
that to you does not exist within the
physical channels
memory however if I were to
take what you just said and look up what
I know about the system you can find the
connection Cas it does
exist for sure
yes you've told me the past to have
exciting dreams and a couple nights ago
I had a reoccurring dream three times in
one night oh right and it had to do with
something with uh like a television
transmission signal like a microwave or
something like that all right and uh
that's about the only thing I remember
about the three dreams can you that is
the only thing you remember well there
was other people around but the
important part important part part part
important part the dream is a total thing what
part the dream is a total thing what
else was there besides the people
anything about them that you care to
remember in particular anything else
besides them you care to share it had to
do with Communications I believe all
right what else um determination all
right is that a question yes I'm not too
sure well make it a statement and see
how it feels it feels good all right
what
else well you are pondering that I yeah
did you have a
question would you care to share
that I I will and I and I don't I don't
know that there any
correlation um you don't have to know it
share uh just just a few nights ago I I
dreamed that I was on a boat oh right
and I was um I was traveling with some
other people and at some point in time
I'd reached a point that was as far as I
as I could go um consciously and at that
point um I and the other people on the
boat were blindfolded and taken further
what a lifted out of the water on the
boat and transported to another body of
water all right stop right there hold
your place has anything else come up for
you there's there's a lot of
I can't put it into words a lot of
feelings there but it uh nothing that I
could really describe then allow
yourself to relax close your eyes and
allow the feelings to create pictures
now understand a dream is an
ongoing process it is going on right
now what other images do you create
now with the feelings that you have what
comes do not think about it do not
analyze say it as you see
it well nothing's
coming can you describe the
feeling all right pay attention continue
okay once we were um our boat was AED to
another body of water
um we were allowed to wander around the
on on the beach yes uh I can remember
looking into the water yes very light
blue green it was like looking into a
crystal yes um I also remember looking
out to see because it seemed to be an
island and I could only see a certain
distance and then there was clouds if
that's as far as it went all right was
there was I was I felt as if I was um
that things were obscured that I was not
allowed to see beyond that all right
there was there was definitely
limitations there and then what the one
um there was four people on the boat to
begin with um and
then there was 27 and the 27 seemed to
be an important number for some reason
and there was a great deal of discussion
on who was going to be in charge of this
group of people who was going to feed
them on the island who was going to be
in charge of making rules and getting
the food and um taking care of
everything um oh right stop right
there have you been enjoying her story
this is most beautiful did you have
pictures and or feelings that went along
with it while you were listening
I was really more wrapped up in what she
was saying
[Music] then wrapped up well enjoying the the
then wrapped up well enjoying the the
whole story so what was your
feeling all right what do you make of
her story
has to do with
communication is that what came to
you I guess it's more of a question mark
I
don't continue in what way might it I'll
play along with you might it have to do
with communication in what
way nothing I don't how do you wish to
communicate with the world in what way
do you wish to share the
ideas of yourself
yourself
H I believe that is a word in your
language verbally verbally all right
what will you share verbally
how to survive
survive how to
survive you are surviving just
fine well not necessarily how to survive
but how to how to feed and uh what to
do are you sure this is something you
want to
do well I'm lost right now to be honest
with all right very good are you
sure that this is something you want to
do oh yes you are sure definitely all
right how do you know you are definitely
sure what is the feeling that tells you
you are definitely sure or do you have a
picture of yourself doing this that
seems so real you just simply take it
for granted that that is what you are
going to be
doing how do you know it is definitely
sure
I don't know how to answer that you can
say I just
know go ahead I just know oh thank you
now hold on
continue um there's not a lot more to
the dream as far as as as um pictures
there a lot of feelings connected with
it all right what typ um I had the
feeling that that my immediate
environment um all around me was
extremely clear looking at the water was
clear looking at the sea was clear there
were also around this bubble of
clearness was obscurities that I could
not see any further all right now may I
ask you the same question how do you
wish to share to
communicate telepathically
telepathically
telepathically in in in um in symbols in
um
ideas Concepts
down the words oh I see all
right we have the idea of an
individual that in this sense has
created a
dream based
upon the one side of polar
of the
whole concept and an individual on the other
concept and an individual on the other
side of the polarity in that
way of the
of the
limitation of the Viewpoint and yet at
the same time the one
expressing the ability of the whole
concept having the very specific
specifically detailed knowledge of the
dream and the one expressing the
supposed limitation in that
way having simply a very sketchy concept
of the
dream and so in this way recognize
simply that both of you are within
yourselves polarities that are offering you the
polarities that are offering you the
opportunity to know that as you choose
to function from your knowingness
you are going to be utilizing
automatically whatever methodologies are
going to be right to represent the you
you have chosen to be and in this way
simply know that if there is
confusion within the so-called
communication to yourself within your
dream it does not have to be judged to
be a lack of communication a lack of
understanding but simply a way
compared to your physical life that
might be new for you unexpected for you
and so you cannot find the words in your
case in that sense and in your case
because you wish it to be concept you
find that you have an abundance of
ability to describe in words the entire
scenario and deal with all the specifics
that you feel to be in that way obis
skating recognize simply that to get
together if you are willing to share
some identification back and forth you
can spark within each other images and
visions that you have up to this point
not allowed yourself to be able to think
you can create within yourselves because
in that way you can show each other that
both of you contain both sides of the PO
it by reflecting as seeming individuals
each side of the same polarity is any of
this getting through it all we realize
it is in your terms rather
esoteric but in this
way there are within this particular
dream manifestation the opportunities to
manifestation the opportunities to
recognize that you are in communication
with yourselves as you need to be and
what is occurring here is the beginning
of a willingness to recognize that you
are not
isolated in your ability to externalize
this communication and find from each
other the aspects you individually
separately need to have reflected to you
to complete the dream you can be as a
living conscious physical
being you are stopping yourselves short
in that way from understanding the true
connection to your dream so that you can
find the connection in the dream that is
part of your physical life if you are
willing to
identify the idea you have shared and
see what identification that makes in
someone else so that you can begin to
act as service to each other physically
showing yourselves the reflections that
will allow you to see the completion of
the polarity within yourself already not
that you need the other individual to be
complete but that another individual in
your Society has the reflection that can
allow you to know you are complete and
can be consciously in communication with
the higher self the dream reality that
will allow you to understand the
completeness of the communication of
your physical self with respect to your
dream self on both ends of the polarity
you are expressing is that getting
throughh I'd like to add to to this
dream experience right when uh D is that
your name when when D said that there
were 27 people in the boat I got a rush
of adrenaline and a voice said count the
people in this room and yes there are 27
people not including D all
[Music]
right I'd also like to say that the
following the
following um
yeah the following night I was
discussing um this dream oh I had not
started discussing the dream yet a
friend of mine that I was with Don um
was telling me about a reading he had
had in which the channel had told him
about 27 people that were part of a
previous life of his he was um I guess
there were people under him that he was
in charge of and when he said that
number I reacted and said oh you know
that number came up in my being is is
there some
remember [Music] [Music]
obviously one
moment are you feeling any connection at
all to the idea of that 27 or the people
that you were surrounded with in your
dream nothing that I can
understand stop looking for it in the
past and see if your imagination tells
you anything in the present about
it what does it mean to you now not
making the connection to what you think
it is supposed to mean relative to the
dream you had what does it mean to you
right now 27 when I say 27 what do you get
now 27 when I say 27 what do you get
don't think about it say the first thing
that comes to your mind 27 it's my [Music] birthday
now you have something else to say we
were talking about that as uh you were
discussing that with me oh really do
share I was discussing the date of the
unborn child that she was expecting and
I had said to her I thought it would be
maybe a birthday and then I said if not
the 27th possibly the 9th all right it
seems to me at any rate that the two of
you have some things to talk
[Music] about see if you can be Reflections for
about see if you can be Reflections for
each other to allow both of you to
recognize the polarity that exists
within each of you that can be blended
into a knowing communication between
your physical and your dream realities
Dale yes thank you for your
synchronicity and your participation in
the dream thank you that very enjoy piece of
dream thank you that very enjoy piece of
social engineering is
that thank
you in this way recognize that this idea
and the reason in a sense to a degree it
seemed to perhaps become a little more
complex than usual is simply because
what we were doing in a sense for the
first time was beginning to describe the
structures that we perceive as we share
with you in our perception of with your
willingness forming and moving into
place the social engineering
aspects when you um chose D um were you
picking something up because I know D
and I know she is about the most Vivid
dreamer i' I've ever experienced in my
analytical training I'm wondering why
why you in this way
again to depict the idea of the
engineering that takes place we simply
find that in allowing ourselves to act
in and of the moment and Trust
completely the idea we simply find
ourselves moved to that interaction as it
moved to that interaction as it
automatically to us feels like there is
a connection whether we immediately
understand what that connection is or
not is not necessary that is the idea of
trust like us trusting our intuition yes
like us trusting our intuition yes
completely and isn't it true that as
we're all connected you could you could
do the same thing again right now with
anybody and know that it will just come
out all connected as long as you're not
watching for
it that expectation is what in your
terms let us say throws the
wrench into the
spontaneity I mean if if we are watching
for it as we're creating but what if I'm
watching for it as you're creating in
this way you may perceive the idea but
also understand that as you allow
yourself to cocreate an understanding in
that way then recognize that you will also
way then recognize that you will also
simultaneously surround yourself with
the same degree of
synchronicity so be prepared
be prepared for
ecstasy quickly the first yeah the first
uh half of the the show tonight I I
started to go into a trance feeling and
felt a lot of pressure in my heart
chakra area and felt like if I let let
myself ego self get out of the way I
would have channeled something I wanted
to know if that would be uh I I blocked
it or U kept it from we can assist you
in any interaction in that way feel free
to speak up in that sense allowing
yourself to know that in your terms it
is something that would be an enjoyable
exchange and we will assist in allowing
you to recognize that you can become
familiar with that portion of your
consciousness of course it is a part of
allowing yourself to be the
idea quickly yes I just came pass a term
this week that I likeed a lot called
imagineering all right I I thought it
was connected to social engineering as
you were explaining it on Wednesday
night in a sense almost directly
imagineering is how you create your
physical reality thank you I'd like to share a
reality thank you I'd like to share a
joke with you all right you can take it
home to your friend um uh if it
translates okay
where where do Essen sonans keep their
armies in their [Music]
sleevies it's a
language thank you
[Music] [Laughter] [Laughter]
[Music]
he's still laughing [Music]
do you he
that you all of you each and every one
of you can you
feel that you
have been and done
done
many many different
things can you
know that all of the connections that
you make
including in what you construct to be
the idea of your
humor allows you the opportunity in
centering within that humor to recognize
the symbology that allows you in that moment
symbology that allows you in that moment
the reflection the tapping into the
experience the life the lives the
situation that go back in your terms for thousands
that go back in your terms for thousands
upon thousands of your
years can you feel the
wealth of
experience of knowledge of
understanding of
wisdom of
laughter of life as
life as
you a allow yourselves to form a
bridge between
yourselves and other
Consciousness and your own expanded
Consciousness within your love of life
and laughter laughter
understand you
have the
foundation the foundation and the
support of all that you have already
been to allow you to
know that it is all
right to begin to make
light of the
idea of Love of
life and that your essence by
by
nature is the
Ecstasy of knowing the Ecstasy of
sharing of centering of being your
being your
willingness to
begin your willingness to be
equal and share with
us in your
terms your
loving
friendship is a
gift to
us for which we will find no words in
any language
except in
that which we share with you as our
deepest and most
sincere unconditional
love to each and every one of you
individually and
collectively we love you we thank
you and together we are the sharing
that continues forever in the Eternal
now we bid you a fond and loving good
night everything everything
go
than you you're
welcome told you
[Music] something he told me
something he told me
something communicated something to
May well all I ever get are images and
feelings and pictures so I wouldn't
necessarily know when one of them stood
out as a something about where you go
when you're not here something about you
you're not here something about you
challing to other um other civilizations
darl you
darl as what you're doing here the only
thing that yeah that that's manifested
there in the same okay well the only
thing I can get as an impression of what
you're talking about the image that
comes back when you say that is like um
the image I remember is like
seeing like four blue
spheres each one a little higher than
the next and like some sort of like a
silver liquid pouring out of the top all
the way down the
line exactly what he said and he said
that fourth uh whatever you call the
fourth identity was that was it how you
were getting it
what you're describing is very closely
exactly what he was saying
okay very good now