and your
collectivity for which you
all come on any gathering and given any
recognition of any portion of the
mass as part of the
process in this life to remember who and
what you are recognize that all of what
you call in your ideation
learning is the process of remembering
who you are. For the ideas that you have
created in this physical reality has
been the idea of being able to forget
who you are that what you have been
exploring for many thousands of years.
Now you are the ending of this cycle of
exploration in that way. Now therefore
you have created the idea in your
consciousness of what you call new age
awareness. This is simply your symbol to
reflect that you are going through a
transformation. This
transformation is simply one of defining
yourself a new recognizing more of
yourself that already exists. becoming
more aware of more of your being, more
of your
consciousness. Remembering that you
agreed individually and together to
create this which you recognize as your
physical reality and to project
ourselves into it for the purposes of
exploring the idea of limitation, the
idea of separation, which is to do one
more way. And all that is of expressing
itself. You are
remembering but you know everything you
need to know. You are remembering but
you are in a case for God.
You see your reality that you see around
you. See yourself reflected in that as
if it is a
360°. What you perceive as your physical
reality which surrounds you in which you
think you exist is a projection from the
center of your
being from the screen you have built
around you to cut yourself off from the
rest of
your way has been yours experiment. You
are no one experience what
you're this is your
reality. This is your dimension.
Now we other civilizations and other
concept level or what we call
density are now able to lend to a
certain extent to a certain extent with
some assistance in your recognition or
remembrance of what you are. But only to
the point that it does not feel with
what you have to see.
It is a
transformation upon your plan. This big
the transformation of consciousness from
third to
fourth. The raising of your vibrational
level so that you will create more
awareness of more of yourself. Have more
of yourself present in an energetic
relationship. And in this way, gather to
yourself all that you have ever been in
this entire
exploration that you have called your
life, your mind within what you call
your third plane of experience.
connected in a sense to you all. Any
other civilization that is interacting
with you is connected to you through
consciousness. We have all cocreated
experiences that are manifesting in your
lives. simply
because we
can recognize that many of you on your
planet because you are coming out of
what we call the habitual ritual of
separation and
limitation have come up with the idea
that your life to be lived means a
specific person and in a sense it does
but many times not
You individual personality construct
that you have created yourselves to be
in this life.
Now that
that
completely that is your purpose to be
exactly completely who and what you have
told you to be. That is your purpose.
Being true to
yourself. Living with the conviction of
knowing what you are all
about. Allowing yourself the freedom of
expression without judgment, without
invalidation to express yourself fully
as the being that you are. If you
bend to living
as the complete
facet that you are of the
multi-dimensional crystal that is all
that is and in being fully
yourself, you then extend to fill your
universe, your particular facet. And by
extending still your fashion and not
withdrawing and cutting yourself off, do
you allow yourself to then along those
shoulder lines touch all other
facets and feel the connection that you
have to everyone else to everything else
in all that
is your
Are you alive?
All right. Sure. Somebody else invest.
In a sense we will pick up from time to
time as you say what we call a signature
vibration but recognize this to our
perception you are not a discrete
personality you are may
I always becoming a new evil
But at the same
time, is it a combination of Yes.
Yes.
But again, many times your perception of
our interaction is simply based upon the
type of interaction that is necessary
with that individual and not the idea of
recognizing who they think they are, who
they think they need to be, but
interacting with them in the now as a
[Music] new uh Well,
[Music]
because understand this many times we do
that because your people in your
civilization do not realize that when
they say a certain thing they do not
think they mean it literally but many
times they lie literally to the letter
of what they say.
Therefore, we simply give them an
opportunity to hear themselves. For in
this way, if they pay attention to the
ideas they are sharing, many times they
can automatically see the answer as to
why their lives are the way they are. uh you
uh you
do each
other and so that you [Music]
know one other thing to recognize again
that there may
be other individuals who may share
similar ideas with you other
of the interaction but what you are
speaking of for now is your
protection you will find that there are
other individuals who will have a
opposite protection they have said many
times regard no matter where I am you
always recognize me the opposite of what
you are saying it does not matter that
way and one other thing in a sense
remember this but we are communicating with
this but we are communicating with
you. And though we are connected in many
ways, you are all your own
expression. I am also my own expression
for my
own in a sense not to mean that any is
better or worse, more or less, but
simply different. Nor modes of thought are
different. Nor modes of thought are
quite alien to me. My moment of thought
are quite
alien and more and more as we
commun and create.
uh around those
times here. Yes.
Yes.
But again many times to us again it will
not matter. The idea that an individual
shares an idea with us doesn't
necessarily mean that we must make a
distinction as to exactly who that
indiv.art or
or
invalidation of you know exactly the
truth came from it experience a fair and
there is not a separation of individual
in that
way but why do you make it why did
it
only have to [Music]
And so by each other
now
understand it to know someone if you
love them on our planet.
If you love each other, you will know
each other.
That's could you share with us some of
the folklore and legends in your planet
history perhaps when you were in density
and
emerging that there was a time let us
say comparable to where you are now
Well, we would a man think the idea of
what you have created to bring major
country in this way in our what you call
history. We simply created them as an
experiment and it was not necessary to
that any particular what you call
ideology had to become fixed.
Therefore, we created on purpose as you
would say different completely different
societies so that we could observe in
each one of the experimental societies
those things that in your term work for
them. We allowed them to be a period where
We allowed them to be a period where
individuals that had lived in one
society would then completely transfer
to another
society. And as you said, vice versa. So
that they now got used to a new set of
rules and saw how the habits they had
formed in one nation could or could not
transfer to the structure of another.
This allowed us through our
determination to recognize what was
essential for
coexistence. For what did not function
from one to another, we had no resource.
For if we were to function as one
planet, then all the conditions had to
satisfy all
individuals within a
given. This then was our history of
nations. But there was no war. Finally,
one was free to go to many nations to
live in those conditions and to find out
for themselves what remained or what was
enhanced or added to the condition to
which they were used to and add to the
overall knowledge in this way of what
was born what we have now with this one.
evolutionary physiologically. No,
but in this way recognize the overall
purpose to begin with of our
civilization did not carry with it the
same extent of limitation that you chose
to experiment with on your planet. Now
intellect much so much higher intellect.
Let us say we started out notification nor
notification nor
civilization is simply the scenario that
you choose to
create. You may not start out with some
equivalent to like in our society we started out
to like in our society we started out
originally in an evolutionary process
until we also had a time special
we also had a time special
non-technological but in this way still
there was always a recognition of the
connection connection with all that is
and all that is the different extent and
different interpretations but never to
the extent and on your planet of
completely
forgetting yes but we have
had no clue that you call your
fail it is not a matter of avoiding you
are assuming that something like that is
not you as a civilization have chosen to
experience the idea of warfare. It is
not as common as it is notable. It is
only inevitable to be because of the
scenario we started out
with in that scenario it is. But our
scenario is not that way. Understand
that when you were
non-physical as a group consciousness
before you enter into the physical of
your own free will of your own choice
you decided what you were going to
lay down that foundation and the
projecting of your consciousness into it
and then allowing yourselves as
consciousness embodied in matter to
experience the specific type of
physiological evolution that you didn't
think based upon the structure you had
formed is what led to the society we now
have. Our inquisition into matter carried with
Our inquisition into matter carried with
it to begin with a different concept
from the beginning. These concepts of
civilization in physical form on planets
are determined
previous heard you say that our best
procedure is to be who we are. Okay.
Now, it's hard for me to conceive of
being anything else but what I am. Very
good. So what is there to you're
implying is something that came
mentioned and another idea of which is
still but in the idea of more awareness
of more of
your well isn't that part of who I am at
this moment the way you are doing it for
you. So there there's no striving no no thank
So there there's no striving no no thank
you
there's no intention to learn
necessarily to grow there is intention
to grow but not to struggle or have you
seen you can live and create in the way
and as you created new moments you
will so far that there's no way of doing
anything wrong. There is no right and wrong.
wrong. There is no right and wrong.
There are ideas you let us say to use
your terminology in a sense may
find maybe less preferable or more
preferable without judging. You can know
what you prefer. You don't have to
invalidate something to know that you
can something
else. But it's simply a matter of
pleasant choosing. You have the ability
to choose anything which for when you
allow all possible choices to be equal.
Then it is easy to choose from among
them with concern without having to
invalidate or lower any of the other
choices or put any of these choices
higher than yourself so that you must
struggle to attain them. They're all on
the same level. Everything is equal.
You always have the free will to be
different in any way you do. And that is
the idea
of recognizing the infinite diversity
that you are as a single [Music]
[Music]
ide I am aware that I have chosen to set
up critics of myself. That's right. That
is who I am. This is who I am. All
right. So that leads to a sense of
imbalance with inner struggle. All
right. Do you prefer that you or do you
prefer to be another you? I don't have a
reference for another you. Yes, you do.
It is called your
imagination. Now what you do you imagine
you will someday be that you would
prefer to be you are
now? Do you have a sense of that at all?
Then in the second you perceive that you
are it, you are that you until you
decide to go back to the other
you quickly
created. You are underline this one.
You are the
creator. Your thoughts are reality.
Yes, you are all that.
As many as you wish.
No, I am now not the you the moon that
created that. I am now the you who knew
that [Music] something question
something question
in the our in respect to what you're
saying as a society as a whole our
society going through this huge
transition and this time of turmoil and
there it's like uh extremely polarized.
Yes. That is the idea of physical reality
That is the idea of physical reality
that you have created to experience
polarity. It is one of the defining
terms of physical.
Yes. And now it seems like it's going to
a very critical well crisis time. All
right. Now it's building. Say it is
reaching critical mass. But that does
not mean you have to experience it in a
crisis manifestation. If you are willing to
manifestation. If you are willing to
change the habit of how you look at
things, you can begin to believe that
you do not have to go through a trial by
fire in order to feel like you deserve
happiness.
Yes. Here's a complication, right? All
right. Let's say someone uh let's say me
have my head clear on this. And then
meanwhile, yay. the rest of let's say
our country and this whole polarized war
mechanism and all the people who watch
Rambo and all etc etc are going at it.
Yes want to get sucked into the whole
mess. Not if it is not you understand
this pay attention you are your own
universe. Do you know what I mean? Take me
Take me
literally. You are your own universe.
You are your own
reality. You
vibrate to ideas. Ideas vibrating to
your level become the reality you
experience. Now, if
you were in your terms the only one to
were in your terms the only one to
vibrate at the level where you do not
contain the idea at all of what you call
war. You would be the only one who would
see another world. The individual you
would interact with would not accept the
idea of war or it would not exist for
them either. Understand this.
Each and every one of you exists on all
the different levels that there are to
exist upon in all the different
variations of the world that there is to
exist within all the same
time. When you change your level of
vibration, you let us say by analogy
tune yourself to a particular frequency
or band width. It is then only in that
bandwidth that your experiences come
from. They cannot come from a bandwidth
you do not
function. Therefore, since everyone is
on every level, then the portion of the
individuals that already exist on that
level are the individuals you will be
interacting with. But understand it is
not that the original so to speak
individuals have changed. It is that you
have changed. You have taken yourself to the
changed. You have taken yourself to the
level where now you only perceive the
portions of everyone else that also only
exist on that level. And in that level
the world is the idea that does not
contain war. So that is
only I don't understand
how I understood it. Yes. If war starts
and we majority is one dimension then
how do we not get
vaporized all you are making the I'll
say assumption that there is only one
reality understand this you are actually
literally a separate
reality the fact that you seem to share
similar ideas is only because of your
dream
You have agreed to do so. When you do
not agree to do that anymore, you will
not individually have something [Music]
[Music]
moment. You are disappeared.
You are constantly recreating the idea
of the
moment so quickly recognize that there
is
break. Thus in the very next moment the
idea of you and what you are you
could vanish from this reality and be in
another one. Now to you, whatever level
of acceptance you have within yourself,
whatever way will not be a shock to you.
You will perhaps not feel like anything
different has happened. But all of a
sudden, everyone around
you, not talking about the same things
they were talking about yesterday.
What's going on? Am I going crazy? Well,
in a sense, yes. That is what insanity
is. Simply experiencing of an alternate
reality that is not the mass agreed upon
reality. It is no less real than what
you have previously to be the real
reality. For what you think of as the
real solid reality is only the product
of your imagination, the product of what
you believe your reality should be. And
so that is when you change the idea of
who you are and the ideas you
contain, you will change the reality you
for you are created in no
one. It does look that way. It is only
the degree to which you are willing to
believe that that will allow you to hear
the changes going on around you.
However, let us say quickly or slowly we
can accept the
change. If you accept the change in an
instant, the reality would change for
you in an instant. Maybe not for someone
else. But you have then in a sense gone
into one dimension. They have gone into
whatever. And the reality you experience bit by
And the reality you experience bit by
bit becomes more the reality you want to
experience because and only because
first of all you were willing to act
like that reality and take yourself to
that bandwidth by acting like that reality.
The idea that we call unconditional
love is that which is all that is. It is
the essence of existence. It is what
supports the universe. It is what you
recognize as the energy of
knowingness. the energy, the
willingness to know that you
contain all and that you are contained
in all.
That is what the idea of war is.
Not so much anymore. ago. I recognized
that there were at times similar to that
idea. More not so much I'll say myth,
more what you may
call. All right.
experimented with the
idea of what you call
in the early
attempt there were
individuals who were not let us
say into a unification of the vibration of
into a unification of the vibration of
our taken upon
themselves the
idea that once they would partake in
such an experiment, they would be
released and free to go where they
wish. When it came time for that
individual to be born a craft, that
would initiate what you call hyper
dump. Of the many individuals aboard the
craft, when it arrived at the other end,
one was no
longer. And it
was from that
day in the
fable way
assumed that the individual became the
path that we had traveled and expanded
himself into the universe and that now
we travel within him upon him and he
died our way.
very shortly thereafter in turn with the
he understand that the individual
think had allowed the opportunity to
transfer himself to another dimension of
reality to track down the timeline
eventually and discover what happened
but then all we realize but add long
since reincarnated many
times for the end of the
still existed for quite some time as
something to be felt so that when we
went to the stars, we always knew there
was always a piece of us
already. So we would read ourselves
everywhere we went.
like that story.
Because we have now become our
we are living
our for to us imagination is probably
Daniel for one and then
Before you go on, allow me to say the
idea in an overall sense of spiritual
leader is a
contradiction. For those that know that
they are spirit and know that everything
is spirit do not need to be, but we
understand the context in which we're so
by all means.
I was wondering whether Yes. And I
agree. I wonder whether these what we
call spiritual needs were people
forgiven as you said before thought who
understood what they were were willing
to go to the first of their own
realities and then immediately or very
very quickly had other people following
that we've heard about many people going
into their reality once that was a
concept you were speaking about
question yes so they experience their
own reality becoming manifest
in the world around me. I've never heard
about it.
Um, I'm aware of a being named Dana and
I'd like to know if you have any
information that you could share with me
about who he is. And in so far as I am a
part of the sisterhood of the
What do you mean the curious energy?
uh of the ocean. Yes. But also of the
star system period
perhaps. I'm not aware of that. But how
do you feel about that star system?
Uh my stomach is
vibrating. Perhaps it has a cold. Yes.
Right. Can you clue to the idea of what
we call the VA in the sense that it is
partaking in an energy way? Let us say
of an energy field living in an energy
field.
Can you say that another way perhaps?
That the being when it thinks of itself
thinks of itself as a quasi plain all
reality quad matter being that exists in
an energy field which is at once an
extension of itself and at the same time
should support medium of all its bre and
yes this at this time is our perception
this at this time is our perception
Thank you. Why do you want to
in your civilization? Do you have a
position between the sexes into male and
female? Yes. And if you do, what is your
matter of procreation? And similar to
and in what way have you resolved what
at least in my own life is a certain
disharmony which exists in our
civilization between the different
sexually by marrying the male and female
energies within each and every one of
them. Yes. Uh
yes. Each and every one of
you are polarized idea of what you call
male and female energy. Yes. Yes.
Positive and negative. You understand?
By
allowing those energies to blend and
balance within each male, within each
female, do you then marry the idea in
that way so that you are
complete and do not need to create
relationships in order to feel complete.
Not knowing yourself to be complete to
begin with can create relationships with
which you can share
equally for you both contain the
equality of the whole.
Yes. If that were to be achieved, would
we see a different manifestation of of
the marriage? Would marriages even be
necessary the way they currently are?
Perhaps not. In our civilization, every
being is married in a sense to every
other being in the
civilization. All children though they
recognize they are what we call
biological parents are the children of
all and all are parents to all
children. And we are connected in this
way in love with each other. There is no
need to worry to wonder where the
children ever
are for we always know where they are
and they are always with their parents.
Now individuals may create different
variances of relationships from
time but again it is simply a
recognition that
relationships even what you call upon
your planet
matter simply serve specific purposes.
Some of these
servings can go on for the physical
life. Some do not. Depends upon the
reasons for which you have created the
ideas. Still, we do not put expectation
or judgment upon the relationship that
it must be such and such or so and so.
We enjoy the relationship for what it
is. For we know that our physical
reality and every situation in it is
attracted by us and thus is a reflection
of what we are choosing to
experience. There are no interruptions.
There are no wrong turns. You are never
off your path. You are not even on a
path. You are the path. You cannot be
off your in relationship things cannot go
your in relationship things cannot go
wrong. Everything that occurs is the
part of the agreement that the two
people created and attracted themselves
together. In
return, for we are again but in this way
we are beginning to understand in that
sense in a sense you do not have to. Now
to a degree we still have some of the
idea in third density aspect of
ourselves of the
limitation of that because we are
interacting with your society and other
societies and so must maintain a portion
of ourselves in the density in which we
can do so. Therefore, the density that
you would recognize, so to speak, as the
one you would communicate with, the
reflection, the version of ourselves
that you would recognize as a physical
being that you would be talking to if
you were face to face, live in your
terms, what is loosely translated, about
300 of your average lifespan.
Now however we do not
age so much as we mature to a certain
point and then maintain and simply when
the person is served for the physical
life same way you do into the other
plains of existence the less
physical and then we make our choices as
do you for what you want to
In our civilization, first of all, the
idea of communication with the entity to
be born is ongoing before the physical
birth. When the child comes, there is a
period of a climate ideation for a being
that has been non-physical to learn to
be physical again. But it is
approximately, let us say, three of your
years. At that stage, they are still in use,
At that stage, they are still in use,
but they have the cognet to communicate
anything they need to. And we can go on
about exploring the world, winding up
where they need to be to learn from
whoever they need to learn from whatever
it is they need to learn to serve the
purpose. in our society.
It was simply misunderstanding back.
Yes. I'm interested in imagination
creativity. Oh, very good. Okay. Is
there is there some way imagination make
no
there's a way to allow or stimulate
planetary creativity and imagination to
be exponential at the time or in your
own what say fourth dimensional
density. Live that way in your own
imagination and you will begin to
attract others who do the same. And by
being that type of an example, you will
offer the opportunity to others to see
the effect in you and therefore choose
it if they also think that would be a
good idea for
them. By being the reality you imagine
you would like to see on your world, you
give others in your world the
opportunity to share that reality with
you. But it is always their choice. You
cannot force them to say. But that does
not matter because as we said when you
change they will
seem because you will only be
experiencing the facets of those beings
that represent the level upon which you
now exist. So you will
how do you define imagination? It is a
dimension of
creation and
indeed in your terms because of the
separation let us say at best all a
lifting of
probability things that can become
because you are in time with your
framework. Things will to some extent
because of your agreement still take
time sometime much time. But the way to allow
sometime much time. But the way to allow
them to take the least amount of time
necessary is to act
like that existence that you desire to
exist already does exist
in then you will be opening yourself up
to the allowance of those things to come
to you to be attracted to you as quickly
as they can. or you will not be closing
any door through which there could come
by assuming that this is something that
can only happen somewhere in the future.
And when you assume that what you want
in your life is something that will
happen in the future instead of in the
now, it stays in the future because you
are creating the future from the
present. And you are creating the past
from the present. The present is the
only time in which you ever experience
yourself. This is true for your past and
future as well. The present is the only
time in which you exist. Now is it.
That's it. Now, here and now. Right now,
right here. Everything you have ever
been, everything you will ever be to use
your terminology is all right here.
Right now. up. If you can imagine it,
you can be it right
now. Because when you imagine it, you
are vibrating at that level. You cannot
perceive or conceive what you do not
conceive. You cannot imagine
nonexistence. Everything you imagine is
Everything you imagine is
real and only the degree of willingness
that you are willing to have makes it as
real as you are willing to
be. Does that clarify the ideal someone?
I was looking I said that if everybody
behaved that way then everybody attracts
some sort of creative vibration on the
planet which makes the
planet exponentially creative. One
moment one moment a couple points. If
you alone act that
way completely, the planet you will perceive
completely, the planet you will perceive
will reflect your own exponential
allowance because you are your own
planet. You are your own reality. [Music] [Music]
a
paradox paradox to you. But understand
that paradox the idea the ability to see
dichotomy polarized positive polarized
negative seeming opposite understand of
the ability to see both sides comes from
you in the center and therefore
somewhere in you both of those seemingly
opposite ideas are blended because you
are projecting the ability to see them
both. But you know that the ability to
see them both means you have the ability
to contain them both without one
one
moment. Do you wish to explore the
imagination idea a little bit further or
is it becoming clear?
Um I I'm I'm sorry I didn't ask so much
as a personal question. I'm working for
some All questions are personal.
Everything is subjective. Everything is
subjective. You do not need to be
concerned about anyone else. By being
completely who you are, that is how you
will serve everyone else.
by giving them the opportunity to see in
you personally how you manifest the idea
of
imagination. That is how you give others
the opportunity to be served by
[Music] you. Is it becoming clear at all?
you. Is it becoming clear at all?
Are you sure?
I'm working. I'm working. Why? Why
should you work hard?
I'm happy with that. All right. You
can't be happy with anything. Anything
at all.
Now the idea of other
individuals simply is that you do not
need to be concerned for them. You do
not need to be responsible for them in
the sense of worrying what is going to
happen to them. For them, you are taking
responsibility for their choices upon
your own
shoulders. You are responsible to them,
not for them. What's the difference? By
being who you are, you fulfill your
responsibility to them to do your part.
By worrying about what they are
choosing, you are taking responsibility
for them, which means you are taking
their power away.
Yes, that's the difference. I
think the real
state is it is all real. But we have
said that to use your terminology, your
analogy, the dream state is more the
awake state because you are more aware
of more of yourself in the nonvisible
reality. And the physical reality is
more the dream state because it is where
you limit your experiences to a specific
ideal. The physical reality is more like
what you normally think of as a dream
state because it is a highly focused
experience and you are not awake to the
rest of yourself. You are to focus in
this life and that is the dream you have
chosen to
live. That is why in fourth density you
will begin to live your dream reality.
The idea of what you call
dreaming. When you wake up you remember
a dream. You are creating that in the
physical world to make the best sense
you can in symbols you understand of the
experience of yourself in a non-physical
reality that is limitless.
Therefore, when you do not create such a
differentiation between the dream self
and the physical self, when you blend
the two through your imagination, which
is the bridge and the link and the
conduit between the dream self and the
physical self, then you will begin to
live your dreams. And you do not need to
have a
creation of a symbolic reference that
you call a dream. You will never wake
up. You will always be dreaming. You
will always be living. One will flow
into the other and there will be no
separation. Then you will know that you
truly can do anything for you know in
your dream you can do anything.
That is an accurate representation. That
sense is an accurate representation of
the experience of being out of your body
and recognizing your unlimited
multi-dimensional creative step. [Music]
[Music]
It can be it can be in our perception.
The first step would be to not create
the idea that there is a
first because you are assuming that
there is a process you have to go
through to get there rather than simply
knowing you already are
there. The creation of steps go
ahead. It is very valid. It's very
significant. If that is your way of
doing things then that is how you do
things and that is your gift and that is
your expression and that is your
creativity and that is the purpose you
are serving. But if you are aware that you
serving. But if you are aware that you
can choose other methodology, then we
simply suggest to you that the quickest
result will come through not needing to
think that you need to take steps but
that you are already there and allow
your life to show you that you are
already there. By becoming the ecstatic
explosion of
coincidence that reflects in physical
terms the simultaneity of existence, you
will attract all the opportunities, all
the situations, all the people, all the
things when and where you need to.
Exactly. What a
coincidence. Yes, it is a coincidence,
but not an accidental one.
Then you simply act upon what you have
attracted. Attract attract
Attract attract
attract. That is how you grow.
Attract. No.
Attract. This is really.
Your process, whatever your imagination
comes up with is tuned to
you. That is what it is for.
Thank you very much. You are welcome.
Yes, you
open. Guys,
I'm a um crystal healer from Hawaii and
I've been living totally my imagination
and all my dreams are manifesting
absolutely clearly. It feels like it. My
life is a total playground. I have
anything I want. Well, my body's going
wild because I want to ask you
something. Okay. I've had this idea
because about 12 years ago, I had a
hyerectomy and I would never be able to
have children. And I'm going to be
marrying this very beautiful man who is
very Christlike in a way. He's we all
are of course the tone service. That's
who we are.
I want to know what you had to say about
this idea that I have that someday I
will have an
immaculate. I know. All right. Very
good. Simply the being you can attract
in this
way will be able to partake of your body
in that way has to project itself
directly into what we call your new
structure and
activate the process of evolution in the
evol. Now likely it will be female.
Therefore, likely not that it has to
be. But in this
way, simply since that idea in your
imagination is a possibility, then it is
a reality that can be real in your
fourth density world.
Now it has happened from time to
time in force but manifest in her. Now
her. Now
also has happened in a sense the other
way around. You will find that there are in
around. You will find that there are in
your planet many ideas about
pregnancy that seem to be what you call
normal pregnancy. And yet when it comes to what
pregnancy. And yet when it comes to what
you call terms, there is no
child. For the child has experienced the
third dimensionality of birth only to
the extent it needed to and is born in
another density.
[Music]
I almost get it but I didn't exactly
simply this trust that the idea you are
creating is a real reality in fourth
century and that it may not be such an
I'll say abnormal method of giving birth in
say abnormal method of giving birth in
your future.
[Music] Now the idea of our procreation has
Now the idea of our procreation has
contained that idea many times to
understand that though there is to some
extent the idea of what you call the
physical interaction, it is more of an
energy pattern. And in this way it is
the exchange which sets up the
vibrational pattern, the electromagnetic
fluid out of which the third entity can
partake of and form its physicality in
the room.
So that cleared up a little bit. So then
I asked the house.
You can. You do not have to, but you
can. Well, now understand that there have
Well, now understand that there have
already been many individuals in your
society that have been told in no
uncertain terms by your medical
profession that they cannot have a
child. And they have had many simply
because you choose the timing of the
agreement with that child. And if it is
not the timing to have children before
that child, nothing you do will have a
child. Nothing. After that time, nothing
you do will prevent the child. For there
have been a many children again as we
have said where medically
physiologically the women have been told
you cannot have a child. It will not
happen. It is not
possible. Oh couple years later
doctor I am having an impossible time.
[Music] Yeah, the timing is what creates the
Yeah, the timing is what creates the
ability to create that idea. But when
you are the
being that is the being that has made
the agreement with that being, there
will be nothing stopping you. Thank
you. All right. Do you wish to take a
short break or do you wish to continue?
I do not need one.
All
right. I I would like if you could help
me understand my understanding of the
transition in the process of making with
you. Um
I my understanding is that I'm in
process of blending myself.
Oh, right.
And I find
myself persistently
persistently
perceiving that uh pain of separation.
And I pick thoughts along the lines of
Jesus Christ. If I
imagine the sentence and the sense of
completion, then I can allow it to to
[Music]
experience what I label
[Music] as I know.
Why? What situation? What ideas allow
you to create the idea of play?
I seem to have a belief
that
I have a belief that somehow distances
me.
Why do you think you have that belief?
Why do you believe you have
that? What does it do for you to have
that belief?
I don't know how it serves me the
[Music] consequences. Do you think
consequences. Do you think
perhaps let us just play around with
this problem that one reason for having
the belief that creates pain is so you
will know that you are tired of creating
pain. All right. Are you tired of
creating pain? All right. Then take a deep
pain? All right. Then take a deep
breath and let it
out. Now in this moment right now, are
you willing to believe? You do not have
to create pain in order to understand yourself. Good. yourself. Good.
Now
understanding understanding standing
under
support yourself as you are. You are
taking support for
yourself. You are not
under yourself
literally. You are removing the idea
that the experience you are going
through in the way you are going through
it is not the way that you should go
through. It does not fit your freedom
notion of how you think it should feel
to blend the energy.
Lighten up on
yourself. Relax about how you have
chosen to do these things. And in that
second of relaxation, you
will remove the idea of separation.
Remove the idea of loss and remove the
idea of pain. Now all pain physical and
emotional and mental, all pain is the
result of imposing a separation
between yourself and the all that is
that you
are. If you truly understand yourself,
you will support yourself as you are in
any given moment totally.
That total unconditional you say
unconditional unconditional love is what will serve
unconditional love is what will serve
you is what will come back to you is
what will support you is what will
nurture you nourish you
unconditional love. If you are willing
to love yourself as you are
unconditionally, then all that is will
be able to love you unconditionally as
well. And that will for you and you will
feel the love and feel the blending and
be the love and be the blending and live
your life.
No,
I don't know how to answer that. Yes or
no? [Music]
[Music]
Sometimes I'll allow a little
mainly there appear to be two levels of
my
life. There's at least a part of you
behind that that is always the product
of a belief system. The idea that you
believe that the idea that a part of you
can be ahead and a part of you can be
behind is real to you. Why put stock in
that belief system if you do not find
it? But you are consciously aware of it
right now. If you become consciously
aware of it, the process of integration
is over. Not.
You many times in your civilization
think that when you ask a question that
is the beginning of a process and so you
create a long process to discover the
answer. The action of a question is the
realization that you already contain the
answer for the question would never have
come up once again only because you can
only perceive that which you already
contained. a question if the answer is
separated for because you are used to
separating the answer from yourself. So
you put it out here and say well here's
a question but the only reason you can
say here is a question is because here
is the answer. This is a
mirror. Look at it and see the
reflection. If there's a question out
here then understand where the answer
lies.
Therefore, the idea of when you
recognize that you are doing a specific
thing, thinking a certain way, believing
a certain way, that is
enough of a recognition to know that
that recognition in of itself is the end
of the
process. You have integrated in that
moment. Only your
assumptions that there is something else
to
do gives you the idea of having to
create a long path which contains
struggle and pain and effort and oh my [Music]
[Music]
goodness in the moment you can see that
you have such a belief you don't even
know you know you have that belief Does
it serve you? Yes. No. If yes, keep
doing it. If no, do something
else. Create in your imagination a new
habit. Create a new habit and live that
way. This idea is now not
me. I am now this idea. Understand again
your imagination is real. Ideas are not
things that you have. Ideas are what you
are. Your reality is what you are. This
physical reality is
you. Then you know it does not come from
you. It is
you. It is you.
This room that you are in is you and you
and you and you and you and all of you.
Look how many rooms there are
here. Each has their own room and they
have agreed to a certain extent to share
that idea. But it is different slightly
different for
everyone. Just get two people to
describe the same situation.
This is an
indication although you have only taken
it as an idea of well let us say faulty
perception of a one real reality that is
not so it is actual perception of two
real realities three real reality four
and in
reality but it gives you the opportunity
then to understand the power that you
are and gives you the opportunity to
understand the reasons for why you
created things and then gives you the
opportunity to experience the things you
create for the reasons you created them
and not assume that you are missing the
point or that what has happened to you
does not fit into your life somehow. You
cannot experience an interruption to the
path that you are. Everything that
happens to you happens because of you.
And everything that happens in your life
is a reflection of the path you chose to
be. And if you think of it that way, if
you get into the habit of looking at
your life as an example of what you
believe you need to experience, then the
moment you allow the situation to serve
its purpose, it will then be able to
transform into something else. For you
will accept everything in your life as
you. And you will not cut off a portion
of yourself from yourself.
How are you?
For accelerating wide and understanding
of
good. I'm really enjoying imagining you.
Thank you. I am having a wonderful time.
Yes. I allowed myself to become the
idea. Oh my good. And ever since I had done
Oh my good. And ever since I had done
what kind you have a specific height or
simply the idea of abundance all the way
around all the way around plus a special
emphasis on my all right um ever since I
have done that the room I was in and the
world I have been in has been okay I've
experienced it you know physically
through my eyes um with a lot of nausea
and dizziness fever
and um an ongoing set of symptoms that
I'm not comfortable with. All right.
Now, all of these symptoms are
reflections, very typical reflections of
the idea of the acceleration into fourth
density. The reason you are experiencing
him in that way is simply because of
this. You contain still within you a bit
of the old belief that you still have
things to do to become a more
accelerated you.
You are
comparing a slower vibrational you in
the present with still a higher
vibrational you in the future. When you
have this dichotomy of comparison and
you bring these two ideas together, the
slower rate rubs up against the faster
rate and creates friction because of the
unidentical rate. This friction
translates into your bodily
consciousness as pain, disease,
temperature changes and all sorts of
things that reflect the idea of
resistance to simply being the idea
itself and not feeling like you are
being carried away against your will.
It is very slightly it will acclimate as
you become used to let us say in your
colloialism shifting your gears.
You, the you you are
now will feel at home spinning as fast
as the you you think you are becoming.
And then when you spin at the same rate
as the idea of your future self, then it
will be erased as you are comfortable.
Yeah, it is simply a slight adjustment
period because you are still connected
to everyone else here and you do not
want to get ahead of everyone you agreed
to share this experience with.
So you are I would say going full
throttle with your parking brake
on. That is what is creating the
friction, the fever and all the
[Music] finish. You will only ever go exactly at
finish. You will only ever go exactly at
the
perfectly worried get ahead, get behind
of anything. All of you have a breed on
the island that you call your own
destiny. They put that always on time.
You will not miss them. They will not
miss you. It is not possible by
definition. Yes. I have one more question. Um I have
Yes. I have one more question. Um I have
also recently man
manifested an experience of what I think
is energy. I saw clouds appear,
disappear, appear, disappear. And I felt
another density, either a ship or or a a
break in time space. Another dimension
through the cloud, like more of a
doorway, yes, than an actual craft, so
to speak. Yes. The idea again is simply
your cognizance of connection to the
idea of your future self and the
beginning consciously to form a
relationship with that you
[Music] my mind and personality seem to go into
my mind and personality seem to go into
a hyperactivity or panic
it feels left out it is not but simply
recognize this what you call your
personality is an artificial construct
not who nor what you are. Thus, it will
only always act as the instrument, the
vehicle that will channel whatever
energy you think yourself to be. Thus,
in this way, it will
vibrate with the idea of let us say the
doubts, lack of willingness, lack of
assurance, lack of trust. As you channel
the energy through yourself but are not
sure of the solidity of your own
structure, then the fragility that
exists in your mind with regard to the
physical body that you have and the
personality that you are will vibrate
and seem to start coming
apart. But it is only a reflection of
the idea that you carry within yourself
that you think you are going to die that
you think that there is a tolerance
limit. You are simply coming up against
the edge of your belief
system, but you will not break. You
are you are in
that way through that barrier to
relax. When you have the experience,
enjoy it for what it is. There's no need
to panic. The panic that you feel is
simply things that you have kept within you
things that you have kept within you
that are coming to the surface that you
are afraid to
face. Understand that is one of the
reasons why our civilization and many
other civilizations do not physically
land on mass on your
planet. The idea is that now again not
to think that we are better than you.
No, but the idea the idea that we
are in our energy fields around our body
around our presence contains the
allowance of completional unconditional
allowance of everything that we are.
when you come into contact with a being
such as upon your planet that in its
energy field has created gaps because it
has I'll say repressed parts of itself
that it is afraid to face when it comes
into contact with a more highly
accelerated field many time that highly
accelerated field will have a tendency
because of your co- agreement to
accelerate your field and bring those
pieces to the surface of service force
Being forced to face what you are not
ready to face causes
panic. And that is why many individuals
that have had let us say brief
encounters from time to time have come
away feeling they have seen one. Demons
they have seen their own reflection of
the people they are
not because they have
run that you are aware of.
Thus, you do not land until you see
yourself
at this is simply all you are
experiencing. Let it happen. It will not
go too fast for you. They know what they
are doing and you know what you are
doing. Trust that and the experience
will be something you will allow the all
right to live through and not run
from. All right.
And last but certainly not something
simply in this way. Again the idea of
the discussion of hiding something from
your attention. So the experiences that
you have must be hidden behind the
crowds since you know they come in a
sense from outside. What obscures the
naked face of that experience on the
cloud? In the same way, you have created
what you call the primitive habit of
finding fear when the source of your
life in past times being the sun was
[Music] obscured. Make the analogy in what we
obscured. Make the analogy in what we
call a primeval habit ingrained in you.
The idea that in recognizing the idea of
the source of your life and having it
obscured cause panic. I thought the idea
in this way that you are reversing is
simply that what you are not yet ready
to reveal yourself because you know that
it is the source of your self. You keep
it
covered so that you will see it a bit at
a time. Thus, it comes to you
symbolically from behind the clouds, so
as to allow you to peek at it until you
are ready to stand in the full light of
your own godhood. [Music]
There is connection that you for other
consciousness. Not third density, not
the third density aspect of those
consciousness. But you are forming that
connection from the purposes you chose
to do in this
[Music] life.
life.
Any connections that you are forming,
any connections you experience in this
life, whether it be the idea of point of
origin so to speak or interaction so to
speak, those interactions, those
recognitions are the result of the
choices that he chose to be in this
[Music] life. We got to clarify the idea.
Oh my years.
Um, so many of the things that you're
saying this evening seems to me that
there were different times in our in our
history and different places in Let me
clarify this in primitive societies on
our planet. I would think there was a
greater understanding of a lot of things
you're saying than in our modern day
society. If that was the case, why is as
a planet that we've done so much to
destroy those civilizations where it
seems like more of the truth that you're
communicating were were available.
Because in this way, simply it was your
decision to explore the idea of
selfation. So you would know that by the time this
So you would know that by the time this
has come around, now the time you are
now in, you will as a being within
creation have explored to the very end
of all density and absorbed for yourself
the understanding of all that all can be
even in the experience of human nature.
Understand that from the level from the
level that you chose to experience
limitation, the idea of limitation is
not a fearful one as you find it to be
what you
are because fear is one of the defining
terms of the
fear. Let us say so to speak that while
you knew what you were doing, you still
pride yourself as to the
extent to which you would forget who you
are. But this would be part and parcel
of being a creator simply because you
can do it. You do it because the creator
creates in any way, shape or form but it
can simply because it can. It does not
need a purpose to create because it
already existence
[Music] is. Therefore, anything that can occur
is. Therefore, anything that can occur
in it will for no other reason than
because it
can. Will that have answers?
Um the only thing that remains
incomplete about it is that there were
other ways of being. You are being all
those other ways too. Understand that
simply this particular way is one of the
ways that doesn't let you remember
that. That is all there is to it. You
are now beginning to remember that there
are other ways and you will remember
that you are living all those other
ways. [Music]
[Music]
Yeah. Well, it seems limiting because
this is the game you are. Well,
everything that you're saying this
evening is a sense that I've heard it
before. Yes. And that being the case, if
I have that capacity to forget, what
will prevent that continuous forgetting
to to continue? You are here.
The idea is that you have created for
yourself an opportunity to remember not
because it is me, but because you are
attracting to yourself opportunities to
remember. That in and of itself is the
indication that now is the time to
remember. And you are in synchronous
harmony with the civilization in which
you have placed yourself. For this is
the time of the transformation from
forgetting to remembering. And if that
is not what you wanted to do, you
wouldn't be here. So being here and
recognizing that that is what is going
on is in and of itself enough of a clue
to let you know that is what is.
Yes. Thank you. Thank you.
question.
It is possible
in now there are many ideas to this and
many of them will depend upon how you
view your reality your belief structure.
Understand again first and
foremost that anything anything you
experience in your reality even even
even communication vocally from you to
another physical
person even that is only experienced
because you are creating your version of
them to have a conversation with.
that extend even to people who have in
your terms
died. You can always create and do
create your version of them with which
you may always communicate. Even though
in the death experience there may be
aspects and facets of that
individual that in a sense are no longer
focused in physical reality and thus do
not really pay attention to your
communication but there will always be
one facet of them that will. Now that
experience of communicating with those
out of the body again only reflects the
symbology that you need to experience at
the moment because that's the belief
system that you have. You are always in
touch with every portion of
consciousness alive dead other alternate
dimensions other
civilizations other
time you are always in touch with all.
You can however create a
scenario in which you do receive
communication and interact with what you
perceive to be the specific persona so
to speak of the older soul that you
remember as the person you have known.
It is possible. Yes. Depend again upon
the reasons for
why and the needs for why and your
specific belief about how it is
possible. That will create the
interaction in whatever way is necessary
for you. And whatever way it does
happen, that is the way you chose it to
happen to reflect who you are.
It does not have to happen in a specific
way for you to know that it does
happen. [Music]
Now that you do not feel in touch
with why do you not feel in touch with
them simply because they are no longer.
I feel that the way I am in touch with
you now is just just my memory. Right?
But understand again your memory is
still present
creation. You are only confusing that it
exists within the time track of what you
call the past which to you is not real
and it is. It is real right now. You are
creating the
past. Therefore, memory is still present
creation in the now. Only your lack of
willingness to believe that your
imagination and your memory represent
real reality in the present keeps you
separate from that
consciousness. Now use your imagination right now and
Now use your imagination right now and
simply in your imagination open up
communication. Send your love first of
all for it is your love that will be
received. Now understand in that
level the love itself is the message and
there is no need for specific
differentiation of vocabulary and
alphabets. They receive your love. They
send you their love. That for them is
all the communication that is necessary
for they are all about their business.
They have been of service to you and are
still being of service to you. Simply
because you have agreed with each other
that one shall leave the physical plane
before another one does not mean you are
through your
relationship. The idea is that they are
being of service to you in the way you
both chose to have the relationship
continue. Because now the idea of there
being in another plane allows you to
stretch your senses and your imagination
and allow what previously was not real
to become real so that you know you are
still connected. That is the service
they are allowing you to perform if you
are willing to take it.
So reach out, feel them, know that they
feel it. And simply allow yourself to
feel them and know that you are feeling
them and that the way you are feeling
them for you is real and it is a real
reality and they are cognizant of it on
whatever level they have to be. But they
are also on about their business. for
the physical plane no longer concerns
them in that
way. You follow follow
what many
can be living in self-created realities
of different sorts, testing,
experimenting. They might be considering
the idea of reincarnation on your earth
or perhaps another civilization or not
reincarnating at all. There are many
opportunities and many options in this
way and until the choice is actually
made it is all the same. There is no way
to really know per se because they are
now a thought form in a world of thought
form and anything is possible and
everything is
real in that level.
Whatever you choose to perceive as the
reality that you are, that is what you
will experience. And to you, it will be
tangible. When you change your mind, the
reality will flicker like that into
something else. And that will be
tangible. That is one way of
experiencing the near after death
reality. Now, as you in your terms
ascend to higher and higher plane, you
become less and less physical and you
simply become not a dimension in which you
become not a dimension in which you
exist. You become the dimension itself
and experience all there is to
experience of yourself actually being a
dimension. For there are many adventures
outside of this
reality. This is not the
beginning and there never will
be for you.
Yes. Sounds color. Nice. Nice. You
Sounds color. Nice. Nice. You
specifically talk about using colored
light and gel in healing. Welter is very
creative and you already know that you
have your own symbology for what each
vibration represents to you in this way.
Our perception of the energy of your
mass consciousness generally thinks of
the idea of red as being applied to the
physical form as orange as applied to
the emotional form as what we call
yellow applied to certain levels of
mental awareness and green to higher
levels of mental awareness the
collective mental rather than the
individual mental and what you call blue
in this way to the spirituality the
electricalness of yourself in this way
and what you call the idea indigo, more
the collective fluid of the
consciousness itself and more the violet
being the representation of the overall
dimensionality of your godhood, creator
consciousness in this way, the over soul
self, the high vibration, the idea also
of ultraviolet infrared extending to
some degree into the aspects of other
dimensionality, alternate cells and the
infrared being subconscious mental
level, subconscious physical levels
those ideas your physiological band
spectrum in this way can be very
representative of this idea. Now those
are generalized terms. You will find
them basically similar from individual
to individual as we perceive the energy
of your civilization at this time. This
can change. Simply use your instinct.
Use your imagination. You will
understand what works. The individuals
that have attracted themselves to you
will understand what works. They will
hear themselves
in relation to adding sound to the
color. Simply feel your own tonality. And in
Simply feel your own tonality. And in
this way strike the core that resonates
within you. Hear what feels
you. Hear what feels
right. Allow the person that is
undergoing the healing to hear what
feels right. Now understand that this
idea in your fourth density reality at
the very beginnings of it when there may
be still a little bit of the idea of
separation can in of itself be all that
is necessary as one tool of healing for
what you can do is begin to recognize
each individual's
tone in an ideal state and when they
come to you you can sense how maybe the
tone is so to speak a little off little
Ah and in this way what you can do is
say all right here is your tone
now here is the tone you are when you
came to me when you were
healthy. All right. Now we will recreate
the tone. And when you allow your energy
field to resonate in a sympathetic
vibration with the tone of your ideal
state, then you will allow your energy
to align you all the way through and you
will simply be in your ideal energy
state and everything that is not a part
of the idea of your ideal state will no
longer be there.
Yeah. Are you familiar with the dim
method of using colors on specific
organs? Does that have validity?
Everything has validity for the
individuals who believe that it
does. Everything is a tool.
Everything. Allow your imagination to
realize whether or not you resonate
through that specific tool. If you do
not, that does not mean it will not work
for someone else.
But you can alter it with your
imagination or choose something else
completely different that will work for
you. Understand this is the great
frustration of your so-called
scientists. The idea of the need to
standardize everything and there is no
such thing.
Something which does not fit into the
scientific paradium can still work for
someone whose belief structure is
outside the scientific paradium.
I didn't get that
very an idea, a tool, a
methodology that does not fit into the
scientific pattern or let us say simply
one way of looking at
things. It will not work in the belief
structure that does not allow it to work
in. But that does not mean it will not
work in a belief structure that does
contain.
This is why you will find that many
times individual will be
healed regardless of what the doctors
say or they will remain sick regardless
of what the doctors say until they find
within themselves the idea that allows
them to accept their power of healing
themselves.
There is tremendous freedom within.
Yes, unlimited freedom.
Unlimited. There is no one way. There is
no one path. If there were only one way,
there would only be one
person. Look around you.
Yes. I understood you to say before that
there was uh no such thing as right or
wrong but only preferences. Did I
understand you correctly? You are
creating the concepts of right and wrong
from attitudes of judgment. But
intrinsically basically foundationally a
thing is not right or wrong. It simply
works for you or it doesn't. It simply
allows you to know you are
self-empowered as a creator or it
creates a feeling of powerlessness. But
isn't there something that is generally
desirable about something and generally
undesirable about other things? You can
again exercise your own preference. I
prefer this. But aren't there some
things that we should not be preferred?
There are no shoulds. Yes. But I'd say
that to me I'm not comfortable with
that. I understand what you're saying. I
made the same statement myself actually.
But I feel that um most of the time
murdering someone else is something one
should not do. It is not something that
is loving. That is in that way true. It
is not something that is
self-empowering. That is in that way
true. But understand this. It is still
the product of a
choice. The choice of the so-called
murderer and the choice of the victim.
so-called for it is the murderer's
option to not be attracted by the victim
but in terms yes but in terms of
desiraability I would still it depends
upon what your idea of yourself is I
understand your terminology let me
simply say this if your desiraability is
for recognizing yourself as all that is
then the idea so to speak direct
directly of dominating someone else and
forcing your reality upon them may not
be the most efficient way to go about
recognizing your own god.
No, but that is all there is to it.
I think I feel somehow that that was a a
dismissal of something I hold very dear,
a lecture. Why I feel it is a lecture I
follow the last 30 seconds, right? I'm
kind of clinging to the notion somehow
that it is desirable not to murder
people. Uh it is only desirable when
your desire is to love everything.
Yes. Okay. Therefore, if your preference
is unconditional love, then simply the
idea of murder is not in that reality.
And therefore, all right, in a sense, in
your terms, it is not desirable simply
because when you are unconditionally
loving, you find yourself never desiring
to murder.
In that way, it is not
desirable, but there is no need to put a
value judgment upon it. For again, each
and every one of you have taken lives
and each and every one of you have had
your lives taken. And all I do mean that
in other lives and all of that has still
gotten you where you are now.
Sure. The beginning of recognizing
yourselves as all that is and loving
yourselves unconditionally.
So while the idea of murder may have in
your term prolonged the time span in
which you forgot who you were, you still
are going to remember ultimately because
you cannot ever really be
destroyed for the reality that you are
now creating. The idea of murder is and
in a sense will be no longer a part. For
the idea of needing to do that to
someone else is simply the recognition
that you believe you are
powerless. For you are powerful enough
as powerful as you need to be to have
anything you want in your reality
without hurting anyone else to get it.
To feel like you must dominate someone
else is a statement that you are
powerless and that with regard to the
idea of recognizing your own godhood is
not something that when you are in your
own godhood you desire to
be sure I'd like to share something on
this uh the way I look at it and that is
that as as a spiritual being who can do
anything. We may select at some point in
time to experience what it's like to
experience murder and you all have or to
experience being murdered and you all
have simply because we can. Yes. So in
order to be murdered somebody has to do
the murdering. Yes. Which in that case
it could be actually a loving gift in a
sense. Yes.
Recognize that simply it is the product
of the value judgment of the idea of
victimhood. recognize that what you normally call a
recognize that what you normally call a
victim is also in a sense the murderer
because the victim is creating the
radiation that attracts the perpetrator
and thus in a sense the perpetrator is
actually the victim's victim
by falling into the victim's
trap. Thus it becomes very blurry in
that sense only in physiological terms
does it seem so cut and dried. But the
idea of the
emotionality that has created that
scenario is that simply when you are
through playing
victim, you will be through playing
victimizer. When you are through playing
victimizer, there will be no victim that
will call forth that attribute within
you. It is all one
event. All polarity, cause and effect,
it is all the same event.
Victimizer and victim are two polarities
of the same event, the same action, the
same energy, the same consciousness.
They are vibrating at the same reality
and they are in that sense yes being of
service to one another. If only to
realize that let us say in the next life
well we do not want to murder anymore.
We do not want to be murdered anymore.
So having the experience, let us know
that. Therefore, it served us. Now we
will create a life in which there are no
murderers. No murders. You follow me.
Thank you for your sharing. Nice.
Express itself in terms of literature or
experiences in a sense, but it is mostly
spontaneous. There is not so much the
idea you call written literature.
But there are the idea of acting out
spontaneously with groups that may arise
also spontaneously. There can be some
that are in a sense planned but again it
is mostly spontaneous in the same way
that many times I have in speaking to
you began our discussion with what you
usually call a
dissertation. I do not plan those. The
second I begin communication with you is
the first time I have ever thought of
those ideas in that
way in terms of how to communicate them
to you.
Yes. The dissertation is created
completely in the moment. I do not sit
up nights writing it out planning notes
cramming as you say. There is no need to
for simply being in the moment with
you allows me to ride the wave in your
reality and for you to ride mine and to
share and co-create an experience in
such a way that it reflects the perfect
timing of our interaction in whatever
way it has to. I simply ride those waves
and the ideas are there.
recreate your visitation
compos for they are the product of your
consciousness. What you perceive you
contain you are cocreating what I am
saying to you because all I am doing is
reflecting back to you what you already
know. My sensing is simply let us say my
My sensing is simply let us say my
art is simply allowing that knowledge of
you from you through me in a way that is
understandable to you.
Thank you.
But why are you
because I have chosen to be of
assistance to civilizations that have
requested assistance in this way. Also,
I am connected in many ways to what you
call the physical channel before you. We
have the idea of a relationship in the
sense that I in a
sense and the physical channel's future
self. The physical channel is the only life I
The physical channel is the only life I
have had on your planet. Though I have
many past lives on my
own. In this way, our bridge and link is
formed from lives on other planets,
other civilizations in what you call
times gone by. And our recognition of
the intensity of the focus and the
purpose of what was going on on your
planet or let us say what was about to
happen allowed us the opportunity to
attract ourselves to you so that we
could be of service in the way we had
chosen to be of
service. That is why you have allowed me
to be here and why I have accepted
you. to allow you to know that you are
all that is. So that in allowing you to
open up, in your choosing to open up,
then the universe for us becomes that
much bigger. How long ago did you feel
this request? I'm talking about hundreds
of
years, thousands of years. Let us say in
a sense only within my
lifetime but the specific focus of the
consciousness that set up the
circumstances are in your terms of
counting. Now this will be very nebulous
but in your terms of counting the setup
is approximately 175,000 of your years
old. Even though I have not determined
this until my
lifetime. In your terms
approximately
157 but this is basically meaningless.
Guys, can we go back to the victim
victimizer scenario if you wish? How
does the victim of of the action of the
victim mind or exercise themselves from
the pain
exorcise themselves from the pain right
by choosing to not be a victim by
choosing to not act like a victim by not
giving the power away but they've still
been victimized. So what that was then,
this is now. Every moment in time does
not have to be connected to the last
moment unless you determine that it
should be. Well, in your scenario or the
gentleman's scenario with the murder,
yes, that is in itself an ending in a
sense. But in many situations where
there is a victim and a victimizer,
there is no ending. The victimizer
continues to victimize the victim. Not
if the victim no longer acts like
one. Understand that because you have
created a repetition in the cycle of
your fear because you do not believe
that you are the creator of your
reality. Because you believe you are
inherently victimized by even being
alive. You are in the habit of assuming
that that is the only way life happens.
It is that habit of assumption that
allows you to continue to recreate
yourself over and over and over and over
and over again as a new victim to be
victimized one more time. Again, each
time a new moment yesterday, today,
tomorrow for all now. Yes. And
therefore, when you change the idea of
yourself in the now, then all of your
successive nows will not contain the
reality of being a victim. But it
doesn't erase what occurred yesterday.
Yes, it does. You are not understanding.
You create the past and the future from
the present. Memory is a present
present. Memory is a present
creation. Why do you think you call
absent-mindedness the product of genius?
The ability to be in the moment
completely alters the past.
You do not have to respond. Only because
you think in terms of linear time do you
think that what you call a past incident
is always going to hang around your
neck. One moment is not the last. And
the memory of one moment does not have
to be the memory of the
last. And that is just as real as the
moment you were a moment ago.
Well, I hear what you're saying. You
simply the idea of being able to create
a new past and agree.
No, I don't think I'll say that. I think
I can agree with that. The problem is
that I can't agree to erase the fact.
That is your choice. And the idea of the
definition of what you call a problem is
simply a situation you will not allow to
change shape. That is what a problem is. You
shape. That is what a problem is. You
fixate and focus upon an idea to such an
extent that you do not allow it to
transform into something else.
Therefore, that is the habit that
recreates the victimhood. But it's
possible also not to be a victim in
every sense, but just to be a victim in
one. Of course, any way that you wish to
create and experience the idea of
victimhood, you can do so. You are the
creator.
Are you true? Yeah, I'm true. Thank you.
Thank you very much. Yes.
All right. You may take a short break.
All right. I'm sorry. Sh.
Um, when we were speaking earlier, I
asked a question about Doda. Nice. And
you mentioned the gentleman named
Chupac. I did not mention other mention
but we confirmed the energy of what is
recognized in your radiation as the
consciousness in your terminology that
refers to itself by the sound
tonality also originates from the
serious system.
Okay. Um when
Um when
I when I spoke with you and got the
answer that I got with you, my body I
started to feel the
um the energy spiral. Yes. That felt
that feels very um primal to me. Nice.
And I'd like to explore more into it. I
have two feelings though that come up.
One is fear to move into all of that
energy. Why? Um I don't know how I can
survive it. Yes. Or feel um ease with
it. All right. Now, let me ask you a
question then. May I? Yes. What do
you do? You believe that you knew what
you were doing when you chose to be here
physically? Yes. Why should you assume
that you have stopped knowing what you
are doing? that you would have chosen
something to do in your life that would
not let you fulfill the purpose you
chose to be in this life.
Yes. Trust yourself. That is number one.
What is number two? Number two is the
feeling of excitement. Loving moving
into that feeling. Very good. And
wanting to live in that. All right. Now
understand that your excitement and your
anxiety it is the same energy viewed
through the polarization of your
physical reality. anxiety, excitement,
same energy. Choose which one you prefer.
energy. Choose which one you prefer.
Totally. Yes. You are simply giving
yourself the opportunity to see both
sides of that idea because you as you
move forward through yourself into more
awareness of yourself are always because
you are doing it from a physical point
of view going to see the polarity in
every facet of yourself that you look
at. just go through it. Mhm. All right.
Yes. Will that be of assistance? Yes. I
need to ask one other guys part.
Um I keep feeling that there's this
beautiful black tunnel to move into. All
right. And as I'm speaking about that now, I'm
And as I'm speaking about that now, I'm
feeling tremendously bountiful
and I feel a huge amount of space.
No, there are
individuals upon your planet who have
been receiving communication from
serious energy for quite some time if
you initiate conversations with them.
They can have much to share with you and
perhaps you will enjoy learning about
that energy from their point of view.
I'd like that. All right. They are
called your dolphins.
You see the relationship? Yes. All
right. Yes. Existing in that energy
seed.
You have received communication from
serious civilization for quite some
time. But you have not consciously
recognized it. They consciously
recognized it for what it was quite some
time ago. You recognized it but in and
let us say through the filtering that
you had created for yourself you I'll
say mythicalized it in a sense
interpreted what you received in a way
that represented the idea of what you
call mythical
creations certain of your civilization
have created the idea that beings from
Sirius have come to your planet in the
form of what you call man fish,
amphibious creature. Now, they are not
literally half man, half fish, but the
amphibious quality reflects what you
could understand at the time to be their
quasi matter energy idea and you sense
them as existing in a type of liquid so
to speak environment.
Water was the only thing that sufficed
at that time to explain that idea and
thus that is the way you perceived them
when their energy appeared to you as
civilizations. Is that Yes. Is that also mermaid to
Is that Yes. Is that also mermaid to
some degree? Yes. Although some of the
idea of what you call mermaid was also
result of your race memory of genetic
experiment in what you call aian times.
You follow me? Yeah.
Are you through? Um, almost. I was tell
you I was the one who asked you about or
Chelton and that the battle of Atlantis,
right? How
is well, is Atlantis and Sirius
connected in a in a fashion for me or in
general? There were many connections during that
There were many connections during that
time during many phases of
Analantis. In this way, you have had
lives there. All of you have had lives
there. And there was some recognition in
that way specifically for you in what
you call levels of priesthood that
recognize that communication in that way
existed so to speak. You are remembering
some of that and some of the vessels
that you used to assist you in
recognizing that connection were made
out of orchow. Yes.
Yes.
Gold, silver, copper, and mercury.
Yes. Does it have a little bit of bronze in
Does it have a little bit of bronze in
it too? From time to time it has, though
the majority of the variations did not.
I've started um expressing myself with
those colors and um I've started making
paintings good using those colors. Then
that is also a form of communication and
it will allow you to open up your
senses to be able to
receive communications on many different
levels. All right. All right. Thank you.
Thank you guys.
How do the dolphins deceive us and what
is their purpose in being here on Earth?
Well, now they have some similar
purposes. In a sense, you and they are
in a sense the co-parallel species upon
your planet that inhabit your
planet. In this way they have created
for themselves the identification
completely of their nature as nature as
to such an extent that you do not even
recognize them as sensient like
yourselves but as animals in this way.
They are conscious in much the same
manner that you are conscious and are
the only other species upon your planet
that creates karmic reincarnation.
This idea also is simply that they are
experiencing the joy and the ecstasy of
that reality and acting as a support
system for your reality in that they
have agreed to well hang
around you.
How do they perceive us? I mean as nasty
people being after them or as sometimes
you know just after um after the shuttle
incident there was they threw a a leaf
on in the area and there were dolphins.
Yes. Yes. There were dolphins there.
Yes. I I
thought they would love to talk to
they separation
to some degree but they are extended
sensorally in ways that are let us say
more closely approximating the idea of a
collectivity. They are in a sense
similar to the way my society interacts
in a
sense but they simply do not express
themselves upon
land. We interact freely and out of
existence boredom
boredom
joy. Yes. Fear. No. Joy is continuous.
Does it get boring? No.
There is always something to learn.
Always a new experience to enjoy. You
experience excitement. Yes.
Certainly. You do not think I would be
bored even with you.
You are always one Italian.
Are there people from our civilization
going to other civilizations through
them as you come to someone? Not really,
not exactly except for other portions of
exactly except for other portions of
yourself that you would not really
consider to be part of your
civilization. However, you will find
that your
civilization, my civilization,
civilization of Sirius is a triad
consciousness and we are taking turns
doing different
things in a sense.
In a sense, not really. But in a sense,
you perceive us to be ahead of you. In a
sense, but not really. We perceive
Sirius to be ahead of
us. Now they are accelerating out of the
triad. We will in a sense take their
place. You will take ours. Another
planetary system will come into the
grouping. And for that planetary system,
you will function as their UFOs, their
entities. You will channel through them
to them.
But at this time that's not happening.
We're not doing that. Not in a
physiological sense. In your dream
reality. Yes. I've had senses in dream
that I'm teaching somewhere else. Oh
yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. You are very busy in
dream reality. You have many jobs. They
are not restricted to what you are doing
on the earth plane.
Yes. Do you report back? I am recording
right now. Are you here studying us or
in the sense that we are learning from
you all the time and as I am making the
connection that energy flow is available
and open to anyone in my civilization at
the moment it is going on or at any time
they wish to connect into it. I do not
report so to speak. I
experience my experiences are a part of
the society for anyone to experience. So
your society can perceive what you are
perceiving. Yes. Thank you. Thank you.
Sure. Uh I'm experiencing some stomach
pain now which I've been dealing with
for quite a few months and I've been
attempting to learn how to cure it or
I'm not sure what the term is. I'm not
creating it.
Oh, what is it about life you can't
stomach? What really gets you in the gut? What
What really gets you in the gut? What
really aggravates you? What upsets
you? What ties you in
knots? What really bugs you? Well, you? Well,
[Laughter]
I don't know. I thought first thought
that I had was being stopped, but I all
right. All right.
Now, do you find that there are simply
things in your
life that you can no longer
digest that perhaps you are still
ingesting out of habit? Or let us put it
this way.
Have you recognized that you think there
are things you should stop
ingesting rather than simply allowing
your system to let you know when the
right time is by simply having or not
having a particular
urge? Do you force yourself to become
more spiritual?
Mhm. What do you think simply asking?
I think I'm deciding what I shouldn't
have rather than following the
impulses. And I don't think I'm forcing myself to
And I don't think I'm forcing myself to
be more spiritual. But I think that I
probably think I should force myself to
be more spiritual. All right. Then you
are saying that there is a portion of
yourself you cannot stomach. Yes, that's
that's it. All right. Why? It has gotten
you where you are. Therefore has served
you. You do not have to keep yourself
alive. You do not have to gnaw at
yourself. Punish him for being the you
you thought you were. It got you where
you are.
Obviously love everything you have
been. Take your arms now and yourself.
Hug yourself. Love yourself. Love
yourself. Love
yourself. Storage yourself. But not put
out yourself. Know that you and everything
yourself. Know that you and everything
you have been does feed what you are
becoming. You do not have to
reject that
food. You are your own flow of
energy. Now understand this as well.
You do not have to rely on your
physiological stomach to sustain
you. You are transforming into fourth
density. The idea of meaning the symbol
of food is becoming
refined. But allow yourself to change as
you feel the change happening. No need
to say, "Well, all right. I better clean
up my act. Better change my diet even
though I really want that hamburger.
But no, no, no. I am a bad person for
eating that hamburger. I am not
spiritual.
No, no, no. I will be spiritual.
Oh, that hamburger is looking better and
better.
Oh, I feel a pain, an emptiness, a void
that only that hamburger can fill. But I
refuse for that is not up for density.
That is my
spirit or wash.
You have created the idea of
hamburger. It is exactly as spiritual as
you are. When you allow yourself, when you
are. When you allow yourself, when you
allow yourself to
change, naturally, you may by being of a
different vibration that does not
require that form of sustenance simply
automatically lose the
urge. It will not be a matter of having
to decide it whether or not to have your
tumbler or whatever you substitute in
place. You will simply not think of
having it. It will
not seem right
somehow you will enjoy being more and
from that is what you will and you may
find that as you move further to four
you make less and less and less for it
is not your organs that will sustain you
normally mentally except in the third
density you are emerging out of what you
call your electromagnetic system
operates in your glands.
The chemical interaction and
electrochemical balance of your systems
is the product of the direct energy
absorption that
comes to your needs. And thus you will
sustain yourself on what will to be a
very minimal requirement that simply
infuses the langular structure with all
the vitality it needs to maintain the
electromotive feeling of your existence
in physical reality.
In this way, therefore, you find that
the idea of your evolution, so to speak, is
idea of your evolution, so to speak, is
that many of your internal organs will
continue to blend back into the idea of
the self and will not need to function,
so to speak, in that way any longer.
This would take some time, but it has
begun. And in this way,
simply trust your body
consciousness not just with the idea of
food, but with the idea of everything it
has always been. For it has gotten you
to where you
are, yourself. Treat yourself with
yourself. Treat yourself with
kindness and
care and love every portion of yourself
and A living light. Living
light. So light up. Time to
Time to
concentrate for a loving deep
breath. One more
time. One more time. Sleep Sleep
peacefully and
awaken one that is filled with
Okay. Um I wanted to ask you for a long
time about uh on your planet do you have
anything uh or do you use a tool similar
to what the tool we have astrology
naturally you wouldn't have the same
planets but I know on on your planet
there is no moon correct and uh you do
not use the tool astrology no okay are
you aware of like vibrational
frequencies and stuff yes
but we are also
aware that we are the creator of the
vibrational frequencies and can change
that idea Yeah. Right. Now, how many
planets are in your solar system? Is
there uh seven? Seven. Which one? They
are like you. The third. The third.
Right. Are there moons on the other
planets? Are the other planets like larger some
Are the other planets like larger some
smaller? And your sun is kind of
greenish or something? It is greenish.
Yes. Right. Okay. Thank you. For you.
Yes. Yes. Uh I'm very much interested in
learning and thinking what you said
about creating your own reality. Yes.
One of the things I notice in myself and
other people a lot of the
time when there's a choice to either
grow or remain the same. A lot of times
even though I want to grow, I find
myself remaining the same very often out
of habit. And I wondered if you could
and and come up several times this
evening in your conversations with
people. Yes. I wonder if you could maybe
talk a little bit about why is it that
given the choice so often of doing
something growthful or staying with a
habit, we very often go with a habit
instead of the other.
Right. Simply
basically let me say that the type of
reality you have created in which you
have chosen to forget has created a
number of types of belief
structure that have grown to the point
where when you are very little you are
I'll say
beaten into learning the reality that
you are expected to learn. Thus you buy
into very early belief systems because
you depend upon individuals around you
for your physiological survival. You
will buy anything they have to
say. Therefore it is
ingrained in you and in a sense because
of the cycle of repetition that you have
called reincarnation upon your planet.
It is also to some extent ingrained in
your soul and that is why it is in your
terms difficult to break that but you
are simply as evidence that you are even
considering the thought you are making
the change.
Or if you were not making the change you
would go on about your life and never
even know that such an idea existed. You
would never hear it.
So you are changing, your habits are
changing. The fact that we are here with
you is proof of that. The fact that you
are even considering that there are
other civilizations is proof of
civilizations is proof of
that. You are thinking a new
way. The more you become integrated, the
less time it will take to have even more
new ways to think. for the process of
integration is the shortening of the
creation of
time. That is why you have taken
25,000 years to explore the process of
separation but will only take
approximately 2 to 3,000 to experience
integration and then you will not need
to reincarnate in the earth
plain. For the idea of
integration does not need time.
Separation is what creates the sensation
of more
time. As you well know, when you are
having a good time, time
wise. Now again, this is not simply a
fluctuation in your ability to perceive
the passage of time. For the idea you
call the passage of time is only an
illusion. When you do not sense it, it
is not because you have not been paying
attention. It is because you have not
been creating
it. You simply are
here then you are
there and the action that you have been
performing will take the timing that you
have ascribed to it and time will not be
considered. Time is subject to timing and obedience
Time is subject to timing and obedience
to
timing. And timing is only you meeting
yourself, you living the ideas that you
chose to live, being the event of your
life. In that way, you can in a
sense live forever. For the
idea of the sessation of felt
time means that the more ideas you
become while you are still in a physical
reality, it will be the less time that
your body will feel will
experience. You will live your normal
lifespan stretched out over many
hundreds or thousands of years simply
because you will be living in the moment
and will not feel the passage of time.
Yeah, you will simply wake up and it
will be a thousand years later and you
have been having a wonderful
I'd like to ask for some pretty specific
information. I feel very privileged. I
work with a a vanguard group of artists
and scientists who are inventing uh new
um mathematics and physics and uh brain
research and um uh investigations into
uh the Gaia politique and all in search
of a integration and uh you planet
sanctity and I uh I'd like to know if
you would be able to furnish these
people that seem uniquely qualified to
help in this interview with dare I say
it a road map of some sort um
delineation of the steps that one would
need to take to help in this time
whether it be in cognition or or
biohysics or um anything any information
at all. We can only assist in a limited
fashion since we do not want to
interrupt the process of your own
creation. But we can share this idea
with you.
you.
When individuals in your society in many
different disciplines begin to
disciplines begin to
allow consciousness to be a factor in
their equations, they will have their unified
equations, they will have their unified
fields. They will have all the inter
relationships of their
mathematics and social
interaction. When they know that they
are creating everything in their
creating everything in their
reality, they will be able to choose
what they wish to create in their
reality. The program is yours to write
and rewrite. Now you have an overall
rewrite. Now you have an overall
momentum toward society. It is
true. And in this way there are certain
let us
say energy overlaps or standing waves in
the patterns that you will meet of
yourselves and give yourselves the
opportunities to lay
down different ideas upon the grid and
see which ones you prefer.
The idea first of
all is to recognize in your social
political structure that you have
created that the scenario the levels
that you have created within it are such
that you have
said take all
take all
government take oh religion take my
responsibility from
me. Protect me from what I
fear. Be a
shell in between myself and the rest of
myself. For I fear the rest of myself.
Take my responsibility. I give it to you
freely. That scenario that you have created has
That scenario that you have created has
allowed there to be a cessation, a
suppression of information that does
exist in your world. First of all, make
no mistake, your governments are very,
very, very well aware of our presence.
Your military has had
facetoface talks with different
civilizations. They know we
exist. They
understand the idea of what our
existence means to
you. But they are the
guardians of your fear. They are the
guardians of your power.
And when you come into contact with that
which says you are your own
power, then it creates a fear within the
guardians that they will lose their
power. not understanding that they are
already selfmpowerment and that to allow you to
selfmpowerment and that to allow you to
take back your power will actually allow
them to feel their own self empowerment.
They will no longer have to be
responsible for you.
Therefore recognize first of all as you
talk about the idea of the grids, the
programs, the structures, the lay lines
of your vision of your own
future. The acceptance of your power,
the acceptance of all that you are is
required to lay down the type of
structure upon which you can then do
whatever you want to
do. You follow me? Yes. Uh, I'd like to
ask you what what exactly is the
relationship between creativity and
consciousness? How can one inject one into the other
How can one inject one into the other
and back and forth or the things? In a
sense, creativity is simply
consciousness recognizing itself in
different ways.
Each and every one of you and us and all
beings in creation are simply all the
different ways all that is has of
looking at itself of recognizing itself.
That recognition is what creates
creation. Mhm. That is our understanding of the
Mhm. That is our understanding of the
process.
One moment of truth.
Um, I'd like to ask one more question.
Um, I recently had a a conversation with
a biohysicist who is a practicing
Tibetan Buddhist and uh has invented or
discovered or worked on a new model of
the brain. Nice. Uh, based on the
practices of Tibetan Buddhism, right?
Um, and well, has this person found?
I don't know. He's just about to make
models of it. But I'm my question for
you is the way in which you do cognition,
is the way in which you do cognition,
right? How is that related to the way in
which somebody who is a biopysicist does
cognition?
You get the result that you design the
experiment for. Thus, if you understand, if you
for. Thus, if you understand, if you
create the idea of yourself to be the
idea that all portions of your brain are
functioning perfectly with all other
portions and interacting and balanced
and using all sides, all ideas, you get
that type of reality. If you concentrate
in any one particular area at any one
particular time, then the feedback that
you get will only come in symbols that
reflect the
biopysicistness that you are being. You
may not see the same
correlation in other fields, other modes
of looking at things, but they are all
there. Simply what you design yourself
to be specifically results in the
specific type of information that you
allow yourself to perceive and only in
that way will you perceive it. Now even
individuals who may think that they
always consider themselves to be
biopysicists change from time to time
though they may not recognize it on a
conscious threshold.
Thus much of what they find to be or
what they think to be progress in their
specific chosen field is actually the
result of skipping around and being many
different things and then simply
bringing it back to an understanding
through the terminology of biopysics or
whatever. You follow me? No, that is
that is actually the process of creation
that occurs in the mental field of your
brain. You are connected to everything and the
You are connected to everything and the
central area what you call the corpus
colosum in this way that divides the
hemisphere. At the very
center there is a segment that is set
aside so to speak allowed to
symbolize what we will refer to in a
sense as a black hole or a white hole or
both through which your higher
consciousness turns into the mental electromotive
turns into the mental electromotive
field that you think of as mentality or
mind which is completely a reflection on
physical terms of the action of
consciousness in an electromotive
electromagnetic field or area of
reality. Are you referring to the pineal
gland? That is one of the areas but no
not specifically. You have not really in
a sense so to speak discovered this yet.
Your penal gland
however is one along with the pituitary
and what you call the medulla of the
three that form a triary base that are
directly receiving from the central
black hole area. this energy and then
translating into the different
methodologies of glandular and cellular
and organic chemical manifestation that
support the body that you are. It comes
from the apex in the very center creates
the idea of the crowning chakra and
creates the idea of the foundational
tetrahedralbased structure that is
exemplified by what you call female
pituitary and
Guys, some time ago we we had discussed
the unified field theory and and we had
had tried to identify a mathematics that
would be used to actually describe the
relationship that exists between the the
four basic forces. Now understand that
you have now begun to consider that
there may be so to speak five
Uh yes right. Yes. In this way however
it is only a clue to let you know that
there is only one. And this new supposed
fifth idea is not really a separation
but will show you the type of
interphasing that goes on to let you
know how the supposed four become one
another. Uh yes. Um when we spoke it I
actually um that evening gained more
insight than I had for many years into
the possibility of understanding the ma
the actual mathematics involved and you
at the time had said that because your
channel didn't know of the mathematics
that you didn't have the language to
communicate with us. Correct. Not in
mathematical terms. in in mathematical
terms and and aside from the fact that
our so-called mathematical terms are
completely unlike yours anyway.
Yes, sure. Of course.
Um, however, it occurred to me after
after I had done much thought and the
insight that I had gotten from you that
night, right, that that in fact the
mathematics I believe does currently
exist, but it is purely at least
currently unapplied. Yes. And and the
terms that the terms that refer to it
are a combining of of tensor calculus
and algebraic topology. Tensor dynamics.
Yes. And I guess what I'm I'm asking is does
And I guess what I'm I'm asking is does
that sound like it's the right ballpark?
Yes. Now this understanding of the new
so to speak fifth
charge will allow you to
develop those mathematics into an
understandable form. That was the in your terms missing
form. That was the in your terms missing
link.
Now, yes, just as the alphabet
exists, which it
does, you now can with this new clue
rearrange the letters to form some new
words. Mathematically
speaking, this will reflect that you
already understand the concept and
create the words to reflect that
knowledge. That is why we say when you
allow consciousness into the
equation, you will bridge that gap of
understanding that lets you know you
have the terminology. Is it a is it a
correct perception that that it is the
conscious the element of consciousness
itself in the equation in the
relationship that in
fact allows for the continuity of the
discrete perception of how the the
physical universe is actually
structured. I I i.e.
If if in in the physical universe we
have one energy level and another and
there is virtually nothing energetically
in between is consciousness and the
inclusion of that in the equation that
element will allow for the
homogeneousness to occur. Yes.
[Applause] Because in this way you will simply find
Because in this way you will simply find
that when you understand what we call
the non-physical consciousness
template, it in a sense is truly
everywhere even within what you
experience as a energy void in your
physical reality. For it is in and of
itself the description of the
relationship that creates the so-called
void. You follow me? Yeah. Yes.
Second simply the skin of your reality
lays upon the bones of the template and
in this way you divine the shape only by
the bones that stick
through but there is an underlying
current that does bridge the both of
them. Now in this way understand this
therefore by this analogy what you call
your proton. Yes. Yes, your electron.
Yes, it is two ends of the same
phenomena. They are linked outside of
your dimension and one causes the other.
One is a spiraling in and a funneling
out. The other is a spiraling out and a
funneling in. And that is why they are
linked in the way they
are. It's like the spiral connection.
Let us say if the atoms are in your
plane of
paper is a loop that goes through the
paper. I see. It's like it's like if if
it were if it were a rubber bone, one
end of the bone as it pokes through Yes.
is the proton and the other end of the
bone as it pokes through is the Yes. And
it is reversed because when you take a
spiral and go this way and continue in
an arc, when it intersects the plane
again, it is spinning the other way. You
follow me?
That gives you your opposite
charges. And the electron is so small
because that is where the funneling is
going in the black hole. The proton is
so large by comparison because that is
the black hole of which the energy of
the electron is spewing back out into
your reality. And that same concept
accounts for electron pair bonding
opposite. Yes. All of that.
explore that idea. See where that takes
you. [Music]
[Music]
There will be in your terms a few more
of your moments remaining for this
discussion. Yes. Thank you very much.
Thank you. With respect to experiments,
you get the results you expect. I know
that is true and they have shown that.
But there are a lot of scientists who
are experimenting doing research and do
not get the results they expect and as a
result create new theories and develop
new ideas and explore new avenues. Yes.
But that is because they are open to
begin with to allow for other things to
occur and that is still part of their
expectation. Ah okay. But that's isn't
that true now for for most scientists?
It is true for everyone. Okay. For
everyone. when we're talking about
research. Yes. Let me tell you. Simply
it is this. Many times the habits that
you have created in your society when
applied to the idea you call
science creates for itself the need to
keep asking questions which create a
need to keep creating processes instead
of simply understanding what is going
on. Mhm. the need to discover by
searching rather than discovering by
being. But that's because we're in third
density and
and there's nothing wrong with that. Did
not say it was wrong. So we said that is
the way it is because of this. Okay. But
but now uh you can blend the two. They
are that is why you have the idea you
call quantum chromodnamics. Right. Okay,
thank you. Thank you for you. Benu,
would you explain a little bit about the
universal template only very briefly?
template only very briefly?
Now, it is simply that our perception is
that there is an underlying now I will
be very colloial
underlying non-physical template upon
which the physical universe is
constructed. Not all of the non-physical
template shows through to the physical
side. But the implied structure is there
and that is what you are perceiving as
the regularity of the energy patterns.
Now the idea is in of itself for us
represented by what you call two
tetrahedrrons that is three-sided
pyramids base to base with one pointing
up and one pointing down. This creates a
symbolic figure, a mathematical equation
to us that represents all the different
ways that this universe takes its shape
from the initial concept. You have the
six planes and the five line phases in
this way which represent the
11dimensionality of your universe. You
have the idea in a single
tetrahedrin of showing if you take the
base to be xyz factors both positive and
negative of location and the apex to be
the factor of time again both positive
and or negative you will understand do
you understand the idea in your reality
to call the uncertainty principle? No.
All right. The idea that you can neither
know both position and momentum at the
same time. You follow me?
Now if you have this tetrahedral
structure and you have a base plane that
is the xyz factor of position and the
apex that represents time or
momentum. You in the physical reality
only have the ability to measure any one
face of the tetrahedrin at any one time.
That is your approach to your dimension.
Therefore, if you choose to know
complete position, you will measure only
the base, but it will not connect up to
the apex where time is. So, you have a
fuzzy notion of momentum. If you get the
complete idea of time at the apex when
measuring any one of the faces to which
the time apex is connected, you will
only have two of the factors of the
position and only have a fuzzy idea of
the position. You follow me? Only in a
fourth density, fourthdimensional state
can you see the whole figure and that is
where the template lies in non-physical
fourth density.
Thank you. Thank you. Yes. One moment.
Yes. Um then you and that will be it.
I have a friend um who appears to have a
disease called melanoma. Can you comment
on that and how this individual could
prevent um the disease from being
created?
Is the individual willing to speak for
themselves? No.
Ben, let me first point out this.
The degree to which you are willing to
share the conviction of who you
are has to do with allowing the totality
of yourself, including the totality of
your physical body to be
present rather than allowing bits and
pieces of yourself to dissolve
away. The idea of conviction, of feeling
the power of the core vibration that you
are as the
creator, standing up for
yourself, loving yourself, centering
yourself. The willingness to share in
the method you have chosen upon your
planet that you call bold
communication is in and of itself or the
lack of willingness to share that is in
and of itself an indication
of simply lack of communication to all
portions of your own physical
body. If
only you are not communicating to those
portions of your body and by reflecting
this idea by not being willing to share
of yourself which is a very beautiful
loving creation with others around you
feeling that you will be judged feeling
your own fears of lack of selfworth and
coming up short. You are then defining
immediately for yourself the fact that
you are withholding communication from
the creator that you are to those
different portions of your body that you
are cutting off from yourself. You are
closing your lines of communication and
the idea of not being willing to
communicate outside is a reflection of
not being willing to communicate within
yourself to yourself through your body
consciousness listening to your body
consciousness. Your body consciousness
is not less deserving than your
spirituality. Your body consciousness is
an extension of your spirituality. You
are a spiritual being in everything that
you even have in physical reality.
Physical reality is not something that
you need to run from. It is not less
than spiritual reality. You do not have
to take yourself through that process if
you do not want it. No one in this
transformational life has to
die in that way.
It can be however looked at like this.
Instead of feeling like you are
punishing yourself, you can recognize
that many times when individuals create
for themselves the idea of
disees, they are allowing themselves to
be of service to other individuals who
recognize the disease within you and
then can recognize the disease within
themselves in the various ways they have
manifested. So you can use what you
normally think of as a negative idea to
know that you may be being of service to
other individuals to give them an
opportunity to look at this idea in ways
they have never looked at it before.
Now this will let you know that you are
always in everything that you do being
of service. You are not flawed. You are
not a failure at
life. You have not failed at sustaining
your vitality. Your vitality is simply
going into the creation of the idea of
disease. But your disease is
vital. Understand you are always using
100% of
yourself. Even if you are using
90% to make the other 10% believe the
other 90% doesn't
exist, you are still using 100% of your
talent. Even if you are allowing the
Even if you are allowing the
10% to allow the 90% to keep pretending
it doesn't exist, you are still using
100%. You are whole. You are whole. You
are not
one. You are a whole being.
Share of your vitality and with your
civilization. Do the things you want to
do. Live what excites you. Share of
yourself knowing that whatever you have
created in your life is a gift to
others. Then you will allow yourself to choose
Then you will allow yourself to choose
another way to express it because you
will be letting the way you have chosen
it up to this point be a service to you
to them to all that
is. Knowing that you are a service to
all that is will let all that is support
you. And you can then be the idea of
yourself that does not contain that
disease. Share your joy. Be willing to
communicate. Open yourself up
completely. You have within you the
belief that vulnerability means
exposure.
Vulnerability. When you look at
vulnerability as being completely open
to
everything, that is strength. Be
strength. Be
vulnerable in
strength. Responsibility is yours for everything
Responsibility is yours for everything
that you create in your life. But
again, when you think that
responsibility means
blame, you are always judging yourself
to be less than you are. And so
sometimes your physical body will
reflect that by throtting
away pieces of it in reflect that to
you. But if you know that responsibility
for everything in your life means that
you have chosen everything in your life,
then you know that responsibility means
you have freedom of choice to choose
anything you want as your life. So So
vulnerability and
responsibility can begin to function in
your world as the freedom of choice that
allow you to feel your complete and
complete strength of self
empowerment. The core vibration that you
are that is all that
is you are extended to the infinite ends
of the universe.
You are
unshakable. You are one
thing, indivisible. Treat yourself that way and
indivisible. Treat yourself that way and
even the divisions that you have made of
yourself will
reflect the
indivisibility of your
existence. Answer me
this. Did you have to
deserve existence to exist? Did you have
to do anything to deserve to exist? No.
You exist. You always have. You always
will. You do not have to do anything to
deserve to
exist. Will. You do not have to do anything to
Will. You do not have to do anything to
deserve anything in existence.
Know yourself as
existence and you will
exist as the complete idea of
yourself in joy and love and ecasy.
I just wanted to ask you, I went to a
seminar a while ago and during it, I was
sitting there. It was like a meditation
type thing and someone was communicating
with me through the mind and all of a
sudden I had a strong feeling to put my
fingers together to make a triangle like
Daryl did when he was becoming a
channel. I was wondering why I felt that
it was powerful thing but I didn't know
what what I was doing or why. We have
instituted this idea in the beginning
with the physical channel because the
connection from what you consider to be
the present self to the future self of
yourself occurs through what you call
the solar plexus chakra. And in this way
it is a crystallization of alignment of
the energy so that it stays focused. So
you are sensing simply that you are
making that connection and you are
instinctively holding on to the beam of
energy that represents that idea to you.
only you are guiding it into position.
You follow me? Thank you.
Thank each and every one of you from our
unconditional love
with always by
always by
sharing with you discover more and more
and more of all that
is that we can explore. Your sharing to
us is a great gift for which we will
thank you
eternally. We, our civilization, your
civilization and all consciousness
together we are the sharing that
continues forever. We love you. Love
forever. We love you. Love
yourselves. We'll find you. We will
build you exciting dream
lives. We will be good life.
[Music] Ah go
Ah go
actually he ain't come [Music]
I have an announcement. Sorry. I have an
announcement. Thank you.
Thank you.
Just just in case anyone had a good time
tonight and would like to see Bashar
again. I would like to let everyone know
about a special event that's happening
uh Friday of next week and Saturday of
next week. is going to be an information
concert featuring Bashar and another
extraterrestrial, a female named Leah,
who comes through a medium named Gaming
Samps. And they're going to be giving an
information concert on the power of love
at the Wilshshire Edel
Theater. And there's going to be uh
music also. There's going to be dancing,
there's going to be crystals. They'll be
talking about the power of love. On
Valentine's Day day, channelneled
information, music, and dance will focus
on the marriage of feminine receptivity
and masculine action within the self and
society. Putting this love's energy to
work in daily living will be the focus
on Saturday evening the 15th. And if
anyone's interested, tickets are $20 and
I have tickets with me now.
Thank you. [Music]
[Music]
What do you think?