I don't say how are you all this seeing
of your time as you create time to
exist. We will begin with the reminder of the
We will begin with the reminder of the
idea of this interaction of what we have
called synchronicity in your language in
this way that word or serendipity or
coincidence or whatever you wish to call
it in that way with your imagination.
Synchronicity, the allowance of the
simultaneous existence of all that is to
manifest as quickly as it can within a
linear time frame structure that you
have created yourselves to exist within.
Synchronicity, the recognition of events
occurring, connected in a sense to each
other as they need to be connected to
each other to allow you to be
effortlessly. The idea you have chosen to be
The idea you have chosen to be
synchronicity. The idea that you may
call coincident not accidental. [Music]
vibration you feel to be true for
you with you have within you of what
reality is to you always it is an
opportunity to know that what you see in
your physical reality is a reflection of
your beliefs and therefore if you do not
prefer it what you see is an
opportunity to
create no sit
meaning negative effect. It is up to
you. Are you following along?
It is very simple physics, very simple
mechanics. And we will remind you in
this way
therefore when you will
rather than your
ego ide lives upon your planet that is
fractionated into many fragments. Is
that true of all of us? You all have
counterparts. Ace,
they exist simultaneously in what you
recognize to be the time frame of the
present. They are exactly the same thing
as a past or future life except they
exist at the same time that you do. And
all your past lives and your future
lives also have counterparts.
Interesting. Several other beings uh
come through u several people.
Is is the mechanism the same way as
works for the Darl? Basically, yes. The
definitions may differ a little bit from
time to time, from individual to
individual, from understanding to
understanding, from purpose to purpose,
but the basic mechanism is the same. One
quick other question is lust judgment in
a sense.
What sense can you It is the judgment of
desire.
So to say that lust is good or bad is
just another judgment upon a judgment.
Yes. If you have decided to create the
idea of a judgment of desire, then
obviously you are creating it for a
reason because you want to look at it
for some
reason. It gives you the opportunity to
decide whether you prefer that
particular judgment or not. Okay. Is
lust for life and beauty and and
spirituality. Now you are simply in this
way choosing another definition with the
same tonality ascribed to it. What you
are now describing in that way is simply
the recognition of your own
ecstasy. Lust for life is not negative
judgment. It is not lust in the negative
sense. Okay. So what we're down to
finetuning what kind of judgment is detrimental.
what kind of judgment is detrimental.
All judgment is negative.
All judgment is preference is positive.
Okay. So I if I say uh Bashar is a
beautiful being does that is that it
depends upon the reasons and the
purposes for why you have concocted that
equation. It can be a judgment. It can
be simply a preference or a statement.
It is always a perception on your part
and it is
There's variety of ways to look at it.
One is that this is a brick wall and I'm
supposed to go a different direction.
All right. It is only a reflection and a
very simple symbol of the idea of
feeling like there are obstacles in your
path to impede your movement in what you
perceive to be the typical forward
direction. But as we have said and as we
know you know anything that you perceive
to be an obstacle is not so much an
obstacle or a wall but a sign leading
you in an unexpected direction. Well now
I was in reverse when I hit this
subject. So
uh how does that cover the uh
in this way you may feel that you are
compromising yourself by feeling like
you might have to back out of situations
rather than in this way standing up for
yourself clearly without needing the
opportunity of creating conflict. Well,
that's an interesting comment because I
was just allowing this entire scenario
to take place with my agent and with my
car and it turned out that uh I didn't
have to back out of it because my agent
did. Oh, right. So, it changed the
course of events by him changing the
agreement. Yes. It was real convenient.
I really just allowed it to happen. Yes.
Another question.
Um you said that crying is centering
from the negative side. Yes. And I
understand that children now in my experience in
that children now in my experience in
this society children frequently will
cry when their demands or expectations
are not met. Do you view this also as
centering in a sense and also understand
that even though you may consider them
to be very
young children in your society learn
very quickly what gets them what they
need and the structure they have been
born into. Right. That was the next part
of my question. Now later on they you
know parents sometimes will try to shut
the kid up or whatever by giving into
his demands even though it may not serve
their integrity or the kid's integrity.
Uh and so the kid learns that crying
gets his way which to my way of seeing
it says that now the crying is no longer
centering but some other kind of tool in
a sense. Yes. It is a reflection of what
the child has already learned about the
parents. It is a reflection to the parents about
It is a reflection to the parents about
what the parents have already taught the
child in terms of behavior in this
society. For recognize again there are
many things that you may consider to be
almost unnoticeable very subtle signals
the child will pick up on them
immediately and very very blatantly as
to what disharmonies do exist around it.
Can you give an example of that? Simply
in this way you may find that a child
will be very telepathically in tune to
tensions abrasions within the family in
that way and may be simply reflecting
the reactions going on in the family.
Yes, I do. It will have already picked
up all of the signals very early and
will immediately begin to be a
reflection of the type of atmosphere
that pervades the family. Uhhuh.
Okay. I I'm involved with a woman who
has a daughter 10 years old and she and
I the daughter and I are interacting in
um how can I describe it in a way that
um reflects what you said about children
pushing um having parents to push
against. She's not my natural daughter
but in fact I've known her for about six
months but there seems to be a
relationship where she's doing a lot of
pushing. All right. Uh my approach to it
is being very firm in terms of my own
integrity. Yes. Uh not giving her slack
where the slack would show her that um
she gets things without giving things
that kind of stuff. Um then you are
fulfilling your part of the bargain. I
believe that I am. Yes. Uh it's pretty
abrasive. It can be quite abrasive.
Although I do feel that I'm seeing in
the last week or so
what I would say would be um positive
change on the part of the child. Right?
An individual who has chosen to lock
themselves deeply within limitation in a
time stream may require a little bit of
time to readjust. If you are willing to
enjoy every moment, you will not need
patience for the idea of the
circumstance, but will be willing to
allow them to take as much time as they
need. That is true.
That is true. Do you have any any other
words of wisdom on this particular
situation with me and her? Simply the
continuence of unconditional love and
the willingness to recognize that you
are both cocreating this relationship
for your own personal reasons and you
will benefit from the recognition of
those reasons. Okay, just for my
information now, I'm not real
consciously sensitive to the telepathic
communication between she and I.
Although the feeling that I have is that
I am being of service to
her in that she does want to um she does
want reflections of a positive the
positive route that she is and she's
putting up a lot of resistance. However,
I feel I'm doing the right I'm going to
say right thing. You are being true to
you. Yeah. Right. Then you are by
definition the person she has attracted
into this co-aggreement.
Be yourself and you will be fulfilling
your half of the body. Okay. Thank you.
Thank you. Sure. You um I wanted to tell
you and everyone I feel wonderful
and uh thank you. Yeah. Thank you for
the trip last week. And I and I had a
question because I was talking to Steve
about the title of the tape last week
and I thought you might have said field
trip. uh as opposed to field trip. All
right. For the title is up to you. So it
it Okay. I like field trip, but it's
just for the catalog. I thought it out
with you. So you're saying Okay, fine.
Thank you very much. Sure. For sure.
Yes. Uh a couple questions. Um one, in
front of human vision, there seems to be
these geometric uh shapes that float by
and avoid direct uh contact. they sort
of move off off to the side. Could you
uh articulate on that? There can be a
few reasons for these ideas.
Primarily, there are different levels of
your consciousness that from time to
time when you are not guarding them so
closely will allow you to expand and
wander into different levels of physical
and non-physical reality on the basic
fundamental level of the primal energy
out of which all your physical reality
is created. Sometimes you can translate
the perception of this energy into the
basic fundamental template or geometric
designs that would represent the
mathematical relationships of all of the
vibratory patterns within the energy
field. It will simply translate into
geometry as you understand it in a
third-dimensional sense.
Does that clarify the idea? Yeah, I've
always well often as a kid I would lay
in bed and I would feel ideas as shapes.
Yes. You know, I take things like joy
and I would suddenly I would it would
come to me that it's it has this sort of
curve to it and such. You are simply
gleaning the most basic conceptual
materiality of the form rather than the
specificity of needing to break it down
into this type of very
specific physical reality. Okay? They
are like the preconcepts before they
divide and restructure themselves into
something more complex.
Right? Okay. Another thing
um I experienced a knowingness taking
the the 120 plus uh elements chemical
elements of of this world and likening
those to the primary elementals actual
who's from which all
uh reality or or things break down and
alchemize and combine into.
And I u those are only symbols and they
only represent one
doorway. It is not inevitable that every
member of your society should perceive
that the breakdown or the buildup of
your physical reality proceeds from
those particular
symbols. It is one way of looking at it.
Okay. It is to some degree archetypal
but there are variances far and wide.
The the actual elements taking gold,
tantelum etc. Are those symbol even the
actual element gold is that symbolic of
a
who outside? is more symbolic of a what
a state of being. And in this way again
joyous synchronicity that you should
choose that one for recognize in this
way. We have been discussing the idea of
gold much of late for it represents the
element that is the stasis and the
transference in this way of the
universal energy into a form that
specifically allows you to perceive
immortality or eternalness within your
physical being. Okay. to their qualities
rather than whose. Yes. States of being
for recognize as you already know what
you call gold does not corrode. Right. I
had much um uh attraction to a a metal
called tantelum and the qualities of
that seem to uh be fixed in that sense
as as a beingness. Yes. But
tantelum in this way in our perception
is sensitive. Mhm.
to certain types of etheric
energies from outside the normal
environment of your atmospheric
planet. It
will find many uses in what you call
space technology,
right?
It is to some
degree connected to some of your
planetary states of
being particularly the
ones that you have attached significance
to with regard to some of your unor
subconscious realms.
It is archetypically significant of
exploration also within the dimensions
of your planet
itself. Everything that is
subterranean to some degree has an
attachment to that as well as it is a
different dimension of existence that is
also of a different atmosphere than the
actual surface of your planet.
Thank you. Okay. For sure. Are you? Yes.
Yes. Earlier you were talking about
centering. My attention is stuck on it.
I've never heard of the term and I don't
know what you mean by it. Thank you.
Centering is the idea most often
attributed in your society to simply
being at rest. Being at peace, being in
the know of yourself, going with your
flow, feeling life to be effortless,
moving with yourself, walking in time to
your tune, that is being centered.
Knowing that you create your reality and
recognize everything around you to be a
projection from you in that way. Knowing
that you are self-empowered to create
anything you desire in your reality. You
follow me? Yes. That is being in
balance. It is having all the different
ideas you have created to be different
levels or polarities in your
consciousness to be blended and balanced
to allow there to be in this way a
stillness and an infinite acceleration
at the same
time. Knowingness is
centering. Trust is centering.
Joy, ecstasy is the expression of the
centered being that you are the being
that contains all possible
realities. You follow me? Yes. Thank
you. Thank you. For sure. Yes. When
Daryl cuts out, does he actually become
you? Do you blend? There is a blending,
but in this way, it is in the formation
of what you would call a third identity.
I do not become him. He does not become
me. We become a different idea
altogether. I see. Does he cease to
exist as an individual consciousness? Of
course not. Okay. All things exist
eternally in their own terms on their
own right. But the definition of the
reality you are experiencing is becoming
something new. And so what will be
recognized as an individual in that way
along with all the rest of you will
simply redefine what you are as an
individual and include many different
probable ways of constructing yourself
to be an individual. I got you. What
specifically happens to Daryl as he goes
in this trick? Can you give me a little
more? In this way, there is the entering
into what you would call the dimension
of imagination totally. Mhm.
I got you. the experience of the
concept rather than the specificity. So
it becomes an idea form. A I got you. To
what degree does
um stimulus response mechanisms in terms
of one having made a recording or
imprint of something they have in the
past being stimulated by a present
perception? To what degree does this
actually occur in it occurs to whatever
degree the individual being exposed to
it has a percentage of belief in the
process. So it's proportional to the
belief of course everything is
excellent. Thank you very much. That is
why all tools are valid.
For it always depends upon the belief.
So the belief structure enables one to
utilize the tool. Yes. Okay. And the
tool is always created from the belief
structure. So they are automatically in
synchronous harmony. Right? So one could
invite one uh people to believe in a
particular structure and create tools
out of that. Yes. And if they choose to
go along with it then it will have value
for them in that way. And that is why we
say always trust that your imagination
is always in step with providing you
with whatever methodology you require
for any particular process you wish to
undertake. For your imagination is
always in synchronous harmony with the
being that you are and can only provide
you with a method that will work for you
by definition. Otherwise, it would be
someone else's imagination. Right? My
imagination, for instance, enables me to
create the first fourth density ice
cream store.
Tasty, isn't it?
Thank you, Sharon.
Yeah. than you. Um, I have a dear friend
who has a condition. A dear friend.
Yeah. A dear friend who has a condition
called dyslexia.
Are you familiar with that? You almost
didn't get that out, did you?
Appropriately secret. All right. They
have slightia.
Yeah. Anyway, um um he said that he has
managed to uh transform it to a certain
degree, but it still occurs and I've not
um had any contact with that idea other
than he mention it to me. Is there
anything that we can discuss or you can
tell me that I can perhaps tell him? It
is an art form of the unexpected.
It is a
method for destabilizing the rigid
structures of communication and in this
way allowing or inviting or allowing
there to be an opportunity for
individuals to recognize that they
understand perfectly well what an
individual means whether they are using
the proper forms of communication or
not. Oh in other words in reading
something if he reads the words
backwards he can still understand it.
And in this way, it is also an
opportunity for you to recognize that
all levels of communication in this way
are simply arbitrary
labels. And in this way also, it is an
opportunity to recognize that one does
not exist within a rigid structure. And
is exploring many different ideas that
the so-called disease can allow them to
discover that someone embedded in the
rigid structure may not. Mhm. Yeah,
that's interesting cuz he said that it
like when he was younger, of course,
that it was uh he was considered a bit
slow and and not as bright and things
like that. Allow your friend to consider
it mastery of a foreign language. He can
learn what you would call proper
language if he wishes to. As long as he
does not invalidate the language he
already knows.
That's great. Thank you, Bashar. Thank
you. Yes. Yes, Bashar. for the purpose
well whatever for the purpose of
creating what for the future and for the
past let's say that the past exists okay
let's say
the past
exists all I'm coming to um
hypothetically guys
that's what I meant guys I know okay uh
if one wanted to regain or uh have full
full recall of his psychic ability. What
would be let's say the system
or something that he could do or may I
ask you all a question? Yes, go ahead.
How long are you going to assume that
there is one background of truth against
which all things are to be compared as
being better than something else?
When are you going to trust your
imagination to supply you as we have
already said with all the methodologies
you require to contain and be any idea
you want to be in present? Yesterday, Yesterday,
[Music]
so so what is the method? You tell me.
Since it is your method provided by your
imagination, what do you feel would
excite you to the vibrational frequency
that would allow you to know you are
always psychic? By definition, you are
alive. You are psychic. That's right. I
know that. All right, then. Act like it.
And you will be psychic.
Exactly as you need to.
Okay. All right. Yeah. Fair enough.
Yeah. Thank you. That's very good. Thank
you. For sure. For sure. One moment.
Yeah. I uh earlier I just had
experienced two episodes of uh losing my
voice and felt like there was energy
coming out of my throat chakra. I was
wondering what it is common again. In
this way, many of you as you increase
the connections to the ideas of opening
yourselves as lines, as channels for
communication from your higher selves
and other consciousness in that way will
find there to be experimental let us say
testings of the energy. At times it may
leave you
speechless and it is only temporary. Go
with the flow and you will acclimate
that much more rapidly.
It is all part and parcel of the fourth
density transformational symptomatic
fevers in a
sense experimental
testings. In other words, you are
allowing yourself to let as much of that
energy through as you are comfortable
with until you acclimate to it and
regain your sense of control. Then you
will take more and more and more until
you become used to it to the point where
you will not have to lose touch with
anything to have mastery over it all.
Okay? It is connected to anything you
desire to communicate to anyone else in
that way. Your own understanding of your
abilities to communicate and your
willingness to recognize that also
within silence is much information.
All right. Thank you. Thank you. Yes.
Yeah, I wanted to ask you about an
associate of mine who is you and Daryl
have also been associated with this
person. Uh this person's name is
Ana. She is a channel who has been
giving us a group of us
information pretty much about our
deaths and she says this information is
un unverifiable through other channels.
Can you tell me if that's true or not?
I mean true regarding the whole
is this a joke? [Music]
[Music]
I am really curious about
this person. If the individual says it
is
unverifiable through another entity,
then how would me saying yes and or no
do anything for you if you have that
belief? No, I don't have that belief.
Then why did you ask?
Because I didn't know. Didn't know what?
Whether it was or was not. I wanted to
give some information about that
particular body of data. But if I said
one thing or another, how would that
tell you whether it was or wasn't? I
don't know.
What do you feel about the idea of the
giving of others destinies?
about the idea of
of being told what your destiny is.
I don't really know. I haven't thought
about it that much.
My destiny hasn't been told to me. Now, understand
Now, understand
this. You are always telling yourself
what your own destiny is. Mhm. Another
individual can
sense what an individual has told
themselves or chosen for their so-called
destiny. That's what I mean. Yes. But in
this way, it is only a reflection of a
sensing of what the individuals being
talked to have chosen. Yes. And in this
way, it means in a sense it is within
your control. Now the overall destiny is
the free will of your higher
consciousness. Right? How you fulfill
the idea of your so-called destiny is up
to your physiological consciousness.
Here there can be sensings of what those
so-called destinies are.
But in this way
recognize the telling of
destinies is nothing but the most
generalized of ideas and any
specifics cannot be predicted for the
specifics of how you fulfill your
self-chosen destiny is up to you.
So destinies can be sensed in a general
way. Yeah. Reflected. Yes. Okay. Um I
want to know this person says through a
channeling that the um the process of
the people who are in the group will be
accelerated tremendously if they believe
so obviously. Yes. All right. Okay. So
all it takes actually is a belief. Yes.
In that your
faith sound familiar?
Is what makes the difference.
It is not your faith in someone else.
No, it is your trust with yourself and your
it is your trust with yourself and your
relationship to all that is. So it's not
actually the physical blending of the
energies of group that would carry that
off. It's oh in a sense because you have
created yourselves to be a linked
mentality within a particular energy
field. Yes, there is that effect. But
first comes the belief that that effect
is real. Okay. Then you derive the
benefit of the acceleration. Gotcha.
Does that answer your question? Yes.
Thank you. Sure. Yes. I have an
additional question about the same
person. Ana is do you have a perception
of what consciousness or entity is
coming through that? We do not in this
way label or
recommend or verify or judge. And in
this way, simply recognize every
individual that presents themselves in
service in that
way always attracts the individuals that
need to interact with those individuals
for whatever reason. Thank you. Yes. But
I understand that I wasn't asking you to
judge label or etc. But whether for
example you describe yourself as coming
from a particular place as a Isani and
there's a chap who comes from Sirius and
I wondered if you had a perception of
the origin point or nature of the energy
coming through that person. Let me put
it this way in another sense. The reason
I answered you as I did is because there
are in your
terms controversies within many
different people about exactly what it
is that is coming through. I see. So you
would choose not to be a participant in
that controversy right now. Yes. Got it.
Thank you. For the way it is is the way
it serves, right? And different
individuals will have a different
definition. Those different definitions
are what serves them for now. Great.
Many of us don't want to don't want to
recognize any definition. We'd rather be
told. That is your habit.
That is your habit.
Yes. Yes.
Thank you.
If as I understand the imagination of
the individual determines whether it's
going to be positive or negative uh in a
sense is it not feasible as has been
suggested by some people that there
could be advanced
civilizations to this one that would um
have perhaps negative
um purposes in the sense of maybe in
what way would who label them advanced
if that is the case.
Well, let's say that they would be
advanced in in as far as they could
perhaps communicate through channels
here or um certain individuals here. It
is not likely for recognize the
idea is only and can only be positive
and negative with agreement. Now, it is
not impossible that an individual in
what you would call your society would
form the belief structure that will
allow them to believe that they can form
an association with that type of an
individual. And so they can. But in this
way, recognize the basic fundamental
definition of what channeling is for the
most part is a positive idea in terms of
the ability to even form an association
with another individual. It involves the
idea of freedom of choice which a
negative individual or consciousness or
entity is unlikely to want to grant.
I understand. I have another question if
I may. Yes. Um getting back to a subject
that intrigues me is the idea of having
four or five
um subpersonalities or individuals. They
are not subpersonalities.
Okay. Unless you mean them to be
subpersonalities of the oversoul.
Well, let's just say associated with an
individual in whatever you know regard
um that fragments of the oversoul. Okay,
that is something that was real to me
and I in fact experienced a
communication uh from an individual that
I felt was very much on that level.
Nice. Um it it got to a point where I was
Um it it got to a point where I was
actually afraid of some of the
communication that was coming in um
because of the reality difference. All
right. But how can there by definition
be in that way a reality difference if
you perceive the communication obviously
in your reality is contained the
potential of that existence. So on
whatever level you will contain it that
is only the level to which the
communication can occur. You do not need
to create a sessation of the
communication through fear. You can
create a sessation of the communication
through the recognition that only as
much of the communication as needs to be
fit the idea you have of yourself will
be able to filter in anyway. Right. But
at that point uh well let me ask this. I
got the idea there would be a benefit
from continuing that communication. Is
that right? Then that is the idea and
the reality you will create. Okay. Thank
you. Thank you. You have done it.
Sure. For sure. Guys, I was going to ask
you about the energy vortexes on the
earth. Guys, see um I heard that you you
were saying that there was a way that we
could use the energy
non-technological technologically. Um
how could we do that and use it
physically? You can stand in the middle
of the
vortex which will open you to all
dimensions of experience within
creation. You can then be opened to a
mirror and a reflection of all that you
are. And you can take out of the
experience what you wish to and add it
to the idea of yourself to change who
you are and change your
reality. It is like going into a
possibility pool.
Now in all reality they are anywhere you
happen to be but the ones of
concentration in this way are many
different places. There is a very what
you would call strong one in what you
call your Malibu area also in what you
call your Sedona area of Arizona.
So um does this mean that we could run
cars off of this if we want to say
instead of using current energy sources
that there is a way to tap it in that
sense but I was under the assumption as
you said that you were referring to
non-technological applications.
Okay. There are aspects of your
There are aspects of your
electromagnetic field in this way that
taps the energy of the relationships of
the vortices to one another. the entire
earth crystal. You can run all of your
electrical conveyances off of that
energy off of the earth energy itself. It has
off of the earth energy itself. It has
already been attempted and suppressed
many times and and that's
electromagnetic energy, right? Sense.
Yes. Okay. And the resonant fields of
your planet in this way the operational
field of approximately 7 and 1/2 cycles
per second of your earth. Seven and a
half. Yes. Approximately. Okay. Thank
you. The in this way speed of light
divided by the circumference of your
planet equals the frequency in cycles
per second.
Follow me right. Yes.
Following a question the other gentleman
asked in the raw materials. Yes. The
entity speaks of two ways to contact
intelligent infinity. One is service
through others and one is service for
self. And it allows or concedes or
suggests that from our perspective we
would perceive service toward others as
a something positive. Yes. And service
towards self as something negative.
izations that are much more, if you
will, technologically advanced and
perhaps in some ways spiritually
advanced. They've contacted intelligent
affinity. They may even be able to
do be aware of being able to do things
such as channeling, going to other
places without their bodies that we are
not aware that we can do and in that
sense more spiritually advanced which
are it's not really advanced but I take
your meaning. Go ahead.
and which are civilizations which can do
all those things and in that sense
advanced or different from Yes. develop
differently who have who are oriented
towards service to itself and there
negative from our perception. Yes. And
okay so that's a statement of something
that exists in the universe. Oh yeah,
for sure. You then you uh you said that
uh suicide is the only act which is not
align with the destiny created by the um
higher consciousness. Basically, I'm
wondering if there's a situation where a
higher consciousness would want to find
out what it's like to commit suicide and
therefore again in that way from the point of view
again in that way from the point of view
of the oversoul nothing is lost as
information and it does learn from
everything in that way and that to some
degree can be a point and can be an
experience in that way. Simply as we
have said
99.999% of the time that is not the
case. I see. So it's possible that this
would be the last act that the oversoul
has chosen or the higher consciousness
has chosen in this
0001% of chances.
And in this way recognize of course that
all death is basically suicide.
You do choose to die. Okay. Another
question relating to your environment.
Are there uh are any of the other
planets in your planetary system
inhabited at your density level? No. Are
they inhabited at other density levels?
Yes. As are most planetary systems.
Inhabited in various density levels.
Yes. I see. Are you in contact with
those other civilizations?
Yes. Can you describe some of those?
They are in various stages of what you
would call evolution in this way. Some
are not unlike your own in many
different ways.
One is relatively
different in the sense that its entire
existence is based
upon one stream or equation that is being
one stream or equation that is being
pursued and has been pursued for what
you would call hundreds of your years.
How to express a
planetary experiment? A planetary focus of
experiment? A planetary focus of
thought, a planetary
search in one mode or line of thought.
Can you describe this mode or line of
thought? Not in so many of your words exactly.
Not in so many of your words exactly.
Except that what they are attempting to
do is explore one at a time each and
every possible aspect and facet as a
mass consciousness.
Aspect of what? Of all they can imagine
but one at a time. That's very
interesting. In other words, a complete
sessation of diversity
as
individuals but an increase in diversity
as to what the mass consciousness will
experience at any given moment. I see
one after another. Interesting. How is
the planet that is closest to us
similar? You say it's similar in certain
ways. How is that similar?
It has similar
ideas of approach to life
technological or yes
basically although what you would call
their relation to the universe is more
let us say naturalistic than religious.
Okay. Well perhaps you could tell us the
differences. Maybe that would help me
understand how they're
different or how they are the same. Tell
me how they're different then I'll
understand how they're the
same. Let us say in this way as an
example they have the idea of gathering
together as you might for what you would
call a religious ceremony.
But they recognize in this way that the
actual exercise will be more of a direct
connection to their planet rather than
the idea of a deifying of any symbolic
individual. Okay. Is their technology similar? Do
Okay. Is their technology similar? Do
they have ground vehicles? Yes. Use
petroleum type products.
So to some degree, although their motor
power at this time is mostly what you
would call steam. Oh, I see. What? But
highly refined applications of steam.
What generates the heat to generate the
steam? An element in their planet that you
An element in their planet that you
would call something akin to radioactive
like nuclear reactors to some degree.
Not exactly, but to some degree. How is
it
different? It is simply a different
frequency generated element in that way
and does not have exactly the properties
of what you would recognize to be the
radioactive element on your planet. The
ionic structure will be different in
that way and only in certain
circumstances is it in your terms
lethal. I see sir it can be rendered
impotent in that way through the
introduction of different elements and
materials within it.
Okay. Is there an an analogy on this
planet? um in the elemental sense of
what this substance is. Torium.
Torium.
Okay. Interesting. Do they have a name
for themselves or do you identify them
by a name? We do not create names at
this time but only the recognition of
frequency vibration.
Do they have a name for themselves? It
would mostly
translate as a symbolic
interpretation. Perhaps you would call
them the planners.
That's interesting. Do they communicate
with language or tele language? Thank
you. Thank you, Mr.
All right. All right.
[Music] Thank you very much. Um, I want to get
Thank you very much. Um, I want to get
back to this thing about service to
self. Nice. That's great.
That's great.
How synchronistical.
I think that is exactly what's going to
happen. Oh, very good.
Uh I have been playing with the idea
of servicing myself. When I first
started on my venture some years ago, it
was like I want to go out and save the
world and everybody else and I, you
know, and then as I got a little more
knowledge, it began I began to
understand that I don't know enough to
go out and tell everybody else how to do
their thing because my You never will.
Okay. Well, in the process, I'm finding
that I have been much more of service to
other people as I have gained more
selfishness to get my own act together.
But in this way, recognize that the way
to easiest allow the universe to serve
you is to be of service to others.
Well, that's where the conflict is. Why
is there a conflict? Uh I'm not sure if
it is a conflict or if it's just a
process of cousing or integrating. Um
what do you perceive to be happening?
Well, I perceive that I'm going through
a slow integrating process if you say
so. Well, an integrating process, but
it's slow or not. It's irrelevant at
this point. Anyway,
um the the conflict
is having
[Music] to chose over helping somebody else to
to chose over helping somebody else to
do something and my own desires. Now,
one moment. Do not
confuse taking care of yourself as being
selfish. Understand that you can only be of
Understand that you can only be of
service to others when you love yourself
enough to allow yourself to in your
terms take advantage of the
opportunities that are automatically
provided to you. So you will be
stable. It is not being self sacrificing
that helps them. It is being of service
to them by being someone who knows they
are stable enough to be of
service. No one is going to receive help
from you if you deprive yourself of the
things that are required to allow you to
exist in comfort.
Okay? When you attract the opportunities
to you automatically with your
synchronicity to take advantage of those
opportunities to allow yourself to be
the person you are in that way to love
yourself to care for yourself to respect
yourself and nurture yourself so that
you can be strong enough to be of
service to others. It goes hand in hand.
It is not an exclusion
principle. We're not talking about
self-sacrifice. Okay. Well, apparently
that's what I'm really looking at. All
right. Very good. Um just an example if
if a person say I have a friend uh who
you have a friend who needs some Thank
you very much.
who needs money and I need money too.
Got it. But uh say I have plastic in
this society. Credit
cards even though I don't have any cash
I could always go to the till you know
the plastic and get money. Although and
that puts and simply recognize within the
puts and simply recognize within the
situation what is the integrity of the
situation. Are they coming to you being
attracted to you to be given an
opportunity to function within their
integrity in this way or is it for the
purpose of allowing you to know that you
can assist them in that way without the
idea of depleting because you know you
are abundant. What is the reason for the
interaction?
Are they asking you because they are
unwilling to be responsible for
themselves and are attracting themselves
to someone who will remind them that
they must be responsible for themselves
that way? If I see this as the other
individual say being responsible okay
and then they have attracted themselves
to you to allow there to be the
interaction in this way of your
assistance to them. A perhaps to assist
them with the actual physical money in
that way, but also B to assist them with
the ideas of sharing methodologies and
opportunities for how they can allow
themselves to be in a situation where
they will not have to ask you.
Okay. Well, I'm not as concerned about
the other person as I am right now
myself. But why should you ever be in
that way concerned? Simply recognize
that if you are recognizing the
integrity of the situation, then you
know that if you have also attracted an
individual in that way and you know the
result of the interaction will be within
your integrity that you will give them
assistance physically monetarily then
you automatically know that if all is
being done within the integrity of the
situation you will automatically be
replenished. Okay, that was exactly what I did. Okay,
Okay, that was exactly what I did. Okay,
that was where I was coming from. Then
you will be replenished automatically.
Unless you choose to worry about whether
you will or not.
Now I use that example because it was a
physical thing that I could grasp
easily. Now in
relationships I'm I'm finding that my
selfishness is really
becoming I mean I'm becoming very
different. I mean, all right. Again, it
does not have to be negative selfishness
to simply stand for the belief you know
yourself to be.
If it is within integrity, which means
you are not worried about never having
enough for yourself.
And that
also relates to losing or gaining
friends or what have you. You do not
lose, right? Well, for lack of a better
term. All right.
A better term. All right.
Okay. Um All right. I guess I have to explore
Um All right. I guess I have to explore
it some more. All right. Thank you. A
very moment.
Can you give me again, please? The
difference between faith and trust.
There really isn't any. I didn't think
so. Okay.
They are both reflection of the
mechanism of your knowingness. Okay. And
they are both purely created. One
creates trust by simply creating trust.
By acting that way. Yes. By acting. Very
good. Thank you, Bashar.
You I was wondering if you could explain
away how it is. Explain away.
Well, how
How can space-time concept exist if time
is an illusion?
How can you understand that in terms of
logic? Logic any frame of reference that
you are in is going to be experienced as
real. It is an illusion from another
point of view, not from the reference of
being in the illusion.
Is that logical enough?
That just says everything's a relative
reality. Exactly.
We have mechanisms or ways of explaining
through analytic thought. But understand
any tool you will devise to explain a
system is created within the system it
explains and proves nothing.
It only reinforces the system out of
which the tool was created. By
definition, it has to logical.
In other words, you get the result you
designed the experiment for.
How is it I can't exist? How is it I'm
not consciously
aware right now of
of timelessness.
You can be
how is how can I do that? By existing in
the now and not thinking about the past
or the future in that way. Not making a
connection to the past to the future.
Not assuming that the past is what
creates the present because it doesn't.
That involves a whole series of belief
changes. Of course, that is the whole
idea. Believe it is.
What you believe, so shall it be your
reality. That is exactly what it
involves. You have hit the nail squarely
on the
head. But that is all this reality is a
belief. You follow me? Yeah, I do. Oh,
all right.
I You can have a good time exploring the
many different beliefs you can allow
yourself to use to create different
realities because this is the
transformational age in which many more
things are now possible and probable
because you are removing yourselves from
the cycle of limitation and judgment and
forgetfulness. All right? You are
remembering who and what you are. So
then the in in uh changing your belief
systems and experiencing for example the now
and experiencing for example the now
that it's the only reason I would have
trouble is because I believe that it's
difficult right very good
you understand this very well
you have an easy way to do Yes. Stop
Yes. Stop
assuming that you need anything easier
than what you have already done to do
it. In other words, you are still
assuming that imagination is less real
than physical reality. And that when you
imagine a concept, you have to do
something to make it real when it is
already real. If you can imagine it, it is real.
real. If you can imagine it, it is real.
It is only your assumption that you need
to still do something to make it real.
That is what creates a timeladen
process before the idea will physically
manifest. As soon as you understand that having
As soon as you understand that having
the concept is not the beginning of a
process but the end of a
process, then you will allow, allow, not
make, allow your reality to begin to
reflect the concept you now know to be
your reality. Simply because you could
perceive it means you are it. You cannot
perceive what you are not. You have to
be on the same frequency to perceive an
idea. You have to be that idea in order
to perceive it by definition. So if you
can conceive of it, you are that
reality to whatever extent that will
fulfill your overall agreement with the
mass consciousness.
In other words, you will not step
outside the boundaries of the overall
game. You have agreed to play with
everyone else. You can, but then you
won't be here
anymore. It is not that you cannot step
outside it. No, that makes sense. All
right. Thank you for
you. Is there a connection with the
imagination and then creating it into
physical reality? The emotional uh
trust, ecstasy, excitement, action,
curiosity. Excitement is your physical translation
Excitement is your physical translation
of the vibration that represents the
path you chose to be. Follow it. That is
how you know that when you are having a
good time, you do not create the passage
of time.
It is not that you do not sense a time
which is passing by anyway. You do not
create time. That is why you are not
cognizant of it when you are busy having
fun. Because ecstasy, excitation and
enjoyment are being in the center point
are being completely in the now.
And being in the now allows you to
experience things as one eternal moment.
Where did the time
go? It did not go anywhere. You just
didn't create it.
You are your own universe. That does not
mean another individual will not have
sensed their creation of the passage of
time simultaneously. They will reinforce
for you to reorient you back to the
reality you still insist upon
participating within that 3 and 1/2
hours have passed just so you won't lose
track. But you did not create those 3
and 1/2 hours. If it seemed like five
minutes to you that is all you actually
created five minutes.
Yes, it is literal. So when we say we
want something as we passingly do at
times but there is no excitement no body
sensation and it's a good indication
occur. Yes that then we know we really
haven't set up the dynamics then
of creation.
Trust that the
ideas that you know you are are the ones
that vibrate that resonate within you
most strongly. And you can take it for
granted, therefore, that the ones that
do excite you are the ones that
represent the course of your path. Only
when you judge those situations to be
invalid, silly, ridiculous, worthless,
not worth
doing, not a way to make a
living. Do you ignore the excitement
that is often very blatantly there
telling you that what you have imagined
you want to do is what you can do? If no
one else does it, be the post.
I have one other question. Yes. Um I
just had a major portion of my property
uh move separate earth movement. Yes.
And I know and accept that everything that
I know and accept that everything that
occurs is part of what I've attracted.
Then how does it serve you? I I'd like
some Could you shed some light on that?
It's It's difficult for me to see. It's
difficult for me to see. Yes, it has
been difficult for me to see. It's
difficult for me to see.
Now, that is a belief. Do you enjoy that
belief?
No. All right. What belief do you
prefer?
May I make a suggestion? Yes. It is easy
for me to see. It is easy for me to see.
Oh, yes. That I prefer. All right.
Repeat after me. It is easy for me to
see. It is easy for me to see. How this
event How this event serves me serves
me. Really? [Music]
[Music]
Well, it may have a little bit of
something to do with letting go, but Oh,
all right. Removing attachments?
Yes. All thank you. Yes. Need it be more
All thank you. Yes. Need it be more
complex than that? Um, no. I don't think
so. Does that fulfill your innate sense
of how you can glean a service from the
event and keep going with your life?
Absolutely. Can you recognize that life
is the only process you need to create
all of the understanding of anything
that occurs in your life? Yes. Keep
living and you will understand it all.
Thank you. For sure. Yes.
I'm in a state of excitement over
something you said a little
earlier and I would like I would like
your help in pursuing it. You talked
about the vortex in Malibu.
I would physically go stand in that as
soon as possible. I would like I would
like your direction.
Will you help me pinpoint how I get to
it? Anywhere in that area? The entire
Anywhere in that area? The entire
Malibu. You will find it. Follow your
intuition. I've always had a soft spot
for that. I love it in that area. Then
you already have found it. Thank you.
I'll go back. Thank you.
[Music] Dad, um, I have a question about your
Dad, um, I have a question about your
like your relationship with Daryl. Good.
If if you're Daryl's future self, so to
speak, so to speak, and there's I mean,
it's kind of hard to phrase it, but um,
it's easy to phrase it. [Laughter]
[Laughter]
You learn so very quickly.
Thank you.
Do continue.
Um, if you if you are Daryl's future
self, then um Daryl must be like
my past self.
just being logical. Um,
then are are you are you two both
creatively like generating co-creating
at the same time each other? How simple
the answers are.
Yes, it is trust allowing the dimension
of the imagination on both of our parts
to be really real. You see, the
interaction that is taking place that
you perceive to be taking place between
myself and you is going on for me within
my imagination. But since I know my
imagination is real, I know the
interaction is taking place.
Whoa. You follow me? I follow you. Thank
you. Thank you. This is this whole
material. What about your what about
your previous explanation about this
link being based upon computer and etc
etc etc what you just said about
imagination would seem to eliminate the
need for all of that complexity
in a basic fundamental sense yes but we
are also still a civilization whose
definition has many specificities within
it so the idea within our imagination is
that we utilize what we call the
computer to assist and accelerate and
boost our ability to do this. That is
the product still of our imagination.
You're still having to trust that once
you get through the computer that it's
getting to us and all that stuff is
going on, right? Yes, we do recognize
that the computer is a projection in
that way. But we are still a
civilization that uses that symbol. It
has purposes for us and it has purposes
in allowing us to reflect to you certain
ideas that are in your terms easier to
understand. So we maintain a certain
level of existence in our way so that we
can communicate with other civilizations
and they can perceive us in a certain
way. So we will not be so different from
you we could not communicate with you. I
understand that last but it
seems there seems to be a dis there is a
disjunction so well you have imagination
which I'm very comfortable with the idea
that imagination is real and is the most
powerful tool we have. You are creating
your physical reality with it. We are
creating our physical reality with it.
But why not? Why not since imagination
is a senior element to the thing that
imagination creates? Yes. Why not simply
go directly from imagination to Daryl
and not bother with the via of the
computer on your planet? Why not stop
being in this reality right now?
Well, I can. Yes, you can. And so can I.
But obviously since you have chosen to
be here and we have chosen to be where
we are then the method we are using
serves the purpose of the interaction at
this time. That is not to say it will
not evolve. Would it be possible right
now as we understand it now for you to
dispense with a computer and simply do
this just with imagination or would
there be is the computer providing a
link between your density in a sense and
ours? Yes. And again it is not that that
cannot also be circumvented simply by
imagination but simply in this way we
must take into account in our factors
the overall belief structures within
your mass consciousness. The idea of the
direct interaction is usually what
occurs with what you would perceive to
be the serious energy and the physical
channel before you. The serious energy
does not use the idea of a computer. But
as you can also see in that way, the
energy level of the serious entity is
something that the physical channel you
call Daryl cannot tolerate for very
long, right? Because it is that much
more of a magnitude beyond the ideas you
are familiar with. That is why we are
doing what we are doing in the way we
are doing it to facilitate the ease of
accommodation according to the overall
belief structures of your society and
the physical channel of course. Okay.
But is it merely that you where you're
physically apparent are imagining this
interaction and therefore it's occurring
and it's real. Or are you in some way
traveling like astral projection and
being here with us astrally? No. Not the
latter but the former. Yes. Now I can
and have in your terms physically
traveled to your planet. In your terms,
I know you physically exist.
I see. In this way, simply I am
describing that what you would refer to
as the mechanism of this interaction is
that it would be the same as if you were
to simply lie down, close your eyes, and
imagine having a conversation with a
group of individuals on another planet
and take it for granted that is real and
is going on. As we went to your
spaceship the last last week. Yes.
But when you came here physically, did
you come with your body or ast in my
spacecraft? In your spacecraft. Yes. Can
you travel in what's what we call on
this planet astrally? Yes. So to go
without your body but still perceiving
it. Oh yes.
How does the serious energy come through
astrally or through their imagination?
Now more again the idea of imagination
but imagination to them is something
quite different and encompasses many of
the levels you might call astral and
atheric and many different other levels
altogether because to them materiality
is very unreal.
Thank you for sure. Yeah, sure.
Briefly. Briefly. Nice. Okay. Um, unless
you choose to continue after your break.
choose to continue after your break.
That would be fine with me. All right.
Then you may all take a short
break. All right. I'll
say continue.
Thank you. There's an individual that I
talked to, his name is Dr.
Kirk and I was wondering if
um if he was outside of myself or if he
was as you say that um relationship with
Daryl is if that's how our relationship
is. Is he is he an entity separate from
myself? sense. Now understand in this way there
sense. Now understand in this way there
is the opportunity to see within your
reflection that all aspects of your
consciousness that you can be in contact
with can represent portions of yourself
and at the same time have their own
reality. In what way does it serve you
to feel either case?
It had never occurred to me before that
it would be
um part of my
imagination, but that just thought came
to me because of what you were saying
earlier about you and Darl. I had always
thought he was totally outside of
myself. Understand? Something that is a
portion of your higher consciousness is
not something just within your
imagination. You're following. It's his imagination,
You're following. It's his imagination,
too.
What we are saying in this way is that
your imagination is real.
Yeah, I understand that. All right, I
understand that. How does it serve you
to relate to the consciousness as
something within you? How does it serve
you to relate to it as something outside
of you, so to speak?
I I don't know about inside of me.
Outside of me, he's
He um can heal and I like that.
Is there something different about what
you would call his medical technology
than from what you recognize to be the
medical technology of your planet? Oh,
absolutely. Does it involve mostly the idea of light
Does it involve mostly the idea of light
and sound or vibrations?
Yes. Yes.
It's all the it all comes through and
the surgery is all done through his
hand. All
right. In this way,
therefore, does the surroundings the
natural environment of this individual
seem not
unlike your typical reality but somehow
different? Yes. Then recognize in a way
that you can view the aspect of the
consciousness as other
consciousness but in what you would call
a parallel earth dimension.
Follow it. And in that sense an aspect
of your future self as you are making a
link up in that way to a portion of your
higher consciousness that allows itself
to have a life in a parallel reality
that has the ability to transfer its
communication to other parallel lives
such as you.
That was pretty quick what you just
said. I'm sorry. The idea that you are
dealing with an aspect of yourself that
from the oversoul has created a life in
that parallel time frame that has the
ability to communicate consciously with
other aspects of itself. Those aspects
and other parallel dimensions such as
yourselves that are willing to receive
the communication. Yes.
Okay. I understand. So in that let us
say life in that universe in that
parallel reality now this is actually a
reality now this is actually a
misnomer but you are that doctor but it
is not you. It is that portion of the
oversoul that is both the doctor and
you. I understand.
I understand.
May I ask you something else? You said
that portion or aspect of ones that are
willing to receive. Yes. Okay. If this
is happening
then is there something that I can do to
serve him or first of all that you have
received is a service. First of all that
you have acknowledged is a service for
allow that individual to expand his
awareness and your awareness so that
there can be a link up of all the
fragments of the total consciousness in
all parallel reality.
Being of service in whatever way your
imagination so delineates, you can
utilize the information to allow the
information to
allow the individual in that sense to
channel through if you wish or to simply
utilize what you can learn from that
individual and apply that knowledge
here. All of those ideas can be of
service. It is up to you. What you
prefer, what excites you will be of
service to that individual. The fact
that you are accepting the contact is
service itself.
Thank you for
Is that link up between the two? Is that
the quote unquote me that I will not uh
allow myself to realize at this point in
time? Not so much directly that, but the
idea of the future of you who you can be
in this
universe. What do you imagine you are
not allowing yourself to become?
Well, I I would assume that I already
am. In fact, I already am.
Um, but I'm not allowing myself to
become. What are you not allowing
yourself to become?
You must have some concept of what it
is. Yeah, I do. I'm just trying I'm
just, you know, uh trying to phrase it.
Uh
phrase it however you wish. That's what
I'm doing. Oh, right.
Okay. Um one who
can completes many many cycles of action
very quickly. One who
completes many cycles of action.
Define a cycle of action.
Um start change. Stop.
Many of you have heard of that. Start,
change, stop.
There's But you are doing that every
moment that you exist. True.
So what are you looking for that would
be different than that? Um the gifts
that I turn away on a daily basis. Turn
away. What gifts? The gifts that I give
to myself. The gifts of life that I
present to myself and I might turn away.
How do you turn them away? Are you
saying you do not act upon opportunities
that you bring to yourself? That's
correct. All right. How does it serve
you to act on the opportunities that you
do act upon?
All the ones that you do not turn away.
Uh it enables me to
um have more time or devote more energy
to uh
um becoming a more enlightened uh fuller
person. How and why do you assume though it is a
How and why do you assume though it is a
very valid way to do it that you cannot
do that also by acting upon the
opportunities you bring to yourself?
Well, that's that was my
point. But in this way, what are you
saying you would gain that would be
different by acting than what you are
already doing when you do
act? If you are recognizing that you are
still in your terms gaining
enlightenment based upon what you do act
upon, why are you regretting the ones
you do not?
Well, before this evening, I didn't
realize what I I didn't realize the
mechanism at all. So, I'm still
exploring it. Oh, are you having a good
time at all this? Oh, absolutely. Oh,
very good. Then, in this way, there is
no need for remorse at all. Of course.
Thank you very much. Thank you. [Music] [Music]
You're welcome.
For sure, guys.
Uh it seems like we have gotten into a
situation uh where we forget our past
lives. Uh I guess the group here the
whole this planet. Uh does your planet
when they have the children do they
remember their past lives and they fully
retain all they can but that is not the
point of our civilization to remember
our past lives. What about the
information they've learned or the
skills or things like that? All
information to us that is necessary to
be there will be there in the moment it
is needed.
The idea that you will find in your
acceleration into fourth density is that
not only will you not need to remember
your past lives, you will not need to
remember the past of this life. You will
know what you need to know in the moment
you need to know it.
Memory will be recognized for what it
is. Creation in the now
moment. Anything you are calling a
memory, you are still creating in the
present. You are only making an attachment that
You are only making an attachment that
it comes from the past. It doesn't. It
comes from now.
Memory itself does. Yeah. Yes.
Therefore, you will find that many of
you will begin to exhibit one of the
symptoms of fourth density
transformation. You will begin to forget
your past.
[Music] Judging that you have a past worth
Judging that you have a past worth
forgetting in the
present is what keeps it in your memory.
Right.
One other question. Yes.
Um you mentioned earlier about the fact
that every death is suicide. uh in an
overall fundamental definition is there
a way of actually leaving the body
without leaving the body and having it
still alive where it's you know you mean
astral projection well no I mean on a
permanent basis where you wouldn't be
killing the body why would the body be
alive the only way you can leave it and
the body be alive is if someone else
takes it over what you call a walked in
so you could actually exchange that oh
yes common situation
many indiv Individuals in this way
obviously are still attached to their
body by one way or another, one means or
another, one reason, one purpose or
another. Who could have bodies? They can see.
Who could have bodies? They can see.
Understand that in what you call further
on in the fourth density reality, it
will not be uncommon for there to be
very few bodies physically upon the
planet that many souls will share in and
out, off and on.
Because you will not need to maintain a
constant existence in physical reality.
And then when you transfer from fourth
to fifth, no existence in physical
reality anymore at all.
Mhm.
Does this answer your question? Yes, it
does. Thank you. Thank you. Yes. Thank
you. Didn't mean to interrupt. Um I have
a question also that I'd like to ask
you. When you speak of the fourth
density, density. Thank you. That that's
not the same as a plane that you're
talking about. Yes, in a sense it is.
You are accelerating into another plane
of existence, another state of
awareness. So another term you could say
the fourth plane Can you talk about your
Yes.
Does that clarify the idea?
It is a state of existence in which you
in a sense see through the illusion of
the third plane.
You follow me? Yeah. All right. One
moment. Male. Yes. Thank you. Um, last
week I female. Last week I chose not to
come here simply because I was attracted to
here simply because I was attracted to
stay home. Yes.
And thanks John. You're a great
audience. The simplest joke. Boy. Um now
normally well for the past year and a
half about year almost I've been
attracted to come and just this was
strange that I was attracted to stay
home and I was kind of wondering why
that was but I wasn't wasn't being too
uh analytical about it. I just felt like
staying home. No. Right.
Yeah. However, I thought
well the reason that I'm feeling this
way will manifest if I just continue to
live. Yes. So, I continued to live and
the reason that I chose to stay home,
yes, has not specifically manifested.
Yes, it has.
Can you help me with that? It manifested
so blatantly and so simply you didn't
recognize it.
Thank you.
You chose to stay home.
It is simply a matter of the opportunity
of you allowing yourself to know you
have a choice. Well, that's true. But
it's more complex than that.
Must be more complex. I'm not saying
it's more complex. I'm saying I already
have that lesson learned. I know that my
choices are very much my own. So, one
moment. One moment. One moment. Okay.
You are making the assumption that
already having a lesson learned means
you do not have the choice of exercising
it again.
But I didn't need to. It is not a matter
of needing to. It is a matter of that is
what you desired.
It does not matter that you know you can
make choices. That does not mean you
cannot continue to make choices. And I
do continue to make choices. Every time
I come here, it's just as much a choice
to come here as it was to stay home.
Right? And that is the whole point. That
is all there is to it.
That is all there is to it. See, I don't
believe that. Aha.
But what do you believe? Well, I believe
possibly instead of making a choice to
to I am goating you, you know.
Undoubtedly. All right. Just wanted that
to be clear. Thank you. I don't know
why, but
uh I'm thinking that perhaps it was not
so much a choice to stay there rather
than a choice not to come here.
So if there was a choice not to come
here, what was it that I was choosing to
stay away from?
Well, I'm not asking you, Eric.
Perhaps you can shed some light on this
for sure. Maybe you
Maybe you
thought I would bore
you. Maybe you
knew that I would have nothing to say
that evening that would be of interest
to you.
Maybe. Maybe.
I I believe that this is something that
I haven't fully
consciously pinpointed. That's why I'm
asking you to reflect that if I am to
the best of the ability of the
co-creation we are creating. I am okay.
Let me ask you this. Of course, not
having been here last week, I didn't
know what I was quote missing unquote
or what I wasn't going to co-create with
you and the group. I did find out that
you all took a trip up to your
spacecraft. Huh?
It did. It did hit me in such a way that
uh I thought, well, maybe I specifically
stayed away in order not to experience
that.
Maybe, but I don't know why.
You know what? What? Me neither.
Does that surprise you?
Yes and no. Oh, why yes? Why no?
One moment.
Every idea that you are present to hear
has something to do with you or you
wouldn't hear it. Right? There is no
such thing as a boring interaction
unless you are simply not willing to
apply the same questions and statements
to yourself to see how they apply.
Catch my drift. Yeah.
Why? Yes. Why? Okay. It doesn't surprise
me because I know that you can perceive
what's going on in my
uh space or however you want to term it.
Um to the degree that I am communicating
it with you at those levels. Yeah.
I'm not always consciously aware of how
much I am communicating to you on those
levels. So if you say no it you don't
know why it's um I'm not surprised
because I'm think I realize well
obviously I'm not communicating it even
though I'm notware aware of how much I
am communicating. So does this answer
both yes and no? Yes, it does. Thank
you. Um
Um
okay there's there's one other thing
here. A couple of weeks ago, I asked
you about my
experience in being attracted to one of
our uh
aircraft and knowing that it had some
relationship to my future um energy that I have
to my future um energy that I have
toward perceiving spacecraft in my May I
interrupt you for a moment? Please do.
All right. Maybe just maybe only maybe
this may shed some light as you say
please in your imagination right now.
Yes. Is
there one thing or let us say what is
the strongest thing that you could
strongest thing that you could
imagine that you could come face to face
to that you would not want to come face
to face to? What pops into your
imagination? Anything at all? Something that I would
Anything at all? Something that I would
not want to come face to face to. What
is the strongest thing you would not
want to come face to face to? Oh, it's
like uh it's about 7 ft tall and it's uh
green and slimy and big and huge and has
tentacles like snakes.
Are you saying that that is the thing
that would truly truly be the most
fearful thing you could ever face? Truly
the most fearful. Well, when you asked
me the question, that was the first
thing that came to mind. All right. I
could probably search it around and come
up with something else. No, no, no, no,
no, no.
But what I'm looking I am asking you
another question. I am not asking you to
invalidate the first one. I am simply
asking you another question. Well, you
know, I asked you about my fears and and
whether I
was I felt that I was quite fearless and
um indicated that I I know what you
mean. Okay. And uh I didn't I forgot to
ask you the second part of the question
that week that I asked the question and
I was like was I fooling myself in in
believing I was fearless or or was there
something I'm truly Thank you again by
stating that I know what you mean. I am
simply recognizing that you know that
you always contain the probability of
expressing fear but that you choose to
recognize fear as your threat and in
that way you can say you are fearless I
didn't completely follow that
always you will contain the possibility
of being fearful yes always but if you
choose to recognize your fear as your
friend you will never manifest the
negative effect that you normally call
fear fear and in that way you can say
you are fearless. True. Well, in fact, I
have looked at this concept and
uh realize that if something
occurs, if I experience something that I
create the idea of fear, I am able to
look at that fear and go, "Oh, I'm
feeling this fear." But not not allow it
to create negative effects on me. In
fact, I created an incident a few years
ago in which I I guess some kind of
entity was uh in my living room hanging
around my overhead light fixture. And as
I approached the entity, it was I was
co-creating the idea of it flowing
fear flows at me. Yeah. And I was going
this is really interesting. It's I'm
create co-creating fear with it. But I
was not fearful. I was not creating any
sort sense of negative manifestation as
a result. I was just kind of enjoying
the sensations of the fear. Yes. And
from this I derived that I truly was
fearless in that I would never respond
in a way that would be negative to this
emotion of fear. Oh, very good. May I
thank you for this wonderful interaction
and remind you that this is all quite
beside the point. But in this way, it is
beside the point on purpose. For in this
way, the idea of what it is you are
asking is not so much that you are
avoiding anything here. nor specifically
being attracted to anything at home. It
is one of those things in that way as we
perceive it that is simply part of the
actual fabric of the way you do things
in the sense that you had a good reason
for simply not traveling the course you
may normally travel because it may have
led to things that simply would not
serve you in that way. These ideas
following your equational paths are not
necessarily something that will stand
out to let you know specifically what it
was you may have been avoiding or being
attracted to in that way, but simply are
your innate knowingness that simply
taking the path you may have taken was
not the path you need to take that night
and it would not have served you the
best because there may have been the
opportunity for interactions in this way
that would not represent the vibration
of the reality you are. These things are
not prone to stand out simply because
they are a part and parcel of the way
you go about doing
things. Is any of this coming through?
Yes. Thank you for reminding me of that
because it did I did conceive of that at
one time. It was last Wednesday that I
conceive of that. I had forgotten. Thank
you for reminding me of that. You are
welcome. Thank you for being open enough
to allow me to remind you. Certainly.
Can I ask you one other thing? You you
have referred to the way I do things.
Now I know how I do things but I would
appreciate your viewpoint. Well, I was
not being specific. Okay. I was simply
saying that an individual in life will
simply go about doing things one way or
another. And many of the going about and
doing the things in and of themselves
will represent paths that are taken for
a reason, though they will not surface
consciously. Otherwise, you'll be too
busy watching every step you make. This
is why these things do not make
themselves evident. When you choose to
do one thing or another, you may result
in a realization of knowing you have
made a choice. But the realizing as to
why is not really very paramount because
it was only a choice made to allow
yourself to take the path of least
resistance. Yeah, got it. Thank you.
Thank you very much. Yes.
Yes.
Um, last week after my channeling class,
I had a dream in
which in the dream it wasn't clear
whether Joseph or myself was channeling
an entity called
Vona. Um, and since I am just beginning the
Um, and since I am just beginning the
class, I have not yet discovered whether
I will be
channeling this entity or not. Then we
will let you find out. Okay. This week
at the end of the class I
dreamed that I was
channeling Monocles who I know someone
else is channeling. All right.
Um can you shed some light on that?
only again that it does still in our
again that it does still in our
perception represent the idea of one
oversoul attempting to manifest
conscious reality and conscious
recognition of its existence in all of
its fragments. Okay.
Okay.
Thank you. May I ask you all a question?
Yes. Yes.
Has there been any increase in frequency
in your dream realities of the inclusion
of what you would call cats?
Yes.
Yes. All right. Thank you. That is all.
Next. [Music]
[Music]
Is there anything or type of physical
exercise that you recommend in opening
ourselves up to a higher level of
knowingness other than the imagination?
Oh, other than that one. Well, no.
Other than the only thing that
encompasses everything you need.
So just imagining it and thinking that
it is so knowing knowing that is so is
now understand that you do not have to
strain and struggle to know it is so.
Daydream enjoy it. That in a sense is
knowing it is so. Enjoying it. Going
along for the ride. Just having the
experience and letting yourself
experience it. It is knowing it is so. All right.
All right.
Thank you.
Yes. There is an entity whose name is
Devon um that I've dreamt about several times
um that I've dreamt about several times
and I the name even daydream it comes up
and a friend of mine just we were
playing around the other day and she
took my ring and she sort of play with
she said Don who's
Ivonne and uh I've been playing with an
Ivonne and I have no idea who it is
This will be a case where there is
recommended a specific
methodology by which you may wish to
play around with as long as you allow
yourself to maintain a likeness of
attitude, a playful attitude and not be
steeped in what you call the negativity
that has been attached to this specific
method that you can utilize to allow
there to be clearer communication. In
that way, this is unusual as a recommendation
way, this is unusual as a recommendation
at this time since it is such a specific
tool. But like any tool, it is valid and
we are simply sensing that the
recommendation comes with a recognition
that it may be valid for certain
portions of you. You can begin it if you
wish. You do not have to and you can end
it any time you wish. But the
recommendation is that you can find
yourself in closer contact with this
consciousness if you use the device that
you call a Ouija board.
We will let you play with that.
Uh can you uh explain exactly what the
chakras are in terms of energy fields or
what in a sense they represent the
doorways or
gateways through which you are and to
which you are connected to the matrix of
all that
is. It is the crossing points, the
fulcrum points, the reinforced
overlapping points in the energy pattern that you
points in the energy pattern that you
are that represents where all probable
realities come together to create the
flow into your specific universe that
creates the reality you perceive
yourselves to be. All chakras are
doorways that contain all probable
realities. They are transfer stations,
if you wish.
Are are there truly colors associated
with the different ones? Yes,
vibrational understanding. Although now
they are beginning to blend in this
transformational age. They are not so
specific anymore. Though they still
retain some degree of specificity.
They are all beginning to contain all
colors. Thank you.
Um, first I I'm curious why why would we
dream of cats?
In this way, they are symbolically
representative of an animal that
consciously exists within third and
fourth density simultaneously.
But why would we dream of those? Because
as you allow animal consciousness to
reflect to you changes going on within
your own consciousness, many of you may
begin to be making associations with
that animal more and more in your
dreams. As you find they are passing
through your dream realities all the
time, you may simply allow yourself to
recognize them and follow them to
different portions of your
consciousness. The animals have opted to
function this way for you. Many of you
may begin to be listening to them in
that way specifically. Not that you have
to, but many of you may have
associations with that animal in that
way. sensing the power of their ability
to bridge both levels at the same time.
We have discussed this ability has
existed within certain civilizations on
your planet, the American Indian culture
being one of them, wherein they
recognized consciously that they existed
really in physical and non-physical
reality simultaneously and many
different dimensions of existence. This
is what the cat be like all the time.
is we also see um this reality within
rocks and plants. Oh, of course. I'm not
saying it has to be a cat. Uhhuh. Just
that it is something that does represent
a common symbol within this particular
society. Uhhuh. Well, a funny thing
happened last week. Oh, funny things. I
love funny things. More synchronicity.
Yes. Yes.
My son got a coupon in the mail, which
is unusual because we very seldom get
mail. All right. But the coupon said,
"Good for one free can of cat food."
So he went he went to the store and got
a free can of cat food. So we put it on
the shelf. So I said, "This has
something to do with what's coming." So
we left it there. And then a few days
later, a friend dropped off a small cat.
And but it couldn't eat the cat food
because it was so small, it hardly had
its eyes open. I had to feed it with a
dropper. Oh, right.
Well, we had it a few days. Yes. And and
uh we didn't know whether to keep it or
not. So I realized that you never really
keep animals. No, they choose you. They
come into this space and then they
leave. So the cat went back to where he
came from.
And uh we still have the can of cat.
I guess there's another one coming.
But I've always found that in your I do
this in in present time most Indian
people did it's called Indian time it's
when when when it gets done and when you
get there you know. Yes. And uh
all things being the same.
Yeah. And
so it's the same with you have things of
your as you you call your past which are
momentos but you momentos like
photographs but you also in your present
have things of your future. Yes. But
you're not really cognizant of that
until the future occurs and then you say
oh that's why I had that in my space in
a sense. So so what you do is you you
relate the two. Yes.
So, this cat thing you're talking about,
I do have a feeling that cats are coming
around. But what has that got to do with
this reality? Simply in this way, again,
reality? Simply in this way, again,
since the cats are in this reality, and
since your consciousness recognizes
their ability, many of you have placed,
even if it is only in what you call in
the western civilization, a
superstitious attachment to them, it is
still a subconscious recognition of what
they represent as the ability to be on two
represent as the ability to be on two
planes at once.
Does that clarify it? Yeah, it does
clarify. Fine.
Yeah, um these vibrational rates, would
you liken those to in a sense a strobe
when one is perceiving and then it's off
that period between creation and
non-creation, creation, non-creation.
Whereas the the greater the density, the
more it's aware of the on period in a
sense. Yes, you can put it that way. And
it is not so much that the idea is that
noncreation in between but that all
other realities exist in between each
other's moments.
Okay. One other thing um so to speak.
Yeah. In the formulation of meaning of
words, the actual symbols themselves,
the shape of the the letters and such.
Someone expressed to me once something
very what was the word he used? Oult.
All right. Um hidden. Mhm.
um existing in whatever range it exists
in a a meaning plate a plate where the
shape of the letter the name the
individual's name would would intersect
and trans like a J for example would go
through existence and eternity and and
does that is that plate is that a a
known thing is yes although it will vary
from reality to reality
from universe to universe Okay. So it's
an arbitrary thing. It's not a
universally established. It is universal
to some
extent. But there is more to the idea of
universe than what you are labeling.
Yeah. some some letters some very like
Zoroest or Zoro or Zeus all these very
specific names uh with very
unusual vibrational reality in general
in your archetypal mass consciousness to
a certain
extent other universes do not see it the
same way oh I see
what is what function does that serve is
that just is that sort of transfer of
symbolic it yes symbolic of the idea
that everything is a vibrational pattern
and that you can reclaim so to speak.
Okay. The essence of the power in the
vibration that you are in that way.
Good. Good could one that is the
original usage of what you call
incantations.
Magic. the recognition of the
vibrational signature of a specific
reality, the ability to unlock it and
change it to another vibrational
signature. Okay. So called
abracadabra, right? Um one thing about symbols,
right? Um one thing about symbols,
there's a aspect of me which I can
occasionally integrate with and which I
am simultaneously and divided with at
times. Yes. Yes. that
um I'm committed to symbols. I use the
car. I you know, for example, a Cadillac
would represent elegance or prestige. A
house would represent this or that.
Depends upon the current notion. Okay.
There are aspects of me which will not
integrate with me because I am in
creation. I am in those realms of
creation and destruction. Um in symbols.
I need symbols rather than the raw
materials. You have chosen to be physically in
You have chosen to be physically in
existence. Therefore, the entire reality
that you are experiencing through your
senses is a symbol. Yes. Okay. By
definition, you are using symbols. All
right. All right. The question is I'm
asking because I use symbols instead of
the raw
materials, would evolution for me be
outgrowing those those tools? Is that
that is a general concept for everyone
but again it is not that you need to
outgrow them while you are still using
them. You will in your terms outgrow them when
You will in your terms outgrow them when
you don't need them. Okay. And I find
that the impact of words the essence of
words. I'm very very slow reader but
when I see a word it's just like 12
dimensions or many dimensions open up
for me. That is your way of exploring
this universe.
Okay. Thank you. Thank you. Bashar.
Yes. Um, I've always been very
interested in cats and I have some
questions I'd like to explore. Brief.
Yes. Um, when cats curl up and go to sleep,
Um, when cats curl up and go to sleep,
they are really exploring out of the
body. Is this
Sometimes they are even when they are
walking around.
All right. Um, they have that ability.
Yes, I had a cat
recently. Um, I had her for several
years actually and we were quite good
friends and
um then she died and
I well I was very griefstricken when I
realized that she was gone and then I
found her body. It was just like she
curled up and went to sleep. All right.
I still um I really don't think of her
as dead because I still feel her around
and I talk to her. Life is eternal. Yes.
I I'm wondering what was her reason for
leaving at that specific time?
What was going on in your life? Well, I
had a lover. Yes. And we were exploring,
you know, closeness in many on many
levels actually. Yeah. Um And I
was well it occurred to me that that she
felt I kept getting this idea that she
was going to die but I didn't know if I
was creating that or if I was getting
that from her. I couldn't I couldn't
obviously both.
It was a co-agment in that way.
Did it allow you to recognize that you
could now begin to function in the same
manner and did not need the symbol of
the cat's presence?
Thank you. Yes, I thought of that. All
right, then you have it. All right.
Thank you.
You um I wanted to ask you, what can we
learn from our dreams? What can they My
goodness. What you learn?
Okay, maybe then you could help me
interpret some. For instance, a dream I
had last night had to do uh with a
feeling uh that I had. The family that I had was
uh that I had. The family that I had was
not the correct family in the sense of
feeling foreign to me and feeling like
there was some kind of mixup and that's
all right. Okay. can be a sensation that
in a sense you are dealing with the
belief system that you are not
natural to this location.
Okay, that's that's very real to me. But
uh is it is there any way to expand upon
that? I mean knowing you shouldn't be
here doesn't tell you where you should
be. Oh no no no
no. That is not what we meant. There is
no such thing as being where you should
not be by definition. It cannot happen.
You chose to be here. That is why you
are here. So obviously in a sense you
should be here. It is not that you do
not belong. In that sense it is that you
believe you do not belong. You're not
allowing yourself to recognize that you
obviously made a choice in being where
you are. Allow yourself to recognize the
idea in your imagination of what it is
you have chosen to be here for. Then in
being of service in that way, it will
begin to feel more natural to you. In
this way, it is not a detrimental thing
in your dream. It is simply the
recognition that you have things to do,
but that you have made attachments to
the things you are going to be doing to
a time and a place that is elsewhere.
You have given yourself reason for being
where you are by basing it upon reasons
you created in another time and place so
to
speak. You are simply now becoming aware
of those reasons as you begin to explore
the idea of the services you will be
providing. Those awakenings will come to
bear. They will come to the forefront of
your consciousness. This does not mean
you are in the wrong place. It simply is
the beginning of the recognition of from
when and where you made the original
agreement to be where you are. You
follow me? Um, not as completely as I'd
like to, but I kind of get the drift.
All right, then you have, but as
completely as you need to. Okay. Thank
you. Thank you, guys. Yeah, Vishar. Um,
I'm a pregnant mother with my baby due
to arrive in a few weeks. And throughout
this, this is my third pregnancy and I
this time I just didn't feel like
dealing with the medical lines, so I've
skipped that. All right, which feels
fine with me, guys. And now the baby's
due in two weeks, and I still don't feel
like going and finding a doctor. All
right. And um I don't know why I'm
saying this really. Yes, it is.
And everyone knows it.
I don't know. Um, well, oh, come now.
Well, actually, what I'd like to do is
just go ahead and have a baby. Have a
good time.
I I Happy birthday.
[Laughter] Oh, that's good. And another thing, this
Oh, that's good. And another thing, this
this might be a little embarrassing.
That's why I'm going to say it, but I
Well, you are devaluing what you have to
say. Oh yeah.
Oh yeah.
Okay. Well, I in my second pregnancy,
guys, I had a very vivid dream that I
had kittens. I gave birth to kittens.
And I remember in the dream, this was
fine. I thought kids. That's fine. It
was fine until I thought, well, now I've
got to call mom. Oh, no. I have kittens.
I'm [Music]
[Music]
sorry. My judge. Oh,
okay. Now, in the third pregnancy, which
is this pregnancy about a month ago, I
had a very vivid dream that that I gave
birth and it just the baby came right
through the stomach. There was no
physical stuff. Just
he was
a a a big white rabbit.
Is your name Alice? Not lately.
Not lately.
around symbolize
big white ones can symbolize the idea
that you already ascribe to what you
call your
wait I don't get through the looking
glass puka very good I don't get it I
puka very good I don't get it I
particular all right what is um you mean
it is going within going into the inner
world in this way and the idea of the
archetypal Tuka is a reflection of archetypal
Tuka is a reflection of archetypal
animal
consciousness. Other portions of the
subconsciousness which manifest
themselves in forms that represent
different portions of your consciousness
that you are now in touch with that are
in a sense more magical than you are
willing to believe can exist in the
normal day-to-day existence. Oh, okay.
They bring you from the seen into the
unseen world and make it seeable.
And the idea of viewing your children as
cats and rabbits are both reflections of
the fact that you know that these
children are coming now and will know
exactly who they are and will remind
you. Oh, definitely. Yeah, that's very
real to me. then you are simply using
symbols that represent their knowing
ability to exist in more than one level
at a time.
Oh, that's neat.
In other words, in this way, you may
find that what you call your second
child may exhibit some of the
detachment of the cat.
The rabbit child may exhibit some of the
intense curiosity and
burrowing into the depths of the
consciousness. Oh, how about the first one? I didn't
Oh, how about the first one? I didn't
have so many animals with her. What did
you have?
Gosh, I don't know. Well, she well she's
very um
if you were to attach in your
imagination without thinking about it
the idea of a symbolic animal to the
child, what would you pick? Yeah, bird.
All right. Thank you. That will speak
for itself. Yeah.
Thank you. Oh, one little question.
Okay. I once had a squirrel show up my
room. What does squirrels signify?
You're nuts. [Music] [Laughter]
[Laughter]
But they can signify the ideal to some
degree of the storage and then the
bringing to the surface of ideas that
have been buried.
Oh, thanks.
Okay. And he showed up one night in our
house. I mean, he the squirrel
materialized and then
dematerialized. Of course, at the time,
I was coming out of a religion that
considers when you come out, you're a
squirrel.
Is that is
that hot?
[Music] Thank you. For your creative expression.
Thank you. For your creative expression.
Yes. Uh I just wanted to ask you are
there any particular methods that more
methods method methods which uh would enhance
method methods which uh would enhance
the accuracy of dream interpretation.
Yes. Honesty with yourself.
willingness to not
fear and above and beyond allowing
yourself to recognize that you can treat
everything, every object, every person,
every emotion, every scenario in the
dream as you. Yeah. And ask yourself
what it feels like to be that idea. And
it will be very clear as to what it
means. Just that's it. Just ask what it
feels like.
Ask yourself, I am this idea in my
dream. And what I have to say to myself
is
very simple. You are everything in your
dream. Be everything. Discontinue to remove
Be everything. Discontinue to remove
things and place them outside yourself.
Be everything and the meaning will be
clear. Okay. Actually, that's the way I
have been doing it. But at times I find
that I'll come up against a symbol.
Maybe not a particular person, but a
symbol in which I try to gain a feeling
for that symbol, but either the feeling
doesn't come true. Many symbols that do
not relate very closely to your physical
reality are simply expressions of the
fact that in your dream reality, you are
on a plane or level of existence that
has very little to do with your physical
reality. and your physical ego picks the
symbol that most closely represents the
experience but many times cannot find a
symbol that would really really
represent it then it's just not
important to not in that way simply
trust that you have absorbed it on
whatever level you need to and go on
is that yes
I have a question about um this what
what a ruby signify because I have a
recollection I used to wear a ruby
necklace. And I don't recall the exact
meaning of it, but I know it was very
important. Did it rest over your heart?
Yes.
One, two, three,
four. Where did it rest?
Right here.
Over your Over my heart. heart. Well, [Laughter] well, well,
um, so
so
it has connections to
to your vibration.
in the chakra of the
Well, it isn't the chakra of your big
toe. [Laughter]
[Laughter]
Are you having a good time?
Yeah, I I was just curious about that. I
know. Just
curious. No such thing as idle
curiosity. Follow your curiosity and
trust your
imagination. It represents the vibration
of the chakra of your heart.
Oh, thank you very one
thank you very one
moment. Thank me. What for?
Well, for for your um feedback.
Feedback. All right.
All right.
Now, can you allow yourself to feel the
vibration, the deep pulsing vibration of
the ruby?
Can you feel it? Can you imagine it? Can
you see it? Can you sense it? The
vibrant red.
Yes. No. Maybe. Yeah. All right.
What does it feel like?
Uh, it feels like life. Oh, very good.
Yeah. Do you feel it strongly in certain
Do you feel it strongly in certain
portions of your body?
More like all over. All right. Is it
warm? Yes. All right.
And it is strong.
Yes. Yeah. Then follow that
pulse. Pulse. Pulse. Pulse. Okay.
Okay.
Thank you. Okay.
Yes. Um, you mentioned cats. Um, I've
been I did
in dreams. Well, I suppose maybe in
passing. All right.
Um, I've been dreaming a lot
about lions. Oh, big cat.
Big cat. And I have a long history of
dreaming about jaguars. Yes. But the
lions, that is a connection to a past
life. Go on.
Um the
um the dreams in which I experienced the
lions Yes. were also with a series of
dreams that involved jewels. Yes. Like
jewels um as if jewels had been. Yes.
Well, go ahead. Yes. They like all the
colors of the jewels. Yes. The chakra
colors. Yes. and as if they had been
stolen from someplace and they were
dropped always like in the grass in
brilliant green grass. All right. And I
was wondering if you could give me some
idea of what do you have any attachment
also to any gold ornamentation
maybe more specifically with what you
call the jaguar
I'm conscious all right how about the
sun
um the Um, I mean, not consciously, but
when you said it, it it did it spark in
your imagination.
Um, radiant energy. Um, and where were
you receiving this radiant energy?
Uh, third eye and well, at the base of
my neck. All right. Were you standing in
a particular location? In the jungle.
Oh, very good.
Anything else?
Um, it's it seems as though the sun is
um coming
through streaming through the
vegetation. All
right. Is there anything
nearby besides the animal
where you live?
Define your home. Think of home. What do
you see?
Um, I just see um what I would associate
as temple. Very good. What took you so
long?
You know where you are.
Aztec. Very good.
Is that the lions and the jaguar or is
the lions separate? Lions are more
Egyptian. But there is a similarity and a
But there is a similarity and a
parallelity to the two lives.
And the jewels are part of that. Yes.
Since you were in a sense priestly or
royal in both. Also, you
Also, you
were a thief.
A royal thief. [Music]
[Music]
Other lives in similar situations.
You did the polarity idea, the royalty
of the thief.
Fabulous. The I remember two dreams in
which the lions the first
dream we were driving in through a
jungle and the driver of the car was
also like a circus leader. He brought
a female
lion and then in another
dream he brought a male lion to heal
them both. Can you give me any insight into
both. Can you give me any insight into
the healing or what the meaning of
those? Is there some
land you wish to go back to? To to touch
to breathe the atmosphere, the dust, the
earth to touch? I think the only land
that I have that kind of desire to go
back to is Greece. All right, you can
begin there and retrace your steps.
Okay. Thank you very much.
What is it about uh so many of us who
are allergic to cats?
[Laughter]
again and quite obviously it can simply
be one reason can simply be the
rejection of the
blending the rejection of your ability
to extend your senses into all those
different levels.
So you reject the symbol that represents
that ability.
But uh physically I mean I really do
have a lovely person
at least consciously but I still can't
is that uh when you allow yourself more
opportunity to experience the
reality of living in that atmosphere
comfortably then the atmosphere they
have around and about them in their oric
fields will not bother you
once you make it your own.
Okay. Uh, I want to share something real
fast. Um, I was on the beach the other
morning and um, for a considerable
amount of time I've I've been fairly
broke and I was on the beach running the
other morning and I realized that the
lack of money because I I'm in Malibu
and I've been living there for a while
as you know. It occurred to me that if I
had money, I'd be out playing and having
a good time and going places and and
because I don't have money, I go to the
beach every morning and I do things
there and I enjoy what's there, right?
And I really it's like it was like a
total revelation. Oh, thank you very
much for recognizing that you are
exactly as abundant as you need to be to
go to the places that you have decided
to enjoy for now. Thank you. Thank you.
Yes.
Uh I wanted to know if there's any
different any difference in the
symbology of a black panther to other
cats. Obviously, otherwise it would not
be a different cat.
What is it? You tell me. Secrecy.
Very good. One idea attributed to the past.
good. One idea attributed to the past.
many civilizations utilizing that symbol
to represent the occult or the mystic
arts. And it is also why you feel still
so connected to the idea of having a
black cat cross your path.
when it represents the stepping over of
a threshold,
the crossing of a path in that way that
leads you to the portions of yourself
that have been hidden for so long that
you simply usually associate a fearful
attachment to that does not have to have
one. I see. Well, I found myself never I
was I've never been allergic to cats,
but I did I experienced being allergic
to one particular cat.
Um, but lately I found that other cats
that I've come in contact with, I
haven't been allergic to. All right. Is
there anything about that one particular
cat is What was it? What? What do you
mean what was it? What kind of a cat? I
don't have any idea. What did it look
like? Black and white swatches.
It could have had something to do
possibly with the owner of the cat.
Maybe. Yeah. Maybe representational of
the polarity between you. Yes, that's
what it was. Black and white.
The owner. Yes. Thank you.
Back where you
um if I may
to Dr. Kirk. Yes. Um I feel kind of
stupid about this but stupid
another devaluation of your work.
You are a gift of sharing. You are equal
and valid to everything and anything.
All right. That was really
Let that one slide.
Just to give you, as you say, a break.
Perhaps the doctor can repair it.
Well, when I first when we first met and
we hawk and he would do healings, right?
It was just great. And I and I had no
fear at all. Nice.
And then a a woman that I work with
um has been encouraging me to to work
with him and that started making me feel
afraid. Why?
Um cuz all all of a sudden it was it
wasn't just between him and I. All put
on the spot, were you? Yeah. Yeah. So,
so I was thinking um yes, do tell. Well,
if I would like to not just put on the
spot. All right, your choice. What
should I do? Just not be on the spot.
not have to feel like you are expected
to
prove anything to recognize you can't
anything to recognize you can't
anyway just like I can't just like no
one can no one can prove anything to
anyone. You cannot even prove you
exist to anyone else but
yourself. For all the individuals that
you may be happily convincing of your
existence that are nodding your head,
nodding their heads in unison to yours,
I exist. Yes. Yes, you exist. All of
those individuals you are so busy
convincing could be hallucinations.
So in this way recognize since you can't
prove anything to anyone, do not feel
like you have to.
All right. What?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. What?
Okay, I'll agree to that. You do not
have to. Why should you agree to that? Why do
to. Why should you agree to that? Why do
you want to agree to that?
Because I would like to think that
that's that's right. I would like not
feel put on the spot. And I know I like
to think that you don't have to prove I
know it's not proving anything. It's
just for all of a sudden if there were
to be somebody else to to be there, even
if even though sometimes Yes.
Yes.
Well, it's like uh one time when I was
caught off guard um
uh and it and it helped another person
and then I was really glad and then
afterwards all of a sudden I thought,
"Oh my god, what if somebody what if
they want me to do it again and then
I'll I'll have to or do you know what I
mean?" Yes. But every moment is a new
moment and is never repeated. Even if
you think you are doing the same thing
again, you never are.
So take the expectation off
yourself. Those interactions are based
upon emotional
connections. When the desire is there,
what needs to happen will
happen. If it does not happen, it does
not need to. Thank you. Thank you.
You Yeah,
Yeah,
that was good. That was going going back
to Black Panthers myself. Um, a week or
10 days ago, I had an experience in my
sleep at least during the night where I
woke up to the sensation to the physical
sensation of a cat um, sort of stepping
on my body. If you've ever slept with
cats, you might know how they press
their front paws gently into you. And I
have not slept with a cat, but I have
had animals in that way touch my body.
Yes. So, I woke up to this and opened my
eyes expecting to see a cat. Um, my
friend's cat, except that I wasn't in
her bed. I was in my own and the
sensations were still there with my eyes
open on my body. Um, so I closed my eyes
again and realized that they were the
sensations of a very large cat that
reminded me of a black panther that has
been in my mind for at least 10 or 15
years that I've been waiting for um or
even looking for. Um, Black Panther with
Animal Eyes. Um, what was that
experience? I mean, was that what level
of my imagination was that happening on?
In a sense, you would call it astral in
that your imagination in the astral
level is immediately real reality and
you translated it in physical terms to
be able to feel a
sensation form. Mhm. So, um, so it
wasn't symbolic to me. Well, it was
both. All reality is all symbolic, but
in your terms, it was real. Is this the
Black Panther that I've known before in
a former life?
It has taken many
forms in many different lives. You have
known it
always. It has served you in many
different universes. You have brought it with you
universes. You have brought it with you
to this one, and it takes the form that
most represents what it needs to bring
in you to the surface.
It has been your companion forever.
Does um does the name Ronnie resonate at
all with this something totally
separate? At this time we are only perceiving it
At this time we are only perceiving it
as an offshoot, not something that
directly represents the same vibration.
The panther is an offshoot of Ronnie or
the other way around. other way round
and not directly an offshoot of the
panther but simply an offshoot of the
energy a connection from another
direction altogether.
Um is Ronnie connected to the star of
Bethlehem to some
to some
degree that is all we will say. Okay.
Another quick question that's wonderful.
Thank you. I have an exciting curiosity.
Yay. um about the way you laugh or don't
laugh and I I experience your laughing
side except that the body doesn't
express it where it's except to the
extent of pulling your cheeks in a
little bit and because laughing is
centering and it would break the
connection.
You follow me? No, not quite. If I were
to completely center, I would not be
projecting into this channeling. Mhm. So
there is an automatic in your terms
suppression in that way though you can
feel the energy right
recognize whether or
not you
experience the so-called vocalizations
to you to be serious or not. I am always
laughing for I enjoy you all very much.
Thank you.
Yes. Yes. Yes.
In this life
persistently I have known that I have
not good
control of the body I'm currently
presenting tonight. You have known that
have you? The control that I possess in
its best is flawless. Yeah. But is also
that of a giant cat in my form. Upright,
two feet, short legs with a magnificent
tail. It comes from a race of warrior
cats, more human than and I can still
feel my tail. I was I have the distinct
remembrance of being captured and the
tail cut as a degrade for my losing the
war. But tonight I can sit and feel the
muscles that would wrap that tail around
my neck. So, how does this association
serve you? Well, I'm I'm looking. Are my
people I feel those those were more my
people than where I'm at now again? And
are those people still here? Yes, of
course. All universes are right here
right now.
Then I can return to that people if I
choose. You are there now and you are
here for a
purpose. You are not here to run away.
Well, I have no intentions but my I feel
myself more as a teacher on this planet
and a learner.
Every teacher is a learner. Yes, it's
continual learning. Yes. Then simply
make the association so that you exist
in both places at the same time. So that
you can bridge the connection and allow
yourself to be of service in both areas
simultaneously.
Then this there was a cat or there is a
cat race that you know of that's more
humanoid than what we would consider
cats. It is not exactly what I would
call a cat but I know what you mean.
Okay. But the the body is very real to
me as my own personal body.
There is and are such races.
But again, it is not that they are in
your terms derived from the idea of a
cat, but there are similarities. Well, I
have the feeling of a lion that walks
upright more like more like a man. Yes.
A large man to some degree. Yes. A war a
warrior teacher cast. Yes. Or type of
people. Yes. And uh like my tail was a
symbol of my pride and my authority.
that dimension and that race in that
dimension exists and it is right here
right now. Thank you.
Sure. Yeah. What what is the uh insect
world about? I mean what is about is
there an individual for every insect?
Is there a being for every insect? A
being? Yes. Or a life force for every
single insect? Yes. Okay. What what type
of life are they? What are they trying
to express? They're not trying to
express anything. You may be trying to
understand it, right?
They express many different things.
Again, they are as reflections symbolic
to whatever meaning you ascribe to them
in that way. They represent and
recognize some of the mass conscious
recognitions for why they are reflecting
certain ideas. But in this way, simply
allow your imagination and your own
personal relationship to reflect to you
what is pertinent for you. Can I get
that if I Of course, you can ask them
too. Okay. Another question this related
uh if I physically want to improve my
eyes, let's say, what would I how could
I do that? Could I do that through
imagination or Yes. Could you give me by
first and foremost trusting that the
reason they are the way they are is to
allow you to sharpen other senses.
Very good. Understand that you see
perfectly clearly in your imagination.
Do you not? Mhm. Then it is an
opportunity to allow your imagination to
be your physical reality. All right. To
live your dream.
Okay. Merge the two and you will see
just fine.
Okay. Thank you. For sure.
Uh, would you share a title with us for
tonight? Cats. Cats.
Thank you. How about the tail of the
cat? How about the tail of the cat? Ta t
a l.
She has to write them, so she likes
cats. Cats will do. And
another question. Uh, no, you may not.
What? You have to listen to me.
What does Mach represent?
Now we have discussed to some degree the
three ideas of a trinary system. Right?
There is no need at this time to
differentiate them but simply take them
as a triad. Okay. Thank you. Thank you.
Yeah. Um briefly I wanted to ask you if
allergies allergic responses are the
manifestations of self-rejecting
process. Yes. All judgment all of it.
Yes. All judgment all of it.
Yes.
Um uh when I relayed my question about
my my channeling, one of the elements in
both of the dreams is that I'm confused
about whether Joseph or myself are
channeling those entities. Could you
give me some insight into why I confuse
whether Joseph channels or I'm
channeling? Why not both?
I guess I was thinking either or instead
of and
[Music] Thank you. Thank you.
Um I'm curious to know I had a dream
just the other night. It was very
unusual. That's why I'm bringing it up.
Um it was about a
duck, a very large duck. It was
mechanically made, but it was prettier
and nicer than a real duck. It was in
the water and it was clacking away. And
then there was a man there and he was
very excited. He was the person who
created this duck.
Yes. And uh um I was just kind of
curious if if there was any kind of
meaning in this because Well, what are
you luring yourself to with the decoy?
What are you hunting for?
Um, oh myself.
oh myself.
In what aspect? In what way? In what
portion of nature? In what form of
blending? Um, my abilities, my
Um, my abilities, my
essence.
Um, yeah, basically
yeah, basically
uh myself beyond everything else. I mean
beyond like the creation of the universe
or anything just me
there is no difference
you understand
thank you
okay there is more to this idea which we
can discuss at another time all right
sure there are in your terms seconds
there are in your terms seconds
remaining for this interaction be brief
oh I'll catch you next
Catch me now in grief. All right. Um I
find that the experience that I am a
piece of myself remaining here in
creation and I'm trying to get through
that eye of the needle beyond creation
beyond knowing beyond knowingness
inside. There is no such place as that
which is beyond creation.
is no outside.
I don't agree. There is a no nothing.
Answer this question if you will. All
right. Can you imagine nonexistence
from an inside the box point of view? I
suppose that's impossible. Very good.
I'm talking outside the box. But then if
you were outside the box, you would not
know it, would you? would not know what
the box in this way. If you could become
nonexistent, you wouldn't know it.
Are we not non-existent? The things we
are not in.
There is nothing you are not in.
Anything you are ever going to
experience is going to be a part of
creation by definition. Otherwise, you
wouldn't be experiencing it. That which
you cannot experience is not a part of
creation. But then you can never know it
because you can't experience it. All
right. These worlds called God the
Nameless and such worlds that will not
be identified or defined or not. That
does not mean they are not a part of
creation. Just because there is no
definition in one realm or another does
not mean it does not
exist. Existence itself may not be
definable in that way. But it is still
creation. They almost as though it is
they it refuses to be defined. It
refuses an identity. The the confinement
or restriction of the freedom by putting
a word or such to it. We understand the
concept and it has validity but that
still does not make it not a part of
creation. What what's its relationship?
Is it the it is creation? It is the it
is existence. Okay. It is that which
pervades all of creation. It's all of
Okay. It is all that is. All right. That
which is okay. So I Yeah, there it is.
It's the It's the whole the wholeness of
the whole so to speak. Yes. Okay. Thank
you. Thank you. In this way, allow us to
extend to each and every one of you our
appreciation once again and always and
eternally and our joy at the sharing
that you allow yourself to be in this
interaction with
us to allow us to learn of you and
cherish what you
are. We thank you for your reflections.
We thank you for your
creations. We thank you for your
conviction. We extend our unconditional
love to each and every one of you
individually and
collectively. We bid you exciting dream
lives. We bid you eternal
nowness and we bid you a fond and loving
good evening.
How did everything go?
Thank you very much, Darl. Thank you. [Applause]
[Applause]
Thank you for being here.