I'll say how are you all this dream?
Allow us to
begin with an idea we have shared with
many of you recently and which we
will reintroduce from this particular
avenue this particular perspective this
evening of your
time as another way to perceive the idea
of all the blending of polarity that you
have been doing in your lives of late.
Now I have discussed with you many ideas
of polarity, many ideas of attitudes in
understanding the blending of positive
and negative
energy. But allow us at this time.
do point out another
analogy that may allow
you a little more opportunity to
recognize the
ease with which you can create positive
action, positive manifestation in your
life. Now, many of you already are
aware of the analogy you utilize in your
own society that you call
an issue or situation having both sides
of a
coin. You recognize as we have discussed
many times that with any one side of the
coin along automatically comes the other
side of the coin. And so this is simply
another way to say that everything cause
and effect positive and negative are
simply both sides of the same event and
are always present simultaneously.
The opportunity for the manifestation of
any situation into either a negative or
a positive manifestation is in that
sense typically generally equal within
any given neutral situation. And we have
discussed many
times. Your
ability to bring into a
situation the particular attitude that
determines and reflects and represents
the beliefs that you are as we have said
once again will determine the effect you
get out of that situation. Negative
attitude going in, negative effect
coming out, positive attitude going in,
positive effect coming out. Since all
situations once again are neutral, flat
and have no built-in meaning.
Now the idea of the blending of this
polarity many times we sense that in you
because you have long experienced the
dichotomy of on the one hand and on the
other hand the this that the positive
the negative the back the for. The idea
of attempting to maintain that balance
or what seems to you to be a need to
maintain that
balance to allow yourself to create the
opportunity to have the decision to have
the choice to choose which one you
prefer, which manifestation you prefer
in your life, positive or
negative. These ideas you have been
dealing with. Now let us add one more
dimension and that is the edge of the
coin. Many of you well
perhaps aren't simply considering the
idea at first simply say well the edge
of the coin represents where the two
sides are equal or balanced are blended
and thus it is a neutral state. Not
quite. Allow us to put it in very
colloquial terms.
Now not exactly in these ratios because
this is your own
terminology. Not exactly in this way but
we will say it in this way. The universe
is very slightly biased towards the
positive. And this is
because the edge of the
cone, the balance
state, equilibrium by
equilibrium by
definition gives you an opportunity and
brings with it because it is a
blending a slight tilt in the positive
direction. So you will understand therefore that it
So you will understand therefore that it
is not that you must go
through the 50% of the negative the 50%
of the positive the negative is in a
sense
49%. The positive is
51. So even if you
can allow yourselves to maintain even
simply the balanced state, even arrive
in the limbo state, even arrive at the
neutral or what you usually consider the
neutral point, you will then
automatically allow a flow, no matter
how small of positive manifestation to
begin to kick into your life, which will
then be able to build up, as you say,
snowball and accelerate in a positive
direction. You all follow along?
The edge of the coin gives you an edge.
allows you to
recognize that even if you are creating
a reality in which it seems that
everything is going
negatively, if you will at
least release let go and cease to worry
about it and go back to your zero rest
starting point, then you will not
point, then you will not
remain in limbo. You will not remain in
neutrality for very long because the
zero rest point by definition is
slightly integrative and therefore
slightly in the positive direction. That
is why simply all you really need to do
when it comes right down to it is simply
center. And that alone will point you
towards positive
acceleration, positive synchronicity and
positive manifestation in your life. You
follow along.
It may be at times seemingly a very
subtle and ethereal
and ethereal
line. But once you are simply in that
state of trust, in that state of release
and in that state of
centering, all positive
manifestation like anything becomes
automatic. All the details will take
care of themselves and fall right into
place.
So in this dream
time simply once again
realize you do not have to try so hard.
You do not have to
struggle. You do not have to create the
idea of making or forcing anything to
happen. If you are willing to simply
allow yourself to
rest in the very highly active state of
centering, you will then allow the flow
of your natural positive manifestation
to begin to trickle perhaps at first
drop by drop into your life.
But as long as you continue to allow
yourself to remain in that rest point,
the drops will become a stream which
will become a river which will become a
flood of positive manifestation. manifestation.
Trust relaxation. After
After
all, do you not associate the experience
of a dream with
relaxation? You are in a state of
rest. When you experience what you call
a
dream, to allow your physical reality to
become as a
dream, be in a state
of all life will be as a dream. And all
dream will be alive and
real. And the dimension of your
imagination will know no
bounds. And it will be the natural state
of your
existence. If you wish, you may entitle
this tape the edge of the coin.
Sharing for sure. You venue. Two two
items actually. Um number one number one
when you when you talk about trust and
you've talked about that many times.
And I know exactly what you're talking
about and I know it's true. But what I
have found is
that it is not something that I can do
consciously. Sometimes I feel trust and
sometimes it sort of disappears. And
when it disappears, I don't know what
processes I need to go through in order
to get it back.
Life. In other words, what you may be defining
In other words, what you may be defining
as your sense of having trust may
change. The sense of having trust, the
way you look at it, the way you perceive
it may change. But why not simply trust
that it is always there. Even if it
comes in a different form, even if it
comes in a
knowingness, even if it comes in a
spontaneously unexpected like
experience, why not simply trust that
trust is always there whether you
perceive it or not? Oh, okay. That's
good. Simply simply say it's there
whether I feel it or not. Know it is
there. Know it is there and act like you
know it is there. Actually, I equate
trust with knowingness. All right.
Again, these things do not have to
manifest as conscious analytical
thoughts. Right? I think I'm trusting
now. They don't have to manifest that
way. You simply live your life. And that
is the only process you really need to
understand everything in your life is to
simply live it. Then after the
experience many times you will then know
why the experience was there. But many
times you do not want to know why it is
there until after you have experienced
it because to know first would take all
the fun out of it. That's true.
The other thing has to do with
excitement. And I was thinking last
night if you have a a very good
salesperson they can get you excited
over something and then you follow you
you know you say follow your excitement
as a saleserson says oh you want to do
this and you want to do that or you buy
this or that and you feel excited. What
is the difference between the true
excitement that comes from within and
the excitement that is sort of generated
by somebody else? nothing really. For
the idea again is that if you truly
allow yourself to create your version of
their excitement, you are still
generating a being. You are still
generating a focus. It may be something
in this way which allows you to fulfill
the ideas you need to fulfill. Now if
you find
find
that getting involved in that way is
something that while you are doing it
you know you really don't want to do but
you're just going along with it. Then in
that sense you know you are not allowing
it to be what you call true excitement.
You perhaps therefore must be in touch
honestly with yourself as to whether or
not you are allowing yourself to
experience the excitement or whether you
are in your terms
perhaps creating well let us say
creating well let us say
hope rather than knowing
it. the idea of saying,
"Well, I would hope that this finally may
I would hope that this finally may
represent something that can serve me."
wherein many times you may recognize
that if you are honest in the
communication and open in the
communication with yourself when you are
involved in a situation with another
individual of the type you have
described then many times you are simply
as you say grabbing at straws because
you are not honestly open with the idea
of what it is that truly does excite you
perhaps not really willing to follow
that excitement and therefore willing to
allow certain ideas let us say
distractions to be what seems seems to
be exciting to you. If you are truly
honest with yourself, you will know
whether what you may be playing at
excitement about is actually excitement
or a distraction that you create for
yourself to take you away from things
you perhaps would rather not
face. If all Yes. Thank you very much.
If it is in this way true
excitement, then it will generally be
something very
spontaneous that as you say typically
feels correct. There will not
correct. There will not
necessarily need to be much convincing.
You will feel no weariness per se. And
you may even sense the excitement before
you actually physically encounter the
being and simply allow the presence of the
and simply allow the presence of the
being to be a representation of the
excitement you already have rather than
quote unquote having to be convinced or
wishing for something that will take you
away from what you truly know you need
to look at.
Many times do not forget what comes to
you as fear is actually your excitement
but it is your excitement that you are
afraid to discover because perhaps you
do not believe that you can handle what
the excitement will bring. So first and
foremost to know what you are asking and
to sense the difference once again
involves very open direct and honest
communication with yourself about what
it is that truly moves you. then you
will recognize what is extraneous and
what is not.
All right. All right. Thank you very
much. Thank you. Yes, for sure. Uh Lois
and Paul send their love and hello. And
uh I wanted to ask about the uh big
bright light in uh in Northern
California. I think it's Northern
California, Oregon that was spotted by
uh many people. Was supposed to have
been very very long. It was uh two two
days ago. It was the the Monday night
channel and it was reported in the news
and it it was rainbow colors and many
things. Do you have any information
about this? Not at this time. Okay.
Perhaps forthcoming. Okay.
Thank you. Hey,
my son and my daughter got this may seem
silly, but they got sick today. Tummy
troubles and it's unusual that they get
sick at the same time. I had a sense
there was something more than just the
fact that the flu is going around. And I
wanted to ask if you have a sense of
what that might
be. Give them three more
days and allow them to recognize what
they may be sharing with each other as a
part of an agreement they made a long
time ago. So there they have a connection. Of
ago. So there they have a connection. Of
course, that is quite obvious. But the
idea simply is that this in this
following three days of your time gives
them an opportunity to examine and see
something in each other that they have
not yet seen in this life which they
need to see in order to gain a certain
empathy, a certain respect and a certain
communicative link with each other.
There is a certain type of sharing going
on and very strongly so in their dream
realities for the next three days of
your Hey, there
Hey, there
are unusually 40 blue whales in a cove
in Monterey.
unusual because they've not been seen in
such numbers in that cove and further
unusual because there are in pairs
although it's not the mating season. I
wonder if you could tell us about
that more and more
interactions are taking place as you
already know between your land and your
water human.
Now whales generally symbolize an entire
collective mass consciousness. Each and
every individual in a sense represent an
entire collective mass consciousness of
the individual consciousnesses that
typically represent themselves as
dolphins. You follow me so far? Yes. In
this way, they're forward. The
whale will generally as you find more
and more interactions taking place
between you and them represent more and
more activity on the level of your
higher consciousness. Now that
particular area is highly magnetic at
this time and let us say that a bit of
an explosion is taking place now around
your world where certain energy centers
are let us say expanding
drastically. These drastic expansions of
magnetic energy will attract these
beings. In this way, the pairing to us
In this way, the pairing to us
represents once again what we have begun
with this night of your time, the idea
of the blending of polarities. allowing
yourself to recognize both sides. And
therefore recognizing that by existing
on that edge and in that balanced
framework, you will be the idea of your
higher consciousness of your collective
consciousness and will accelerate the
explosions taking place in the
ethereomic energy that represents the
idea of all the mentality of your
civilization.
We have based upon this idea, this
symbol and this understanding a bit of
what you might call a bulletin for
you. as we had
begun in your terms of time 3 years of
your time ago these communications and
these channelings with each and every
one of you. Many of you will recall that
we represented our relative position to
you in your terms. Not that it was
really literal in many ways, but as a
sufficient analogy or symbol that our
relationship to
you relatively speaking in terms of time
was approximately 300 years in advance
of your civilization. You follow me?
Yes. It is
now 150 years. You have
You have
within the next
approximately 13 of your years the
opportunity to render that difference
down to approximately half yet again 75
of your
years. At that point the accelerations
will go as you say off the scale.
But now you are beginning to see
explosions. All of the energy centers
are now beginning to widen enough so
that they truly do incorporate all other
energy centers. And you may find that
there will be many
visitations by these sea beings to many
different areas upon your
planet as these interactions increase
between you physically more and more.
This idea of physiological interaction
between yourselves and the water beings,
dolphins, whales, is
now one
of the most highly
acceleratable situations you have upon
your planet. since they are of your
world and yet in many ways are truly
alien to you. This is your opportunity
to truly establish the first link with
an alien
civilization. And in so forming that you
have absolutely no barriers to this
accomplishment. Absolutely
none. There is none of those ideas by
which we must abide in terms of holding
back because the timing is not correct.
you have
absolute absolute free and clear
opportunity with them to form an
absolute link with their entire
civilization. So any steps taken in that
direction at all will cause a tremendous
explosion of acceleration
towards our ability to interact with you
as well.
You will now begin to see more and more
of these interactions with the whales as
well as the dolphin.
Those of you who have a particular,
shall we say, twist or
bent that may be to some
degree, let us
say, magical or that which generally has been
magical or that which generally has been
in your path attributed to the idea of
wizardry or sorcery. Not necessarily in
a negative way, but the idea of that
type of
magic may find themselves
encountering the sorcerers of the sea,
what you call the
orthus. Now, they are also in many ways,
and again, this is an analogy, but it
will do, as we have said, the samurai of
the sea. They are the polarity symbol
sea. They are the polarity symbol
itself, the black and the white, and
there is no accident to their
coloration. In this way, many of you that find
In this way, many of you that find
yourselves linking with these
beings will find yourselves on journeys
that will completely unravel any sense
of reality that you
thought. For they are in many ways what
many of you may have called the bro.
The idea of the shaman, the wizard rich
Spanish for rich. Now
the idea not in a negative way but the
idea of the shores of a path, the livers
of a path in a sense they have a code so
to speak much like the idea of what you
call the samurai code and that is why we
make the distinction and the connection.
It is
one of the idea of
direct manifestation. One of what if you will
manifestation. One of what if you will
excuse the pun in their referential
terms of a handson experience.
The idea simply is that many different
forms of the being all the way from
dolphin through the many variations of
whale up to the blue which represents
the complete connection of mentality and
higher consciousness will now becoming
more and more obvious, more and more
spontaneous and more and more apparent
and let us say occurring more often as
You now explode into action with them.
Truly truly welding a society together
with them. So
that by the time your world interacts
with our world, you will
be the combination of an association on
your planet of two alien civilizations.
As far as we are
concerned, we find you
um in terms of this uh increasing
probably confrontation with negative
energy, confrontation,
blending, lending. Um in in the office
where I work, there appears to be a
small number of people which uh tend to
encourage the the kind of negative type
of energy that we've spoken about
before. In other words, trying to do
right things up the idea of manipulation
and domination and stuff like that. All
right. And um I find this particularly
upsetting. All right. Why are you there?
And uh obviously I I decided to uh live in
uh obviously I I decided to uh live in
this environment for some purpose and
I'm just wondering may I ask you a
question? Yeah. Do you consider yourself
to be a part of the vibration that they
are? Um I consider myself to be somewhat
Um I consider myself to be somewhat
opposite.
Then why do you find them upsetting?
Uh
if you find them upsetting that means
you are choosing to create upset.
Choosing to create upset is a negative
manifestation. Therefore you are of
their vibration. Oh,
so if you are willing to love them
unconditionally and simply recognize
that they are learning whatever it is
they need to learn, then you will
radiate your unconditional love towards
them and in that way therefore you will
create your reality experience to be
that only reflective of the vibration in
which you exist. Therefore, situations
will change accordingly as they need to
change. You will either leave, they will
either leave, they will change, you will
change. Whatever is necessary for the
idea of any blending to be represented
by the energy you are being. But until
you are being that energy, then you are
only going to reinforce theirs.
Thank you. Very nice. Does that assist
you? Yes. Fine. There is no need for the
idea of confrontation for thinking in
those terms is in and of itself a
negative perspective. Yeah, that was
that's what was so
unsatisfactory in my experience and
that's why I was trying to look for what
is there to do, what is there not to do.
This is why we have shared with you the
idea this evening of your time of the
edge of the coin.
Four, if you are willing to go into a
state of balance and
nonvalidative judgment, then you will
judgment, then you will
discover that any situations occurring
around you will not negatively affect
you. And you will be in a state of
choice and
preference and will be able to then
radiate that choice and preference so
that they can understand what you are
all about. And if they choose to join
you, they then see in you an opportunity
and an
example which they
can choose as opposed to what they are
choose as opposed to what they are
doing. But if you recognize it as
confrontation, then you are not
blending. For in the center there is no
confrontation. Everything is one.
Everything is one. And when everything
is one, how can there be conflict? Thank you.
I am very attracted
to other Not usually.
Not usually.
No. There are the ideas of what you call
their food. Generally speaking, it is
what you term
seals. Now, in this way, the few times
there have been the idea of the
ingestion of a citation form by an orca.
It has to do with many of the ideas of
their agreements and interactive codes.
And much of it many times has to do with
certain ideas that the dolphin desires
to experience. But this is extremely
rare and you will find will become even
less so. Many of these ideas are of the
past and will change. Sure.
Sure.
Um I have some very exciting
realizations this last couple weeks that
I want to share. Right. and get your
reflection on one particular aspect.
Maybe maybe
and also I wanted to ask you something
about what you just discussed about the
orca being black and white. So it
represents polarity. The dolphin being
gray would it represent a blending then
in a sense a balance.
It also represents a grounding in a way.
All right. What I want to share is that
um I had a couple of incidents involving
my car and with those I come to some
real exciting realizations. All right.
And first one, you are not the only one,
I'm sure. The first one was someone
tried to break into the trunk of my car
and they jammed up the lock when they
couldn't get it open and dented a little
bit around the hood, which since I had
just had it painted was was kind of
upsetting. Oh, more upset.
Yeah. At the time. And then last
Thursday, um I was driving down Federan,
which is a thoroughare near where I
live, and I was going about 35 miles an
hour, and a woman pulled out of a
driveway uh right in front of me, and I
broadsided her, and it was a a real hit.
And um if I had been going faster, it
would have done a lot of damage as it
was. It the car is damaged more
cosmetically than anything. Her car was
pretty terribly damaged. But um I got
hit on the head pretty hard and I got
out of the car. My first impression was
to be angry and think, why did this
woman pull out in front of me? And there
was plenty of room to see that there was
a whole line of cars coming and I was
the first one in the lineup after light
change and it was a very dangerous thing
to do. And then I shifted and I thought,
well, life is an adventure. So I'm going
to look at this as an adventure. All
right. So, we went over to the side and
we were exchanging information,
insurance things and all of that and and
u one of a student because it's near the
campus of UCLA ran up and said, "Um, I
saw the whole thing. It wasn't your
fault. I'd like to witness for you." And
I said, "That's great." And she said,
"Uh, could I call the police for you?"
And I said, "Oh, that would be
wonderful." And so, she ran off. And
then, um, the tow truck was called this
other woman's car. And meanwhile, we
talked and I felt very compassionate for
her because she was very upset. She
said, "Please don't tell the insurance
company about this because until I see
if I can get the money to repair your
car." And um she said there's a lot
going on in her life right now. And she
was having a lot of problems. So I gave
her a hug and I told her that look, we
would figure it out and I would call her
and get an estimate on the car and it
would be okay. And the tow truck came
and and she drove away the tow truck in
her pot. And then I was there still kind
of busy from the whole thing. And this
this man walked up and um he was
well-dressed and he seemed like a real
nice person. And he said my window was
down and I was waiting for the witness
to come back and he said um did this
just happen? And I said yes it did. And
he said, "Well, you know," he said, "I
work for Universal Studios and I'm a
stunt driver and we work on cars all the
time." And he said, "I can see that this
won't be any problem to fix and I'll I
can see too that you get the parts and
this can all be handled." And I thought,
"Oh, wonderful. This is great." You
know, synchronicity.
So we went back to my house and he made
all the calls to the studio supposedly
the studio and got all the numbers and
things that he needed on the
identification of my car and colors and
what we needed a fender and all of these
things and he was very charming and very
concerned and he said you know don't
take aspirin don't lay down here let's
put some ice on your head and he was a
very nice person he seemed to be and so
I called also the woman Anita who was in
the accident and suggested that he see
her car. So, he went with me over there.
We looked at her car and he assured her
he could get that repaired and and she
felt much better and he was very
concerned about her and he talked to her
husband on the phone who was furious
with her and made a deal that the parts
for my car, they would give him
$220. Actually, they were giving it to
me. I would give it to him. We had phone
numbers for
him and um we had a place he was
supposed to to be located. He used to
locate and all this. And as the story
goes, I gave him the $220 and we went to
lunch together and he talked about all
of his experiences he had at the studios
and how he fixed Cars and Stars and all
the friends he had. And he was this
wonderful, colorful, talkative person.
And then um I went home and uh he went
his way with the money
and later about like 4 in the morning I
woke up and I realized that I had been
taken. I knew that. I thought I felt
sick to my stomach at first and then I
was kind of entertained. I thought well
that's the most amazing performance I
have ever seen.
and and so um I called her back and told
I didn't tell her that I'd been royally
taken because I they are in the middle
of a divorce thing and she's so
emotionally upset that I knew she would
feel that they had lost the money, not
me. So I thought, well, I'll just handle
that. And I told her that he would no
longer be able to help help us with the
cars and that would she come with me for
an estimate and see, you know, if she
could help me with the rest of what my
car would need. and it came out that
it's going to cost
700. So I talked to the insurance
company and the insurance company told
me that I would be best selling out of
court because I have a perfect driving
record and if I if it goes to court I
will be with a block on my record the
same as her. They don't care whose fault
it was but my premiums will go up. Plus
my deductible is 500. So I'll get two
from them anyway. And uh hers is like a
thousand on her car. So um it got all
very interesting. You know, I called the
people and they said that I was I was
absolutely in the right because I had
been in a thorough affair and that she
would be considered wrong no matter what
because she drove in front of me from
the sidekick or from the driveway
actually. So I I listened to people get
upset and I listened to people advise
and I saw her a couple of times that saw
her upset and how sick she was and how
much many problems were happening in her
life and how she wasn't sleeping
wellness. And I I decided that that I
really didn't want to be in the
vibration of of accusing and of being
negative and calling lawyers and all
this. And I decided I would much rather
be in a loving vibration. And so I told
her that I would accept the 220 as a
settlement and that we would just go on
with our lives and so I will just handle
my own repairs. Now the realization that
I got I had a kind of a little thing
happen in a relationship that I'm
involved in right now Saturday night and
it applied a little more pressure and
Sunday morning when I was kind of in
that state between sleep and waking I
flooded in some realizations of some of
the pattern I've had do share for a long
time and first of all I want to say that
it's my intention to be completely in in
theness of who I am Oh, you certainly
were. Yes. To be there completely. So I
realized that I have a pattern that has
not been allowing us. And so I what I
got in my mind my mind the voice in my
head said if you jam your feelings and
lock yourself up the trunk, you're going
to run boom smack into yourself the
front of the car.
And I thought great, I got it.
Wonderful. Do you recognize allow me to
ask you in your terms the physiological
age of the woman approximately?
All right.
right.
Regardless of the physiological age
relative to you, did you not recognize
in her your past? I felt the
love. Yeah. I felt compassion
in many ways. She's exploring now. many
of the things you have already explored.
I saw the past in her. Yes, I could see
that I had come many of the similar ways
she was coming. Yes, through the voice
and all these things plus her attitude
and how she feels about life about
herself. It's very simple. This is
therefore the completion of a cycle
meeting your old self and allowing the
old self to deal with the new self. And
that in turn will also allow you the way
you are now to open up channels to the
you will
become. And as you have assisted your
past by helping her, your future is
assisting you now. You have opened up
doorways in both
directions. You have done so in a very
exciting way.
And you have explored the ideas of the
vehicle that you are and the idea of
your abundance all at once.
Oh, that's amazing. Oh, by the way,
Michelle, what does he represent this
man? What I I'll tell you what my son
said, which I think is
funny. I told this to my son. He's 15.
Okay. He sat there and he's psychic your
son. Yes, I understand. He really is for
the things he does. Thanks. He said,
um, he didn't say, "Mom, you're stupid.
You got taken all these things." You
know, she stopped there for a minute and
he looked at me and said, "Mom, what do
you think? Did you enjoy the
show?" He said, "Do you think it worth
220?" And I said, "Actually, it was the
most amazing thing I've ever seen." He
says, "Well, there you are."
Very simply put and very precise really.
Yes. Now recognize many times this has
been and may still be for some of you
for a while simply a particular method
that many of you will use when getting
into touch with the idea of your
abundance. Many individuals when they
begin to explore the understanding that
nothing can really in an ultimate
fundamental sense be truly taken from
them and begin to connect into the
understanding that they are infinitely
abundant and have everything they need
to remind them of this and get the flow
of abundance moving. They will attract
an individual who may still be
functioning on a level where they seek
the idea of negative expression, but
they will attract the specific
individual necessary to quote unquote
take something from them to get the flow
going. Many individuals on the verge of
exploring the idea of their infinite
abundance will have something stolen
from them. How they deal with it will
determine how quickly they allow the
so-called vacuum to be filled in as you
say spades
for you will find that once the flow has
started what will then come back to you
will be geometric in proportion. Now, in
no way, shape or form does this really
excuse the individual. For they it is in
this sense their duty to find the
strength within themselves not to
necessarily express their powerlessness
by feeling they must quote unquote pray
on the situations of others. But in this
way, that is his lesson to learn in his
own timing.
You may also be
surprised that some of the idea of
interaction with that individual may
crop up again in a different
light. But for now, allow yourself to
recognize that while you were
distracted, you allowed a little bit of
slight of hand into your life. A little
bit to show
to show
you the idea of the differences between
the foundations and the
surface and to allow you to experience a
little bit in your own way in a positive
way of this illusion.
Now in this
sense you will
find let me wrap up a very long
statement in two words and we will allow
the timing as we perceive it to be
unfolding to make sense out of these two
words. when you arrive at a particular
time. Though you may think you
understand what they mean now, you will
really understand what they mean in a
little while. The two words are simply
in your language, merry
Christmas. We will allow you to unwrap
that present when you get to it,
but it will be connected and
representative of the situation you have
just explored and experienced. And it
also to some degree will have to do with
your own expression of your own art.
Thank you very much. Oh, thank you for
your sharing and your willingness to be
so bold in the transformation of your
reality.
Now, hey, there are two
who have who were captured six years ago
and they have since experienced
they have experienced some of the best
of human education. They have
experienced some of the worst of of our
civilization. They've been drugged.
They've been abandoned. Now there are a
lot of people who are who are pretending
or presuming or projecting to re-educate
them and reintroduce them into their
wild state. The dolphins are called Joe
and Rosie. there were the John Lily
Dolphins and there are a lot of people
concerned and a lot of people involved
very egotistically I feel in their
future. Have you any insight as to what
their future might properly be? If
there's any way that we can make amends
to these two beings, if there's any way
that we can repair the damage of Since
you do recognize that certain forms of
what you would call damage that exists
in human beings has been greatly
assisted by dolphins. Why cannot natural
dolphins assist their own reverence? [Music]
How do you feel now? I feel fine. All
right. I feel
What images came to you in the
experience? [Music]
Is that what you have
now acquired?
Yeah, I have some. Yeah. All right. Did
you work with them then? Yes, I did. All
right.
All right. What I'm wondering though is
why am I putting myself to this pain? I
know that I'm doing it.
Much of the idea as we have also
discussed is once again simply ways you
have been taught to look at
things. Ways you have been taught things
quote unquote must be
processed. Now when we discussed getting
in touch with your beliefs in that sense
that is the level that we were referring
to not so much the beliefs themselves
that cause the pain but why you believe
that things must be done in that
manner the foundational beliefs that
give rise to those beliefs that create
prophecies in your
life. A process in and of itself may be
representative of a belief. But the
existence of the belief that you need a
process in that manner in and of itself
many times spurs from a very highly
ingrained and foundational belief that
you carry with you as a child either in
this life from this life or from other
lives.
Now if you are able to go into your
imagination right now will you do sir?
Yes. All right relax. Take three deep breaths.
breaths.
Now, will you
take will you take three more deep
breaths? And before you
start, I mean
really really stretch yourself.
Are you already done?
All right. All
right. All
right. You feel relaxed? Yes. All right.
Now I'm going to ask you a
question and as best as you can without
judging the way the answer comes to you
simply respond with the first thing or feeling
respond with the first thing or feeling
that comes to mind even if you think it
will come out as gibberish. All right. right.
What do
you about your last
life regret the
most? Answer now.
What did you get? I got what?
All right. Anything else? Look
deeper. Any feelings that came with it?
any very slight no matter how subtle.
No. Thank you. All
right. Relax into the same state you are
in after you finish the three breaths.
All right? You do not need to take three
more. Simply keep breathing, but allow
yourself to drift back into that state
for a moment. All right?
Do you feel yourself to be there?
All right. Think about the gift. Think
about it for a minute. Explore it. What
does it mean to you?
Confusion. All right. Confusion, you
know, does not have to be
negative. It is simply cousion. Fusion
with more of yourself. An opportunity to
explore more portions of your
consciousness. Confusion may be the first step in
Confusion may be the first step in
disassociation and disorientation from
reality that you no longer believe in to
give you an opportunity to examine all
the probable realities you may want to
choose to believe in. Confusion is not
necessarily negative. Think some more about
negative. Think some more about
you. Anything else come to
you? Do not think about it.
All right. How does it feel to have you?
right. How does it feel to have you?
I'm terrible.
All right. Now, how does it feel to know
that you can use your guilt to learn
something positive?
Wonderful. All right. Are you willing to
learn something positive about guilt?
Yes. All right. What?
But it's not necessary. Not
necessary. All right. Perhaps it used to
be. Yes. That was
then. It is
now in your life.
Now, can you
imagine a
situation in which you might feel it
would be necessary to experience guilt?
Now, yes, now. No, I don't. All right.
Why not?
Uh because I don't think I don't believe
in it. Why not?
I I find it useless.
Youthless. All right. Why?
What is it that you are? Because I feel
like guilt is something
that created.
Do you remember that guilt is the
opposite of love? Not hate. Guilty.
Yeah. All
All
right. You do not need it now because
you are willing to love yourself.
Yes. No. Maybe. All right. Yes. And yes.
Love yourself. How?
unconditional. Oh, thank goodness.
What does that mean? Unconditionally.
Without condition. All right. In any
situation, you still know that you have
infinite love. That's no meaning. Yeah.
All situations. Yeah. All right. Now,
let's talk about
pain. How do you feel about pain?
I feel it's unnecessary. All right. Why?
Because it's obvious from love in a
sense. Hey. Yeah. All right.
If in those moments of contact and
connection with those portions of
yourself that seem to come through as
birthing, if you love that portion
unconditionally and with open arms
greeted and accept it joyfully into you,
then you will not feel as if you have to
process that portion as if it were
something that did not belong like a
mistake. There is nothing within you
that does not belong. Even if it is
negative, it belongs in you as a part of
the idea that you are. You do not have
to experience nor express the
manifestation or expression of the
negativity, but it still belongs to you. All
All
right. You are, as we have discussed,
giving birth to many different portions
of
yourself. And therefore, you are
constantly making room for a new birth
by going through cycles very quickly of
your periodicity. You get one out of the way,
periodicity. You get one out of the way,
as you say, and make ready for another
birth. Process that. Get that one out.
You say out of the way. Make room for
another. Yes, you are accelerating.
Yes, you are accelerating.
Yes, you are accelerating. These are all
the different fragments of yourself you
still think you need to look at. But as
we have said, as soon as you accept more
and more of them in a positive
way, then you will find that it will not be
then you will find that it will not be
necessary to feel as if you have to
clean the slate for
everyone. The idea is that they will
blend and melt into you in a more subtle
way, a more benign way. And then the
idea will begin to even out until, as we
have said, the arteries will become
farther and farther apart until you
experience them no
more. This is probable and possible for
almost every single female upon your
planet. There are females now that do
not experience them in the course of an
entire year. and not because of what we would
year. and not because of what we would
call stress but because of allowance and
blending. But many of them first
experienced an increase because that is
as many birds as they were dealing with
all the different fragments of their
being. Call
Call
upon also at all times. Feel free to
call upon the dolphin consciousness with
the assistance of any type of birth at
all. Then you can allow yourself to feel
immersed in the ocean of that energy.
That immersion will support you and
create a less painful
experience for you will lose track of
where your body ends and the ocean
begins. That is one of the symbols for
the idea of water birth upon your planet
at this time.
All right. Then create for yourself
whether it is physiologically present
for you or not. The energy is available.
wasn't
ma'am. Yes. Um I have given a lot of
thought lately to the history on this
planet of the negative interaction
between ourselves and the
whales. Um and I guess you know this is
Um and I guess you know this is
changing. Yeah. Oh, absolutely. I love
it. I'm so excited about that and I see
more and more evidence of it all the
time. I guess what I'm interested in
knowing is what is their viewpoint of
all those interactions.
They know it is serving a purpose to
bring you closer together. They know
that at first perhaps the idea of
negative interaction was necessary
simply because that was your overall
point of view. And to them, let us say
in an overall plan, negative interaction
at first is better than none at all.
But they knew it would be relatively
quick as things go and were willing to
place themselves in those positions to
simply bring to your consciousness the
fact that they exist and exist in every
way, shape or form equally to you. And
they are not as you typically think of
them as animals. Oh, of
Oh, of
course. I think one of the the clues for
myself to the fact of the dolphin
spirituality was that
um I I read about an incident where
Japanese fishermen were driving into the
shallows and slaughtering them by the
hundreds because they feel they
can changing as well. Yes. The thing
that I realized in looking at that was
they must know themselves as spiritual
beings or they wouldn't allow this to
happen with absolutely no resistance on
their part whatsoever.
And the other thing that I realized was
that because of their non-resistance and
because of that incident there was
worldwide attention brought
and a real cohesion between uh humans
all over the earth uh incompassion
and protest that sort of interaction
I guess mainly it was I've been curious
what is their viewpoint of all this
because we have really been hard on them
for hundreds of years. We slaughtered
them. They understand, but they do not
have nor express exactly as you do the
same type of viewpoint. They do not
create so much exactly in the way you do
opinion. So to give you their viewpoint
is to simply refer you to their actions.
Yeah. And their attraction to that is
their viewpoint that you are worth all
of this.
Well,
That is their point of view.
Unconditional love. You have a prime
example of unconditional love on your
planet. You may
all but not a break in
energy and not a break. Put it.
This our love for you. Our exchange in
the recognition of the creator balance
within us, balanced within you in
equality. Our total
being is a reflection of your total
being. The experience of one is the
experience of all. The experience of all
is the experience of
one. Our
reflection of
this reality
is
translation. What language? Our own
remnant language. Sure. you. Thanks, Thanks,
sister.
Um, following your assistance in
enabling me to transfer transform some
rather negative energy of one type, I ex
I enjoyed
um, ecstasy uh, fun centering
wonderfulness and then moved into what
he sees to be a sea of very viscous
negativity. [Music]
[Music]
Oh, nice imagery.
It's been one of my forte, the imagery
of it all. Yay. From 30 to 40.
Anyway, um some reflection of assistance
in uh why the hell all of this crap is
going on and uh from a third density uh
judgment viewpoint and from a fourth
density full loving viewpoint. By all
means, how the hell do I transfer all
this energy into a more flowing high
acceleration? Define the energy you
experience now.
Um what I would have turned before
apathy, heavy uh heaviness um
congestion in the uh dream reality um
congestion in the dream real. No, no,
no, no, no, no. That's that in the
conscious reality. All right. In the
dream reality is more of a free flowing
war.
Have you invited all your friends?
No. All my
enemies, apparent enemies, but not
friends. No, not friends. Um, not
friends. Well, from the fourth density,
very much friends reflecting, giving me
the invitation to trans
uh transcend or transform negative to
positive, which I was doing extremely
well. Don't really fully understand what
the hell's been going on.
means um what is being allowed to manifest in
um what is being allowed to manifest in
your physical reality?
What is being allowed to manifest?
Eight. What reflections in physical
reality are occurring to represent what
as you say has been going on?
um going off at a project direction
which does not seem to materialize
according to the excitement that I uh I had when I
to the excitement that I uh I had when I
generated the project seems to hit a
dead end scene right scenes stop yeah
scenes where did the excitement then
transfer itself didn't seem to vanish
seem to transfer
into heaviness rather absence of
excitement Um Um
dispersal. No.
No.
Um. All right. Let's lost back up. Okay.
Oh, at the moment. Can you remember the
moment if there was such a recollection
when the excitement seemed reddish?
Well, the first thing that comes to mind
is the last channeling
um when we got together seemed dull to
me. All right. And that wasn't the start
of it. All right. But it was a definite
manifestation of dullness. Oh, all
right. I want, you know, there was a a
judgment, an old discouragement off of
the previous was so exciting. Do I have
to get myself into a crappy situation in
order to then experience uh a magnitude
of joy? You know, maybe maybe not.
Maybe. Do you think you need that? No,
not anymore. All right. So, we are
through with comparisons.
All right. All right. Done. Through with
comparisons. All right.
Then when you no longer need to make
comparisons this against that, then
perhaps you will not continue to create
the idea of needing a low tide in order
to recognize when it is high
tide. That is one idea and you are
dealing with that. Yes.
Now, some of the dullness can also
simply be your way of telling you you
don't need these interactions and that
you have what you need and that you can
begin to trust it.
Of course. All right. The doing rather
than the talking.
Yes. Yes. I have gone into the doing.
Yay. All right. Now go ahead.
This idea once again of when you think
the excitement vanished. Now between the
time it appeared to
disappear and the time when you saw or
recognized the manifestation of the
apathy. Was there at all in any way,
shape or form a gap between those two
experiences? Was there any time at all
in between the disappearance of the
excitement and the appearance of the
appetite? Yes. What was in that moment
for that time? That time seems actually
fairly wide. It looks like a
uh it's more of a feeling. It's a
sinking. It's a black hole that's
falling to a depth. All right. This or
by the way, I want I want to share
something with you. I think you know I
don't come here out of need.
Great. I I love playing. No, no, no. We
understand. Okay, great. We understand
the sharing. But simply you may find
that if you are creating certain
situations in your life that are
carrying some of these energies with it
and some of that in being in some of
these interactions because of the
purpose for which some of these
interactions are being created may seem
to have at times nothing to do with you.
Why did you say? In other words, some of
the idea of dullness may simply be
because there are times when that
dullness is a reflection of when you
actually would find your energy out
doing something rather than being in
this interaction. No matter what the
reason, our energy very good, very our
energy is primed into each and every one
of you to spur you towards your own
self-empowerment and interaction. Yes,
the idea of enjoying the sharing going
on is all well and good and we always
enjoy each and every one of you. But
once again allow us to remind you that
true equal conversation with us is
actually in the doing not in the
talking. Therefore, many times we'll
find that because of the type of energy
we are giving off, so to speak, that
individuals who may come to these
interactions whose timing may be more
representative of the ability to be out
doing something may find some of the
energy we are giving off a bit dull
because it will then spur them to scan
with their curiosity to find what it is
that will be more exciting. Excellent.
That's what happened on the last one. I
came when I didn't really feel like
coming would have been more impressible.
Hey, then you would have been
encountering the ideas and the
situations in which you could have
recognized where the excitement perhaps
went. Mhm. Instead of simply doing the rope
Mhm. Instead of simply doing the rope
thing. Excellent.
Excellent. So it is in that limbo state
when the excitement appears to vanish
before you create the idea of the apathy
or the puzzl. It is always within that
state that you have more than enough
available time to see where the
excitement got off to and then to follow
that idea since that is an extension no
matter how it may appear to be or not.
That is the extension of where the
excitement was.
That does one more point. Oh,
what I have been judging
uh not judging is not quite the right
word. attempting to
determine whether I should be following
one particular path through to
completion and coming out of this moment
to moment
integrity which seems to lead from this
project to that project to this project
to that project without a follow through
especially economically.
Do you recognize that any particular
manifestation you may create gives you
the ability to follow it through as you
would say to the end or does it take
that ability away from you? If it gives
you the opportunity to follow something
through to the end that originally was
the representation of excitement then
you may find it very likely that that is
what could be done instead of going from
one idea to the other. The idea is
always to recognize what you are capable
of acting upon with the excitement that
comes into your life. If you find
something does excite you, but it
doesn't bring with it any ability to act
upon, then that in and of itself is a
symbol to keep going the way you are
going and simply recognize that the
excitement is simply there in a sense to
inspire you, to spur you on, to give you
the energy in the direction you are
already moving. and that it is also an
indication that at some point down the
line many of these ideas that are
becoming inspirational will then
ultimately click in. I've got you. So I
I think yes, there was a judgment on a
path that went so far that I thought was
going to go farther than it went.
But then because of the the mechanics of
the the exchange flows of the universe,
hey, that one ended. Amen. At any given
time, we do recognize that there is once
again many times a very fine and subtle
line in the recognition of where the
excitement is or where the knowing is
until you become completely entrenched
in the new habit of always being
sensitized to it. Therefore, allow
yourself to realize that for now because
you are still acclimating to these
ideas, many times exciting ideas will
come to you and it will seem as if it is
an indication to go off in different
directions. But if it doesn't come with
an ability to go off in that direction,
then by all means don't struggle to do
so. Understood. Very good. Now, as I'm
speaking you to you now, I am
feeling a bit of this heaviness and a
bit of judging loss of a level of
of judging loss of a level of
rapport. Again, that's judgment. In
fact, I'm judging a level of rapport and
affinity we had before wanting that in
preference to the solidity and heaviness that I am
to the solidity and heaviness that I am
feeling. May I first of all take this
opportunity to reassure
you that I will never ever ever be
capable of loving you less than I ever
have. Of
course, understood and known. The
affinity is always there. Though the
definition of how we relate, like any
relationship, may always
change, it changes simply to allow you
the leeway and the freedom to truly be
yourself and explore your expressions in
whatever way, shape, or form you truly
desire to do. So that was marvelous.
Thank you, Michelle. We thank you. My
pleasure. you than you.
you than you.
Um Oh, well, you know, my mother is new.
Yay.
Was she not here in the room? Hey, but
you are
um what is it with family that makes you
feel so heavy?
Many times it may simply be the
recollection of many of the agreements
you have made in many many many many
many many many
many
lives and from sometimes the perspective
that you have that may seem to be very
heavy because experience in that way may
carry weight or mass. When you look
down or back a road that you think is a
very long one, well then just looking at
how long that road was may make you
tired. If you think of it as a long
road, it can simply also be that in this
particular life in learning that this is
the transformational age and recognizing
that of course you have made your
agreements with all the individuals you
are interacting with in life
particularly your family your immediate
family. Then the coming to the
Then the coming to the
realization of what it is you are in the
society you have been has given you more
than enough opportunities to explore the
idea of how perhaps from time to time
you have each fought against your own
ecstasy and that can make you very tired
and you feel like things are weighing
you down or have weighed you down.
Many times it is
simply in a way from time to time once
you go through a doorway and pass on to
another level until you actually give
yourself the opportunity to pass
beyond regret beyond guilt beyond any
sort of negative association or
self-doubt. In that way, each time you
make one of those steps, you may still
create well, let us
say posttransformational
depression because many of you still
think that it takes a great deal of
energy to have made such an abrupt
change. And so, after having made the
change, rather than recognize the ease
in which it was created, many of you
would simply go
Whoa, that was a big step. I guess I
better rest for a
while. It feels very
heavy until you acclimate to the new
level of energy. You see, each and every
time you take a new step, you do expand
the i.e. of your awareness of more
energy. But because you have just come
out of a frame of reference in which the
energy is very real and tangible to you
in a negative way. Then as soon as you
run into all that new energy, it is
mass. Energy is mass. Mass is energy.
And as soon as you run into that much
more energy, it feels like a lot of
weight. Feels very weighty. Paying
attention.
Therefore, at first it may seem as if,
oh my, well, I've just done a wonderful
thing and I've made a big step, but now
I've run smack into all this navy
energy. Oh, I'm going to get tired all
over again. When you begin to connect
into the understanding that all of that
energy is what will uplift you and
support you and accelerate you, then it
will not seem to carry weight. It will
not seem to be a barrier that you have
to wade through like
viscous energy. And in this way therefore you
energy. And in this way therefore you
will not continue to feel as if every
transformation you go through makes you
tired because you go obviously through
many transformations with your immediate
family. Is this assisting you? Is this assisting
Is this assisting you? Is this assisting
you? He left
me something else. No fine. All right.
Well, enjoy the
fourth. It is very very very sweet.
One more you want next.
Earlier this afternoon, I uh experienced
a a resurgence of something that I've
created before
and a lot of money is involved and the
idea has been created not by me that
perhaps tomorrow I will be in jail and I
would just wanted to know your
perceptions. Not created by you.
Thank you.
Any other perceptions you have? That was
a question.
Okay. Not created by
Not created by
you. If it is not in any way, shape or
form in any part created by you, how
could you be discussing it with
me? How could you even be aware of the
concept if it was not at least in part
created by you?
It was fair to meet that idea. Yes, of
course. You cannot experience anything
in your life that is not
to some degree. Now, how much relevance
it has to you is another matter. But
created by you, your version of it, it
was. Yeah.
Now, do you feel you are functioning
within your integrity? Yes. Truly. Yes.
Do you find within your imagination the
capability of expressing your integrity
and explaining the idea that you are to
the extent where you can then
extent where you can then
radiate a reality that may allow the
others involved in the
cocreation to not necessarily perhaps
see the need for the idea of the
limitation and the confinement.
I've explored this earlier this
afternoon and some progress has been made with it.
and some progress has been made with it.
Um, but it seems to be there is a little
difficulty there. There are always
always alternatives. Always other
alternatives. I made the offer of an alternative. All
I made the offer of an alternative. All
right.
And yet within that
offer it seemed from it seemed to me
from the other individual that there was
still not a
real willingness. All right. Love them
no less. All right. and trust no less
that again what is unfolding is going to
be what serves you. There is nothing
that happens in your life that
interrupts you. When I was coming up to
to be here tonight
um we stopped on the way and the person
who was driving the car went away for a
little while and I had a chance to
reflect on it because it come up kind of
suddenly and
In that
reflection, I really was able to totally
accept this as a exciting experience
because it does excite me the idea that
this is happening. All right. Very good.
Recognize that many times whether it
needs to as you say go through complete
physical fruition or not. Many times
another idea, another avenue, another
expression that many of you will have is
that as you begin to explore all the
different ways you can be of assistance
to the society in allowing everyone to
realize their own innate creativity and
freedom. At the same time, you will
explore the opposite polarity of the
idea of limitation and confinement so
that you will really, as you say, get a
handle on what freedom is and be able to
express the reality you truly believe in
to see that it works for you
before you present it to others that you
are attempting to convince will work for
them. You are getting in touch with what you
You are getting in touch with what you
truly believe about your reality to see
it in action for you so that you will
then be able to proceed without a shadow
of a doubt. Shadows of a doubt are
truly what are the bars of your day.
So you are
exploring all of these
shadows. Is that what the The deep
emotion that I created out of this
earlier this afternoon seems to surface.
Yes. To some degree a deep connection,
deep realization with the very core of
your beliefs. You have now in a sense at
least along this particular line been
completely stripped of all
surrounding circumstances that represent
old belief systems. And now you are
forcing yourself to deal with the
absolute core of your foundational
belief so that you know that it works
for you. I had a sense that this was the
opportunity to really know that I can
create anything I want. That is what I
just said.
Your terminology.
Thank you very much. relax
relax
and realize how very very interactive
you are in your dream reality with these
other individuals as well. Last night I
did dream about the situation
in a sense it didn't really surprise me
at all. Oh, very good. Thank you for
that. Then you are in touch. Yeah. Yes.
Bashar, I wanted to thank you first of
all for the meditation you gave me last
week. That was you mean that meditation
you gave yourself?
That's the one. Oh yes, I remember
now. Thank you for allowing me to
reflect it to you.
Well, thank you for allowing me to
reflect it to myself. Oh yes. and also
for what you said about
um the fact that I see more than I
analytically am aware of because that
also enabled me to get more out of the
experience because I didn't have to
analyze it. I could just do it, feel it,
be it, live it, and dream it. And that
was wonderful. Well, thank you for being
full of wonder.
It's my pleasure and ours. Yes, I know.
I have
um a message from a friend of mine in
Switzerland. And I just want to preface
this by saying that I saw her this
summer for the first time in nine years.
And we we sat up late every night, you
know, drinking wine, comparing notes
about our lives. And it was a source of
absolute amazement to me how parallel
our lives had been in the last nine
years since we had seen each other. And
I got this sense of that she is a facet
of myself. I said, you know, we're
cosmic twins, Carol. We're we're
How long is that individual going to
remain in that area? Well, she's
thinking of leaving. Actually,
physically she's leaving to go to
Vancouver December 11th or 12th, I think, to see
December 11th or 12th, I think, to see
some friends. And is she going back to
Futurland? Well, at this point, she plans to.
Well, at this point, she plans to.
And will she be back there in March?
Yes. Before that, she will be back there
in January, I'm sure. All right. Our
suggestion is that she remain in Ireland
through March, maybe April. Fascinating.
Can I tell her more about that?
Tell her to feel the openings in her
heart.
Tell her to listen for the harmonic
vibrations. I will. She wanted me to ask you if
I will. She wanted me to ask you if
there is a psychic in that area that she
would contact that you know of.
contact that you know of.
can perhaps find
in
March if necessary.
All right. May not be
necessary. Desire to find may be
indication of sensitivity to what we are
also as you say picking up upon.
Okay, I understand.
Um she related to me by letter that I
received today an experience that she
had recently when she and her daughter
were watching television and there was a
faith healer that was leading meditation
and they both closed their eyes and
participated and I guess it was amazing
experience for both of them and she said
that she contacted
uh what she described as a whiteness of
purity that she felt was total she had
connected to a total trust and she
wanted me to ask you about this. I feel
she just connected with her own higher
consciousness and snow. So March and
April. Okay. So that's all for now. Thank you.
Thank you.
Sure. I went into action right away on
what you said and completed some
activities. I was told that you had
something that you I'm done. I'm done.
Share.
Oh, what I don't remember exactly. Oh,
yes, you do. I remember this.
How come? It has to do with heaviness.
She asked about her family and a sense
of heaviness which related to the length
of a past looking back. When you when
you come up, you come good. Here you
come. Pay attention. I already got the
concept from this perspective. Go ahead.
Go ahead. Oh, you feel when you come
come up. New level, more energy. More
energy. When you come in space with a
new type of energy, new level, more
energy. Yeah, like you know I feel great
with everybody but then my mother
idea is basically that when you go from
one level to another because of what may
still be being brought with
from the lower level to the higher. When
you get to that next higher level and
you see that there is more energy, you
may still translate that more energy as
the idea of your habit of thinking of
energy as mass. And that is what may
cause the heaviness and the viscosity.
Because as you arrive on that level, you
only see it as more mass to push
through. But as you finally get beyond
the idea of those judgments and those
habits and ways of looking at things,
then you begin to realize that more
energy being there on the new level is
what will accelerate and support you and
create a sense of lightness. tiny bits
of [\h__\h] when a high level of awareness
of more.
Okay. Thank you.
Hello. Good morning. Hi. Two things.
first um tonight in my tonight in my
channeling class um which I just brushed
something remarkable happened and I
don't know. Are you going to remark on
it? Speak up then. Okay. Um I'm not sure.
Speak up then. Okay. Um I'm not sure.
I'm just a beginning channel and Oh,
nonsense. You are all old professionals.
Oh, believe me, there's always another
party in there and that's my good old
mind going thinking about everything
that happens, of course. All right. And
um what happened was I got out of the
trance and then was looking around at
everybody else and then I went back in
the trance without doing my
invocation and some different energy
came in that was kind of rough and I
didn't really feel anything negative
from it or anything like that. And it It
was um kind of abrupt and it it said
this sound was thinky thank you thinky
and then it insisted that Sora and Ral
help it
depart and it requested that they would
help it depart. Okay. And so I guess my
question is did it depart? Okay. Oh, it
did. But the idea is also to give you an
opportunity to get used to the idea that
you have a belief that you need the
invocation and that you are not just
simply intrinsically
level. Do not
forget a belief in the
need for precaution
invites the experience that reinforces
the
need. You follow me? If you know that
you are simply centered in the idea of
the expression of positive love and
light, then the idea of an invocation is
simply seen as another tool, as another
level, as another idea, but not
necessarily necessary. Knowingness will precede all
necessary. Knowingness will precede all
of that. The invocation is the
reflection of a belief, not a
knowingness. Tell me anything about that
that energy cuz I didn't see it as being
a negative energy. It wasn't. Yeah. Um
but it was your
mind echoing back to itself
in a sense. Mhm. You have created an
echo chamber from the belief of what you
have thought of of your mentality and
allowed, let us
say, a type of doppelganger energy, a
ghost energy, so to speak, a ghost echo
reflection of a portion of your
consciousness to feed back into itself
so that you could hear yourself thinking
about yourself. Oh, perfect. Yes.
Would that had that taken on existence
in my energy field? Yes, of course. As
as something that's been there for a
while, it had its own archetypal
consciousness for the purpose of the
interaction. It is now in a sense to
some degree reabsorbed into your energy
field. It is not so much that it's
departed. It diffused.
Is it going to be a problem in the
future or in
Are you making a prediction? No. No. No.
No. I just want to know if it's if it's
done with and I Are you making a
prediction? Am I making a prediction? Do you not
Am I making a prediction? Do you not
hear the contradiction in you? No. Do
you not hear the echo? Is this going to
be a problem? Oh,
is this going to be a problem? Problem.
Problem. Problem. Problem.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. Is there anything else you
want to tell me on that? No.
Okay. I have a guest tonight who is a
person that I was married to
was you all are. Yes. Well, this is
true. And uh
his pettian as some of you know him.
pettian as some of you know him.
And um I was I I have a feeling that
we've just been together an awful lot
and have been very
awful. We have been together many times
wonderful fashion and I was just
wondering if just
wondering is this curiosity being
presented in idle fashion or are you
capable of utilizing it to conduct your
own exploration? Yes, I'm here will be
utilizing the my own expert and
therefore what has attracted you that we
can assist you with as long as you take
the first step. Okay. Um I know that in
this lifetime
um he appears to be a person with a dark
skin and I appear to be a person with a
light skin. Okay. I never noticed that
the whole time we were married. I mean
really. And so now that I've been in
metaphysics for a long time, I realized
that probably many times that we were
together before that was either reversed
or changed or different. And I was just
wondering why this happened in this
lifetime and or just anything you might
be able to Well, what have you learned
from it? Oh, I've learned um that from a
individual level, person to person, of
course, there's no no issue. All right.
Then you have learned that that is one
reason. What is
embarrassing? Embarrassing.
Embarrassing.
All knowledge is a gift. Yes. All
knowledge is why be embarrassed? Okay. I
will be embarrassed. A large part of the
reason why we so want knowledge is more
having to do with society than with each
other. All right.
Now you have learned that society will
generate and other individuals will
generate their own belief structures
about certain ideas and that you can
either choose to adopt those structures
for yourself or remain true to what you
know is the vibration of your
being. You either retain your own power
or you give it away. Oh yes. Anything else?
Did you share something of of one of our
past lives with
we find that in this particular
connotation the one that stands out most
primarily for now at least
first will be one in
which let us call you
homesteaders in what you call your
American west west
approximately 1860 [Music] 637 637
approximately area you
area you
call the
Anna to begin with.
situation was similar
then. Same sect,
same race for
each. And you dealt
then much more strongly than you have in
this life
also with
society perspective of your chosen
situation. But you have been together so
many times that you simply knew that you
times that you simply knew that you
really did not care deep down what
society thought. But in that light it
was a little bit more of a struggle for
you. So you decided that where it would
be more comfortable for you to express
this relationship would be in a portion
of the country that had as yet not
become so structured. So together you
moved what you call out
west and
homestead. There were in your terms
difficult times. There were in your
terms wonderful
times. That will do.
Will that have assisted you?
The light is
now. It's beautiful. We
beautiful. We
thank you
both for the
reflection of the
opportunity for that which exists in
your society to see within you. the
reflection of the facet of themselves
that can also represent their ability to
look inward and allow all portions of
their being to be equal to all other
portions. Thank you. Shark
you. What do you think of this reality? It is
What do you think of this reality? It is
very exciting.
How does it compare here to
different? It is more highly focused in
many different ways because of the
exploration of limitations that you have
undertaken for many hundreds of
thousands of years is very highly
energetic and therefore energized in
that direction. But therefore to our
direction. But therefore to our
perspective because transformation is
not the product of mediocrity just as
deeply negative as you have explored
will be the degree to which you explore
positive integration. So it is very
active in that way, very energy active.
That to some
degree in the way you express it is
quite different from our reality which
is very active and very spontaneous but
in an overall sense much
more moderated in the sense that all beings
moderated in the sense that all beings
within our society are in alignment in
generally speaking the same direction
regardless of very very strong and
unique expressions of individuality
which of course are not stifled.
But it simply is that each and every one
of our individual expressions always
feeds the whole automatically. That is
simply the definition of our society at
this time. In general, the same can be
said for your society except that the
whole that it feeds for now is the whole
idea of the exploration of each and
every one of your diverse abilities. And
so there seems to be very
much disagreement when in fact what you are
disagreement when in fact what you are
doing is exploring all the different
ways that each and every one of you can
be so that there can be an allowance in
the diversity and an equality and a
validity in the diversity and that is
what will create a unity upon your
planet that will then create your
civilization to be very much more
similar to our own.
How do you express yourself in your
civilization?
telepathically if that is what you mean.
I do that. Now recognize that in a way
so do you but many of you are simply not
aware of it because first of all many of
you do not have a belief system about
it. It goes on nonetheless and each and
every one of you are connected
mentally. You share this mental
connection if only to create the general
reality you all experience. You all
obviously agree to experience a similar
reality on some level and basically that
is the level on which you agree to
experience the same thing almost the
same thing. Is is there anything that holds
thing. Is is there anything that holds
us back from being in your in your
space? unconditional
love. Lack of willingness or the fear to
express unconditional love and absolute
trust is the only difference.
Thank you. Thank you. Yes.
Yes.
I had a question about um primal
vibration. Primal vibration. All right.
Primal energy. What what why is it what
exactly is it and why is it important
that we are that we get in touch with
primal? Well, there can be many
definitions to this idea, but as we
generally mean the idea primal energy is
simply the so to speak background
vibration that
is common if you will to all realities.
It is the original signal so to speak
from that original modulation of the
primal energy field out of which all
realities are created comes all the
diversification that you experience as
all the different realities. So when
each and every different reality allows
itself to express its differences and at
the same time paradoxically be in touch
with the primal vibration that connects
all of them then those differences can
be equalized
on the level from which they all are
equally created.
Is the earth um is that is that our prim
is it the primal vibration or does that
come from the earth? It comes from
creation itself. that comes from
existence. Now your earth because it
represents a total congregation of your
civilization has a manifestation of one
particular vibration that does represent
a type of foundation to which you are
all connected. In a sense it is a primal
vibration but it is not the primal
vibration of
existence. Yet it is the definition that
connects all of you as a
civilization. You follow me? Yes I did.
And I just had one last question. Um the
Thunderbird I'm
still I'm still interested. Is this
connected with some sort of kalini or
some sort of um it can be it is a
recognition of power on that level. The
lightning strike, the thunderbolt which
the condundalini energy is a connection
and a representation of. You do
recognize the idea that a lightning bolt
and the thunder. That whole idea of that
manifestation of energy and power is
that when you see the lightning bolt, it
is because a path has already been set
up. A connection has already been formed
between a positive and a negative pole
in the sky and in your earth. You follow
me? Yes. When that path is linked, then
you see the both. It is the same thing
with your brain and certain other
portions of your body. In that way, the
spinal column represents the probable
path. And when you create a linkup, as
soon as you connect the two poles by
clearing all the different doorways
along the spine that represent all the
different levels of your chakra, then
you make a connection and in making that
pathway connection, then the energy can
shoot along that path completely free
and unobstructed. And that is the same
thing as a lightning bolt. And that is
the same thing as the experience of
instantaneous revelation.
Is that what the Thunderbird symbolizes?
It is one aspect. It symbolize many
things. That is one aspect. It does
symbolize the freedom. It does symbolize
the higher consciousness. Therefore, the
perspective to quote unquote look down
upon what was formerly an isolated
reality and be able to see from that
perspective the expanse and the inter
relationship of all that
is. You follow me? Yes, we do. It is
soaring as yourself. It is a total
freedom and allowance and it is a
doorway and a gateway into the dimension
that represents that idea.
Okay. Thank you very much. It is also
once again connected in similar ways to
the symbol you call the phoenix and in
some levels the symbol you call the
dragon depends upon the point of view
and therefore the representative culture
created from that point of view.
Thank you. Thank you very much for you.
I my first born here. I'm very very
pleased to be here. Um we are always
overjoyed. I have a um recognized a very negative
I have a um recognized a very negative
pattern in my life that has become so
intensely uh um mirrored to me that now
I am in a state of uh of uh almost
panic. Oh, to know which direction to
go. If I should all right seek a new uh
situation or if I should wrestle this
one out. I'm not sure. What are you
doing in your life? What excites you the
most? Uh, a lot of what I do in my life
Uh, a lot of what I do in my life
excites me a great deal. Yeah. Are there
things that excite you more than what
you are doing that you are not doing?
I'm not quite sure I understand. Are
there things in your life, the things
that you are not doing that actually
carry a higher degree of excitement than
the things you are doing? Yes. Yes. Some
of them. All right. When will you do
them?
Tomorrow. All right. As soon as I
possibly can. I I'm not sure if this
situation is holding me back or if I
should. Nothing holds you back. Nothing
holds you back.
If you are willing to recognize every
situation is there for a reason and you
can glean positive reality and
understanding out of it, then you can
allow it to serve you which will allow
you to go on. You do not need to create
difficult decisions. All you need to do
is simply follow at any given moment
what moves you and excites you or what
you know to be true for you. The rest
will take care of itself automatically.
There's no need for struggling. If you
feel that quote unquote being persistent
in a situation is a reflection of your
integrity, then by all means stay with
the situation. But if you find that it
is a struggle and an uphill battle and
that you are not sure it is a
representation of your integrity, then
by all means do what is a representation
of your integrity. There is nothing
nothing nothing in the universe that
says you have to suffer or struggle or
strive to achieve whatever you desire.
It is completely and utterly deserved by
you simply because of the fact that you
exist. Give yourself the permission to
let it be that simple.
All right. Yeah. All that is and the
infinite creator has created you out of
unconditional love. Treat yourself with
the same respect and let your life be as
simple as the creation itself is in
creating you. Now the
Now the
idea of these reflections that you give
yourself in life are not there to make
you think that you are stuck in
something. They are there to show you
what your beliefs are. And if you don't
prefer them, to change them, to redefine
the idea, to know that because you can
see this apparent negative situation in
your life, because you can see it, that
lets you know you can change it.
Otherwise, you wouldn't see it. You
would just go on and on and on and on
and on and on and on and on. I love you.
Yes. and never never know that the
situation was anything that could be
changed. It would seem completely
natural no matter how insufferable it
was. To see situations in your life,
even when they occur in a negative
fashion is to be shown the doorway out
of that
situation. All you need to do is treat
it as a door and walk through it, not
avoid it.
Yes. I I had a very very strange dream
last night. Oh, goody.
be uh uh inviting into my bedroom uh an
an old lover uh who I associate with
some violence and having a boss that I
am now associated with who is also a
very uh uh verbally violent person
sitting next to me in the bed reading a
newspaper and then walking out into the
backyard and seeing a tree with no
leaves where the branches fell off and
gates with locks all over them. My my
Yes, I know. It was a very strange
dream. Yes, but obviously very accurate
in terms of your energy and your beliefs
about the situation you have created.
Now once again all you need to realize
is that your capability of seeing it and
the capability to imagine you would like
it to be otherwise is in and of itself
the ability to create it to be
otherwise. More than that, the ability
to see how you would rather it be is the
actual changing of the situation because
you can only perceive what you already
are on a level of.
And all you need to do is remember that
your imagination is as real as physical
reality. Your physical reality is
created from your imagination. And as
long as you think that well here's an
idea I would really like to be. As long
as you think that that ability to
perceive that new idea is something less
than real and that you have to do
something special in order to become
real with that situation. Then you will
not allow the imagination or the
perception of the situation to be
reality in itself. Once you allow the
imagination, your ability to perceive
the situation you would prefer to be
reality itself. All you need to do is to
start acting as if it is truly real and
really believe it. And then you will see
that reflected in your reality. Because
once again there are no situations that
have built-in meaning. No situation
means anything. It is simply a set of
props of circumstances. You give them
meaning. The meaning you give them
determines the effect you get out of
them. So if you see a circumstance and
say this is negative, that's the effect
you'll get. If you say well it is
obviously here to serve me in a positive
way, then that's the effect you will
get. No symbol has built-in meaning. All
situations are neutral. Neutral.
Neutral. blank. Nothing comes that
imposes anything upon you. You provide
through the belief systems you have been
taught in this life the meaning to any
given situation. And therefore, because
the universe serves you, you are given
an absolutely 100% accurate down to the
very minutest detail reflection of that
belief. That is there to let you know
what your belief is in no uncertain
terms. And if you don't prefer it the
way it is, to fine-tune it and home in
on the way you do prefer to be to
recalibrate the definition and know that
the second you recalibrate the
definition and start acting like the new
definition, that's the reality you will
get. Thank you. It is that simple. Let it be
Thank you. It is that simple. Let it be
that simple. Trust, trust, trust. Is
there a is there a process that I can
use when I'm
live live? If you feel you need any
particular process, I could give you
techniques. I could give you exercises
and I could give you processes from now
until infinity. But the idea is to recognize
infinity. But the idea is to recognize
that anything I will give you will be
altered by your imagination in the way
it needs to be altered anyway. So why
not simply begin and end with your
imagination which is key to your
vibration and able to provide you with
whatever process you need if you believe
you need one. Okay?
Go with what you feel will move you. emotions, energy,
motion, desire, and trust. And know that
what you vibrate most strongly to is
that which represents the being you
chose to be. That's what excitement is.
That's what knowingness is. It's your
physical awareness of the vibratory path
that represents the idea you chose to be
in this life. That's why you can always
feel free to move towards your
excitement. No matter whether the
situation that is exciting seems to have
anything at all to do with any other
situation you have ever done or seems to
be connected in any way, shape or form
to anything you think it needs to be
connected to to get you where you think
you need to be going.
All the details take care of themselves
when you supply the automatic
trust. Your life becomes a synchronous
ecstatic explosion of
coincidence. The right place, right
time, right people always. That is the
way it always is. But when you allow it
to be positive, then you are aware that
that's the way it always is.
Thank you. Sweet dream. For sure. For
sure. you. What is it? Uh uh what are
the how do you perceive the mechanics of
how physical reality seems so solid and
and fixed and unrelike when it is that
way? Well, to be pragmatic about it, you
are modulating the primal
energy, the frequency with which you
modulate that energy.
When it
is
expressed in equal terms with the
frequency you are being at any given
moment, it obviously must seem solid
since a frequency on whatever level you
are must be quote unquote
interactable. Is this making any sense
to you? No. Could you give me another?
An idea that you are, any idea you
become at any given moment will be
represented as a particular frequency in
the primal energy of existence. I see.
Any expression of the frequency you are
since it is of the same frequency will
obviously for the purposes of
interaction have to be quote unquote
solid enough to interact with. It is
solid enough to interact with because it
is the same frequency of the idea you
are being.
So it's a particular frequency that
solidity is the product of equal
definition or equal
identification. As soon as you identify
with something, it becomes quote unquote
real to you. Mhm.
You follow me? Is this is this right? Is
this the uh the template
uh universe template that you were that
you talked about before?
The template is what allows you to
perform this
miracle. The template contains all
possible frequencies. The frequency you
are, if you choose to exist in an idea
in which there is the idea of separation
and interaction, then everything you
create in that universe will be of your
frequency. Those that are not of your
frequency seem to be of other universes
and therefore you don't interact with
them. Correct. So solidity, the illusion
of solidity comes from equal
identification with an idea.
So would the people of Sirius who are
not in physical experience solidity in
their fashion? Yes. But in your
description of solidity, it would not
seem to be solid at all. And it is not
even exactly the same type of
manifestation as the solidity you
experience as a parallel earth which
shares a similar type of expression of
solidity. Yet you don't share their
solidity. The serious solidity to them
in a sense is solid but not the same
type of solid that you think of as solid
because they have in their primal
equation an entirely different
definition of how they create the idea
that they are. Is this making sense?
More flow a little bit. All right. Let
us just say it is basically that way for
all levels. Let us keep it simple,
right? Whatever you identify with is
what is real to you, right? Is what is
solid so to speak to you.
Solid simply
basically refers to the capability to
interact with.
Okay. Mhm. Matching the vibration. Yay.
A that creates an apparent validity. Is
it is it that part of the agreements of
the physical is that fixidity?
Okay. In some physical realms, not all,
some there are some physical realms in
which there is a high degree of
malleability, conscious recognition, for
there is a high degree of malleability
in your reality as well. But you're not
focused on the malleability or have not
been. You have been focused on the
so-called continuum or
consistency. Other physical realities
are focused on the malleability and in a
sense that is what you are shifting
towards. Right.
Right. Very rapidly. Hey, thank you.
Thank you. Sorry. You. Thank you. What
about me? And then you all right? So I
need um your assistance in understanding
something first of all. Yes. Or your
reflection please. Um first of all I I
was referring to the word need
but go ahead. Okay. I don't need it but
I would like
thank you. Um this week starting from
Monday I suppose I'd say has been very
exciting in very many ways and I look at
everything as being positive. No. Right.
Yeah. And
on Monday, I found myself doing
something uh in a service for someone
else. Found yourself. I I did it. Yes.
Yeah. And I I was at a deposition and I had
And I I was at a deposition and I had
not started out my day knowing I was
going to be on a deposition helping
somebody else. Yes. I spent my whole day
till 10:30 at night being the service.
And I got home and I I actually went in
I started crying. I thought what the
hell was I doing today? Because I could
have been earning some money which I
haven't been doing recently and I could
have been doing something else. Are you
playing what if instead of what is well
what is is that I did that that day.
Yes. So why not let your life continue
to unfold so that eventually you will
find out why you did what you did then
and see where it fits into your life
later. Yeah. Okay. On T. Yes, I could do that.
Yeah. Okay. On T. Yes, I could do that.
What? It's up to you. You don't have to.
It is simply that many times. The
so-called negative puzzlement that many
of you experience about, well, why did
that happen? Simply is because you do
not allow yourself to live the life and
see eventually why it happened. If you
allow yourself to gauge any situation in
your life, not simply against what has
already happened, but also against what
is yet to come, then perhaps you will
extend your understanding to the
appreciation of situations that have
been similar in your life. When maybe in
the past, as you say, a certain thing
happened that you did not understand at
the time, but now where you are now, you
do appreciate and understand the ideas.
So why not simply assume that the
experience you are having now if you do
not understand them immediately in the
present will someday be understood and
when they are understood will be exactly
when they need to be understood and not
a second sooner and get on with your
life and live in ecstasy and joy knowing
that you will understand everything you
need to know about this life you chose
to live otherwise if you don't what's
the point
well there isn't any point I mean I'm I
am having fun yes And
then why play all of these what if games
with yourself? Oh, I could have been
doing this. I could have been doing
that. Well, I did that in that
particular instance. All right. You will
learn from that as well then. Yes. And I
don't normally do that. All right. On
Tuesday, I had a lousy day, but it was
positive.
I feel I feel now physically I my I feel
safe. All right.
And excuse me, I knew I was not going to
die. Okay. But I felt like I was going
to die. And what I was doing was
actually just ending a process. All
right. Yeah. So, but I went into a lot of grief
Yeah. So, but I went into a lot of grief
on it, too. All right. I guess that's
okay. Of course. Um, well,
okay. I'm confused. All
right. What do you want to do with your
computer? I would like to put my life in some
I would like to put my life in some
order except that it is probably in fact
it is probably my life is in order. It's
just that there are so many things
happening right now. It's in spontaneous
orchestration. It is
spontaneous and it's even not too fast
for me except of course not
right. I was going to go to Europe this
evening. Not this evening. I was going
to go to Europe at Christmas time. All
right. Okay. This evening before you
started talking and while you were
talking that whole idea just well I
already traveled there and did it so I
don't need to do it. And I was what it
would be kind of fun to go actually in
the physical universe. Then go. I don't
want to. Then don't. Well um
Well um
now I have to create something else
which I will do. You already have. I
know I have and I don't know what it is
yet. What are you doing right now? I'm
creating. Then you know what it is.
Whatever you are doing right now in this
moment is what you have created next.
Well, I'm still feeling lightheaded.
Actually, it's okay. I just feel like
it's okay.
Yes. Maybe you are lightheaded because
you are lightening up
and becoming
enlightened. Well, I am. I am.
Then don't be so hard on yourself.
Relax. Enjoy it.
Well, pier next to me here is solid. I
mean, no, the body is here and so I can
I can touch it and I Okay, fine.
Whoa. It's
just fun and it's exciting and I'm still
lightheaded and enjoy it. Come on. Okay.
Next week, she'll be saying, "You know
that lightheaded feeling? Boy, I wish I
had that
back. How can I get that again? I was so
euphoric there for a while and then all
of a sudden everything became so solid
again. I now want that euphoria back."
Hey, you're learning how humans work,
don't you?
And in one sense, I have already learned
that. Well, I'm going to be a grandmother in
Well, I'm going to be a grandmother in
March, and I just want you to know that
I'm really, really happy about having
another physical being in Well, that
being in all reality is probably very
happy and happy and happy, happy, happy
to have you as well.
[Music] Yeah. Thank you. Thank you, Bashar.
Yeah. Thank you. Thank you, Bashar.
Now, now
Thank you. No time like the present.
Actually, I have a situation in the past
I want to share.
You will share it in the present.
this morning. my first client, okay, in
the work that I do, uh,
57year-old Yungian psychologist,
okay, and I are working together
and a situation that's come up in the
last 3 years of our
interaction re um, let me see, I was
going to say repeated itself, provided a
another opportunity to look at a similar
situation from a different
view and I chose a whole different task
which in communicating with this
individual he has this way of if there's
something that needs attention in his uh
physical body I provide a specific
um alteration for that area. All right.
Okay. That always to be included within
everything else. All right. And so that
every time there'll be something added
if there is
something extra needed at that
particular moment. Oh. Okay. So
when I perceive
no need for that special attention,
I forgo it. And he always calls my
attention to it. Oh, what? Did you
forget this? Right. And you say no. No.
Right. Well, then is it better doing it
this way? I go, "No, different." And
then he goes, "Different. Don't give me
any of that
shit." You know, in the sense of that
I'm coping out. All right. In his
terminology. So, okay. So, then
um I go, "Oh, the judge is here." All
right. We called a certain part of
himself the judge. Okay. So, as soon as
I said that, he went into beyond the
judge mode, more the attack mode.
The attack,
right? Beware of attack.
So, he said, "Oh, I found a spot and
I've got my finger in it and did this
thing that I thought, well, you're
projecting your idea on me." I go,
"That's not my truth." Right. And he
said, "You're act well, were you asleep?
Did you not want to add this or is it
better? I go, no, it's different and it
doesn't matter whether I add it or
subtract it. This is the way it is right
now. So, we got into this thing where he
wanted to engage me definitely like
actually threatened that he was going to
hit me, right? And I said, "All right,
that's it. That's the end of today's
session. I don't want to talk about it."
And I left the room. Don't wait. Okay.
He um uh got ready, came out and said,
"We still have time. We can talk about
it. I don't want to talk about it." I
said, "I don't want to engage you in
your psychological mode." All right.
Because talking is his tool. Oh, what?
All right. So, yay.
So, when I'm my question,
you know what my question is? Not
really. All right. I can feel your
intention. Okay. But not the specificity
of your question. All right. My
intention is to know that because I in
the past I chose the mode to humor him,
you know, allow him to like manipulate
me. Allow some of my power to be given
to him. All right. And now you are
allowing him an accurate reflection of
the being you actually are. Right. All
right. Okay. Now when that comes to a
point, now I don't look at it I didn't
look at it today all day as negative.
Well, right. uh but rather a very
different very exciting change because
this personality that I was dealing with
is very strong and overbearing right in
a sense has been overbearing and it's
the first time I stood for who I am and
who I know myself to be oh you are a
very good patient
and that individual a very good teacher
okay so and vice versa
so he left in really
a confused his state because I would not
deal with him on the level he wanted. So
now he must deal with himself.
All right. What I'm looking for or what
my my intention
is because it was such a volatile thing
and I chose not to talk.
Yay. I I kept you know going back to the
situation looking I know I handled it
exactly how I should have at that moment
cuz that's obviously what I did. All
right. But as I look back, is there you
know where was I on the positive
negative on the edge of the coin as we
talked about discussed from our
perspective positive positive let us
say at the one point where you refused
to
re-engage there was what you are sensing
is that there was the opportunity to
allow that to be either positive or
negative in the sense of either simply
acting or reacting. All
right. It is our perception that for the
particular individual you are describing
it was an action in the overall sense
and now this individual must rely upon
themsel and cease to rely upon you
because you have now shown them who you
actually are. And they must decide
whether or not the reflection of you
that they have created in their lives
for themselves to see is something they
wish to continue or not.
Now you have put them squarely in touch
with their own self-empowerment and
their own ability to see an example in
you that they can either choose to
become like or
not. You are giving them their power.
You are allowing them to create their
life and make their own
determination. Thank you. Thank you very
much because the last three months has
allowed me to see that ability and have
and demonstrated in doing this of my
work. Good. Thank you. Oh, thank you
very much for sure.
I do have one other question. All right.
Is it possible? Okay. Uh I have a a
friend. I've recently uh
uh engaged a uh a sharing with okay and
when I perceive any kind of like
connection I don't get anything
necessarily in the past but what I do is
get an immediate idea that this is
actually a relationship of the future.
All right. In a sense, understand that
you have many connections, but what
stands out at any given moment is simply
those portions that you need to look at
to be the person you need to be in this
moment. If you are exploring much ideas of
If you are exploring much ideas of
centering, then if you have already
centered with many ideas in the past,
then perhaps the strongest reflection
with any relationship will be one of the
so-called future simply because you are
creating the past and the future from
the present. So you have the opportunity
to look in either direction. So it's
actually creating or focusing your idea
into a a point which will in a sense in
our time space reference draw us into or
magnetize yes to allow you to become
that ideal you have of yourself as a
so-called future being. Okay in the
present. Thank you for
Thank you for
male female. I had a question for the
dreamer and I wondered if it would be
possible to ask it directly. Can you
speak up for the mic a bit?
Question for the dreamer.
Ask me.
All right. Uh, a week ago, we had an
right. Uh, a week ago, we had an
interaction in Florida between a group
of people and a group of
dolphins that was monitored very
successfully by a by a physician, by a
doctor. Uh it was rather marvelous. Uh in spite
Uh it was rather marvelous. Uh in spite
of an incident which occurred the day
before the interaction when we
introduced the doctor to the dolphins
for the first time. He had never been
with dolphins. Not true.
You answered my
question. A many interactions in dream.
be many many
many interactions in
Atlantis. This is something familiar and
that is why the change was so
abrupt. Uh the incident that I was
referring to was not in context. He went
into the water with three very gentle,
very lovable dolphins, one of whom bit
him pretty severely. Yes.
To wake him up. That was a pretty angry
dolphin. I think not really.
It was simply, let it say, that they
recognize an old friend
asleep and that friend needed to be
awakened very quickly, very abruptly,
very shockingly.
They know what they're doing
instinctively.
Thank you. Thank you. I'm sorry.
Y finally um I am learning from a
situation in my life which speak which
is how to speak up reject
my which may relate to another situation
which I'm also learning from which has
to do with a um injury I've created in
my life twice, which is spraining my
right wrist. And in learning from this
um opportunity, I've looked and seen
some feelings that may be represented in
this injury, such as the a fear of
expressing myself or a lack of
integration between like the arm as an
expressing outward from the heart and
the hand as as somehow interfacing with
the world. All right. All well and good
as symbology. Does it suffice to allow
you to be in touch with the fact that
you are expressing yourself just fine
right now?
Yes, but earlier this evening I felt
very out of touch with that. That was
then. That's
true. So anyway, I'm looking at the
situation and my root is taking a fairly
long time to get back together and seems
to not quite be totally there. And um
I'm looking at that and then saying well
then there's something more I still am
trying to learn from this or still
wanting to learn from this situation.
Sorry. Do not be sorry.
Do not be sorry.
Okay. Other people. Okay. So then when I
was reflecting on this and what it is
I'm I want to learn. Yes. These images
came to me at one point where I got this
feeling of of fear which related to my
own sort of negative selfimage and sort
of part of myself that I didn't like or
wasn't relating to or right in that sort
of a dark spot and dark spot. One
moment. Will you do me a favor?
Will you take one deep breath and hold
it? Okay. And go. Okay.
One more time.
All right. One more
time. H. All right.
Now, inhale. Exhale. And then make the
[Music] noise h.
Exhale all the way. Then make the noise. Oh. Huh.
Oh. Huh.
Now, where do you imagine the sound to
be coming from?
Body. The body. All right. Or the energy
of the body. All right. Very good.
mouth. While what you call air will be
responsible to some degree, voice is
very largely a manifestation of
electricity. The vibration of your vocal
cords is as much an electrical phenomena
as it is a vibration from air. In many
ways, actually more so.
Allow yourself to get in touch with the
resonating frequency of the
idea of the expression of yourself and
allow yourself the opportunity perhaps
of
inhaling,
exhaling. Then allowing yourself to see
that you have the capability of
generating the idea of vocalized
expression without as much expulsion of
air. This perhaps will tie into the
This perhaps will tie into the
understanding that you are not giving
anything up that sustains you in order
to
communicate, but allows you to rely on a
much more simplified and a much more
energetic source of
capability. You will begin to vibrate in
accord in harmonious accord with the
energy being that you
are. You follow me? Um, no. I I don't
follow this concept that you just
mentioned about
You are energy. Do you follow that?
Do you follow that you are energy? Yes.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yeah. Yes.
Yeah. All right.
Allow yourself the opportunity to
communicate as
energy rather than thinking that you
have to
expel something from you in order to
communicate, in order to be heard.
You follow me? Yeah. I don't really see
the distinction. It seems like the the
expression would be the energy. Not
necessarily. The idea also can allow you to create a
The idea also can allow you to create a
scenario in which you will simply know
you are being heard regardless of what
you call the decibel
level. You follow me?
Not really.
Could you restate that in a different
way? What could you restate that? What
could you restate that?
Now, do you know that I heard you? Well,
I think you did. You think I did?
But you said what? Like,
so do you know that I heard you?
I assume so. I don't know.
What? I I assume that you heard me, but
Are you getting the picture at all?
I'm not sure.
When will you be sure?
I I do I don't quite understand what's
going on right now. So, all right. When
would you like to understand? Right now.
Right now. Yeah.
Yes. Yes. What?
Do you like Zen?
Um, I don't know a lot about it. All
right. Perhaps it will be of some
assistance to you. It is one suggestion
for one symbology, for one tool that you
may find some association with that may
allow you the opportunity to recognize
that as soon as you believe you are
worth listening to, you will be heard.
And you will know you are being heard
regardless of someone else's
reaction. And therefore, you will not
have to be insistent about what you are
saying. You will simply express yourself
as clearly and concisely as you know
represents the being in the vibrational
energy that you are. And you will not
have to expend effort in being heard.
You know that I heard you. You know I
heard you. But you are simply completely
unwilling to trust that you knew that.
So the real issue is trusting myself
that I'm waiting to be heard. Innocence.
Yes. Allow yourself to know that what you
Allow yourself to know that what you
have to say and what you feel like
sharing from your heart, from your very
core, from your being is a gift. Not
that you have to force it on anyone, not
that anyone really has to listen. But
the idea is that if you are willing to
know that the expressions you
share are sufficiently shared simply
because they are being given in service,
they are being shared so that you know
what you are all
about. Then it doesn't really matter how
anyone else takes it. You know how it
was meant to be taken. Therefore, you
know that on that level that you
intended it to be taken somehow someway
it was
heard. Whether it appears to be or not
on the surface doesn't necessarily
matter.
You follow me? Right. So, so don't be
concerned with the exact. Yes. We can't
with the truth
in general. Yes.
If you are sharing with integrity, then
you simply recognize that the effect
will be a reflection of that integrity
and positive
awareness. So, do you um agree with what
I said about my does that make sense in
this scenario?
It is connected to some degree but more
in the
sense let us say it is a parallel
symbol. If you feel that you have not got a
If you feel that you have not got a
handle on things and the communication
is a very important handle then you may
also be
reflecting the idea of your incapacity
to get a firm
grip. In this way also it is another
form of
communication. It is another level which
you see being expressed through this
physiological channel all the time.
It is another level of the dialogue we
are having with you.
you.
Perhaps if you are willing to know that
know that
sometimes simply reaching out to
touch is all the communication that is
necessary. Perhaps you will not put a
high demand on the way you think you should
demand on the way you think you should
be able to
communicate and will reinforce and
strengthen all modes of communication
within
you rather than cut yourself
off. You follow me?
Um everything except for the last sleep
on it.
Okay. Do
things, gentle things, loving things
with your
hands, peeing
things, things of service. And the
energy that flows through your wrist and
your hand will also center and heal you.
And it will be a form of
communication. And it will paradoxically
strengthen all other forms of
communication.
All right. Yeah. Thank you. You're
welcome. Thank you.
There will be but a few moments
remaining.
Basha, when you were talking to Joan
earlier, you me and she mentioned her
friend from Switzerland. You said
something about March and April and I
thought it was really strange because I
had I have tentative plans to be in
Switzerland in April and I was wondering
what was that related to Switzerland or
was it related specifically to Joan's
friend and her relationship with
Switzerland? I am so very happy that you will find
I am so very happy that you will find
out.
Okay. Thank you.