All right, I'll say how are you all this
evening of your time as you create time
to exist. Great. We will begin this
interaction this evening of your
time by continuence of an
idea that many of you have discussed
with us off and on. As you
share, many of you in
your what you label to be searches into
the idea of your understanding of the
universe of all that is usually find
yourselves approaching this idea
from one generalized direction because
of the way you have created your society
to be because of the type of
understanding you have created for
yourself in your
society. When you begin the endeavors
of your so-called spiritual search for
yourself. In this way, you will come
upon ideas, questions, and formats that
have to do with the very structure of
what you consider to be the universe
itself. This many times within your particular
This many times within your particular
civilization, within your society will
bring you because you are used to asking
yourself questions in order to form a
foundation for your search. You will
bring yourself to the question well
why does the universe exist
anywhere? Many of you have shared this
idea with us. Now to begin with from our
point of view the
idea sometimes comes about as a question
in the form of well what was there
before there was creation and from our
point of view creation always was is now
always will be time the concept of
before and after are something that
belong within creation and are subject
to existence existence is not subject to
time. Therefore, in this way, what is
simply always is and from your linear
time frame referential point of view,
always has been and always will be.
Although the terms has been and will be
are only symbolic reflections of another
way to say that it simply always will be
is in the now, always present. You are
eternal since you are created from all
that is in a sense you have always been
are now and always will be not
necessarily the idea within a time frame
reference of the particular fragment you
call yourself now but the overall idea
of your
consciousness always exists. You are
eternal since you are made out of
eternity. Now the
Now the
idea of answering so to speak the
question of well why is there existence
anyways can in a sense be answered. But
you may find that when you
begin to involve yourself in forming a
relationship to things that are dealing
with what you call fundamental, the
basic very generalized fundamental, the
primary foundations of existence, then
the answers will tend to become more and
more and more simple.
But it is not so much that there isn't
so to speak an answer to that question.
Simply it is that the answer is so
simple you have overlooked it because we
do not think that that degree of
simplicity represents anything real to
you. Now we can give simply our point of view
Now we can give simply our point of view
as to the idea of why existence exists
to begin with. But we will share with
you that we may recognize because we are
to some degree familiar with the ideas
you have created, the points of view
have created, the way you look at things
in your society, we might be able to let
us say imagine that you may or may not
find this to be in your eyes an
oversimplification. But that will simply
have to be the way it is if that is the
case for you.
Therefore, you may recognize the idea
like this. When you ask yourself the
this. When you ask yourself the
question, well, why does it exist? You
are making an assumption that there is
only one side to
exist. In this way, you simply ask the
question because you think that it was
possible for everything to not have
existed. But recognize you are making
the assumption that
nonexistence is not something that is
real. In this way, recognize that there
is both existence and
non-existence. They both occur at the
same time, so to speak, to be colloquial
in your language. It is not necessarily
a matter that the universe either could
have existed or not existed. Both
realities are present. There is
existence and non-existence. However,
the reason you do not recognize the idea
that both exist simultaneously side by
side is that now you are dealing with a
very fundamental
foundational reference point itself. And
when you deal on that level so to speak,
what you are dealing with forms its own
definitive reality.
In other words, it defines
itself. Therefore, simply recognize it
is not that existence and non-existence
are not both real, but by definition,
existence is the only thing that can
exist. Nonexistence doesn't
Nonexistence doesn't
exist. That does not mean it is not
real. It simply means that by definition
non-existence doesn't exist. Therefore,
it is not part of what you perceive to
be as existence.
You cannot imagine
nonexistence in your reality. The only
definition that you have is your
perception of your participation in
existence because that is the only
reality that allows you to have a
perception. Non-existence by definition
does not allow there to be perception of
itself. It is not that it is not real.
It is not that it did not come into
fruition quote unquote at the same time
as existence. It is not that the
universe could have gone one way or
another to exist or to not exist. Both
are real. They are the primary
polarities in that way. But on that
level, they are only what their
definition says they are. And since the
definition of non-existence is that it
does not exist, you cannot experience
it. Therefore, you are simply experiencing
Therefore, you are simply experiencing
the side that says you can experience
it. That is all there is to it.
You follow me?
Sharing.
No. Once again, even nothing is
something. You have no ability. No one
does has any ability to even conceive of
nonexistence. If you were able to and
then came back into existence, you'd
never know. You had been
gone. For you do not have the apparatus
to know where it was, you
weren't. You follow me. Therefore, any
concept that you find in your reality,
no matter what definition you give it,
no matter how it feels experientially
perhaps to be like a void or like
nothingness, it is still something and
it is still a part of existence simply
because you can define it. You can
experience it. It is something to you.
It has a label. You follow me? But is it
true that we are nonexistent every
other? No, no, no, no, no, not really.
The idea was simply an analogy as we
have defined the parallel universes in
your time frame reference viewpoint. The
idea that you let us say flicker on and
off. But it is not that you so much
flicker into non-existence. You simply
flicker into other parallel realities
which from this point of view you do not
consider to be real. You follow me?
Like the Hindus talk about the day and
night.
It is valid for them. But once again, it
is not truly non-existent. If they can
describe it, it is not truly
non-existent. If you even have a label for the
If you even have a label for the
concept, then it is only a symbol one
step removed from true non-existence. It
is not the non-existence itself that
they can experience or talk about. It is
only the symbol of non-existence. You
follow me? Okay. And are we about to
reach the end of the expansion?
Whose expansion cycle? your universe.
your universe.
Do you mean physiologically? Yeah. No,
but that that that does not recycle that
way. Oh, it can. Many universes do. But
you can also find that there is one idea
that your scientists have not yet
realized regarding what they call
entropy in terms of recycling, so to
speak. It is this. Many individuals in
your society believe that rather than
contracting the idea that your universe
will eventually become homogeneous. You
follow me? What you call
entropy. Do you follow me? Yeah. Like
everything. In a sense they usually refer to it in
In a sense they usually refer to it in
your society as the idea of temperature.
They say that
once, let me phrase it this way.
Your sight is
perceived that all
interactions are able to be interactions
because they occur from or between
states of being that are different. That
is how you know there is an
interaction because something goes from
something that is different to something
that is different.
The idea as they express entropy in the
universe is that they are speculating
there will come a time in what you call
many of your millions and or billions of
years where
everything will in a sense burn out, die
out, no more atomic activity, no more
interactions. Everything will become a
homogeneous soup of energy all at the
same level, all of the same temperature.
You follow me?
Now at that point many of them speculate
well that is the end of the
physiological universe. No possibility for the idea of
universe. No possibility for the idea of
contraction. No possibility for the idea
of reforming order out of this
homogeneous state of nothingness.
But in this way what they are
missing is that it is still in a sense
able to contract so to speak
because once something reaches a state
of complete and total
homogeneousness. That also means that so
does space and so does
time. Once something reaches a state
where you cannot tell if time is going
forward or backward, then it could just
as easily be conceived as going
backward. And as soon as it is equal to
the idea that it could be either forward
as you count time or backward, it can
become backward and the universe can
reassemble itself.
So, it is like passing through an
entropy doorway, perhaps in a sense, a
softer transition than many of your
scientists believe with the idea of
there being more than enough gravity to
simply draw all the material back, but a
contraction nonetheless, a cycle
nonetheless. But all of those ideas of
physiological cycle whether you create
your universe to be one that expands and
contracts rhythmically in that way or
goes through the entropy state these
ideas as you count time are in your
terms many millions of years off.
You follow me? Yes.
in and out. It is simply the idea like
you are familiar with your device, your
radio. Yeah. It is simply the idea that
you are switching the dial back and
forth across all the frequencies,
hearing bits of this tune, bits of that
voice here and there. You are simply
generating a frequency at which you are
doing this. And the idea is that any one
of those individual frequencies only
considers itself to be real or solid for
the time it is switched on and does not
perceive all of the other frequencies.
Not that it can't, but it simply has
designed itself only to pay attention to
the frequency upon which it exists.
Therefore, it has only considered itself
to be real in that sense. That does not
mean all the other frequencies are not
real, but they simply take turns
experiencing their own individual
reality. You follow me? So it's not flickering
You follow me? So it's not flickering
into nothingness into others. Yay. Yay.
Okay. When was talking about
the hecious reality?
hecious reality?
So that's why he called it that.
It is an
experience and symbols are not the
experience.
Thank you. Can that which
exist non-existence? No. Again the idea
is that what exists carries the idea of
existence as what it
as what it
is. In that way there is transformation
within existence but all transformation
takes place within the idea of
existence. What is is by definition what
is not is not but all that is always
will be. What
is you follow me? By you. Yay.
Oh, not necessarily. For again, it
simply may be a matter of the idea that
you are creating your particular
universe to be relatively limited in
terms of its ability to conceive what
does exist.
Now that may mean it does not have
materialization within your particular
idea of your universe but that does not
mean it does not exist within all that
is
by
definition. In a
sense, everything is
transformation of all that is into other
states of all that is. It is not exactly
from non-existence. It may be from
nothing but not from non-existence.
Nothing may be referred to as some sort
of
homogeneous potential energy state that
has no form.
Point Thomas Aquinus the philosopher had
a law called the law of potentiality
which stated that that which can be but
is not yet. Yes. And basically that can
be
what you're talking about in a sense a
anything you can imagine must somewhere
be a reality or you wouldn't be able to
conceive of it because you cannot
imagine non-existence
in the another area when people talk of
old souls and new souls they try to give
a chronology to spirit right as I'm
understanding it it would just be a
person's uh character that he would
assign to himself that somebody else
could perceive or he was perceiving
someone else being an old soul who had
been around a certain planet for a long
period of time more than somebody else.
It is simply the frequency vibration
that may translate into your particular
reality as what you call old or new.
Right? But all souls are the same age which is
But all souls are the same age which is
ageless, eternal. Right. I have
something else. Uh there's a new book by
Wendell Steven who was writing this
Indian book. It's called contact k I
believe in South Africa around
1974. And these people stated to their
contract there was an antimatter
universe that their I think their system
came from uh and that they had taken up
a group of scientists at that
time on a little celestial tour
apparently and asked them if they wanted
to have earth join the confederation and
the scientist said no they refused. I
haven't read the book this is just worth
information but do you know anything
about that? There is such a realm but in
this way we will find that some of the
information is more symbolic than
literal to our perception.
They said there was the earth
counterpart in this antimatter universe
that's called
epox and it seemed to indicate we also
would have counterparts in that universe as
have counterparts in that universe as
well. This is likely but you have many
parallel realities in many different
universes. Uh-huh. There is the idea you
call antimatter realm so to speak,
negative energy realm in that way and
there are counterparts there. Again, the
definitions may simply be symbolic of
something that is pertinent to your
civilization. Thank you.
What are we on particular?
I have been told that an electronic
watch will upset the magnetic field
of if it is within your fundamental
belief system that the idea of your
electromagnetic field can be disrupted
by other electromagnetic fields and it
is a primary fundamental mass
consciousness belief to some extent then
it is very likely that you can create
that type of aberration in your oric
field. It does not have to occur. It is
likely that there will always be some
perturbation of your oric field by any
other electromagnetic field to some
extent simply because you are
interacting as a series of
electromagnetic fields. It is a
fundamental vibratory belief system
within your reality. This does not
necessarily mean that it always has to
be as negative as you might think. But
there can be interaction. Yes. Only way
to get around that is to wear your watch
in your right hand supposedly. You can
also simply not wear a
watch since you are always now anywhere.
Oh, it does exist because you created to
exist. But you do regulate its flow.
Thank you.
No. Um, I've got a couple ideas that I
can explain. The first
one is our personal
Now you know the answer to this one
already.
Well, in a sense it can be. But simply
once again, what type of society are you
in the habit of
creating? One that has forgotten that it
is its own higher self. Therefore, one
that does not remember it is in control
of its reality. Therefore, one that may
seem to set up scenarios in which it
appears to be in opposition to any
definition you would give to a higher
sense. Okay. Um because many times the idea of
Okay. Um because many times the idea of
the society, the reality you have
created allows you to be able to
conceive that what you call your
negative ego is what is creating the
idea of the energy that you use rather
than simply recognizing that the energy
is your consciousness. that the negative
ego in this way is not what creates
consciousness. It is consciousness that
creates the negative ego.
So in that consciousness are we
referring to higher consciousness? What
you may term higher? Yes. But what we
would prefer to simply recognize as one
consciousness. The quote unquote habit of continuing to
The quote unquote habit of continuing to
think that you are a lower consciousness
that has a higher consciousness is what
continues to be the opportunity for you
to create seeming discrepancies between
the two levels because you create two
levels to exist. So they can have
discrepancies. Um okay how how does the principle of
Um okay how how does the principle of
the east work in the sense of that one
consciousness it is a reflection to some
degree like many other tools recognizing
certain patterns within the mass
consciousness. Now some of these
patterns because again of the
separations you have created may be
instilled within the mass sub or the
mass unconsciousness but recognitions of
the mass consciousness vibration
agreements they are to some extent
nonetheless. So how does this pattern um it's just a
So how does this pattern um it's just a
symbol that's reflected in a sense let
us say it is a symbolic
way to read the contract that you have
made with everyone to recognize the
overlapping patterns and interactions
that you have agreed to have with
everyone. It is one way to reflect these
ideas to yourself. There are many tools
That's interesting. I bet you I have a
curious question. How do you a curious
question? I have a curiosity that I'm
going to try and put into a question.
Try and a curiosity. You are going to
try to put into a question. Okay, here
it goes. My mind.
How do you how do you uh perceive what
how could you describe very
well? Uh what? Mostly as feelings, mostly as
mostly as
interactions, connections in a sense
what you would call, as we have said,
holographically. We see the idea or
perceive the idea or feel the idea of
you as a conglomerate of interaction
even though we do recognize you have
your own signature vibration.
So you do see the
interactions say of the individual and
then you also can see the interactions
that they are connected with with their
mass consciousness and other in a sense
although perhaps to clarify the
idea it is recognizing the definition of
all of the
interactions that you
are that gives us the ability to
recognize you As an
individual, let us say we recognize you
by your combination
code. The combination of all the
interactions you are being gives rise to
the individual you consider yourself to
be following.
So how do I translate?
who translate as an individual that is
connected in many different ways and
recognizing many of the connections and
recognizing not some of
them. But this is as we will say not to
be demeaning typical of your society at
this time. But in this way we do not define
time. But in this way we do not define
the idea of how we perceive you to make
a judgment upon it or a comparison. So
when you ask how do we perceive you, we
are always going to perceive you as
perfect like anything else. Whatever
interactions you are choosing to be are
the interactions you obviously feel you
need to be or you would be something
else. That is how we perceive you. We
simply read what we see as the
interactions that make you what you are.
You follow me? Um yeah, I'm trying to I
guess I'm trying to get a visual sleep
on it.
Remember about the cloud.
How did in this way the idea of the
cloud chamber may only cause to confuse
I always get this image of of patterns
with interconnected day that will
suffice as your symbol of understanding.
Suffice it to say that on your own terms
you understand. You have your symbol for
it and your symbol for you is
correct. You follow me?
Sure. How do you perceive yourself? And
much the same way. Although we also
allow ourselves to recognize that we are
the interactions we are
perceiving. That in a sense is the
difference. Whereas even many times you
may perceive the idea of all the
interactions you are connected to, we
perceive ourselves as the interactions
themselves. Does that then allow for all
of you to be aware of where you are all
the time at work? Of course, because we
are each other
consciously as we have said, everything
is the same one thing manifesting in
multi-dimensional aspects
simultaneously. Everything is the same
one thing. But but right now you're
sitting here and a part of you is
discussing these issues with us. The
idea that I am
contains the aspect or ability to
communicate in a fashion that you can
conceive of with you. Yes. In a sense,
however, this is still a part of the
interaction. I
am. It is not something separate from
me, so to speak, from my point of view.
Yes, I understand that fundamentally the
I am. I understand that. But I need to
pinpoint it even further. Why? Because I
want to. All right.
Um so that at this time that you're
speaking with us, this this part of you
that I understand isn't a part of you.
Um I don't have the right words for it.
Uh you are also aware of the other
experiences and interactions that are a
part of who you are to varying degrees.
What do you mean by that? Simply what it
says to varying degrees according to the
purpose that they serve to be aware of
them. But you're consciously
aware. So does the varying degrees
um does it cover the range of emotions?
This is what is causing the
misunderstanding. Everything within all
that is, if it exists as something you
can recognize as an identifiable
separateness, to some degree must be
separated and limited to some degree.
Therefore, even we function with the
idea of some degree of limitation.
Otherwise, we would simply be the idea
of the homogeneous one all that is. and
he would not perceive us in any way,
shape, or form as differentiated at all.
Yes. Therefore, to varying degrees of
limitation according to the purpose that
it serves, I allow my consciousness of
the interactions that I am to fluctuate
to serve different purposes, such as
communicating with your civilization.
But still, I recognize that the
communication between us is not
something outside of me, but a part of
me. Does that clarify the idea? Yes, it
Does that clarify the idea? Yes, it
does. Fine.
You
may a while
back one of the highest forms of healing
to I think it was a lady that had
cancer. She spoke about how to heal
others. how you said different things
how to allow others to heal themselves
I can't remember how it say
there are many many ways again none is
so much higher than another way but
simply there is the ability to recognize
that you are living light and in this
way you can identify with the idea that
you are a perfect pattern so to speak
you have the idea of the pattern you
prefer to be. Knowing what that pattern
is, knowing the feeling that it
represents, the vibration of anything
that is not that pattern, including the
idea deceive.
You follow me?
Well, I have been of assistance to you.
No, I meant like if you want to send
love and light to someone else. Go
ahead. How do you feel? You just did by
thinking of it. You do know how to do
it. It is automatic. When you think of a
concept, you are that reality. You are
that vibration. You cannot conceive of
nonexistence. Everything you conceive of
is real in that way. Particularly in
your reality, the idea of a notion that
has anything at all to do with another
part of what you recognize to be your
reality is
instantaneously the reality you are. as
soon as you conceive of it. So when you
have the notion of sending what you
consider to be light and love to someone
else, it is sent automatically. There is
no process involved. You become the idea
and it is
done. Now it is still up to the other
individual whether or not they wish to
in a sense receive the gift so to speak.
But it is always going to be there for
them to be able to receive it when they
are ready to.
You follow me like even years later in
what is time to love.
[Music] You follow me. Does that assist you?
You follow me. Does that assist you?
Thank you for then creating that reality
for yourself.
Hey. Yeah. I was going to ask this
existence. What's the use of it? What
are we talking to learn to experience
it? It is one of the ways you can
experience all that is. Why not?
Well, fair enough. If you feel that um
you've got a handle on it and you you've
been in and out of most of the holes in
this world, right? The idea primarily of
what you would represent to be your
universal reality in your civilization
as you call it has been primarily for
the purpose of experiencing all the
different forms of limitation that there
is to experience. But what for what?
Why not? Well, why have you done it? Not
to the same extent. Why not? Because it
simply does not suit my definition of
myself. No, maybe it doesn't suit me.
Then you wouldn't be here.
Okay. Now, the idea once again is that
when you allow your physical reality to
be an obvious reflection of what you did
choose to experience, then you'll begin
to see why you chose it. But as long as
you refuse to acknowledge that where you
are is where you put yourself, then you
are not saying you are in control. Thus,
you do not give yourself the opportunity
since you do not believe you are in
control of where you are to understand
why you are where you are. Very good.
All you need to do is take it for
granted that you chose to be here for a
reason. So ask yourself, why are you
here? Okay. I' I've I've almost got to
the answer to that question, I think.
All right. You'll only know when you get
there, of course. But on the other hand,
what is the point of it? I don't
understand. All right. Again, this may
result from the overall confusion of the
idea of looking for purposes that seem
to be ultimate purposes. Now recognize
that all that is in a sense, now I am
speaking in linear time frame colloquial
terms, so it will translate most
clearly. All that is, let us say,
existed, so to speak,
before the creation of the idea
purpose. Purpose is one of the creations
of all that is. You follow me so far?
Therefore, that which has existed before
purpose was created does not need a
purpose to continue to exist.
It simply is what it is. Now you are a
part of all that is. There are many
aspects, many ways to experience all
that is. If you are experiencing one of
those aspects, it is simply because
foundationally, not specifically,
foundationally because you wish to have
that particular experience of that
particular fragment of all that is. So
that you will know that there is then to
you more understanding of what it truly
means to experience all that is because
this is simply one of the ways you can
experience it and you want to experience
as many ways as you can. So why not? Now
you may in any particular life such as
this create your own specific purposes,
goals, desires, wants, joys, struggles
and so forth and those can serve you.
You can understand why you have created
them as well. But those are your
specific desires within any given
fragment life time frame and has really
not so much to do with the overall idea
of well what is the purpose anyway to
any of it. All that is does not need a
purpose to be anything it can imagine
itself to be. It simply does so because
that is the nature of all that is to be
what it can imagine itself to be. Thus
experiencing another aspect of [Music]
itself. If you are there, take it as a
sign that the assistance is necessary.
But that experience you are describing
is occurring within your reality not
outside of it. We in a sense while we
share some ideas are for all practical
intents and purposes as you define your
reality not exactly within it yet.
And so in that way what happens in your
reality is up to you not up to us.
Okay. Will you say that we've decided
getting off that one onto the latest
remark statement was that we have
decided not to blow up the world? This
is as we perceive your energy now. Uh
America at the moment is creating a lot
of hot spots. As we have already said,
much of the acceleration in what you
perceive to be violent acts is because
you are now bringing all these things
out into the open, living them through
in a very open way so that you can
expose the idea to the surface of the
consciousness of the world and allow
individuals to choose what realities
they desire. In a sense, you are getting
it all out of the way rapidly so that
you can go on to a peaceful existence.
You are cleaning up the last dregs of
limitation, so to speak. Good. Well, I
have a fear about what are we going to
do with the nuclear waste that's hanging
around. Why a fear? Well, because why
not a creative burst of inspiration
instead? Okay, good idea. All right.
Where does now our
perception is that there may be many
ways for you to come to terms with what
you have created in that manner. Let us
say to be simply fundamental for a
moment. You could, someone could, it is
not impossible, simply come to the
realization that it can simply be
thought away.
Why not? It was thought into existence.
Just because it was thought into
existence along means you consider to be
physical doesn't mean it has to go out
that way. Also, you can still recognize
that if you wish to do it, let us say
more in line with what you consider to
be appropriate for your physical
reality, not wanting to break physical
etiquette, you can then invent
something, a substance that may be able
to contain it. We do perceive that this
can be a combination of some of the
ideas of metal crystallin and polymer
plastic structures that can be created
in sheetike form surround the idea of
what you call your radioactive elements
and absorb all the radioactivity.
Yes, that's fine. But already we've done
that with some metals that I feel or
heard they're inferior that have been
again you can create something that is
not quote unquote inferior. What do we
do with the ones we've got already out
of the ocean that are going to break
open once
again? Why not create this all to be one
reality? Why keep separating? Well, what
about this? Well, what about this? Well,
what about this? Well, what about this?
It is all one idea. And if you simply
can come to the terms that you can
create in your sphere of experience the
idea that it will be taken care of then
in your reality it will in whatever way
it has to be it will be maybe you will
help. Who knows?
Well I have to uh I have to they don't
have a submarine that can go down there
to get at these things. What does what
you have now have to do with anything?
The next now is different.
Use the
imagination. Someone may come up with it
in the very next second. Why worry when
you can assist by being creative in that
way and co-creating the type of reality
in which whatever is needed can be
created. If you give your energy over to
the type of reality in which such an
inspiration can occur in the very next
second, then you will have done your
bit to support a reality that can think
of something to deal with the
situation. Right now with all your
concerns and all your worries, all you
are doing is saying, "I can't imagine
any such reality coming along and
solving this problem in any amount of
time I consider to be relevant." So, you
will struggle along and still experience
the effects and side effects of all
these ideas because you're not willing
to support the reality that can deal
with the situation. Well, in actual
fact, I'm passing those things over to
you to get your answer.
You operate this
world. We can assist you in reflecting
ideas to you. But in this way, the idea
is your choice. If that is the reality
you prefer, if you prefer to exist in a
civilization that can quote unquote
solve its problems, then believe you do
exist in that kind of a society, support
it by believing in it. Act like you
believe it, and then you will assist in
cocreating a type of reality that can
recognize that a problem is only a
situation you will not allow to change
shape.
for sure for you. Thank you. Yay. Okay.
We're told that we are told We are told
We are told by Okay. I believe Thank
you. That brings it home. I believe I
believe that prayer okay creates thought
forms that are a type of energy that can
bring about certain things to manifest now how
about certain things to manifest now how
lovely is prayer then a useful tool does
it work for you oh definitely then is it
not a useful tool for you thank you not
for sure
but it can be used as a tool in this
case concerning with the nuclear waste
problem. If enough people get together,
however, pray about it. However,
however, however, the idea of prayer is
a knowing connection, a connection of
knowingness, not a connection of fear,
not a connection of we better pray or
else. Oh, never. All right, then. That
is the distinction. Thank you. Thank
you, guys. You made a statement about a
week ago that uh every situation that
happens in our life is fundamentally
neutral. Senate this evening of your
time as well. Okay. I came on the second
um I guess but I was interested in um I
think what you were saying that the
effect that it has on us really uh
depends on how you look at it. How we
look at it right? But basically every
situation is fun. Yes. Once again
perhaps a helpful analogy will be the
train if I may. Really? The individual
is wishing to as you say catch a train
the conveyance upon your planet in that
way and they arrive at what you call the
station and the train has left. Now the
neutral situation is simply that the
train is moving this individual is not
on it. That is it. That is all there is
to a situation. Now whether you or let's
say that individual decide that this
situation is fundamentally positive or
negative will also determine the effect
that they get out of it. Let us say they
choose to think that it is a negative
situation. They allow themselves to
become irate.
They will then perhaps go and complain
to the station master about the fact
that they have missed their train and
how come they run such sloppy schedule
and all these ideas. And perhaps they
will not recognize that having just
gotten off that train is a friend they
haven't seen in 10 years that they
desire to see very much. But because of
the choice to view the situation as
negative, they blind themselves to the
possible opportunity that the situation brought
opportunity that the situation brought
to them. So it's our our judgments then
that that can interfere in what might
have been our not interfere. Judgments
create their own realities. It is not a
matter of interfering in another
reality. It is in and of itself its own
creation. I'll bet the negative one. But
the reality
But the reality before that perhaps was
the reality we wanted anyway. Perhaps
the reality you preferred. Yes. But
again, you change your reality every
second if you wish to. So while you may
have had a reality of preference in one
moment, your choice to view the
situation from a judgmental point of
view will then perhaps change from a
preferential reality to a judgmental
one. Okay. So just a question of our
choices. Absolutely. Bottom line, as you
say. Thank you. Thank you.
Sure.
What prompts you out of your the idea of
contempt and service when you talk about
laughter and knowing this to be publicly
centered? I have that experience and I
have that experience when I create or
when a program is created for me. Hey,
and in many ways a large part of me has
no need to take it out. disservice and
to manifest that television program any
further than some ideas manifest to a
certain point and that is what they are
necessary for and that is it but I'm
saying that about every idea there there
is a contentment in me all right having
but you can also recognize that if you
are willing to share that as your idea
then you may be serving other
individuals by allowing them to see that
change is the only constant and
therefore the only stable foundation in
the universe understood understood all
right what promps you to do that because
you don't have to take that out to show
people the fact that you've manifested
it is already there.
So why be assured with your teeth when
in fact if we're with you we know that
you're that you're laughing I am not
laughing with my teeth.
The idea once again is simply that I am
in what you would recognize to be a
so-called trans state. My mental energy
is being translated through the
physiological channel in that way
according to how it creates an automatic
reaction in the body. That is all.
Understood. What I'm asking is
something. All right. What what prompts
you to feel the need to come and be of
service rather than to remain I enjoy
it. So it's a furthering of your own
So it's a furthering of your own
content. Of course. Why else would I do
it? The idea of being of service to all that
The idea of being of service to all that
is is the automatic support of anything
I choose to be because I am a part of
all that is.
You follow me? Fine. You for sure. For
sure. Can't you reach
a reach a point I think I know what he's
talking about in a sense of um where you
just feel so serene and and so that way
that you just don't feel like um doing
anything doing anything or not really as
a matter of fact you will find that in a
sense the more serene you are the more
you can do
but it will not be an effort you will
find yourself becoming more serene and
therefore more creative and then simply
find that Your creations will be easier
to manifest
in this way. Therefore, it may seem like
you are doing nothing but you will be
creating spontaneously all the time
around you. Whether it is something that you
you. Whether it is something that you
consciously choose to recognize as a
creation is up to you. But recognize
that sometimes just being who you are
serenely creates an atmosphere around
you that is of service to other
individuals. That is what we refer to
when we say be the idea you are and you
will radiate the opportunity for other
individuals to see reflected from you
something they can also choose. That is
still being of service. Yeah, that is
still doing that is still creating. When
I felt that way myself, I always somehow
it was just hard to get the idea of
sustaining things at that level. That is
because you are thinking in terms of
time. When you create time, then of
course you create the notion that this
effect and this feeling that you have
has to be sustained across a band of
time instead of simply living in the now
where everything is one now eternal
moment and then no sustaining is
necessary because it simply is now. It is what is
because it simply is now. It is what is
now. You don't have to carry it across
time, which is the thought of doing that
can sort of bring you back into more of
a linear time frame and maybe out of
experiencing being in the now. So, well,
anything that you conceive of that
contains the notion that you have to
become it creates time. Simply being it
puts you in the now.
Act like it. Enjoy every moment for what
it is. Because every moment that is is
you. It is what you are at that moment.
Plain and simple. Not better, not worse,
just different. I guess I started to
worry about uh coming off of feeling
that way or something. Again, it is
simply because you are in the habit of
thinking that you have to carry the idea
across time.
When you think of time, you think, "Oh,
well, this goes on
forever. How long can I keep this up?
It's getting heavy already."
But when you exist in the now, then you
don't have to go anywhere.
It is simply there where you are always
find you.
Hey, um I'm wondering is there a such
thing as truth? Hey,
the truth is composed of all
truths. Truth is what is true for you.
What is the vibration that represents
the reality you chose to be that is your
truth. Someone else's truth is their
truth equal and just as real as your
truth and goes into forming the truth
which is composed of all truths. Is
there an integrity truth?
An integrity truth for lack of a better
phrase. Let's say that in a sense
recognizing that the truth is the
product of all truths is the recognition
of integrity. Because you are saying it
is integrated. Thank you. Thanks. Thanks.
Um,
where where does fear come from? And can
you describe that emotion? I mean, what
it really is?
Fear can be not so much the idea of an
emotion, but a judgment. Oh,
Oh,
the judgment of
emotion, the judgment of the
reality as being something that has
nothing to do with the path you chose to
be when obviously it
does. Fear basically is
judgment, invalidation, unequalization
of something, separation of a portion of
yourself from the rest of your knowing
self. Sure. If I remember correctly, in one
Sure. If I remember correctly, in one
earlier lecture that I saw in video
cassette, you mentioned that fear also
there is a positive aspect to the idea,
but it is not what you usually recognize
as fear. Correct. Yeah. Just a way of
seeing it as a a stop for you to make a
decision about something. Yeah. You can
look at it that way, but then you do not
experience it in the negative sense that
you call fear. Correct. Yeah. You simply
again have a cognition that what you
might translate negatively as fear may
simply be something to give you let us
say a guideline the idea that well here
you are in physical
reality. If you are standing on the edge
of a cliff and you take another step you
will die. In a sense you can say that
that is a manifestation of the idea of
fear what you call self-preservation.
But in this way you can simply recognize
that it serves a positive effect
different from the idea of what you call
incapacitating fear which is usually a
judgment and creates a negative effect.
Sure. I have another fear that I think
that everyone has speak for yourself.
Well I I know that I look at America and
I see it very clearly. You see your
version of it. Okay. It's a a fear
where, you know, say say you have a
million dollars in the bank. I have a
million dollars in the bank and I put I
go up to the store and I buy a Porsche.
I go and buy a house. Yes. I go and buy
a a motorcycle. Yes. And then it comes
around to what I want to do. I want to
make a movie. What you want to do? Did
you not want to do all the things that
you just bought? Yes. I'm not afraid of
those because I can trade them back in
and get the money back. They're tangible
objects. Awesome. Something like a movie
which is got to be something other than
what you might like. What everyone
likes. Do you know what everyone likes?
Why do you have to know that? Because to
get your money back of the movie. You
see with the house you know that
everyone likes that house because well
everybody likes a certain kind of house
for so much money. The realtor will tell
you how much it's worth and what you're
going to get for it etc. But it may be
averages. But why can you not extend
that idea into the simple recognition
that you have always done what you
wanted to do because it excited you and
a movie doesn't have to be an exception
to that? Well, it does in a way because
the money might take you 10 years to
get. So, but you can lose it in 10
weeks. Lose it? Well, you make a movie
that someone Are you saying that money
is the only tool that represents
abundance to you? Abundance? Yes.
Abundance. You are naturally abundant. Abundant is
You are naturally abundant. Abundant is
simply being able to do what you want to
do when you want to do it. It doesn't
necessarily mean that money has to be
the tool that creates that reality.
Well, to create this movie that I want
to make. Not necessarily. Oh, well, that
doesn't come out. I mean, I just can't
materialize a camera and a crew and a
Why not?
Well, I haven't got that ability. Oh,
yes, you have. Recognize you are simply
putting it in mysterious terms. That is
all. The idea of being the idea that you
want to be will allow you to know that
if you are simply acting upon something
out of excitement, then all the
necessary ingredients that need to be
there will come from
someone because you will attract only
the other individuals who are as excited
as you. And many of them will have
different skills. Just as you are
bringing your skills, they will bring
their skills. Maybe some of their skills
are the money that may be necessary. But
the idea is to simply go into it because
it excites you and then simply trust
that if it is something that needs to
occur, it will automatically attract all
the other individuals that need to be
there to support that idea. If that
doesn't happen, it doesn't need to
occur. Okay, I'll tell you in 3 weeks.
All right. But again, simply recognize
that whatever does happen is still the
product of what you believe needs to
happen one way or another. Mhm. Thank
you, Sharon.
Sharon.
Sure. Thanks. I'm going to follow my
excitement and help with the help of a
friend co-create your anti-gravity
device. Oh, fine. You is not mine. Well,
the one you're helping us to do. Yes.
I'd like to just quickly run through a
thing if you could follow my review.
Start running. It's going to be a six
inch 6 inch copper disc about an eigh
inch thick. Quarter quarter inch thick.
Okay. And it's going to have an axis of
quarter inch diameter. Half half inch
diameter. Okay. About 4 in 5 in high
deep. That is variable. Okay. And it's
going to have um surrounded a
non-conductive disc about 8 in in
diameter. And embedded in those radially
are going to be some eighth inch copper
cores about every half inch on center of
which will wind the about 300 windings
on each one. Will there be the idea of
what you call the iron electromagnets in
the center of the windings? Well, that
would be the copper core copper about an
eighth inch diameter by about an inch
long. But you have said that there is
only copper. Oh, okay. They could be
iron just solid iron. the idea of having
what you call an
electromagnet wrapping an iron core with
copper, not just a copper winding. Okay.
Right. All right. Okay. And those will
be about/ inch down center radially. All
right. Embedded into the and the winding
from one will proceed to be the winding
to the next. Yes. Can those be wound
individually and then connected
individually one to the next? Yes. Okay.
And about 300 windings each. Yes. Of a
real light gauge wire. Ice. Okay. And
then on the top and the bottom will be
almost like a dinner plate type disc
almost conicle with a bearing at the top
and the bottom which will hold the shaft
vertical shaft. All right. And that
shaft will pro protrude down through the
bottom. Nice. Which will then just make
a flexible connection to the motor which
will drive it at about 2,800 RPM. A
disengageable connection. Right. Nice.
So it can just lift off of it. Nice.
Okay. Do I need to strobe that to get an
exact RPM?
You can experiment. It will vary
according to the magnetic fluctuations
of any particular local to some degree.
Okay. Do the uh aluminum discs that I'm
going to use for the top and the bottom
as they come out in their conical shape
and reach. Now the
idea of the
aluminum dishes. Yes. They should not be
the supporting mechanism for the central
rod. Oh, is that right? They should be
complete unto themselves.
In that way, the idea is that you can
create another non-conductive material
to be the supporting
mechanism inside the two holes.
So, you can in your terms still have a
hole in the bottom of the bottom dish so
that your idea of the central shaft can
protrude, right? But it should not be
reliant upon the idea of support upon
the hole. It should have its own
internal support. Well, I was going to
put a bearing strike not in the hole.
You will disrupt its ability to disperse
the field. Okay. Does the top and the
bottom uh shells have to be connected at
the perimeter to each other at the rim?
Yes. They do. So, they have to go on out
beyond this non-conducting ring that I'm
going to make to hold the magnet. Yes.
Okay. And those those magnets are just
connected in a series to each other and
that's it. That's they they go no place
else. No. Electrically. Okay. And then
the so the bearing that I'm going to put
at the top and the bottom of the shafts
will have to reach out from a framework
out to the external perimeter frame.
Right. The nonconductive
Okay. And can I put all of that within a
nonconductive vertical cage so that when
it does lift off, it can contain itself
and just kind of go up and down,
so to speak, so that I don't lose it.
You may attempt that. It will depend
upon how much power generation you have
as to whether the so-called cage will
survive the impact. Well, I'm going to
have a very close fitting so that you
can't That doesn't make a difference.
Uhhuh. You do not understand the
magnitude of the energy that will be
released. Oh, is that right? I couldn't
do this in the room. Huh? I mean, I
thought it would not necessarily be
advisable to do it indoors. [Music]
[Music]
Unless of course you wish a skylight.
I thought I was just going to lift
gently off as soon as I reach the black.
It will reach a certain potential
because you have not exercised because
let us say this is a quote unquote
primitive version. There are no
controlling factors. You are simply
achieving the effect. It will in a sense
be a rogue effect.
I don't understand that term. Run wild.
Oh, run wild. Okay. So, I just stand
back. Yikes. At
At
least 10 ft. Okay. And then I should
just have a variable control on the
drive motor so that we can just stay
back and watch it and just kind of crank
it up until lift off. Yes. Oh, that
sounds exciting.
All right.
Thank you. Oh, and excuse me, one more
thing. On the half inch diameter shaft
as it goes through the plate, the disc
itself, do I need to connect that with a
a flange so that we make a real good You
can. Yes, it would be advisable that it
be very stable. Okay. So that the spin
will not create what you would call
gyroscopic wobbling. Okay. That'll all
be within the cage. Should that chat be
anything in particular as far as
material? Obviously steel. Nice. And the
disc should be copper. Nice. Okay. In
the course. Great. Thanks a lot. I'll
let you know how it works. All right.
We will at this time
therefore allow once
again our appreciation of your
willingness to cocreate a
sharing of ecstasy in allowing us to
experience your consciousness so that
together we may
be the dream reality.
and the sharing that continues
forever. We thank you. We express to you
our unconditional love and our joy that
interaction with the idea that you
are. We bid you exciting dream
life and a fond and loving good evening.
All right. Allow me to say as well that
the idea many times of
idea many times of
simply
realizing that your
life has been going just
fine. in and of
itself can allow you more conscious
awareness of the idea that your life
will always continue to accelerate in
that same way.
Thus many times it is not so much that
you may find that realizations will
bring you understandings of how to be so
much different than you have been. But
to simply recognize that what you have
been doing for the you that you have
created yourself to be at any given
moment in your past has always been the
perfect thing to do and always will
continue to be the perfect thing to do
according to the new definitions you
have of your tent.
You all fall alone.
Sure. For sure. Hey, I had some
curiosity as I as All right. Once again,
allow me to remind each and every one of
you there is really no such thing as
idle curiosity. When you allow yourself to
curiosity. When you allow yourself to
create curiosity, recognize that that in
of itself lets you know you have a key
to answer your own questions. Curiosity
is what allows you to delve into the
dimension of your imagination and know
that you are creating your reality and
that a question is the recognition of an
answer but separated from yourself.
All right. Therefore, continuing
uh the black crow bird. I was um as I've
been walking down the street a few
times, it seemed like there was a lot of
I almost got a sense or my imagination
was sort of pulling me into perhaps they
were trying to communicate something to
me. They are always
communicating. Maybe you are the one
trying to listen, but they do not have
to try to communicate. They are always
communicating. Now, what do you imagine
that their relevancy is for your
reality? What have you created as your end of
What have you created as your end of
receiving the communication into what
symbols have you created their
communication to you? Always
communicating they are what have you
turned their communication into in your
reality.
just felt like some sort of an an
acknowledgement of some kind of what? Uh
of some aspect of myself. Such a
Come on, fire that imagination.
[Music]
Uh well, it was more of a kind of like a
No, the only word I get is kind of like
a little applause of some aspect of
myself. You mean something to crawl
about? [Music]
[Music]
I hesitate to say that because it don't
sound egotistical as a word, but does
not have to. If you simply recognize
that you are able to have cognition of
the fact that you are complete and
perfect as you are. This does not mean
that you have to become negatively
egotistical. Just just kind of a
recognition there without the negative
just a cognition.
So So then my that's that's so that's my
imagination works. Well, thank you. Very
imaginative. Ready?
Yes. I'm still with this idea of
contracts and agreements and I'm
wondering especially because of the
experience that I had this afternoon
um are these when you said about the
echene reflecting the contracts and
agreements that we have um are these
already existing or are we in the
process I mean are they ongoing
agreements that we're constantly making
in the now in a sense yes you may create
a sensation to some degree only in the
most generalized terms that there may be
an ongoing agreement but it only
manifests in the most generalized terms.
The majority of the specifics of the
agreement how the agreement is being
manifested are always being created a
new in the now by you. Okay. So before
this lifetime um we also made agreements
and we continue to keep them in
basically but only again in the most
generalized of ways. Recognize once
again the idea we have discussed with
you as the two types of free will. Free
will of your physical being, free will
of your higher consciousness, which to
the physical being from time to time may
seem like predestination. But the free
will of the higher consciousness only
manifest itself in the most generalized
of
themes. How you experience those themes
is completely up to the free will of
your physiological personality. Now you
follow me. Mhm.
Sure. Does that answer your question?
Yes. Oh, [\h__\h] you. Is it possible that
uh if you get wiped out before you
complete one of these contracts? Wiped
out your plane crashes or you die. You
mean physiological death? Yes. It cannot
occur before the contract is completed
unless there is only one exception. You
take your own life consciously. That is
the only way that you can remove
yourself from a contract and most likely
what you will do once you are in a
position to realize what you have done
is you will put yourself right back in
in the same
situation. Well, very well. In that
case, say for example, a chap races
motorcycles, he's immortal. If his
mission is not complete until he
Absolutely. And that is why you see so
many individuals mysteriously,
miraculously surviving accident where they should
surviving accident where they should
have died.
Yes. because their idea is not complete
and simply what they are experiencing is
one of the ideas that is a part of their
contract in the way they wish to
experience it. Not that having to be in
an accident is necessarily a part of
their contract but they obviously chose
to believe that that was one way they
could experience the general theme that
they are exploring by having had the
access and that is simply not the end of
their contract but simply one of the
ideas along the way. Right? When the end
is the end then that is the end plain
and simple. Let us say however that it
is only a transformation from the end.
Yeah. We are simply being colloquial.
Yeah. And all the diseases along the way to
And all the diseases along the way to
remind you that you're off the track or
off the freeway or wherever you are. Yes
and no. The idea really is that you can
never be off the track because the track
is what you are. You can't be off
yourself. But in this way it is perhaps a reminder
But in this way it is perhaps a reminder
that you still have the opportunity to
choose what way in what manner you wish
to explore the idea if you wish to
explore within
integrity integrated than the idea is
that you do not necessarily need the
tool you call
disease. However, if you choose to put
more stock in the belief that the
disease is necessary in order to
experience the idea then the disease is
what you will create. Mhm. But you do
not have to. But it does not mean you
are off the track. It is still an
opportunity to recognize that you can
still learn from it. You can learn what
you prefer. Learning what you prefer is
not being off the track since what you
experienced got you there.
So if you're reaching around 100 years
of age and you still haven't gotten
around to it, you will not die. You will
not die. No. And again, the idea of what
you call your
lifespan will and has been beginning to
increase according to the idea you have
of yourself in terms of what it is you
do wish to accomplish within the span of
one lifetime rather than taking many
lifetimes. This being the
transformational era upon your planet,
you will find that many individuals
living in your society now and many of
the generations now being born will find
that their lifespan can increase
according to the ideas they wish to
experience. Since it is no longer
necessary for you to believe that you
need many lives in which to experience
certain ideas, you can simply do it all
at once and have a time frame lifespan
according to fit the occasion of what
you wish to experience. Thus you will
find that many individuals that are in
your terms alive now in your terms of
counting will still be alive in
approximately 300
years. That is as we perceive a high
potential degree of probability for many
individuals physically alive upon our
planet now because that is how let us
say radically the belief systems will
change within the next 30
years. Whether that manifests as what
you call medicinal ideas or not does not
matter. Everything is only a symbol. If
it is something in what you call
medicine that gives you the opportunity
to live that long, it is still a
reflection of the fact that you believe
it is possible. Otherwise, the medicine
symbol could not be there. It simply may
be the easiest way for some individuals
to allow their belief that they can live
that long to be manifested in ways that
they are comfortable with. Well, if I
don't get that medicine, then I can't
live that long. But if I do get it, no
problem. However, other individuals will
find other ways. Individuals will
perhaps simply find that as they become
more and more and more in the now, in
the moment, they will be having such an
ecstatic time living their lives that
before they know it, they will look up
and 300 years have gone by.
[Music] will recognize the idea that when you
will recognize the idea that when you
live in the moment, it is not that time
speeds up. It is that you don't create
as much time. It literally doesn't take
as much time
to have the experience. That is why now
that you are forming an integration upon
your planet, you will find that you will
most likely as we perceive the energy at
this time only remain as an incarnate
civilization for approximately 2,000
more years. Whereas as a society
experiencing limitation, separation, and
judgment, you have been experiencing
yourself as an incarnate society for
tens of thousands of years. Once you
integrate, you do not create as much
time. So your experience, your total
experience of incarnation in fourth
density does not have to be that long.
Okay. Now the other question is it
doesn't matter what we eat. Not really.
Again, if it is part and parcel of your
belief system that it does not matter,
then it will not matter. However, if you
find that in your reality, something you
eat does cause the idea of a reaction
within you, then that is an obvious
reflection that you obviously do carry a
portion of the mass consciousness belief
within you that you are attaching to
yourself to. Well, how is it that people
all all the people I know who are trying
to reach a higher spiritual level than
most of them simply because many of them
do recognize that the way your mass
consciousness reality usually looks at
the ideas that as you become a so to
speak more rarified vibration then the
ideas that sustain you also will exhibit
the same degree of rarification or
simplification. But the idea is not so
much that you have to force yourself to
have that kind of a diet, but that you
simply find that as you accelerate, you
lose the urge for anything else. You
simply eat what sustains you on the same
vibratory level. Right?
What about alcohol? What does that do to
people? Uh what's detrimental about
spirits apart from the fact they hang
over? In this way, you will find that it
may be one tool that will allow an
individual to lose track of where they
have laid their
responsibility. In this way, it is a
tool like anything else, but it also
brings with it as you have created it
the recognition that many individuals
will utilize that tool when they are not
willing to take responsibility for what
they are creating in their reality.
Uh-huh. Mhm. But sometimes it can be
very helpful and uh again to a certain
extent in losing your fear and relaxing
it there can be to some degree the
recognition that it may allow you the
opportunity to see that it is possible
to quote unquote lose certain
inhibitions in that way. However,
recognize this about all such tools.
They are only tools. They are only
reflections. And the idea that the tool
is creating the effect is not so you are
creating the effect by believing in the
tool. Thus a tool like that or what you
call drugs many times when taken as a
tool can let you know what it is
possible for you to do but then you
don't need the tool anymore.
Well I don't know about that. One more
time. One more. The idea is this. You
seem to think that the drug and the tool
has more power in creating the
experience than you do simply because
that is what you have agreed to abide by
within the mass consciousness. That
certain things seem uncontrollable,
automatic laws of physics, laws of
chemistry. But you have all agreed to
create what you call laws of chemistry,
laws of physics and to abide by it in
general agreement. That still does not
mean that it is not you that is creating
the effect. You are creating the effect
by believing in the laws of chemistry
which says that this drug will create
this type of effect. But it still comes
down to you agreeing to live in a
universe where that is a physical law.
But there is cases where people
consciously do not know that they have
taken a drug that has nothing to do with
it. Again, it is all one consciousness.
And many individuals while not being
willing to face the idea on a conscious
level are very very very aware of what
they are doing on a so-called
unconscious level. And thus they create
the reaction. Recognize this.
Unconcious knowingness
is the same thing as conscious
unknowingness. Oh my god.
Oh my god.
I consciously choose to not know is the
same thing as saying that whatever it is
I do know is relegated to my
unconsciousness but that is creating a
separation. They know what they are
doing. They are simply not willing to
admit it and so create a level you call
unconsciousness where they can put the
knowledge of what they are doing. So
they don't have to take once again
responsibility for the creation but they
know what they are doing. Yeah. And this
uh I mean when it comes to a point where
you've taken too much of a drug and say
you stop breathing for a time uh and you
perhaps meet a guide who says stop
messing around and get back and get on
the track this is the point where if you
do it again what happens to be that
guide again you can't it is up to you
but again the is simply being translated
into your physiological terms many
different things cannot
Earth. Many individuals can create the
idea of their physiological death that
way and many have. That is the
experience that they have created. Now
the idea of experiencing that type of
thing unconsciously in a sense in some cases
unconsciously in a sense in some cases
is what allows the experience to be an
experience and not conscious suicide.
So that necessarily the individual who
created physiological death in that way
will not necessarily choose to have to
come back. It will simply be taken as an
experience because they have the quote
unquote reality that they did not know
what they were doing consciously. So
sometimes the creation of
unconsciousness allows the idea to be
taken as an experience rather than a
removal of the self from the agreement
one made to have. In this way also
recognize of course that all death is
truly suicide. But we are making the
suicide. But we are making the
distinction of what we call conscious
suicide. But is it also there to scare you away?
But is it also there to scare you away?
It can be. Again the differences and the
reasons are as numerous as the
individuals who create the experience.
There are as many reasons for the
experience as there are individuals
creating it. It is up to them.
Thank you.
I will as well.
Yay. Um, in relation to what this
children was talking about, um, I took
the tool ecstasy and within the first
hour of the experience, um, I had this
sensation and I'm experiencing it right
now without having taken the drug. Um,
of moving and seeing everything in a
sort of foggy way almost as if it were
the I got the sense of the astral plane.
as if everything was a room within a
room effect. And my skin, which is
already starting to feel right now as
I'm speaking to you, uh became very
siliconey, like it was smooth in a very
interesting way. And what I found very
interesting about it, and I'm finding
very interesting about it right now, is
that I am totally recreating this
experience for myself continually. As
soon as I tap into the idea of having
taken the drug, the experience starts to
manifest itself for me
immediately. And I wanted to share that
to show that that is indeed a
possibility that it happens continually
if you need to. Why are you doing that
with your
or why is Daryl doing that?
Physiological translation of one type or
one level of my laughter. [Music]
[Music]
are just I I know what you're laugh
you're you're laughing with me. You're
enjoying the experience.
I can sense that. Well, thank you. Thank
you. Thank you for the co-creation.
Wait a second. What I wanted to say, you
see, this is tremendous.
No, it's great. Was that um I had this
sensation that things were speeding up,
accelerating, and yet what I'm seeing it
as is actually that things are slowing
down. Well, you know what we have said?
No. What have you said? Fine.
When you are infinitely accelerated, you
are everywhere at once. And being
everywhere at once is the same feeling
as standing perfectly still. Is that
what you meant by me when you tell me to
keep moving?
Thank you. [\h__\h] you.
[Music] Did you teach her to laugh like that?
Did you teach her to laugh like that?
Sure knows how to laugh. In this way,
recognize that what you are receiving is
a translation of one level of my
laughter. For the idea of allowing
myself to completely laugh would be a
complete centering and in a sense the
breaking of the contact of the
channeling. For I would center completely into the
For I would center completely into the
idea of myself in my precise and
specific locus of dimensional reality.
Laughing is
centering. But in this way, because of
whatever blending has occurred, there is
to some degree an allowance for some
recognition of the idea.
So people who are laughing are
unscented. Is that it? Laughing is
centering. So people who have to laugh
are unentered.
Okay. In one sense, in one sense, this
is correct because the
idea is that if you were functioning as
the idea of always being in what you
might term the centered, you would
simply find yourself within a constant
state of ecstatic serene
knowingness, which would not necessarily
manifest itself as what you call
laughter. Therefore, to some degree that is true.
Therefore, to some degree that is true.
The idea of laughter is because you are
centering from a positive point of view.
Crying is centering from a negative
point of view. Both are releasings.
Thank you for your co-creation. Thank
you.
Do the masters cry?
Cry. They have compassion. Yes. But
there is no need for sorrow for they
love you
unconditionally. And in this way they
know you are just as bright and shining
a star as any consciousness within
creation. And why should they cry about
that? Well, they have mentioned that they're
Well, they have mentioned that they're
crying in their proteges on planet Earth
doing something. Oh, we understand the
terminology, but again recognize it is
simply an extension of compassion. It is
only your planet that interprets the
emotion as sorrow. So there are no
tears. Not really. Are you familiar with
Commander Ashta to some extent? Well,
Commander Ashta says that one moment. Third density
Third density
translations of what Ashtar
consciousness says is
that there are 13 million spaceships
ready to evacuate.
Stop. Once again, third density
translation of what Ashtar consciousness
says is that you think you might create
a situation in which you need to be
saved. But
But
recognize the idea you are expressing is
being translated in old
terminology in old ways of thought. The
idea of being
rescued has been used to represent an
idea that you simply are not all
familiar with yet. The idea is this.
First and foremost, because you are
equal in power to anything in the
universe, it is our point of view and
the association's point of view that you
do not need
saving. The idea to think that you need
saving would be to
reinforce the belief that you are
somehow less than capable of creating
your reality.
The idea of being
rescued can simply be translated in a
fourth density way as
follows. You create for yourself the
recognition that other consciousness is
available to communicate
with. You then take the next step of
recognizing that you wish to exist on
the same level as that consciousness to
recognize yourself as equal to that
consciousness. This is what we and the association
This is what we and the association
consciousness are assisting you in
understanding that you are equal to us
not less
than. When you finally adopt and accept
the understanding as a society or even
as an individual that you are equal to
the idea of all within the association
what you may refer to as federation
colloquially. Then you recognize that
you are vibrating already on the same
plane. And so what you are doing is you
are elevating and accelerating
yourself above the need to experience
disaster upon your planet. And that is
the so-called rescue.
It is
identifying with our reality, creating
it to be your reality so strongly and so
equally that you do in a sense elevate
and accelerate yourself beyond the need
to experience the type of transformation
that says you have to experience it as a
trial by fire and need to be rescued.
You are in a sense rescuing yourselves
by identifying in that way. But it is
not ultimately a rescue so to speak
because you are an infinitely powerful
being and do not need to be rescued from
anything because you never never never
end there. Therefore, many individuals upon
there. Therefore, many individuals upon
your planet when receiving the
communication from Ashtar consciousness
have simply translated the message in
terms they are used to understanding.
The terms that you are most often used
to understanding when you receive
communication from what you perceive to
be a so-called higher level is that that
higher level consciousness is most
ambitious wish in life is to save you.
But that is not the
case. You have always considered higher
consciousness to be something that is in
terms of a
savior. when in fact what higher
consciousness is reflecting to you is
that you are equal and not in need of
saving. Once again the analogy may be
appropriate to recognize that Christ
consciousness was never looking for
Christians but reflecting to you that
you are all Christs
equally and that is how you share the
reality of being within our spacecraft
with us so to speak. For our spacecraft
are also only projections of our
consciousness and also only an
indication of the level upon which we
believe we
exist. Thus, the idea of spacecraft
coming down and lifting you up is only a
very colloial way of saying that you
simply accelerate your vibration to be
on equal terms with us so that you do
not have to experience the idea of the
transformation in negative ways. While
many individuals may decide to do so,
but that is up to them. You, if you are
simply of that vibration that knows you
can experience the transformation
without catastrophe, will simply always
be where you need to be to not
experience it in a catastrophic
way. That is our interpretation of what
is being said by Ashtar consciousness.
Most people misunderstand it simply
because of the way you have created your
society to think of itself that it is
not capable of experiencing the same
level of energy as that which you
consider to be above
you. But it is all one and the same. You
are living
light. You are infinite. So will we be
able to change the consciousness of the
whole planet earth in a sense the light
worker in a sense before it's too late
before somebody blows it up we have
already now the perception that you have
decided not to do
that recognize that much of what you are
experiencing as so-called accelerated
violence in a sense is accelerating
because in a way you now know it is safe
to purge yourself of all of these events
live them all out because you know you
will not annihilate yourselves. So you
are bringing everything that was
formerly hidden to the surface living it
all out in the open so that you can each
decide for yourselves is this what we
want or do we want to change this.
So from our perspective you have already
let us say as a mass
unconsciousness decided not to destroy
yourselves. Otherwise you would find
that in all reality so to speak we
probably if you had decided to destroy
yourselves would not be communicating
with you because you would not be up the
vibration recognize that this is a
possible way to exist.
Thank you. Thank you very much. Going
back on your no one needs to be saved.
Hey, is that mean that uh boy falls out
of the boat, let him swim? No, no, no,
no, no,
no. He'll be all right.
recognize that that can occur that way,
but also recognize the idea of how you
have structured your own society and
that the things that happen within your
reality are different than the ideas
that so to speak happen outside of it.
Therefore, if you
are you are simply not willing to allow
what it is that does excite you to be
equally valid to these so-called greater
questions of life. You think there has
to be some earthshattering revelation
for the universe to have meaning. Is it
not enough to simply know that you can
live your life as you choose to in
complete and total ecstasy and enjoy and
create whatever you desire? Is that not
reason enough?
Well, it appears to me that you're in
greater ecstasy where you are. But that
is simply your choice. Okay. How do I
get there? Do what excites you and trust
that when you do act upon what excites
you the most out of all the things you
can think of. Now we are not saying that
at any given moment once again you have
to have the realization of what it is
that in your entire lifetime would be
the thing that would excite you the most
right now. Whatever it is right now that
you are cognizant of that does excite
you more than any other thing. If you
are willing to act upon that excitement
and trust that acting upon it will
always allow you to be automatically
supported in your
endeavor. You will then find that acting
upon that excitement, taking the initial
step, having the conviction to trust
that what it is that does excite you is
representative of the path you chose to
be in this life. Then taking that step
will always always bring you more opportunity
always always bring you more opportunity
for acting upon more exciting things. It
is an automatic self-feeding system. All
you need to do is take the first step
and it is downhill all the way.
All you need is the willingness to stop
invalidating the things that truly
excite you more than anything else. to
stop invalidating them as not being
worthy of doing because you think they
pale by comparison to some other grand
idea you should be looking for. I'll go
through as soon as you allow every single
as soon as you allow every single
concept, every single opportunity, every
single interaction, every single relationship,
interaction, every single relationship,
every single experience to be exactly
equal with any other experience you
could have. That is how you will
paradoxically attract to yourself the
idea of complete unending total ecstatic
experience. Wonderful. One moment. One
moment. One moment.
Do you follow me? I got to assist you. I
follow you very closely, but some of the
things I feel I have to do to obtain
this is going to upset a lot of people.
What do you think you have to do to
obtain? Why are you creating the need for a
Why are you creating the need for a
process rather than simply just being
now? Feel being, does it? All right,
that is because as we were about to say,
it is simply a remnant habit of your
society to continue to believe that the
thinking of a thing is not the being of
a thing. You simply do not believe that
your imagination is real. as real as
physical reality. As long as you
continue to create a separation between
your imagination and physical reality,
judging physical reality to be more real
than your imagination, then you will
continue when you have an idea of what
you want to do to still believe that the
idea is not enough that you have to do
something or create some long involved
process in order to
become the idea. But in that way all you
are doing is creating a reality of
becoming and not a reality of being. If
you can conceive of the
idea you have to be that reality in
order to conceive of it because the only
way you can have a notion is to be on
the same level as the vibratory
signature of the notion you are having.
A notion is not something you have. An
idea is not something you have. A
thought is not something you have. They
are what you
are. All you need to do once you have an
idea of what you would like to be is
simply act like you already are that
idea. Give off the vibration that the
thought you have is what you are. And
your physical reality has no
option being a reflection of you but to
reflect back to you what you are willing
to believe you are. That is it. It is
physics. It is mechanics. What you
believe you are is what your physical
reality reflects to you. Thus, it does
not have to be looked at as the idea of
frustrating struggle or having to strive
to overcome what the physical reality
is. It is simply recognizing that if
your physical reality is showing you
something you don't prefer, then that is
a gift. It is an opportunity. It is a
mirror. It shows you what your beliefs
are. So that if you don't prefer them,
you can change them.
Seeing the physical reality does not
mean you are stuck in it. Seeing the
physical reality means you are
unlimited. You can be anything you want.
Physical reality in a sense as we have
said is the shadow of the soul. Now if
you were standing out in your bright
sunlight and you have your shadow upon
the ground and you want the shadow to
change shape, do you pull and tug at the
shadow or do you change the shape of
your body? The idea is similar. Physical
body? The idea is similar. Physical
reality is the shadow of what you
believe it to be. So if you want your
physical reality to change to be what
you desire it to be, then be that idea.
Act like it, function like it. Know that
that vibrational idea you have conceit
of is what is true for you. Act like it
is true for you. Act like there is no
other reality for you. Act as if that is
your reality. Take it for granted. Act
that way. Your physical reality has no
choice but to reflect that back to you.
It is the idea of trust that your
imagination is real and that all you
need to do is act upon it and allow your
imagination to manifest in the time
frame spatial reference structure you
call physical reality. It will and it
will not take very long. We do recognize
that you exist in a time frame reference
point that allows there to be what you
call things taking time. But
realize in your time frame structure as
we read the energy
now, anything primarily that you can imagine
anything primarily that you can imagine
you would desire to be within your
physical reality, you can allow simply by acting
reality, you can allow simply by acting
like you are the idea to manifest in. No
longer at extreme cases, no longer than
3 months. The longest it will take upon
average is 3 weeks.
That allows enough time for all the
other individuals necessary that are
going to interact with you in any given
idea to also gather themselves into the
right places, the right time
synchronistically so you can meet them,
interact with them or the objects or the
situations or whatever it
takes. That is the mechanics of your
physical universe. It is what you
believe it to be. All it takes is trust.
I
guarantee I
guarantee 100% that as soon as you are willing to
100% that as soon as you are willing to
believe that what you desire what you
prefer your reality to be as long as you
are not judging what you do not
prefer when you prefer a specific
reality in that way it will manifest if
you believe that there is no other
reality for you. Well, that's happened
all my life. Then take it for granted it
will continue to do so
for sure. Thank you very much. Thank
you. Y Lazar talks about it
Y Lazar talks about it
manifesting ideas in the physical
reality. Uh he calls 33 seconds. Can you
explain the the physical time limitation
of 33 apply to
do you mean the idea of relatively
instantaneous manifestation? No,
he is I'll try to explain as best I can.
He says that there are tiny answers in
the Ah, thank you. The idea is simply to
our perception representative of the
recognition of a certain pattern within
your triad structure physical reality.
But in this way, 33 seconds in this way
is all it will take for your entire
brain to rewire itself completely into
any given reality state.
For all the synaptic junctions to form
into a cohesive new structure
for you, do recognize and do remember
that every thought you have does
physically rewire your brain.
May I ask a question?
Since I'm a channel for spiritual
healing, I work on animals. A thought
becomes an action. Now, I want every
animal to be healed as well as every
human being. Oh, thank you. But
recognize also at the same time that
animal consciousness loves you all very
much. and they are very willing to
continue to function as reflections of
the things within you that need healing.
So many times an animal will refuse in a
sense to take a healing as long as it is
of service to you to see in that animal
a reflection of the disease you have
created for yourself. Oh really? Of
course they love you unconditionally.
That is what they are doing is
reflecting to you the ideas upon your
planet. Recognize as we have said
before, the animals in your world are
basically territorial only because you
are. They do not have to
be. The idea of the recognition of the
harmony of animal consciousness without
disease will be when you allow yourself
the same
recognition. Then they will have a
healthy reflection to give to you to
represent the peace and harmony and the
blending of the polarities that you have
allowed to occur within
yourself. You follow me? Now this does
not mean that you cannot find that when
you attract if that is how you function
specific animals in this way that can be
quote unquote healed by you in that way.
It is simply part and parcel of that
particular specific interaction and that
is what needs to occur as a part of the
reflection. The fact that they can be
healed in that way. But we are talking
in an overall generalized sense. They
are all in a sense just fine because
they all know what they are doing. Yes.
What about the people who aren't
territorial? In this way, you will find that this is
In this way, you will find that this is
growing in your civilization and will
allow there to be an opportunity once
again for more and more of what you see
around you that you call nature to begin
to reflect that to you. Things will seem
to become tame.
It is not.
How is it how is the process of your
higher self different from that?
Um she asked her question earlier about
um why the personality
predominates over the higher self and
you simply because you have created it
to do so because you believe or are
coming from a belief that physical
personality is all that you really are.
Right. But I I've heard you speak from a
an entity called Shipop and I understood
that to be your higher self and I was
wondering how you differ. We'll defer to
the terminology that you can understand.
Again, from our point of view, there is
less separation than we may be
indicating by using your language to
define that idea.
It does exist in its own right as what
you would call its own entity as do I.
But in this way from our point of view
when there is quote unquote
interaction it is more closely
associated to interaction as rather than
interaction with.
Does that answer? Yes. Thank you. Thank
you. Guys, I was wondering if there was
ever any point in our linear conception
of time where all that is did not have
consciousness of itself. And if if if
that is true, then did the beginning of
consciousness also in a way parallel the
creation of our physical universe?
No.
Well, was there any point where it did
not have? No. No.
You may create within any idea of a
given physical reality the so-called
recognition of a beginning point. But it
is for all all intents and purposes
rather arbitrary. For even within a linear
arbitrary. For even within a linear
dimension, it is still infinite. And
anywhere on that line is really the same
as anywhere else on that line. It is
simply if you wish to designate this as
a beginning point a rather arbitrary
designation but it may serve you to
create a structure for a particular type
of universe you wish to experience
yourself as thus to you the idea of a beginning
as thus to you the idea of a beginning
will have validity.
I see. I was just wondering because I've
been uh doing some reading on various
religious texts like the Bible and
others. They talk about the beginning as
being word or the beginning as I as a
sort of a creation of an I in aense
capital I. But that is the only way that
physical reality the one you have
created has been able to come to terms
with the idea of infinity. To your
physical reality there has to be a
beginning point.
Sure. Sure. you. Yeah.
And let's say you have a point and a
point. Oh, right.
Time, right? Divide that in half and you
got halfway point and
you've got infinity between the halfway
point of course. And so each point is
infinity. In actuality, there is no
there's no point A to point B.
There can be if you create that reality
physical reality. Yes. But in the
overall sense it is all arbitrary. It is
all relative as you say. Well I take it
like this like you're running from or
going or driving there's nothing from
point A to point B. Right. Right. Well
you're driving whatever it is. You're
going to arrive at point B. Right.
Right. But in actuality you know if you
try to analyze it you never really get
there. If you try you know the pathway
that is an indication. We do recognize
the idea of what you call the
mathematical paradox, but it is an
indication in more ways than many of you
think of the real reality. You actually
do not in fact go anywhere.
You create the illusion that you do,
right? But you will find that what you
do consider to be a mathematical game or
paradox does actually give you a very
valid answer. You actually do not
travel.
That one's a bit
You mentioned an idea earlier about the
idea of a fragment of ourselves being
this personality. Could you explain a
little bit more about that and the idea
of whether we have like other aspects of
our consciousness then that are so to
speak doing different things in
different places or differentity levels?
Can you tell me a little bit more about
that? What is there to say? Well, I
don't know.
There are different fragments of the
oversoul wherever and whenever the
oversoul has decided to have an
experience that requires a
fragment. So all of what you call your
past self, your future selves, any
parallel reality you, any counterpart
self that may coexist in what you would
perceive to be the same time frame. All
of these are fragments of the same
oversoul. So we're experiencing all
those things simultaneously in real. I
mean the oversoul is the oversoul is uh
as how do you define oversoul then is
the collection of all the fragments
that the oversoul has fragmented itself
into and me as this personality here is
like a fragment over although you also
are the same whole thing
holographically but to what you consider
yourself to be within this particular
illusion it seems that you are
self-contained and separate. Mhm. for
the purpose of experiencing the illusion
that is the way it must be otherwise you
wouldn't experience the limitation.
Okay. And that's in other words the
physical body moved here but we didn't.
The physical body is you in
physiological dimensional terms. It is
your soul in physical terms.
Your consciousness is everywhere.
anywhere any portion of you is the whole
consciousness is but it can create the
illusion that it is not.
So the idea that your body is here but
the rest of you isn't is an illusion so
that you can live through the illusion
that you
designed of separation
always. Yeah it sounds like a big game
in a sense. Yes. But recognize that that
does not mean that it has to be in your
terms invalid or flip flip.
It is still
experience and you can always grow and
learn from experience no matter what it
is. So it is up to you to decide whether the
So it is up to you to decide whether the
game is boring or ecstatic. Yeah. Well,
it's like walking through a maze, you
know, something like that. Does not have
to be. But then many individuals enjoy
that. with
it simply depends upon what definition
you give to it. Remember every
situation is fundamentally
neutral. Neutral. No situation has
builtin meaning. You give it the meaning.
Then that is the effect that you create.
Positive attitude to neutral situation,
positive effect. Negative attitude to
neutral situations, negative effect. The
situation is neutral to allow you to
create whatever type of effect you
want. It is up to you to
Well, I think you can learn from both.
Of course. And recognizing that fact is
what will begin to allow you to
experience only positive
effects because you have now blended and
made equal positive and negative
energy. Recognizing that you can learn
positive things from negative reality
always creates positive reality for you.
And that will once again be what
paradoxically allows you to begin to
experience in your own perception
nothing but positive realities to
reflect upon. All
right. Well, thank you. Yes. Um I know I
know like imagining becomes reality, but
why do we get so stuck? Is it because we
believe we're stuck? Like we choose this
one personality and we have it our whole
lifetime. No, no,
no. No, the you that is saying that now
is not the you that you were a moment
ago. But I mean basically generalizing
people feel that they're the same person
or personality. They may choose to feel
that they are but it is only the choice
of having that feeling that creates any
seeming illusion of continuity. Right?
So it's just because we believe it. That
is it. Where is it written in steel that
this is a law of the universe? I agree.
And why is there still so much insanity
and and
oh oh
I just can't believe that one moment one
moment we understand what you mean but
recognize and pay attention to your
definition insanity is not in itself negative. You
insanity is not in itself negative. You
have defined it to be negative. All you
are calling in a general sense to begin
with insanity is someone who experiences
a different reality than you do. Okay.
Now the idea of what you call
perpetration and
victimhood is once again simply a result
of
you not
recognizing that you are as a being as
powerful as you need to be to create
anything you want without having to hurt
anyone else to get it. You are simply in
the habit of thinking that the only way
you can have power is to force yourself
on someone else. But that is actually an
expression of powerlessness.
Now recognize that the idea of
perpetrator victim in this way is quite
the same event.
An individual that carries within
themselves a
belief and or a fear which is a belief
that they can be
victimized will attract an individual
that is not expressing the integrity not
to be attracted by someone's cry of
victimhood.
Yeah. Now therefore it can be said that
a victim is taking advantage of another
individual's internal weakness.
Therefore the perpetrator becomes the
victim's victim. And in that way the
victim is a perpetrator at the same
time. Yeah. It is a as you say two-sided
coin. It is one event and can never be
separated in that way.
When you are willing to know that you
are as powerful as you need to be to
have anything you desire without having
to harm anyone or yourself in order to
get it. There will be no victims to
attract perpetrators. There will be no
perpetrators to reinforce victimhood
there because the idea will simply be
that if someone wishes to be a victim,
they will not find anyone willing to
break their integrity enough to play
perpetrator so as to not reinforce the
idea of needing victimhood.
They will say, "No, thank you. I can
teach you that you are just as powerful
as me." Now recognize we are not saying
that the idea of a perpetrator is that
they are excused because it is up to
them to recognize that they have the
integrity that they do not need to harm
anyone else. It is their quote unquote
duty so to speak responsibility to other
individuals to recognize that if they
run into a so-called victim whose fear
or belief creates the reality for them
that they can be victimized. When they
run into such an individual, it is their
responsibility to that individual to
say, "No, thank you. I do not wish in
that way to break my integrity. I know I
am completely as powerful as I need to
be and do not have to force anything on
you as an expression of my powerless
net. Therefore, I can reflect to you
that you also do not need to be a
victim."
Would the muggers and rapists in New
York understand that? if their victims
did. So in other words, they're walking
So in other words, they're walking
around with this fear and attracting. Oh
yes. Once again recognize as we have
said any
individual or society that feels it must
force its point of view on someone else
does not believe in that point of view
for its own sake.
Therefore, when you recognize that your
reality is created by your beliefs and
you recognize that if you fear something
will happen, that is the same thing as
saying you believe that is the most
likely reality to
happen. That's what you get.
So these people that were I forget the
some guy that was carrying on
ridiculously with a knife around here in
LA few months ago or six months ago was
running in people's windows and spearing
the whole life out of the city here in
the middle of the night. Night talker
was he was probably more attracted to
houses with the most fear. Yeah. The
most beliefs that that could happen
that that was a reality for those
people.
So he's like a the devil and like when
they say they satize he's the one who uh
brings the devil to reality in a sense
he is the one that allows you all to
understand that he has chosen to be an
embodiment of your creation of a devil
in your reality. has did Hitler for
those people who want to go to help in a
sense. Well, do you think enough people
on this planet will change their
viewpoint so that Oh, it is changing
now. We perceive in your energy that
within what you call the next 30 of your
years will be the beginnings of the
understandings within that time span
that you do not need that tool anymore.
Really? Oh, good. That is up to you
really. Good. That is our perception of your
Good. That is our perception of your
energy at this time. However, you can
change it. We will however at this time
also perceive that it is unlikely it
will change because you have a great
deal of momentum behind the idea of
integration. And once you so to speak
kick over into
integration, it brings with it by
definition a geometric progression of
energy that is in your terms almost
unstoppable once it has started. what
integration I'm speaking of all the
different ideas you are exploring now
what you call old to new age awareness
the idea of unity oneness that you are
self-contained that you are in
relationship to the universe and all
that is that you do recognize you are
self-empowered that you can create and
do create your own reality all the
things that let you know that any unity
you desire to experience upon your
planet will be the product of granting
equality and validity to all the
infinite diversity within it.
You may all take a short break. Thank
you.