All right. Also, how are you all this
evening of your time as you create time
to exist?
Allow us to share with you this evening
of your time. Within this interaction,
we have cocreated the
understanding of portions of your
non-physical reality. The idea that you
would call some experiences of existence after
call some experiences of existence after
physical death.
In this way, do recognize that because
of the type of civilization you have
created yourselves to
be. Many of you will enter the idea of
the non-physical reality upon physical
death with some degree of adherence to
what you believed would be possible in
your physical life. You may create
scenarios based upon those beliefs and
allow yourself to actually perceive
those scenarios upon physical death
simply because you held such strong
beliefs about them in physical life. And
once you become a thought form in a
world of thought forms, then what you
thought would be real is what you
immediately experience as the reality of
the so-called
afterlife. In this way, therefore, do
recognize that many of you have and many
of you will find a degree of
excitement when you have allowed
yourself to, so to speak,
surmount that initial concept of what
you think would be real upon entering
the non-physical reality. Then you allow
yourself to know that many individuals
enter that realm with these preconceived
beliefs and they need in a sense to be
assisted or helped beyond that
viewpoint. Thus, many of you have been
and will be again the idea of what you
call spirit guides, assisting and
reflecting to these individuals the
ideas that they may then live
through their preconceived notions of
the so-called afterlife and allow
themselves to come to terms with the
idea that the afterlife is exactly what
they conceive it to be, what they wish
it to be. and that they can also gain
the perspective of being of assistance
to other individuals who are bringing
with them into the afterlife their own
preconceived notions. And it is a very
exciting thing to do, a very exciting
thing to receive an individual who needs
the assistance in that way to be able to
gain the selfawareness and insight into
their own self-empowerment in
non-physical reality.
Many of you acting as spirit guides will
find and have found that this is a very
exciting endeavor, a very exciting way
to be of assistance in love and
enlightenment, expressing your
unconditionality, your unconditional
love for them. You will find in a way
that it may be according to how you use
this term in one sense very
challenging a challenging idea to in a
sense take under your wing so to speak
speaking figuratively the idea of an
individual seeking enlightenment in that
way seeking the idea of self-cognition
in that way to know that the reality
they may be immediately perceiving is
only a manufacturer of their belief
system of their thought system of the
idea system that they perceive
themselves to be thus giving you an
opport opportunity to reflect to them
all the scenarios that are necessary for
them to come to the realization that
they are in fact creating that scenario
for themselves, creating that
seemingly solidified afterlife for
themselves. recognize that this degree of
recognize that this degree of
assistance, this degree of willingness
to partake and participate in their
self-created afterlife
scenario, you assisting them up the
so-called ladder in that way bequath
unto you the understanding that there
are many exciting occupations even in
non-physical reality as many as there
are in physical reality.
And in this way you will understand that
you yourself do not cease to be. You
yourself find an amazing if I may use
that term array and assortment of
endeavors and
opportunities with which to occupy
yourself with which to allow yourself to
recognize your own growth with which to
expand the notion and idea and identity
that you find yourself to be even in
non-physical reality.
It is your physical
death. A transformation into a very
exciting light. Very helpful, very
light. Very helpful, very
open,
growth, expansion, excitement.
expansion, excitement.
Do not cease with physical death, but
only transform into more and more
transform into more and more
opportunities to continue your
excitement, to continue your expansion,
to continue your growth. You are
eternal. You exist
forever. You will transform into many
different ways of existing. Do
remember that existence and
non-existence are both real right now.
Non-existence is not something that
existence can
become. If you exist, you always will.
That which exists cannot become
nonexistent. That which is
non-existent already occupies its place
in reality. side by side with existence.
It is simply that because you
are in this way containing both
realities simultaneously. The only side
of the polarity that you can experience
is the one that carries with it by
definition an ability to experience it
which is only the existence side. It is
not that you do not have already an
existence and a non-existence side.
Simply by definition you cannot
experience the non-existence side of
you. Because non-existence does not bring
Because non-existence does not bring
with it experiential
ability. Your existence will never
become non-existence. The side of you that is
non-existence. The side of you that is
existence will always be
existent. There are
births occurring this night of your
time. many new gateways and many new
many new gateways and many new
energies being sent to you this night of
your time. And we will once
again remind many of you that this is
what you might term the 40th
orbit. 40 being in a sense a rather
significant number in your mythology
being the number of days and the number
of years for grand transformations.
distances and times between one gate and
another. 40 years, 40 orbits or 40
days. What you call your date of 77
747 began such a gate and another gate
will occur on
7787. In this way, you will recognize
that this 40 years comprises the time
your civilization has been
absolutely consciously aware of the
existence of other civilizations.
civilizations.
7787 will be the ending of the 40th
orbit of such an
awareness and the beginning of a new
level of such an
awareness. New opportunities for new
interactions
For as we have
said on
7747, did your civilization become aware
beyond a shadow of a doubt that you are
not the only civilization in the
universe? on 7787. Will your entire
civilization have an opportunity to
act as an entire
civilization to express what you know to
be
true? That you are aware of other levels
of
consciousness. And that you yourselves
holographically contain other levels of
consciousness. and the beginning of the
willingness to express the conviction of
your knowledge will begin to
revamp the entire face of your planet.
From that day
forward, you will have passed through
another gate. Nothing from that day
forward will be the
same. You will accelerate beyond
measure and it will thus in that sense
represent that you have approximately
13 of your
years until what could be called primary
ignition of fourth
density. And from that point, the
solidification, the other side of the
pendulum going into fourth density will
begin to solidify. What you allow
yourself to know that you
are on
7787 will be the theme that is
written for the first
block of the remaining period of the
beginning of your life in fourth
density. You will begin to solidify your
reality. They are
They are
to manifest something in this dimension.
Which per knowing that? Knowingness.
Knowing that. All right. And then a
person who who drops their body, which
perception would um physical perception
that is would tend to to be most
available to them. Could they still hear
things though? It would seem as if they
could. It would seem as if they could
see it. in many ways along some of the
quote unquote lower levels of
non-physicality may carry still the
illusion of
physicality. You will simply seem to be
an
incorporeal incorporation. Yet you will still
incorporation. Yet you will still
translate in many ways the senses in
much the same way even though you will
notice differences.
But you can create it to seem as if you
are seeing, to seem as if you are
hearing. Though as you evolve, it will
change. It will be more and more simple
knowingness.
All right. Secondary to knowingness in
the manifestation process, which
perception is in physical reality?
Belief. Belief. Yes. Then emotion and
then thought. And then where's sight and
such come in? as part of the process.
In this way, they can enter on any level
because it depends upon how you react to
them either through knowingness, belief,
emotion or
thought. They are not in and of
themselves one of the levels, but they
interact with every
level. You follow me?
um site you you're saying as long as you
are in physical reality you will create
visualization and tonality to be
representative of the idea that you are
you will create reflections using the
illusion of physical reality which means
sight and sound touch in that way
seeming solidity
to reflect to yourself the idea you are
being so whether you are utilizing
knowingness, belief, emotion, and or
thought, you will still utilize as long
as you are physically in existence all
of the terminologies of physical
existence to interact with.
Okay? Now, the uh the perceptions of
sight sound not independent of you. No,
you create them. You create them as your
methodology of understanding yourself in
physical terms.
You to understand yourself as a physical
being create
spaceime. Sight and sound is a product
of the creation of your illusion of
spaceime. Do you understand myself as a
physical idea? Oh, I see.
Has that answered your question? Yeah.
Thank you. For you, Sharon. Hey,
um you think you could speak further
about what you mean by um and the
differences between belief knowingness
and belief and emotional thought? Thank
you. Thought may allow what you call the
Thought may allow what you call the
analysis of a
situation, the possible further
separation of that situation from you,
so that you may create many
illusions and confuse yourself as to
which one bears the most validity for
you. Emotion can be representative of a
closer understanding, closer to the
vibration of the idea that you are. And
in this way may allow you to function
through instinct and thus gain an insight as to
instinct and thus gain an insight as to
simply identifying with the vibration
that is the opportunity that presents
itself to you as the one most closely
valid for the situation that you can be
representing the idea that you are.
belief in this way is a level of trust,
a level of
awareness that allows you almost
immediate manifestation based upon your
manifestation based upon your
emotionality also contained within the
belief. Eotion, energy motion, the
actualization of your beliefs. The
belief simply being the blueprint or the
way you believe reality to be. It is
your structure of reality. It is your
blueprint, your self-created, chosen
template of the reality that you believe
to exist for you. That is belief.
Knowingness is the direct
identification, direct
perception, direct knowing of the idea
you are being and the simple allowance
of whatever beliefs, emotions, and
thoughts go hand in hand with your
knowingness to simply be the emotions,
beliefs, and thoughts that occur in your
life.
That's great. Um, is that why sometimes
if you're dealing with just thought, you
can think a lot of different things and
yet not know which one is true, right?
Because thought is the creation, the
utilization of physical reality. It is
the utilization of the electromagnetic
energy that creates your physical
reality, your mentality. You are
exciting the idea of the physical
reality and you are in a sense jostling
it into more and more representative
probable physical realities. Creating
more and more illusionary echoes or
vibrations because you are creating the
physical wavelengths to be more noisy by
using more thought than
feeling. You follow me? Yes. Thus you
are creating many echoes that may be
confusing by simply using thought
because all you are doing is vibrating
the electromagnetic field out of which
your mentality is created. So to
So to
make changes manifested changes you have
to move into emotion using emotions.
Emotion is the activator of the beliefs
that you have. All we are simply saying
is that if you come from the viewpoint
of only being cognizant of the thoughts
as being valid then you allow your
thoughts to run your beliefs in that
way and only create yourself to be
confused about what your beliefs are
because you may look at it this way. Let
us say you start as a clear single voice
that is your knowingness. All right.
Mhm. Then you decide that you have the
idea of a polarity. So you create a
reflection that is your belief.
Then you allow yourself to begin seeing
nuances and different levels in the
polarities that is your emotions. Then
the thoughts create all sorts of echoes
of those nuances and more and more
illusion so that you lose track of where
the one single clear voice originated
from. Yes. In your knowingness.
That was great.
[\h__\h] turns for sure. On the 7747, is
that when the uh spacecraft crashed and
Yes. When you say gateway is going to open?
When you say gateway is going to open?
That is a gateway. Why do you call it a
gateway? Because it
represents in a sense another level of
awareness that your entire mass
consciousness accelerates into. It is
like walking through a gate into another
level of
yourself, another room, another arena.
Right. Can I ask if uh your opening
address if there are any members of the
association present with you? Yes. Are
they still here? Ice to some degree. You
sense the difference in the energy? Yes.
Yes. Could you tell us who they are?
There is no need. Although in this way
we will say that there
is
Arcturan serious and plleadian energy
serious and plleadian energy
blended in in high quantities.
Thank you. Twins are
when you speak of the births that are
happening tonight when you refer the
physical birth
more are happening as well more the idea
once again of your own spiritual
births your own accelerations into more
of yourself
and how is that there are many many
gateways within each and every one of
you many of them beginning this night of
your time will begin to open and form
connections
How is that related to them speaking
about it is that you are now opening up
to more and more
assistance from those that are
non-physical who have allowed themselves
to blend in another type of association
to impart their energy to you all.
Thank you.
There are many levels of consciousness
in contact with you this day of your
time and this night of your time. to
proceed towards the idea of
7787. You may all feel yourselves to
becoming a bit more
disoriented, but in this way it is all
part of the interchange and
exchange. You are simply unlocking from
the reality you have held to be so real
for so long and understanding that you
are beginning to walk as if in a dream
because your physical reality is a
dream. You are only beginning to recognize that
You are only beginning to recognize that
sharing.
You um I was sharing with Daryl on the
way over here that I had had a
discussion with my famous mother in
terms of my
um and that I was proud of myself
because I'm more willing to say no I
don't agree with you. know this is, you
know, let me present a different way and
and finding different ways of presenting
things to her yet feeling on one level
as if because it was me, because I was
just a person. Often times people that
what you say can be real and not to make
you more valid, but that often times
people you can say the same thing to
them and then you can say it and it
allows them to see a different
perspective. It doesn't matter who it
comes from.
um it will allow them to think of it in
a different way. That is simply why many
of you have found yourselves attracted
to many different interactions with many
different levels of consciousness
because you are allowing us in a sense
to be representative of the ways you
will begin to listen to yourselves
a than you. I you're acquainted with
with staff a um staff came through
something like what 45 different people
over 300 over 300. How many do you come
through at this time? Seven.
at this time? Seven.
Where are they located? Not at this
time.
Is that seven on this planet? Yes.
In this way, our
energy is
available from our
civilization for you to form reflections
for yourselves. In this way, you will find
yourselves. In this way, you will find
therefore that there may begin to be
individuals who will form their own
simolacum of their own
representation of a
consciousness, beaming their
consciousness into our civilization and
creating an echo, a reflection that they
can then
channel. Therefore, there will now be an
acceleration of energy from our
civilization upon yours. And there will
be a lack of differentiation as to the
specifics of my own consciousness and
simply the consciousness of our
civilization in general being
exemplified upon your
planet. This is why the labeling and the
specificity of this time is not
necessary for it now will begin to
change accelerate in a chain reaction response.
Sure. days. Could you explain a um a day
that you had or what a typical day is
for you? Thank
you. In this way, there will be of
course always the simple interactions
that synchronistically occur with any
other member of my civilization and any
member of any civilization within the
association who chooses to drop in.
There will be conversations with many
civilizations as such as we are having
with you as we have with many other
civilizations going through similar
processes of understanding themselves
and allowing us to be reflective of
assistance to them. There will be the
piloting of craft upon the idea of
explorations of new civilizations, new
dimensions in the universe, new
understandings of expansions. In that
way there will also be the creation of
new what you would call materials new
understandings of the materials and the
physicality in which we exist. What you
would call exploration of
experimentation research of what you would recognize as
research of what you would recognize as
a so to speak scientific
nature. There will also simply be the
idea of the spontaneous enjoyment of any
idea of art form andor once again
expression of self interaction
with the planet
identification with all that is at
various times through the day.
So Bashard, you and Seth discuss your
meeting that you have with us? Not so
much in specific terms, but on a general
level, although from time to time there
are some specific interchanges,
the friends that you have that you share
these things with, are they sharing this
evening with you? In a sense, yes. This
is what was already sensed as there is a
gathering and a connection of more of
the association this night of your time
and that is why there is a difference in
the energy fields.
I find you quite a bit more serious and
I don't know how to express it but it
seems like depression and I don't mean
to say depression. We understand it is
because we are forming a link with a
more varied cross-section of
consciousness and in this way we are
representing the generalization of all
that consciousness. So we are in a sense less
consciousness. So we are in a sense less
distinctly my own personality. You
follow me? and all of us as well as you.
Yes. Thank you. You
Thank you. You
um it seems in my memory tape that I
recall the number
777 representing Christ consciousness or
the arising of that on the planet in
your mythology it is one of the
understanding a so is it is it just a
coincidence that there 17
when you say just a coincidence
You do understand that there are no
accidents. Well, is it all is synchronicity which
Well, is it all is synchronicity which
means the same thing as all is
co-incidental, not accidental.
Co-incidental. There are no accidents.
If it has meaning for you, then
understand you are tapping into levels
of the mass consciousness mythology that
allow themselves to be reflected in some
of the patterns that reveal themselves
to you in your time frames. archetypally. So,
archetypally. So,
no, it is no
accident. I was wondering if it is a
common choice once we release ourselves
from our physical body to continue to
believe that we still are maintaining a
physical body. It is not uncommon, but I
would say the majority of you do in fact
realize you are dead.
You sure? It was not always so.
It wasn't a joke.
[Music] No, guys.
No, guys.
I know that
at exactly the perfect rate. Uh, one of
the um people um
um people um
One of the people um been really
um helpful to me is an Indian teacher
named Davaji and I was with him um in
Los I was staying in the same house with
him in Houston.
um body just just
just kind of went on automatic Indian
dances and dramas and things and um I I
was wondering you are simply
transliterating the energy through your
physiological form in whatever way is
comfortable for you. You are channeling
it in comfortable, expressive way so
that you can allow yourself to remain
quote unquote open, quote unquote clear
to allow yourself to know you are in
touch with all portions of yourself and
that all portions of yourself are in
touch with all other levels of
consciousness that it needs to be. You
are exemplifying through your
imagination and acting in the idea of
being your imagination. You are
channeling in whatever way is exciting
and comfortable and enjoyable and
ecstatic for you.
Is it um reflection? Everything is now
coming together in this transformational
life. You are becoming all you have ever
been. All you have ever been. That goes for
All you have ever been. That goes for
all of you. And um I I felt it coming to
me about three days ago and everything
was integrating and I
understood that knowing something just
really that is the whole idea that is
for density awareness.
You understand and support
yourself and be who you are and act like
it and
live. There is nothing in this way that
you need from us except the assurance
that if you continue to act upon your
instinct in your
ecstasy, you will always be consciously
exemplifying the path you chose to be
and therefore will always only attract
yourself synchronistically only the
situations that will allow you to
continue to be the path you chose to be.
dance.
At this time, we will also, although
once again, we would urge you to
remember that we are in a sense speaking
symbolically using your terminology.
But you may also now begin, if you have
not already, to perceive that some some
of the idea connected to the Arcturus
energy may be perceived by you in your
symbolic terms as consciousness you
would call angelic.
I am very conscious of the birthing
process that's happening within my own
being. And I'm also having a real difficult
And I'm also having a real difficult
time friction in my solar plexus. I've
done a lot of energy work todaying and
breaking the template that I see of of I
get an image a symbol of how I have
created my physical form and how I find
how I pour my energy through it. And
today I had a visualization of a
breakthrough allowing more room. And yet
I have such a intense constriction in my
solar plexus and I have moments where I
can move that energy up into my heart
and and feel it blending. But most of
it's extremely painful and I would
prefer not to have a painful birth
process this time. Breathe more deeply
and a few times a day faster than you
are used to breathing.
Three times a day.
[Music]
Then you sit
still and listen and
gather and blend. All right. Thank you.
Thank you
for today. I became aware probably for
the first time on a conscious level of
this part of these people. um certain
limiters uh frustrators or something
that were the only thing blocking ice uh
making what I would call the difference
between the astral and the
physical and uh I was suspending these.
They were like energy boxes that were
they took quite a bit of creation to
interfere with with will and and make
things not appear to happen and uh uh
that sort of thing. Do you see what I'm
saying? They were the partition so to
speak, the primary partitions. So they
may serve a pipus. Oh yeah. I'm not
denying that. I'm just saying that
um I just identified that today, you
know, rather than just blanking it on
wrong reasons and such. There are actual
things I'm doing to uh myself. Yes. So
that you can be the idea you chose to be
as a physical being. Yeah. Do you have a
word for those? Do you have a better
description? Agreements. Agreements.
Contracts. Yeah. I actually felt them in tact
Yeah. I actually felt them in tact
tactical terms like an energy like an
electromagnetic field inside. They are
simply definitions. That is all definitions.
definitions. That is all definitions.
Definitions. Yeah. And um are those
dissipating at this time? Is that they
are changing changing? How does one um
erase them so to speak? You never erase
them. Yeah.
Your recognition that they are there for
a reason is what allows them to
transform in the way you are desiring.
They become less obtrusive,
become less obtrusive,
restrictive, so to speak. Yes. When you
recognize they are there for a reason,
they become less restrictive
paradoxically. Yeah. I want to share
something that I I felt it too. I
thought it was just me. But today in the
the group tonight seems very in a
sedated sort of a you know does everyone
else feel that way? Today has been sort
of like wow what happened? I thought it
was just me.
[Music] You are simply all becoming consciously
You are simply all becoming consciously
aware of the gate through which you are
passing. [Music]
[Music]
So, I'm not going crazy,
only in a positive way. You know, it was
funny today. Um, I felt so good. Um, I
said felt I felt so good. Felt better.
I feel so good. Oh, thank you.
That I thought
um it was so it was so different for me.
I felt like I god dang, I went too far
or something, you know?
Let's move on. Yeah, there just a little
echo in the head there. But
can't turn back now, but I just thought
I'd say that. Thank you. No need to turn
back. Yeah. Thank you very much.
Scariness, you know, in a sense of a
adolescence uh new experience. We
understand excitement. Yeah.
Bizarre. doing.
Last Monday, I
um you and I did some work together on a
pain that I was feeling in my
chest. And when I woke up that morning,
I had a knowingness of what was there
yet not knowing. And you aided and
assisted me through it and gave me an
incredible amount of love. What? You
gave me an incredible amount of love.
Incredible.
It was so incredible that it swept me
into I I just merged with it and I was
sweeping so much at just a higher
consciousness and it helped me to to
work through what was there.
Thursday I was with Tora and she
commented on how you did such a complete
job of
huh how you helped in doing such a
complete job of healing and
then the other day Friday I guess no
Saturday I had a china cup incident
where I was washing the dishes and I was
washing one of my china cups and it fell
and it bounced off the counter and And I
just knew that when I looked at it, it
was going to be broken and chipped or
something. And there wasn't anything
chipped or fractured. And then I got
this incredible inner voice that came to
this credible
this this credible inner voice that said
to me, "Don't you see the parallel of
the China cup in you? That you are not
as fragile as you have always have been
thinking. that that you are. And that
that incident of that past life where I
had been
stabbed after that incident, I had
decided to give up an incredible amount
of
power incredible amount
astounding power and that that I have
now integrated back with that. Oh,
and it's it's just been a real
delightful whole week. Thank you for
creating yourself to be centered in that
way. You have chosen to be that idea.
You have chosen to heal yourself in that
sense. And you have given yourself a
lovely symbolic reflection of the
understanding that no matter how thin,
no matter how seemingly fragile an idea
is, if it is known that that idea can
only be in that shape, it cannot be in
any other shape.
You follow me?
[Music] [\h__\h] you. Right. Thank you. Also,
[\h__\h] you. Right. Thank you. Also,
dude, thank you, Bashard. I was
[Music] um we were discussing a little earlier
um we were discussing a little earlier
that the evening has quite a different
tone to it. Um it's not half as crowded
as it normally is either. Correct. Is
that part of it? Nice. There is more of
a
subdued passage through a limbo state.
passage through a limbo state.
And in this way you will find that many
individuals have taken the opportunity
to find their own space in which to
float. They are all in their own way
receiving the same energy as
you. Thank you.
Uh just recently I purchased an energy
energy chair from Midnight Song and I
had my little boy. I said Paul sit in it
a couple days ago. So he sits in it and
he's never seen me really sit in it and
he held his hands about like this and
closes closed his eyes and he starts
taking deep breaths which I don't do you
know very heavily and I thought it was
kind of I don't know uh maybe you went
back in the past that he at one time did
that but it was really strange seeing
him do that what it is only a natural
cognition an expression of knowingness
when one identifies with an energy one
does what one needs to
do by simply knowing what that energy
represents and allowing the energy
through you. Understand in this way
children in your civilization simply do
not put the expectations, the blocks or
the forgetting upon themselves. So in
this way they simply respond naturally
to an energy and channel it through in a
natural way.
See, uh, another question. Last week, my
wife was coming home and she looked in
the rearview mirror and it's like it was
a figure standing like on the trunk or
just directly behind the trunk. Can you
tell me what that could be? She didn't
kind of scare a little bit. Again, you
will understand that a fourth density
symptom is as you expand your awareness,
more and more individuals will allow
themselves to begin to
perceive through sight and through sound
more levels of consciousness in more
dimensions of experience. It is like you
are now able to actually see through
doorways into other realms.
Mhm. And one last thing. Uh couple days
ago there was a large feather in my
backyard and uh it's I don't see how it
could be from a bird. Is that from my uh
Indian guide
or now let us say in a sense for now
simply follow the energy that you feel
from it. Yeah.
Thank you very much. It will guide you.
where you have created yourself to be
guided.
There are in our perception at this time
as we sense your
energy symbolic ideas that would call
wells pits in the earth in this way
connected to some of this
idea that you may partake
of and allow yourself to be in touch
with some of that
energy. Do you like the desert? I used
to hate it, but I'm liking it more now.
Then the change has begun.
Find yourself wandering there and coming
into contact with many individuals.
Some of which may be willing to take you
further to teach you what you wish to
know.
Any particular part of the desert or out
of Arizona more likely than California?
Is that your suggestion? Yes. Yes,
then you already have a sense of your
own direction. Follow it. Thank you very
much. Thank
you. Hey, in the manifestation process of
Hey, in the manifestation process of
taking a dream and putting it into
actuality or reality, is there an
activation process or or a particular
thing which makes it which keeps those
dreams from initiating versus those that
actually manifest? Is there an
activation trigger or something there
that could you discuss that? Yes.
starting now.
Not needing a
process is what allows it to occur most
quickly. Removing the gradient, so to
speak. Yes. The understanding that once
again, if you can conceive of it, you
are it. And all you have to do is act
like you know that and allow your
physical reality to reflect what you
know to be
true. No other process is truly
necessary.
So, so some dream some some dreams are
just idle and and by doing none of them
are idle but in this way many of them
have to do with different portions of
yourself to allow you to be in touch.
Simply follow what excites you the most
and understand that the way you may
envision it is not necessarily the way
it has to specifically manifest for you
to have the same effect as what you have
envisioned. I see. Oh, also on on
Wednesday, I noticed
um um there was a very different group
there that night and always. Yeah. And
is it as though as though you were
speaking it felt that you were speaking
to a very earthy earthy group in in a
sense of um you were else would we speak
to one
more type thing?
two quarters. All right. At least in the
middle.
But uh it was as though they had come
and you had addressed them. I just
noticed that.
Okay. You say so. Well, it seemed that
way to me. All right. Thank you. Then on
what level were you? Just about two and
a half.
Two and three. All right. Thank you.
Oh, by the way, I appreciate the whole
help you given me. I I told Daryl that,
but I think maybe maybe Bashar didn't
hear that. I appreciate all the
assistance you have given yourself.
Yeah. Thank you, Bishard. Yes. Um, I have a
Thank you, Bishard. Yes. Um, I have a
question.
Oh, I am so very surprised.
It was actually kind of a sneaky
um about like doctors and health and
stuff like that. Yeah. Um my my belief
is that um going to a doctor to get
pills is just your belief that those
pills will allow you to get better. Yes.
And that there really maybe there isn't
really a necessity to find out what it
is that you have. But my question is
maybe that it you know is it important to know
that it you know is it important to know
what you have because like like not
necessarily as long as you recognize the
reason for why you have it so that you
can as long as you once you get a
symptom let's say if you get in touch
with whatever the feeling is or the
knowingness of why you have that ask
yourself how it serves you what the idea
is you are attempting to show yourself
and how can you give yourself the same
message in a positive Okay.
And but and in that way you can allow
those those symptoms to transform into
something else. Right? Many times the
only reason you have those so-called
symptoms is because you have not been
willing to pay attention to the message
in any other way. So you force yourself
to look at it by slowing yourself down
and forcing yourself to take a look by
incapacitating yourself. Interesting.
You follow me? Yes. Yes. Or just to by
making a symbol of some sort that you
might be able to clean yourself. Yes.
Thank you. Should I shine? You then you
say the arctarian energy is more what we
would refer to as angelic. The star
terus kind of shines through my window
at night and Thursday there was this
what I would refer to as an angelic
beings. Very very much like the
paintings off of our cyine chapel. That
is your
physiological archetypal symbolic interpretation of
archetypal symbolic interpretation of
Arcturus energy. Are there physical
beings on earth or or on some levels but
the energy level that we are dealing
with at this time is mostly
non-physical. It is represented
symbolically by the 12 ray
star and orange on white on a black
field. I I had picked up a book that day
that had the the 12 race stars on the
front page.
Thanks. Thank you.
You have uh Barbie's question how you
responded to it. Uh I've had a problem
with assimilating food. What a
situation. Of course. Of course. a
situation of assimilating food
digestively for about 9 years that
doctors or therapists have been able to
figure out what the problem is. So if
okay situation
uh if it's physiological or
What is it you will not allow yourself
to try? Yes.
What is the problem?
There is no problem.
A problem is only a situation you will
not allow to change its shape. Can you
give me any insight on that situation?
Are you doing what you would most enjoy
doing in life? No. Why not?
For how long have you not been doing it?
Uh, couple of decades. Oh, God.
Do you think that it is time
to respect yourself? Yes. I see.
Then perhaps you will allow
yourself in a sense to begin to live
with yourself. You follow me? Yeah. Perhaps
yourself. You follow me? Yeah. Perhaps
you will allow yourself to begin to
assimilate sustenance when you know that
what you are assimilating what is
sustaining you sustains you for a
reason.
Whereas now you feel that your intake of
sustenance serves no purpose. So you
find it hard to
digest for you are not supporting the
you you wish to be but someone you are
not happy about
being. Follow me
mostly. When you do what excites you the
most? You are channeling your energy let
us say in the most efficient way. You
become in a
sense a being of
light. You become
enlightened in this way. Therefore, you
allow whatever energy comes into you
that represents sustenance to be a part
of that channeling to go into the
expression of energy that allows you to
be who you know yourself to be and not
to block up because you know you are not
applying that energy in the ways that
would represent the path you chose to
be. Do you follow me? Yes.
Do you follow me? Yes.
When you allow yourself to know that you
can trust that if you simply do what
excites you the most, you will be
automatically supported by the universe
in any way, shape, and form that you
need to be supported, to continue to be
the idea that you chose to be, that you
desire to be, that excites you. Then you
will allow your energy to channel
through you in such a way that you will
be
sustained and need much less to do the
sustaining. You will process all the energy
You will process all the energy
smoothly, flawlessly,
effortlessly. You will have new
vitality, new levels of
energy. All you need to do is to act
within trust and integrity upon that
which excites you the most. Recognizing
that excitement, the energy of excitement
excitement, the energy of excitement
itself, is the physical translation of
the vibration that represents the path
you chose to be. Therefore, you can
always trust that you can follow your
energy because your excitement is your
barometer that points you consciously on
the path you chose to
be. Therefore, it will always and
forever support
you. You follow me? Yes. Will you do
that? Yes. It is up to you. Not because
I say so, but simply because you know
that you can begin to treat yourself
with respect. The same respect that all
that is has for
you, all that is created you, therefore
all that is obviously thinks you deserve
to
exist. Treat yourself with the same
degree of consideration that all that is
treats you. All right. Okay. Thank you. Do what
you. All right. Okay. Thank you. Do what
it is that moves you and then your
entire system will move.
All right.
Thank you. Good job. Great time. All
right. All right. All right. All right. Steven.
Yeah. We'll speak after the
break. You may all take a short break.
All right. I'll say
[Music] Steven as that we have to some
Steven as that we have to some
degree already accessed a
co-identification with your
consciousness. There may if you wish be the opportunity
There may if you wish be the opportunity
in this sense
therefore in any way shape and form that
is comfortable for your consciousness
for your beliefs for your emotions for
your
thoughts made in this way available to
you our blending our
consciousness for sharing and for
service. You may, if you wish, form it
in the shape of energy that is blended
with the energies you are already
familiar with, so that in this way it is, in your
with, so that in this way it is, in your
terms uniquely your own third identity,
as it always
is. What any
degree of the consciousness that you
would perceive in your own
symbology that you would represent to be
interaction with our
own is available to
you. All right. Thank you.
Ice. earn when you wish to express it in
the form of the service as has been
discussed of what you call the
channelings. you
you
aside from the
being you call
Carol that is in this way affiliated
with that energy of our system you know
as
anima to in this
sense to the physiological
channel can be and function if you
within the
partaking directly of our energy
meaning channeling ace.
Yes. When when he
wishes and when it is of service
can you be more specific? Well, we were
all talking earlier before the session
started that I'm going to be channeling
Daryl was in Hawaii. I'm going to be
channeling here on August 18th and
19th and uh we all thought oh wouldn't
it be hilarious if I channeled the show
rather than the energy I used to
channel. So it is available to you.
So it is available to you.
Great. What is available to me?
Is your name Carol? Yeah. I see what
there's another woman named Carol who
channels. Oh because I'm channeling
more. I'm chilling too.
Okay. In this way,
for you at this time, any energy you are
comfortable with can be formed into an
identification for you to form as a
symbology. In this sense, we are simply
making a more direct
reference with Steven.
Allow yourself to simply continue to
follow your own understandings, your own
symbologies, your own connections, your
own intuition. Our energy in general as an
intuition. Our energy in general as an
energy is available to you to allow your
imagination to utilize in whatever way
you wish. In this sense, all that is
being said is that my specific
personality can be applied through the
connection that Steven has formed.
within his own identification with me.
Thanks. I'll enjoy that. You may blend
it again if you wish in whatever form
you are comfortable with with any other
energy you are already used to
channeling.
I would envision that would be how it
would begin. All right. Do recognize
therefore in this way that a great deal
of
congruency can also occur in that sense
as there will
be
co-incidental channelings at
channelings at
approximately the same time in your time
frame reference as with Daryl and
you
simultaneously you You thus then simply
participate in a type of
linkup that will allow me to
perceive further the understanding of
the shiftings of what you call time and
space and the illusions that they are
and the simultaneity of
all and the methodologies by which we
connect. We thank you. Thank you. Are
you uh associated with that green energy
to some
degree for green is our sun.
One moment. Green is also the emerald
ray of your earth and it is through that
emerald ray that you are also
identifying with our star and forming a
balance and a
blending in a natural way for me. Mhm.
Thank you,
Carol. Yes.
Our perception at this time is that in a
sense there is an aspect of
consciousness that you might call
crystallin and faceted and
reflective and spirit
like that hovers around you. Yeah.
Avail yourself of that friendship, of
that love, of that
assistance. Ring with a crystallin
tone and feel the love and the ecstasy
of the assistance being shared with you.
How does one ring with a crystallin
tone? How do you imagine that you
do? When the phrase comes out, how do
you interpret it?
There's a kind of happiness then. Right.
You can feel the vibration. It does not
have to be auditory. You can feel the
understanding of the core that it
strikes within you.
You follow me? Yeah. Simply feel the
tone you know to represent when you are
aligned with all of yourself and you
will be ringing with a crystallin tone
and open and vulnerable in infinite
strength to all levels of energy that
wish to be of assistance to you.
Vulnerability is strength not weakness.
It just seems like it hurts too much at
times. That is only remnants of your
judgment. It will pass. Understand that
nothing will come to you faster than you
can utilize it. Otherwise, there would
be no point in the universe does not do
pointless things.
All right. I understand that. Trust.
Trust. Trust.
Do not be impatient. All right. Yes.
Only by needing patience do you create
impatience. If you are enjoying every
moment, you do not need patience, for
you are not waiting for something better
to come along.
And Houston, I
um dreamed about something. Yeah.
Someone um two nights in a row.
I don't know. It was It was not really a
dream. Not three.
It was like in a twilight sleep
sleep in wakeful and um it's a very
pleasant dream. Yeah. And
um I was wondering like you know how
much of it is true? All of it. All of
it. Everything is true. Everything is
true. How much of it becomes true and do
you mean becomes physical? Becomes
physical. It depends upon your
agreement and the level at which you are
willing to express your
excitement and the level at which you
are willing to simply trust that it does
not have to manifest specifically as you
may have visualized it but that the
total effect will be
felt as
manifested and
manifestable in whatever way it needs to
be following. How do you know about your
agreements and what is manifestable? It
is simple. Whatever is occurring in your
physical reality is the product of the
agreements you have made because nothing
else can
happen. That is why if you allow
everything in your life to be a part of
the path you chose to be, then you will
allow yourself to perceive how it is so
and will not be assuming that something
can be there that has no bearing being
there. And then you will not judge it
and create it to seem to be an
interruption. You follow me?
It is that simple. All it takes is
trust. As soon as you are willing to
understand that every situation is
fundamentally neutral and that no
situation comes with built-in meaning
and that you give a situation meaning
and the meaning you give it is the
effect it will create in your life. Then
you will understand that if you simply
allow yourself to recognize that every
situation has a positive meaning, you
will only glean a positive benefit from
it. All right.
It says that Darl ano channel you as we
have already said crystal consciousness
hovers about you assisting you loving
you and allowing you to develop at your
own rate of comfort. How is that
different from my other like my guardian
angel? It
represents, let us say, a different
level of awareness, a different level of
energy, and again, a willingness to be
vulnerable and open to more of all that
is. Does it have to do with my crystal
meditations that I've been doing? To
some degree, that is your symbolic
representation of your awareness of your
connection to that level of
consciousness. And again, it is the
degree to which you are willing to be
comfortable in forming a conscious
recognition of that connection. The
crystallin consciousness does not care
how long you take. love you all the
same. Um the 10 plus one crystal meditation
Um the 10 plus one crystal meditation
that I've chosen to do uh does that have
anything to do with it? Yes, you will
understand that the idea of the 10
representing empowerment in that way of
the singular and the plus one
representing the matrix of 11. The 11
being representative of mass
consciousness levels of density
dimensional experience from one
dimension to another will represent a
template for the fastening of a master
crystal that encompasses your entire
mass consciousness. I quit that for
about 5 days and I've been doing it for
every day consecutively for a while now.
Do you recommend that I go on with it?
There is no recommendation to make. Do
what excites you. Do not do what
doesn't. You are your own best guide.
Follow your imagination if your
imagination gives it to you. If you are
excited about doing it, that is your
signal. When you are no longer excited,
do what does excite you. That is your
signal. Excitement is your signal.
Follow it. Trust it. Do it. I feel that
I am influenced too easily by others.
You are the only one who influences you.
If you feel that others are influencing
you, it is only because you choose to
believe that others can. And so you
create for yourself a scenario in which
you seem to be influenced by others but
you are doing the
influencing. You cannot be influenced by
anyone but you because you are your own
universe and you must create your
version of everyone else in order to
interact with them.
In that dream I I dreamt that I was
going to be his guardian angel. Is it?
You are and have been and he and have
been for you.
You follow me? Yeah. You are all simply
recognizing that you are all connected
and part of the same consciousness and
that you have danced around and around
and around with each other and many
other beings for a long time. You are
being mirrors and reflections. In this
way, I've also felt that I was uh ready
to ascend. But I You are ascending. You
are ascending. Do not worry. Do not
worry. Do not worry. You are in step.
You cannot be otherwise. All it takes
for you to know you are in step is for
you to know you are in step. Period. You
are exactly always at the right place at
the right time interacting with exactly
who you need to be interacting with. It
cannot be
otherwise. There is no extraneous action
in the
universe. You follow me. I follow you.
You are where you need to be. know that
and you will give yourself conscious
recognition that you will be where you
desire to be. That will attract into
your life situations that will allow you
to know it is so.
All right. All right. Remember it is
that simple. Period. It is that simple. That
simple. Period. It is that simple. That
is crystal and clarity. It is that
simple. Do not fight your own
ecstasy. It is that
easy.
Trust. Love who you are
unconditionally and you will love all
unconditionally as all that is loves you
unconditionally. Thank you. Thank you.
Michelle,
was there a female? Yes. All right. Um,
Mashard, what I wanted to ask earlier
was about astrology and how it fits into
our lives. Obviously, we we've chosen
our lives as man, woman, or whatever of
the kind. We must have chose our signs
and our aspects as well. Yes, in a
sense. Although many of that is
changing, you are all blending. And the
idea of astrology, while it is a
recognition on a subconscious level to
some degree of the overall patterns of
the agreements you have made as a mass
consciousness, they are
fluctuating. You are changing. You are
becoming more amorphous in that
sense. You control your own destinies.
Therefore, we can change our our pattern
in our in our astrology.
It is all changing. Well, the uh the
planets are changing. Everything is
changing. The entire universe is
changing. Thank you. Thank you. You
You
um what's the phone number for the
pleades?
Love and light. Well,
2000 is that
it's cool for you. put here
is well you spoke of the communication
device that you gave out a while back as
being your phone number and the pyramids
as
being a phone number for a different
civilization. I was just wondering if
we're going to contact the Plleadensians
first. I'd like to some of the vibration
of what you call humanity the number
five will connect you to some of those
ideas. Is there a device that sort of comes
Is there a device that sort of comes
together pentagonally or
mostly it is tone?
I'm interested in building a device. I
guess follow your
imagination. Think
plleadian and see what you
get. Understand that the second you
think plleadian, you are in contact.
Uh-huh. Yeah.
You already have made the connection.
Allow the information to come back along
the line that you have created. Trust
your imagination. Follow your intuition
and have a good time.
All right. Sure. Thank you. Thank you.
All right. got a question about I'm
going to build a anti-gravity device and
I just realized that looking at the one
gentleman that's built one already
according to your directions is
different to what my perspective is.
There are many different ways. Okay. Is
it all right if I have the uh the core
of the electromagnets
uh going in the same direction as if
they were the uh spokes in the wheel
perpendicular to the shaft. In other
words, his has got the the axis being
perpendicular to the disc. Mine is going
to be have the axis of each of those
electromagnets as if they were spokes in
that disc that were see what happens.
All right. I just wanted to make sure
that it wasn't totally in the wrong
direction. It is not. Okay. And is is
like 30 gauge wire good enough. It's
pretty lightweight.
Can be good. You will find many
different degrees to experiment with,
many different variations, many
different fluctuations in the energy
field. Every single one of these
differences will tell you something that
you need to know and can be utilized in
an overall control mechanism later.
Great. Thank you. Thank you.
There will be a time when also you can
experiment again with the idea of quartz
crystal wrapped in copper as well for
more quote unquote solid state
variations. Yeah.
Very good. Thank you. Thank you. For
sure. You Uh last week I had a very
extremely realistic dream and I can
still p see it in my mind's eye and uh I
was at my friend's house that I hadn't
seen in years and it was like an estate
and in one corner I could see it wasn't
I don't believe it was a Catholic
church. It was a tall church with a
steeple. There was a a gigantic church
and I could see it from his property and
he had a view and then I I then my wife
was on the property and sitting like at
a picnic table and I could see servants
all around from my friend and I looked
at the house and it was I guess if
anyone watches Dynasty was like
Dynasty's house but like four times
larger but there were two of them side
by side and then like I read my wife's
mind and like she was very envious of of
this and in my mind but I never told her
But in my mind in the in the dream I
said don't worry honey I'm going to
you're going to have one just as big
nice so the interpretation you tell me
it's going to be
you are expanding the idea of the house
that you are as you expand the idea of
who you are what you are as an idea your
physical reality follows suit in
whatever way shape and form it needs to
to allow you to be the idea you have
expanded into. Whether it happens
literally that way or not does not
matter. In one way, shape or form, it
will happen to reflect the idea that you
are. Do remember once again that
abundance comes in many forms and that
someone you consider to be wealthy has
no more than they need to be who they
are. What's a symbol of church? I was
saying you are connecting to the idea of
some of your spiritual self and also in
a sense at the same time incorporating
and integrating some of the past ideas
or beliefs that you have into something
a little let us say less ritualistic.
You are simply recognizing that one
house can serve as a house for all in
that sense and there need not be the
differentiations that have been created
in your society any longer.
Thank you very much.
Your world is your
church if you follow it.
Thank you.
Guys, what's your interpretation of of
the energies right now as far as the the
ending of the negative scenario between
our governments and the extraterrestrial
ideal? Again, as we have suggested,
there is grand opportunity 7787 for the
idea of the expression and equalization
of your society in this way to allow to
commence more
communication. But it will again take
the equalization and the recognition in
this sense that you are your governments
and the willingness to communicate with
them on those terms will allow them to
know that contained within you is the
understanding of the true balance of
power.
Thank you. Thank you.
Um, I'm creating a a line of bumper
stickers and the one idea that I don't
have represented
um is something to stimulate a an
expansion of openness towards the idea
of outer spatial beings and
communication. Would you have any
suggestions? Is up to you. Okay. One
other thing. Um, make one now.
What is it you would wish to say?
Not that right now. It must come out in
the finalized worded form. What is it
you wish to say? Um uh
uh
that the idea of communication with
outer spatial beings is real and valid
and available. All right. All right.
[Music]
Have you hugged your ET today?
I thought you used to get like was great
make one
now on board.
[Music] What about teacher brothers on the sky?
What about teacher brothers on the sky?
I I had thought of ET. I'm listening.
Yeah. Okay. Um did you have any other place
Okay. Um did you have any other place
you wanted to go with that? All right.
Because I had another question. Go
ahead. Okay. Uh there's a device called
Bob Beck's brain
tuner. Would you comment on
that? Once again, these are symbolic
interpretations. Any symbol is valid for
the individuals that feel so attracted,
so drawn. What we will share is that
they simply represent along with many
other devices that you are creating the
beginning of the understanding of a new
way to look at your brain. a new way to
understand the physiological symbol that
you are as a projection of consciousness
into physical materiality and the
utilization and creation of mentality by
the impingement of consciousness upon
the electromagnetic field. All of these
ideas are the beginnings of your
willingness to be cognizant of how it is
you interact as a physiological reality
through the opaces of the creation of an
electromagnetic field. They are all of
service. They are all valid for varying
ideas, varying degrees. You will simply
find that bit by bit and piece by piece,
you will consolidate many of these ideas
into a few devices that will allow you
to recognize once again the primary and
basic beginnings of what you call your
artificially intelligent computers that
will allow you to understand that all
you have done is create a device to
allow you a comfortable means of
communicating with your higher self in
physiological terms.
It is simply one
something else. Yes. I I was wondering
if you had any um suggestions as to
devices which were um most evolved that
are available. Pardon? Crystals.
Okay. Thank you. Nice. The shard. Nice.
What are you doing with your arms when
you move them the way you do when
someone's asking a question in this way?
I recognize I am not moving my arms but
the arms of the physiological channel
are responding to pulses in my energy
field in my consciousness field because
there is more communication coming to
you than what you are perceiving or
hearing translated vocally. So the
spillover in a sense is translated in
bodily terms and there are many other
levels that are not translated
physiologically at all but what you
simply feel.
In this instance, the idea is simply
that there are patterns of energy that
are ongoing that reflect certain ideas
being shared in your mass consciousness
that we are simply tapping into and
giving you a symbolic subconscious
reflection of. These things do tap into
you in certain ways. Even though you may
not be consciously aware of what they
are doing, it is opening certain gates
with you because we are simply
reflecting to you energy patterns we are
picking up from you. Even seeing them in
a form that does not seem to make
conscious sense does make subconscious
sense and allows you to begin to blend
the unub and consciousnesses into one
level. You might say in a way we are
defining an energy pattern. We are
riding the waves of your mentality and
by showing them and reflecting them to
you in this way you are being given a
graphic understanding that you do
understand on some let us say deeper
level even though it may not make
conscious sense to you.
You are seeing a reflection of some of
your own soul patterns.
I have another question. All right. Um I
read a book called out-of- body
experiences and in this book this man
had left his body and during his
experiences he had communicated with
quite a few of his friends. Hey um they
communicated back subconsciously when he
approached them the following day in
physical form and and told them of his
experience in communicating with them
they had no recollection of it. No
conscious recollection. That's what I
mean. Nice.
Um, I have had an out-of- body
experience a few times, but one that I
remember where this also happened where
I spoke to some people and they don't
remember. Is this obviously it is
because this is part of what you were
saying happening all the time like
perhaps right now. Okay. So that's in
this way it is simply not their timing
to allow themselves to know they can
remember. So they do not
but there are many times where they can
remember. Well, they always can. It is
up to them to choose to. You follow me?
Yes. Would this be the reasons they
don't remember? Because they don't
believe they can remember. That is one
idea. They may be afraid to remember.
That is another idea. They may simply be
doing something that allows them not to
need to remember right now because they
are not finished with what they are
doing about
forgetting. You follow me?
Yes. How about this one? I one time
wished someone to dream something only.
Uh I was I was well rewarded by whatever
I had wished. I don't remember what I
wished but this person acted it out.
Then in a sense you have quote unquote a
reversal. The understanding that you
attracted yourself to someone who was
willing to mirror something to you that
you did not necessarily have to bring
into conscious recognition. But then
when it was played out, you had a
reflection that allowed you to make a
connection from one level to another by
being surprised in a sense.
Oh yeah.
Thank you. It is simply one of the
creative ways you allow yourself to
remember who you are.
Thank you for sharing. Thank you. For
sure. No, we talked a little bit about the
No, we talked a little bit about the
theoric uh or template universe. Nice.
Okay. We we observe that streaming from
the central regions of most galaxies the
dense clouds of hydrogen gas. Well, that
is not the template. No, I understand
that's what we observe in physical
universe. And I read some ideas about
how matter is formed. And and one of the
ideas that I thought was interesting was
they said when some of these force
vectors that say intersect or collide
with each other in the atheric say
region or plane when they actually
intersect or collide do they form
neutrons? Do they form physical matter?
Okay. And so there is always
physicalization of matter coming out of
what you perceive to be an energy void
constantly. They are called virtual
particles. Right. But of course well
that's not but that's non-physical. Oh
they are physical for a brief period of
time. They are called virtual simply
because they are only physical for a
brief period of time. There is not a
need for them to maintain a physicality.
But the potential is always there. They
are constantly transforming into matter
into energy, to matter into energy, to
matter into energy to matter into
energy. When they need to manifest, then
there is a concentration or a focus of
the energy that allows itself to impart
materiality to more of the
particles. Do understand that what you
call your black holes are also
responsible for some of the creation of
this materiality. They come out the
white holes. In this sense, you will
find that these virtual particles are
always created in what you call matter
antimatter pairs. Therefore, if you find
that as they are created, before they
have a chance to come back together and
in a sense cancel each other out back
into energy, if one of them is absorbed
into a black hole, the other one must
remain material. Mhm.
Thus, it appears as if the black hole is
radiating.
You follow me? Sure. Sure. We that's you
bring that up. Um it's also one of the
theories at least I've read that photons
are neutrino anti-utrino pairs and that
and that some of that energy interacts
with biological beings and that's what
helps us sort of light up our third eye
in a sense but they are not exactly
nutrino anti-utrino pairs. Okay. There
is another understanding that you will
come to. You shed some light on that
now. No.
Okay. One more question, please. Um,
assuming that gravity is a quantifiable
field and there are certain units that
you can number this field or the vectors
within the
field sort
of what I'm trying to get at is is there
some way to mathematically convert E
fields or electric fields or magnetic
fields into some type of algebraic
relationship? Uh once again when you
allow consciousness to be a part of the
equations perhaps right all right is is
or in a sense in a sense not meaning to
be mysterious
consciousness is gravity gravity is
consciousness in a sense
I'll let you play with that
now that you talk about playing with it
we're going to be playing with a device
that we built uh I talked to Daryl
during the break and he's not available
this Saturday. So, if you're all
available next Saturday, that's August.
I guess the second uh we're going to
give the spinning disc anti-gravity
device a shot. Um if you'd like to get
together the carriage in at Burbank and
Sophia at 8:30 in the morning, have
breakfast together. We'll go out to the
site if any of you have Can't do it on
Sunday. I play baseball. Sorry. But if
you're available and if you have a video
camera available, if you have an 8 mm or
60 mm camera available, I'm more than
willing to share the experience with
you. No charge. Just meet us. Two
Saturdays, August 2nd. What's the
carriage? Carriage. It is a motor hotel
at Burbank. It's supposed to
in need of welding information. Somebody
was needed some sophisticated welding
technique. Was that you? Uh I might
avail of that later on. Okay. I think he
needed it more than I did. Oh, okay.
Yeah. For the copper, we got it taken
care of with an epoxy, but we Okay.
There's welding called diffusion
welding. Uhhuh. It's a solid state weld.
I'll talk to you about that later.
Great. Yeah. A more synchronicity.
There will also be others present.
Oh, thank you.
Do
remember, do not stand any closer than
10 ft. Oh, sure. I have a 50 foot
extension cord
at the ready. What's going to happen?
Will it record on videotape or film?
Does it matter? Will both mediums work?
Does it matter, guys? Yeah. I was afraid
that the magnetic field that we generate
might just botch up any videotaping we
do. So, that's why I wanted something.
If you are locked too close,
50 ft is uh outside of the field. Yes.
Video with the zoom. Thank you. Thank
you. There will be simply from the act a
type of crystallization that will occur.
Thank you.
More acceleration during the event.
Leave your imaginations open and
running. You will absorb more than you realize.
You follow me? Sure. Thank you.
Nice. My daughter Taylor, um, she's
special to me. Uh, she she impresses
others as being special and mature and
such. She'll be 7 years old on this date
you indicated is 7787.
Anything beyond a coincidence on her?
Ask yourself why you named her as you
did. Taylor. Yes. Taylor Alana Holmes.
Um, my mom wanted her to be named
Taylor. I of the apes. Taylor. Taylor.
Planet of the Apes. The idea of a
tailor. Tailor made.
The idea of someone who fashions in your
in your
society, guys.
Thank you. In this
sense, in our perception,
literally in the child's hand at some
point in her life can be the literal
manipulation of energy in many different
ways.
She will draw heavily upon the vibration
that you have indicated that you call
Alana for it will be her connection to
the past and the
future. It will be the fulcrum and the
balance point. There is
point. There is
also no literative accident in what you
call the vibration you call your last
name as well. In this
way, the child can function as a
valve in the transformation as many of
the children of the transformation
do. a valve, a black hole into a white
hole between the
dimensions or what you may symbolize as
the bow
tie. That is our remnant physiological
symbol for an energy
gate. What you would recognize perhaps
as an elongated X.
For always in going in one end do you
come to a point that contains infinity
and then in a sense explode into the
particularly chosen vibration of the
next universe you are
visiting. But everything in the
transformation compresses down to that
one point before it explodes again. For
at that point you are infinity and all
is possible.
I lost. What's the timing on that for an
individual? I'm losing someone. No need.
No need.
Thank you. Thank
Perhaps if you are
willing, make the sign on what you call
a piece of paper and show it to your
child. Okay.
Okay.
Thank you. All right. Thanks. sharing
sharing
eggs. Yes. I had I have an ant that told
me once that
um that if there's a certain fly that
was roaming around my room that it
symbolized a spirit visiting me and um
it's like every time every time I I see
a fly I mean it's not like just regular
flies flying around but it's like a
certain fly and I can feel a sensation
that someone is around and I know that
everyone one. I mean, it's like all the
time someone everyone creates their own
symbol. Erica, would you like to share
something?
Flies. Gays. Gays.
Uh, I don't know exactly. There was I
think there was a mosquito in the room
last night. It kept trying to land on my
ear. It was pissing me off.
You are missing. couldn't find it to
kill it. Um, you never
can landing on your ear. One more time.
Apply what you are saying with
obviousness to what has just been shared
by that individual. Well, if it's
bringing you a message and it was
landing on my ear, maybe it was bringing
me a message. All right.
And upon the idea of what you call the
immediate search, no physiological
representation was evident.
We lived around that room and that's why
we didn't think it was a flyf fly
because you can hear them all the time
and they keep flying. There was no
place.
Then in that way simply recognize that
you are tapping into a level of mass
consciousness that allows you to know
that many times the small buzzings are
in a sense whisperings from another
level
and are simply being interpreted in the
symbolic fashion of what you call a
fly. But many times you will find that
as you look for them you cannot find
them. The shark. Thank you. Thank you. Nice.
The shark. Thank you. Thank you. Nice.
What if it's a butterfly?
They don't both. Then simply recognize
you may be reflecting your own
metamorphosis. I had an interesting
experience, but I'll just talk about it
briefly. All right. Um, I was reading
this book of this woman who had a
butterfly land on her finger and she
knew that this was a calling for her to
leave and join her friend who lived near
a tree that was cluttered in
butterflies. Anyway, it's a long story,
but I thought, gee, how amazing that
this butterfly should keep landing on
her finger and urge her to go 5,000 m.
Everyone creates their own symbols and
the animal consciousness is more than
willing to participate where necessary.
The next day, I went to work and I was
sitting at my desk and this fly, this
butterfly kept trying to fly into the
door and hitting its head and finally
flew away and I thought, I don't believe
this. It was, obviously, you did. [Music]
[Music]
And and what and what did it bring me
to? Yes. Oh, I just thought, well,
that's pretty pleasant. I don't
know. I don't know what basis it had to
me. Do you feel that in your own
transformation there may simply have
been a symbol that you were running into
invisible walls?
That I was running into invisible walls?
How can you do that?
It is a very creative thing that many
people in your society have done.
The idea that you think you can see
where it is you want to go, but for some
reason it seems as if there is glass in
between you and your so-called goal.
You follow me? Yes.
Are are you following yourself as your
own butterfly? Well, I'm
You are
what? I'm flying into it with a wall.
I'm I'm trying to figure out how this
how I'm how I'm accepting that. I When I
saw the butterfly zoom towards me, I
thought that I was seeing things. And
when I saw it come at me and it hit the
glass, then I thought that I was
preventing it by not opening the door. A
case closed.
Thank you. the shot.
In addition to the butterfly, I this
Saturday I was sitting down and um there
was one one yellow butterfly that flew
right next to me and it it was very
windy and uh that was in the garage and
um I says, "Okay, what is this
representing?" And then it just flew
away. Tupac, it just disappeared. And
then and then I says, "Well, I didn't
get anything." So second time there was
a bigger butterfly with more color into
it. And then I said, "All right, this
means freedom. What is this must mean
freedom?" I went like that and then all
of a sudden it just poof it
disappeared. And um I thought I'd want
to share that to you. That that's what I
got into it. Thank you. Shark. You are
the butterfly. Guys, when I was living in
butterfly. Guys, when I was living in
Arizona, a few years ago, Marina and I
were staying out in a guest ranch in the
desert and we were living in a house,
but it was right in the desert. And uh
one night I looked down on the floor and I
night I looked down on the floor and I
saw a tarantula as big as a Steven tape
recorder. And uh Marita had her back to me and was
And uh Marita had her back to me and was
washing the dishes. And I didn't want to
say anything to her cuz she would have
went nuts. I didn't want to have to
handle a tarantula and her at the same
time myself.
So, I started I found a glass jar I was
going to try to put over it and then
went very quickly into the bedroom. This
is all I needed for this thing to hide
and I got to start poking around for it.
So, I went into the bedroom was right at
the edge and uh it was still and I
didn't want it to become afraid where it
would, you know, again hide under the
bed or something. So, I just kind of sat
down a few feet away from it and I
established a very strong mental contact
with it and I said to it, "Look, I won't
kill you if you let me put this jar over
you. I'm just going to pick you up and
bring you into the desert and let you
go, but don't bite me cuz I want to
smash you." And it's just it came a few
inches closer to me and it stayed there.
And I'd been to the desert museum that
day and I'd seen the difference between
a male tarantula and a female. I knew
one of them was poisonous, but I
couldn't remember which one it was. So,
I took this jar and I just gently placed
it over and they let me do it. And then
I said, "Okay, now I've got to slip
something underneath. So, if you would
crawl up the jar for me so I won't have
to feel you when I put the newspaper."
So, crawled up the jar and I stuck the
newspaper underneath. And Maria's still
watching this. She was in humming a
tune. And I walked right past her and I
said, "I'm just going to for a minute."
And I went out the back door and I
walked, you know, a couple hundred feet
away. And then it suddenly flopped on my
hand on newspaper. I just
went this jar away and made sure that it
left. But it's funny that my stay in
Arizona triggered off more instances of
real like terror or fear in me that I
had to come to terms with and release.
Yeah. Do understand the animal knew
where it wanted to get off.
Oh really? And that was an energy center
to which it was related to which you
also were related. Wow. Really? I in
this way it was symbolic interpretation
of coming to terms with many portions of
the hidden
self. Information you deem to be secret
or
inaccessible to you. For in many ways
that is what that particular animal
represents. knowledge of what to you may seem to be
knowledge of what to you may seem to be
inaccessible information
and it is connected to some degree with
what you call the nature spirits of the
desert archetypally and some Indian
American Indian culture understandings.
You were standing in its energy spot
when it released itself. Wow.
And therefore allowed yourself to form a
nodal point within yourself. What's
that? A nodal point. a balance point of
energy. I see.
Thank you. Thank you. Nice. What type of
spirits are horses and what type of
spirits are? Animal consciousness
Animal consciousness
representing many different things to
many different individuals in horses in
the general mass consciousness
conception. service of service of
support,
new styles of movement, freedom of
expression. In many ways,
ways,
assimilation of many different
concepts in the goat
form and different types of connection
into primal nature energy and in the goat
primal nature energy and in the goat
archetypal mythological subconscious
massconcious
energy. Again dealing with assimilation
of polarities.
Thank you. Thank you. Yes, you are. You
know, you talked about us as being all
infinite creators. are all creators.
Where does the uh the the duality of
creator destroyer come from? Say in the
Hindu cultures and eastern cultures.
Does that have a The reason I bring this
up is we were talking about insects
earlier and every time it gets moist
outside the ants start crawling all over
your garbage and on the walls and stuff
and you have to stamp them out, you
know, because you feel like germs and
stuff. Well, I don't always do that, but
but you know what I
do happens by understand you are simply
recognizing or in their mythology, they
are simply recognizing a very primal
energy manifestation, the very basis of
what it is you've decided to explore in
this physical reality. The idea of
positive and negative polarities. Thus,
one simple expression is creator and
destroyer. Okay.
All right. Thanks. It is a fundamental
energy cognition.
Does that also have to do with the the
yin and yang symbol? Okay. To some
degree, although that will carry more
recognition of a blending as well rather
than a separation. Those
extraterrestrial origin particular symbols.
origin particular symbols.
Not exactly. Let us say there may have
been influence based upon your choices
of cognition in ancient times but only
as you interpreted your own
extraterrestrial energy. There is some connection to that
energy. There is some connection to that
but it is not the total
idea. There will be a few moments
remaining for this interaction this
evening of your time. sharing.
sharing.
Sean, would you share with us um an
energy exchange relative to the full
moon in Cancer? Now,
the opportunity to be in
direct communication with all that you have
communication with all that you have
created to be unconscious within
you. And the
understanding that you can change
sides. All that you know to be conscious
can become unconscious. All that you know to
become unconscious. All that you know to
be unconscious can become conscious so
that you will be turned inside out. And
in this way allow yourself to
experience a passage through your own
fulcrum, your own black hole into white
hole experience.
All right. All right. Crystallization has
Crystallization has
commenced. See the vibrations that you
are. Act upon them. Sing them. Live
them. Dance them. Be them, feel them,
share them, express them. You are the
vibrations. You are the nodal points of
all the agreements that you have made as
a mass consciousness. The overall mass
consciousness agreement has given birth
to each and every individual as a nodal
point within that agreement.
Each and every one of you are the
indices, the intersections of the matrix
of the mass conscious agreement in
electromagnetic mentality. You are the
vibratory zero state rest centers, the
holographic points within the
field, the structure, the matrix.
You are the concentration of energy out
of the virtualness of all the probable
realities. And you exist in every
probable reality as a different
reality as a different
reflection.
Multi-dimensional lives to you.
exciting dream lives and life
dreams. Our unconditional
love, affirm and loving good night.
Thank you. Good night.
Do not
forget that along with the blending of
the association and the available
energies, do not forget the one closest
in proximity to
you, the dolphin
consciousness, sweet dreams. M same to
you always
for I am sweetly dreaming right now.
Don't let the bed