all right Al how are you all this
evening of your time is you create time
to
exist allow us to begin with the idea of
this interaction systems of
interaction systems of
belief this can also be your title for
this evening if you wish what was that
systems of
belief systems structures the
the
idea of that which forms a
part A series or cycle of
ideas or
observations which allow you to create a
perception of
continuity and
cohesion systems of belief now we have
discussed with you many times the idea
that it is your belief
that create the physical reality you
experience each and every one of these
beliefs is the representation of a particular vibrational particular vibrational
resonance
particular frequency of the
frequency of the
fundamental energy pattern that gives
rise to physical reality
a
particular vibration and so as that vibration is
vibration and so as that vibration is
manifested into your physical reality as
it is manifested as your physiological
experiential reality because it operates on a certain
reality because it operates on a certain
wavelength shall we
say it will have a
tendency in physiological
reality to gather to itself
patterns of vibratory frequency that are
similar in nature to the original
vibration in this way it will key
into other beliefs other vibratory
patterns that will
aggregate around this primary belief so as to set
around this primary belief so as to set
up what appears to be a frame of
reference in which to understand and be
able to perceive the original belief by
surrounding itself with slightly out of phase
itself with slightly out of phase
vibration similar but not exact so that
you have a reference point some
surrounding some illusion of a
background against which you can see the
primary belief this aggregation this drawing
belief this aggregation this drawing
together of similar belief systems so as
to allow the primary belief to stand out
occurs quite automatically quite
naturally within you as you say quite
second nature so rapidly so quickly once
again that you may not even realize or
have not realized that this is what you
are doing to create the seeming
background of reality that in your
Society you have had a tendency to think
of as simply quote unquote that's the
way reality
is your life happens in this reality and
the specific beliefs of your reality
manifest itself against this backdrop of
the overall reality but this overall
reality is not simply that the way it is
it is the background that you
create by surrounding the primary belief
structure you have with similar belief
structure so that you can create a gr
ation A variation of beliefs to expand
outward from you to create a backdrop
against which to see the primary belief
of your life the primary focus of your
life now these structures after a Time
have become ingrained within you to the
extent that you take this background for
granted and you simply as we have said
think of it much as if it is something
that exists without you
in this way it has been one of the
primary mechanisms that has allowed you
to experience the illusion of the
universal reality as seemingly outside
of
yourself you in this way may
recognize that in your Society quite
often because of the repetition of this
idea because this is now the way you
automatically as you say set the
stage you have created many ideas in
your society that there is only one way
for this stage to be set and it is
against only that background that you
measure everything in your
life but
recognize as soon as you change the
fundamental primary focused beliefs that
represent the being you are the entire
background changes with it everything
changes everything is connected
everything is the same one thing and a
change in the primary focus creates what
you colloquially call the domino effect
and changes occur all the way down the
line in the entire pattern in the entire
backdrop it may seem at times to be
subtle but they are far ranging and
quite widespread if you will allow
yourself to recognize that they
exist many times
therefore when you seek to create
changes in your own life your own
primary belief Bel system Focus many
times you will only continuously weigh
that primary focus or change against a
background that you will not allow to
see yourself has changed but if you are
willing to recognize that everything
changes when you change anything then
many times you will not still see the
primary background in the same light you
will begin to realize that something is
different somewhere
somehow in this way many times this is
why many of you create the seeming
contradictions in your life for you say
that you wish to change the primary
focus but then when you look around in
the background you continually watch to
see the same background in a sense to
see the idea of your primary focus
against the same background rather than
allowing the entire background to be a
part of the primary focus and change
along with it when you look at the
background in the same way you used to
you immediately cancel the change you
made in your primary focus because it is
all one and the same thing the echo the
background carries its origin point from
the original
sound many of you many times will look
to this Echo to see changes occur in the
Echo before you will allow yourself to
validate the changes you know you have
made or you desire to make in the
primary focus of your being but if you
seek validation in the Echo then you
will only continue in the reality in
which you have already focused yourself
because the validation must come in the
primary sound the primary signal first
before you will see it in the Echo of
the background reality you consider to
be your exterior
universe is all of this trans lazying
lazying
therefore recognize simply that one
primary belief will always in physical
reality extend itself to create a
seeming system of belief with which it
becomes surrounded and supported so that
the primary belief can have a place can
have an existence in physical reality no
belief will exist unto itself in a void
as you say every Le brings with it a
complete and total
Entourage if you will a complete and
total set of props a complete and total
backdrop a complete and total stage and
a complete and total audience receptive
to that particular
play a in this way better for allow yourself
a in this way better for allow yourself
if you truly desire to change the
primary focuses in your life the the
primary beliefs that you are allowing
yourself to be in touch with do not play
them out in the same stage allow
yourself to know you are in a completely
different local everything has changed
local everything has changed
everything you follow me thus then you
can recognize that whole
recognize that whole
systems of
reality not just one portion but the
total system of reality that you
perceive your lives to be will then
change from system to system not just
particle to particle everything will
transform in that
way many
individuals in your
Society simply have but to realize that
many of the things they wish to see
occur many of the things they desire to
see valid ations of in a particular
specific sense will also occur if they
will change the entire system
first then all the particles again that
go along with the representation of the
new system will also be there as well
you can do it either way as we have said
cause and effect are the same event you
can work it from both directions you can
have a cause which creates an effect you
can have an effect which creates a cause
you can change the whole system you can
change a specific within the system and
in every case both the specifics and the
system change you can work it from either end
change you can work it from either end
Inside Out backwards forwards upside
down it doesn't matter simply when you
do make a change allow yourself to
function as if a change has occurred
across the entire Spectrum otherwise all
you are doing is focus ing yourself into
a localized specific effect and in that
way you do not allow yourself to see how
the change you have made within yourself
has made a change in the reality you
desire around you to
see you follow
along Sher oh my all right
Sher oh my all right
okay remember Don
Jones okay he's got a question all right
and he wants to know his roommate is
sick right now all right she's
unconscious and the doctor says she only
have a few days to live oh right and he
says that he thinks that she's trying to
communicate to him but Don is not
getting it Don usually thinks he is not
getting it that's right and he's been
sick to all right so yeah like May
simply be the idea of sympathetic
transformation what you call sympathetic
vibrations recognize that the time is at
hand for that individual to realize that
some of the individuals that are in his
life are going to transform now in ways
that will allow him to transform as well
if he is willing to extend his senses
into the realm they are going to proceed
into to allow them to function as
mirrors to allow them to function as
lures to allow him to expand to reach
out and broaden his understanding of
what he is capable of knowing he does
not have to have conscious analytical
awareness of a specific message word for
word coming from that individual the
basic message is to Simply feel that
that individual is still vital still
alive and always will be and therefore
to feel the vitality and aliveness
within himself no matter what realm what
level what plane he chooses to perceive
that individual existing in he is in
touch with that Consciousness as he is
in touch with own Consciousness the idea
of wishing to be in touch with that
being as that being make the
transformation from physicality to non-
physicality is what will let us say lure
him or trick him into being aware that
he is in touch with his own non-physical
aspects right now because he will be
willing to reach for communication with
that individual beyond the Physical
Realm and that will lure him into being
in touch with more of himself basically
that is the only message he needs to to
know trust the feelings recognize the
Vitality in the individual no matter
what the choice of transformation all
transformations go on all
transformations keep
occurring everything in life is a
transformation the idea is that there is
no need to give support to what is
perceived or thought to be or judged to
be the negative aspects of this but to
recognize that it is in a sense its own
kind of birth and he is attending at a
new birth in that way if he is willing
to have the sympathetic vibrations for
that then he himself can also be reborn
in that moment and recognize himself to
be a far more expanded being than he
previously fought himself to be you
follow me really yeah sure not all right
I have a one moment I have another
question all right another friend of
mine whose name is Janu um I don't know
if you remember her come here she's
French Canadian anyway she just died um
I guess two months oh right two weeks
ago and
another friend of mine wanted to find
out how she's doing what what she's up
to just fine going through period of
transition period of relearning period
of acclimatization there is a little bit
of disorientation in the sense of not
understanding how the mechanisms of the
non-physical reality work but she is
having assistance and you may find again
that there is no accident in the sense
that the individual also to some degree
about to cross over as you say can also
Al add energy to the overall event and
that they are connected both of them to
some degree have some connections and in
this way they can reinforce each other
you can reinforce them by simply sending
your unconditional love to allow them
the most speedy orientation that is
possible for them you follow me yes they
are simply relearning a new
understanding of the way reality is
structured they are learning as quickly
as they can they will be just fine they
are as you say in good hands
great thanks thank you all right you yes
how do you have some suggestion about
how we can isolate for ourselves the
primary belief vibration that defines
each of us as a being all right now the
idea simply is once again to recognize
what is going on in your life and allow
what is going on in your life to show
you what the primary beliefs are within
you that you are examining at that very
moment then once you get in touch with them you
then once you get in touch with them you
can then know what the definition is and
if you do not prefer it redefine
it all you need to do is allow the
physical reality going on around you to
be an accurate reflection of the primary
belief you are working with at any given
moment the situations that occur in your
life as they occur are indicative of the
order in which you need to examine your
different beliefs
okay you follow me I do thank you you
then you going with um following in this line
you going with um following in this line
all right I've been dealing with an
issue that I would like to transform and
I would like to get at the primary
system of belief here so that I can
transform it what iss you okay this is
um regarding my work um I have created
in the past and I I gathered this
through other systems of belief
situations which uh where my Integrity
is questioned and um I
get told that I either I done something
that I didn't do which is this case or
um when I tell somebody about something
that somebody else does has done I am
not believed and the feeling that comes
up with me is I want to be I want these
people to believe me and in their not
doing so I have in the past lost jobs
over it I do not want to create that
this time because I am truly doing what
excites me the most all right and you
may still be creating a double check
system in your life for yourself
recognize that ultimately you are the
only one that can question your
integrity if you know you are
functioning within your integrity then
simply trust that the situations you are
attracting in your life are simply your
belief that you need to consistently
test whether or not within your own mind
you are functioning within your
integrity if this is simply a program
that is still running that serves no
purpose any longer then simply recognize
that you no longer need to test yourself
as to whether or not you are functioning
within integrity and therefore no longer
need to attract situations that bring up
this idea it is simply that you are let us
idea it is simply that you are let us
say running on excess
allow yourself to Center do not be so
fragmented do not be so ready to accept
the idea of the judgments placed upon
you from
outside as long as you continue to react
to them and choose to be upset by them
you are still buying stock in the
validity of those points of
view this is your opportunity to
recognize that if you truly believe that
you know what you are all about and
truly believe that you are functioning
within Integrity then even if you
attract a situation of that nature it
will not cause a reaction within you you
will simply say what you need to say to
represent the being you know yourself to
be and you will let it go with
that this can be also do not forget an
opportunity for these other individuals
to learn something as well not just you
so you may be co-creating a situation in
which you are willing to provide a
service to them by allowing them to see
how maybe they are very willing to judge
and invalidate other individuals all too
quickly and by simply being centered
within the being that you are you can
then attract the situation to manifest
and unfold in a manner that may point
this out to them wherein then they may
come back to you and say sorry we
understand while you were doing what you
needed to do all along my mistake you
follow me this is a two-way
situation not just all heaped upon you
poor you I don't want to come with with
victim and in fact I've been going in
the my girlfriend said in the opposite
direction all right then trust that you
truly are going in the opposite
direction and I've been I think to the
point of overtaking responsibility okay
why did I create this how did I create
this what is it supposed to serve all
right all right One Moment One Moment
One Moment now when we talk about
Moment now when we talk about
trust it does not necessarily have
anything to do with the idea of having
to analyze every single scrap of data
that comes into your
life you do not need conscious
analytical understanding of every single
event as a matter of fact you do not
need it for most events in your life
living your life out will allow you to
understand all you need to
understand if you had absolute conscious
analytical awareness of every single
circumstance and situation you would
never have a spontaneously unfolding
life you would be sitting there
analyzing yourself to
atoms stop chastising yourself because
you think you are incapable of
understanding you understand in whatever
way will let the life
unfold you will not have an
understanding on a level that will
impede your
acceleration which many times is a
conscious analytical understanding not
always but many
times in this way cease to invalidate
Yourself by assuming that you are not
picking up on what you need to be
picking up on if you simply know you are
functioning within your integrity then
simply act like it and stop berting
yourself for thinking that you are
not I I guess I wanted to understand so that
I I guess I wanted to understand so that
I don't have to keep repeating the same
lesson in my life but you aren't
repeating it that's the point you are
creating the illusion of a repetition
nothing repeats everything is always
different remember what we talked about
surface situations have no in inherent
meaning you are still assuming that they
mean the same thing just because it
appears to be the same thing on the
surface if you know you are different
then give it a different meaning simply
assume it has a different meaning do not
continue to assume it is a repetition
and then you will allow things to show
you how they have in fact changed you
are the one that is not letting it
change because you keep assuming that
what you see on the surface is a
repetition and it
isn't you keep giving it the same old
meaning don't give it the same old
meaning give it a meaning that is
representative of the new person you
know you are so just by by
my um and it does not even mean that you
have to have an absolutely cautious
analytical meaning to place to it simply
trust that it has a different meaning
now because you are now a different
person then eventually as you simply go
on with your life you will see how it is
different you do not have to have a
conscious understanding in the
moment simply live your life according
to the Integrity you know is there and
the events will synchronistically unfold
to show you how it is
different well when you were talking
about the systems of belief in the Echo
guys I was just wondering if I've been
buying into the the Echo and what I need
to do is change my basic syst of belief
so that the effect will therefore be
different or I change the effect so that
the fundamentally yes but the idea is
simply far simpler than you
think the situation is there to show you
that you are still invalidating yourself
and still giving old meaning to
apparently surface Old
Situation therefore you have now once
again been given the opportunity to
recognize that that what is what you are
doing you are exercising in that old
belief system if you are different then
exercise a new belief system that is all
the situation is there to show
you what belief system could I put in
instead to create it to be that it is
not a
repetition that it is something new that
things are playing out exactly as they
need to play out trust trust trust
because I know I am functioning in my
integrity and I know therefore that the
situations my life must be a reflection
of that inte integrity and cannot be
otherwise that's the new belief rather
than the old belief of oh yeah well I
must be still doing something wrong
these things keep happening I must still
be doing something
wrong that's the old belief now is your
opportunity to change
it you see many times you do not simply
realize what the old belief is because
it is far simpler than you think it
needs to be in order to call it a belief
system they are deceptively simple keep them
they are deceptively simple keep them
simple keep it right out in the open
right on the
surface I see I am reacting to the
situation I am reacting and therefore
basically fundamentally the situation
must have existed for the purpose of
showing me that I still
react in the old
way a lot of fear I mean of and
showing me how much this job has come to
mean to me and I do not want to lose
this job you can't lose
anything if you continue to place such
specific importance upon that need you
are the one that is pushing yourself
away from
it
relax if you know you are functioning
within your integrity and if you know
you truly are doing the thing that
excites you the most in life then trust
that you will continue to do
so if the situation changes then trust
it needs to change in order to allow you
to continue to do the thing that will
turn out to be the next most exciting
thing that you need to do not next in
terms of greater or lesser next in terms
of
order you follow me yes if the situation
changes then do
within that situation the most exciting
thing you can
do is any of this assisting you yes it's
assisting me I keep it simple keep it
simple trust that you are different you
simply are not trusting that you're
truly
different you're right I'm trusting this
I'm seeing the situation and judging
that therefore must mean that I'm still
doing this thing you yes as we have said
you are taking validation from the echo
rather than giving validation to
yourself to begin with you are
attempting to base your validity on the
existence of an
echo it has no substance you are the
original signal validate yourself and
then the Echoes you perceive will
reflect that original validation if the
Echoes you are perceiving are that which
reflects invalidation then the original
signal you are sending is also one of
invalidation you follow me yeah so at
this point basically to just let go and
not say or do it try to do anything more
to you always have the opportunity to
stand up and share what your beliefs are
State them simply State them honestly
State them clearly then go on about your
business act as if you truly believe you
are functioning within your integrity
and it will get
across if you walk away from a
situation acting as if they are
correct then you are only going to
reinforce the idea that you truly are
not functioning within your
integrity you follow me yes and I acted
I acted so emotional over the fact of
being accused that I you know I said to
them I'll swear on a stack of bibles if
you just believe me that I'm telling you
the truth that it didn't happen the way
you're telling me you see if you know
you are telling the truth then you do
not have to prove anything to
them period telling me that I do have to
prove it so you decide to listen to
them that is your
choice your proof prove is in being who
you are and how can you prove anything
to anyone anyway if they truly do not
want to see the proof they won't see it
no matter how much proof you attempt to
provide simply function within your
integrity know you are functioning
within your integrity you can comply to
within what you call reason to point out
that you have been functioning within
your integrity but set your own
standards set your own limits in that
sense there is no need to abase yourself
to their belief system in order to feel
that that constitutes proof of your
integrity because then you are not
functioning with in your integrity you
are attempting to live out their ideas
of what you should or shouldn't be doing
oh all right yes thank you so much thank
you very
much one moment you are next go ahead
first of all I'd like to thank you all
for creating these sessions I've been
listening to the tapes for about 6
months so I've been with you down in
Costa Mesa actually and it's had a
tremendous impact on my life in terms of
creating greater excitement joy and love
it's been very much fun sharing it with
friends and clients may I ask you a
favor will you share it a little more
loudly please my concern has very much to do
please my concern has very much to do
with your introductory remarks and
probably can be based in that I suspect
I think what has happened in listening
to your ideas I have been forming new
beliefs all right and what's happening
now is I'm attempting to integrate them
with a little difficulty with a series
of beliefs that I've probably had for
lifetimes as a none and currently coming
out of a yogic uh system of belief I see
which has to do with reverence for
Spirit surrender to Spirit uh as seeking
the higher will as opposed to the lower
will be done that kind of thing and
there is nothing contradictory in what
we are saying you are simply using
different semantics which perhaps has a
different understanding of the mechanism
the mechanism can be described
regardless of the symbols that are
utilized to represent it and the
mechanism will be found to be the same
for both ideas the ideas we are
presenting the ideas you have now just
outlined simply have one particular
mechanism though many individuals may
look at them in different ways and mean
them to represent different kinds of
action can you talk more about this
mechanism yes the idea simply is that
what you call surrendering and going for
the higher will as opposed to the lower
will in that way is simply the
understanding of centering within your
being surrendering is in a sense taking
control being control being fully
responsible for what you create in life
surrendering is going with the flow but
going with the flow means you then have
paradoxically given yourself the ability
to create what you
desire that means you are in control
surrendering is being in control it is
not giving up the idea of going with the
higher will as opposed to the lower will
is simply recognizing that you have free
will but that you can choose to express
yourself in a negative way or a positive
way and that you choose to experience
yourself in an integrative positive way
then you will be in synchronous harmony
with the higher Consciousness that you
are and you will be able to know that
you are in synchronous harmony with the
higher Consciousness that you are
whereas if you choose the negative way
what you call the lower will simply by
definition you may not know that you are
in synchronous harmony with the higher
Consciousness that you are you follow me
yes do you wish to
continue no I I knew that there would be
a way of integrating a way to hold all
of that I just wanted to hear you say it
thank you we thank you for bringing up
the idea for you will find that this is
of Paramount importance in your Society
at this time in each and every one of
you as you examine the different ideas
of belief systems that exist within your
Society will recognize that very often
where many different societies think
they truly disagree it is only a matter
of how they are calling the idea rather
than truly disagreeing on the
fundamental Basics many individuals do
not realize that what they purport to be
true within their system of reality and
what they report to be false within
someone else's system of reality is only
a difference of labels and nothing else
nothing else thank else thank
you
you then I want to explore that concept
of surrender because in our language in
our society it means giving up guys it
doesn't mean taking
control there is in some factions of
your Society a new understanding now being
Society a new understanding now being
applied to the term surrender we are
assisting in providing that
understanding you simply utilize as a
society that term because it is the
closest approximation to the idea that
you have in your
language it does not necessarily
precisely describe the mechanis ISM that
is involved but it is the closest label
you have absolutely closest there's no
better synonym for what the concept
you're trying to
convey let us scan
we find that the majority of the
references within the vocabulary of the
channel that are in your language will
all have to do with the idea of giving
up
control and thereby gaining greater
control ex thatly the idea we are saying
is that all of the reference words that
could possibly be used from your
language will all generally mean the
same thing as your colloquial meaning of
surrender you do not have a word in your
language that means giving up and taking control
that means giving up and taking control
at the same time but that's the concept
you're attempting to convey to give up
yes control and therefore gain greater
control no no no no no no no not to give
up control to give up
trying to give up trying to give up
trying to control is to have ultimate
control that does it that does it okay I
have another Paradox I'd like to uh
that's a parent Paradox for me that I'd
like to ask you about right in your
initial remarks and in my question
um well when you were answering the
other lady who said trust that
everything that's happening that you're
perfect don't look at the echo for
indications that there's something wrong
with you trust that you are doing fine
in your integrity so that's one concept
but when I asked the question you said
recognize that everything happening in
your life right now is a reflection of
what you may need to consider changing
yes just as her Echo is an opportunity
for her to get in touch with what the
belief system is we are simply saying
pay attention to it but do not seek your
validity in
it seek your validity in yourself then
the Paradox is
a person is valid and but nevertheless
there's room to change and grow of
course always but then when you change
and grow you become a different
validation and from your New
Perspective we have a tendency in our
concept of growth to look back on where
we were and think boy am I glad I'm here
and not back there it's all right with a
concept of but with you're suggesting
that that's what you can always
recognize the joy of being where you are
we are simply adding to the concept the
idea of allowing yourself to recognize
that where you are is
also in existence in your linear terms
because of where you were and thus where
you were is a part of where you
are so to truly invalidate where you
have been we are not saying that you
cannot appreciate where you are now
comparatively speaking but the idea is
not to invalidate where you were not to
invalidate yourself for being the you
you were then but to Simply recognize
that by validating the you you were then
that is what allowed you to be the you
you are now whereas if you had
invalidated yourself as the you you were
then you would still be that
you thank
you you I experiencing confusion in just
you I experiencing confusion in just
about all areas of my life right now
good yeah I thought you'd say that um
some of you remarks earlier on uh uh the
backdrop of one's reality my backdrop
actually has changed and um I think that
that's part of my confusion is that I
don't quite know what to do in it now oh
very good this is once again still to
some extent the limbo state in which you
have unplugged from your previously
conceived of structures and you have as
yet to plug into the idea of the new
structure so you are still examining all
the probable ways that you can create
that structure to be it may seem to be a
foundering state but that is simply
because you are not used to the idea
that change is truly the only constant
when you recognize that all the changes
that are going on that may make you feel
as if you are in limbo is truly a solid
foundation because you are now in touch
with far more probabilities than you
were before then you will be able to
find solidity within it and give
yourself a sense of direction now within
that limbo State once again the idea of
orienting yourself is always very simple
very simple do what excites you the most
at any given moment that you are able to
act upon well that worries me a little
bit because why well because uh I've
always um thought that I had to have a
job okay my belief system yes says I
have to have a job and yet I either look
I either leave the job or I get fired
and recently I've been fired in the last
three months from three jobs and all
right did you enjoy those jobs well
actually I got a lot done but but I also
didn't enjoy being in the office space
that I was in in all three well then I
wasn't doing got what you wanted didn't
you I did I wasn't enjoying it all right
and it wasn't that right there is what
we are talking about by taking that as a
sign that everything is working
perfectly you got what you wanted your
life always works always works when you
place invalidations upon yourself you do
not see that it is working that is the
only difference I do see that that I did get
difference I do see that that I did get
what I wanted and now um as I'm really
concerned oh concerned yeah I'm
concerned I don't then you are still not
willing to trust that your life is
working perfectly well it is working
perfectly then why are you concerned
because I haven't paid my
rent maybe you don't me
to
well oh she was about to consider it
just for a
second you are not as closed as you
thought that's true um if you truly
trust and are willing to do what excites
you the most you will have what you need
if you need the money to pay the rent if
that paying of the rent is what will
allow you to continue to be the thing
that excites you the most then being the
thing that excites you the most will
allow you to pay the rent if you can be
the thing that excites you the most
without paying the rent you won't get
the money oh God but that means you
don't need it because if you can be the
thing that excites you the most without
having to pay the rent then simply take
it for granted that that's not something
you have to worry about you will have
what you need you will be comfortable
because if you are not comfortable you
can't be the thing that excites you the
most one way or another you will be made
to be
comfortable it doesn't have to be having
to have money to pay the rent does it
can it not be that someone may simply
give you a place to live yeah well all
right all we are saying is that why not
open up to the possibility that another
Avenue can come to you rather than being
so insistent on the particular Avenue of
having to have money to pay the rent
because that's what closes the doors
that allows all the other things to come
to you perhaps even more easily than
having the money to pay the rent you're
right oh thank you that's
true I I did have a look at that and and
and you're right about that and I want
to ask you one thing about selflove and
that is there's I've had the most
wonderful experiences with people
recently and their Reflections are
absolutely beautiful as are you thank
you you are welcome now I'm wondering
why it is that I don't quite
understand why they
should like me or love me the way they
do because because you don't believe you
love yourself that much or that you are
worth loving well I think I am wor worth
loving then why is it a
mystery um are you willing to love them
oh yes well then why is it a mystery
that they love
you I'm not sure why it's a mystery then
it isn't one okay all right it's not a
mystery thank you you're welcome one
more thing and that is is I have a
constriction in my throat which occurs
at no predictable time that I'm aware of
and like I what is it you wish to do in
life um talk I
[Laughter] see I really enjoy talking well then
see I really enjoy talking well then
when you allow that to be the thing you
are and when you use
it as what excites you the most there
will no longer be a constriction will
there no when you let it flow you won't
constrict it it's czy that I don't let it flow all
it it's czy that I don't let it flow all
right then you're right let it flow and
there will be no
constriction may I remind you your
primary job in life is to Simply Be you
and that is a job you will never get
fired from you have it for
from you have it for
life well I do enjoy it all right then
enjoy it in whatever way you desire to
enjoy it enjoy it in the way that
excites you the most you will be
supported plain and simple
trust trust trust is all there is I
agree oh find
you thank you you're welcome yes in
relation to what the uh last girl was
just saying about her job situation
that's the last girl
yes so in doing that I realized on
Wednesday night that I had set up the
idea that the only way to pay the rent
was to do something that I didn't really
enjoy all right so when I realized that
that limitation that I had
created it immediately had served its
purpose and so the next day I left like
I gave in my notice for the job all
right so I just wanted to share that
with you that we do impose limitations
sometimes on ourself to show us no
kidding thank you for letting me in on
that you're most oh thank you very much
yes about this I remember an experience
I had many many years ago where uh I I
almost I almost died but this is it's
really a beautiful analogy to what
you're talking about all
right um it was in Pennsylvania there
was sort of a quarry there with a
waterfall that that it fell into some
very turning water and then it uh moved
over to the right and down in this long
shoot of water into a kind of a quiet
pool and um people were swimming in it
and they were used to doing it and it
looked very exciting so I jumped into it
I and um and into this changing water
and uh when I jumped into it it was very
changing indeed because I found that I
could not really keep my head on the
surface and I was getting tired very
rapidly and I began fighting it in an
effort to remain on the surface and
remain in control and of course my
because of that my uh was depleted very
rapidly and the only thing that I could
do um in my fashion was to register as
much Terror on my face as I
possibly to the person who was up on
this rock that I jumed off of and um to
register the idea that yes indeed I was
drowning and I I thought oh my God I'm
drowning I'm actually drowning I don't
think I want to do this and because
because I I got so tired from fighting
it I had to surrender I actually had to
surrender there was no choice the
current itself took me over to the side
and I thought oh God I don't want to go
down that long you know that long
stretch like a tube of water I don't
want to do that and um and the current
kept taking me over and I didn't quite
realize it but and I and I reached out
my hand and no one could grab it they
wouldn't grab it and there I started
going down that shoot that I didn't want
to go down down and it was that shoot of
water that actually kept me on the
surface and I just kept my feet up and
then I went down to this pool you get
the analogy what a beautiful
analogy and you will also find the
analogy that that is why many
individuals simply because they have
been taught no other way will continue
to try and try and try and try and
struggle struggle struggle struggle
until they get so tired they can't do
anything else but let go I do that all
the time um I do have one quick question um
time um I do have one quick question um
last week you mentioned something about
the um the mucus and my throat mixing
with milk um causing mixing with the
toxicity in there I would like to know
what the if you if you can tell what the
toxicity is you can do your research the
vocabulary does not exist within the
physical Channel you will find that the substance
Channel you will find that the substance
that you call the milk will create
toxins within the system and it will in
many ways reveal itself in the form you
call the increased production of the
mucus I see I thought you metioned it
that the toxicity of the milk was mixing
with another toxicity in my body that
was um causing this some of what you
call your milk does have toxicities I
see this has been going on about two and
a half months um and then the other
question is um there there's a thing I
got in the mail about whole brain
learning this guy John Davis has an
Institute a a doctor of whatever I don't
know many a doctor of
whatever and the reason I'm asking is
that he can be a doctor of whatever
whenever he
wants or caught my interest is that it
deals with whole brain learning or the
idea of blending those two sides of the
brain and it does this by having I
believe Seven Levels there there are
tapes involved and many other things but
there are many tools that can allow you
to recognize that you are one whole
Consciousness Avail yourself of whatever
you are attracted to but recognize that
all the empowerment and all the ability
is within you okay I just one is
subliminals is I suppose it's whatever
you consider it to be some some back off
on subliminal if you have a strong
belief that the idea can be more firmly
implanted within you through what you
call subliminal suggestion then that is
what will generally have a tendenc to
occur in your reality course all right
thank you thank
you um I'd like to pick up from a
convers conversation was happening
earlier all right regarding self love
unconditional love um all right self
love unconditional love I need speak up
all um in
my experiencing unconditional love I
started on a gradient with my dog which
was very easy oh then I moved up into my
close female friends and that was very
easy all right I've moved into other
gradients and they were very easy I'm
taking easiest of all of those groups
however I find and I'll put it one other
way I find that I serve as a reflection
to others in terms of unconditional love
all right and I find
that um when they flow unconditional
well I've already said that okay what
what problem or excuse me not problem
however I want to change it from a
problem to a situation and then I want
to change the whole belief system what
I'm getting at yes is there seems to be
when it comes to unconditional
selflove there seems to be this
incredible hard to believe that is
separation of self from
self there there seems to be self okay I
don't know okay just to put it very
simply thank you there is
an there is an enormous there appears it
appears that I have created the most
enormous barrier to self love I can love
in any other direction I can see others
loving others I can
receive love from others but when it
comes love from self to self
contradiction I am St contradiction
great well that's probably it so how how
can you help re receiving
love from others is giving love to
yourself yes I can have it on that
gradient but there's one moment I'll
tell you what the barrier is right now
you think in
gradients instead of
holes whole ideas whole
events if you think in gradients then
you have the possibility of creating a
gradient Beyond which a certain idea
will not proceed right if you think in
whole Concepts then everything simply is
where it needs to be all at
once and each and every event is each
and every other
event to give love is to have love to
receive love is to have love is to be
love it is all the same
thing wow there just seems to be
some huge amount of counter intention to
that occurring then you enjoy
gradients and you are learning something
from them then simply assume that you
have something to learn in the
exploration of the gradients and love
your gradients I prefer to change the entire
gradients I prefer to change the entire
belief system then it is
changed to have the ability to have a
preference to change it means it is
changed all you need to do is start
acting like you believe that you truly
have a preference to change
it and stop insisting that you have a
gradient within
you f something I had thought oh think I
thought of everything else all
right well thank you I'll I'll enjoy
that all right thank you very much if
you wish sleep on it I certainly will
thank you very much thank you you for
about 6 years I've been um trying to
control my life visualiz all right
trying okay
trying trying has it been tiring it's
been very tiring and I've been very
frustrated because yes well trying will
generally bring on frustration but I've
been told that you can change certain
things about your life yes by
visualizing it the way you want it to be
yes so I set up expectations for myself
if they don't happen and I go the hell
with it and I want to throw it all away
and now I'm just at the point where I'm
tired of swimming all right now
expectancy and expectations are two
different things expectancy
is what you need in your
visualizations that is simply the
knowingness that the idea you are
focusing on is truly representative of
the being that you are expectations many
times are actually invalidations and
judgments because you are saying if I
don't see it exactly this way then it is
not valid in any form you follow me many
times if you are not truly honest and in
touch with what your belief systems are
to begin with you will simply not allow
yourself to experience the manifestation
in the way that it could come to you
most easily you will remain insistent on
seeing it only in a particular way you
will create a stubbornness within you
that will not allow you to experience
any manifestation of it whatsoever until
you see it exactly the way you think you
need to see it and therefore you will
feel like you are not making any
progress right there are many different
manifestations many different ways it
can manifest if at
first your your exact visualization does
not manifest allow the way it has manifested
manifest allow the way it has manifested
to be the way it needs to to show you
what you need to get in touch with
within yourself to then restructure the
belief so that you can get closer to the
exact manifestation you follow me you are not
manifestation you follow me you are not
letting yourself learn from what happens
you are simply being
stubborn you follow yes all right now
also the idea of doing that requires
complete and total honesty with yourself
about what you truly believe you want
for many times the things that you are
visualizing for you do not really
want so get in touch with yourself on
that level as well and many times you
will find that the idea of a
visualization can simply be an overall
pattern that will point you in the
correct direction but does not
necessarily have to manifest literally
who knows it may actually happen in a
more Grand way than you were capable of
visualizing but since you insist upon
the visualization you also may not let
it happen in the grander
way well I'm I'm swearing off
visualization for a while you do not
have to Simply relax a bit about the
idea now
there are once again techniques that
many of the individuals in the room with
you tonight are aware of in particular
one that comes from the Consciousness
Lazarus that may be able to get you in
touch with the idea of visualization and
the idea of what your belief systems are
and this we can suggest to you and it
may be of some assistance but the idea
as you have already expressed it is to
relax for you see the idea is that if
you are trying too hard in the
visualization then you are not allowing it into your
then you are not allowing it into your
life you are trying to make it happen
you are trying to force it to happen and
when you do that you are invalidating
what is going on in your life right now
allow the visualization to occur do not
force it to happen or make it happen
allow it to
happen Okay treat it as a Daydream enjoy
it okay I can I can do that because it
sometimes it excites me so when it
excites me just do it yes follow your
own timing and trust your instincts in
that way then simply trust that you have
activated something let it be an
activation in whatever way it needs to
be simply be on the lookout for the
signals but do not put expectations on
what those signals must be right let
yourself be just as sensitive in the
intuitive way as to what they turn out
to be and that will give you the clues
to let you know how to home in on the
original visualization many times once again you
visualization many times once again you
will find that sometimes the original
visualization is not truly what you
wanted after all and the situation the
way it occurs can put you more directly
in touch with what it is you truly want
thus the visualization may change great
thank you very
much you
venue guys I have a question for Rosie
not here tonight all
right she has a problem with her knees
oh what a situation with her knees is
hurting her a great deal I see and she
said this used to only occur after she
did exercise like gardening or something
and today it started up when she was
just sitting at her desk at
work and she wants to know if um you
have the only suggestion we have at this
time is to examine the circumstances
going on around her at her job and her
particular attitudes toward the
situations that may be
changing to be aware of the Tendencies
of the shifts going on in her job and
see if she can create a correlation
between her attitudes about it and the
idea that she is creating in her
physical body thank you thank
body thank you thank
you m yes I um recently about two three
months ago situations in my life started
to fall in place very easily toward
things that excited me the most and
seemed to be very much in line then
abruptly they stopped and leaves me sort
of very
disoriented they have not stopped they
have only changed in an
unexpected way do not assume they have
stopped otherwise you are reinforcing
your inability to perceive them in the
manner they now present
themselves all right open up open up
open your vision
wider acknowledge more symbology than
you are used
to all right all right thank you thank
you you um all of a sudden I got to speak up
you um all of a sudden I got to speak up
all of a sudden speak up all of a sudden
a I saw a dolphin in your chair right
beside you a black
dolphin very
beautiful is there anything that there
is a blending of the energy you are
simply perceiving the idea oh and there
will be the idea of communication after
your break to some
degree thank you one moment
yeah hi B thank
you telepathic is Hell tonight
AR how are you doing much better thank
you K thank you yeah my pleasure um I
guess you were aware I came in and how
is your
heart doing better than it was all right
I laughter
thank you for your gift yeah you haven't
heard it from you for a while you a
little bit of time
as are you
relaxing yep beginning
to just put your feet up and make
yourself at
home you're a
doll thank you I don't know whether um
you know I created of course phenomenal
consternation which I'm sure
conation yeah yeah over the last two
days is that one of the countries on
your planet think it's one of the countries
planet think it's one of the countries
in my
plan yeah I think I
uh I'm going to dissolve the country all
right transform it into something else
allow trade to occur across the former
[Music]
border it will only enrich the overall
productivity of the entire planet that
you are the entire universe that you
are well I think I I want to address
this uh game just a little bit with you
all right it sounds like my friend
dreamfinder coming through later on that
would be neat dreamer dreamer
nice um I went in
um I went in
today to uh someone who is very caring
but also uh very dedicated in their path
and their Direction all right and very
lovingly uh invited me to consider that
uh I was going to lose the true path to
what I wanted to achieve and I took that
invitation created a lot of misery for
myself right and uh nice of you to
accept generous of you to accept the
invitation to their party
now you are tired from partying with
them [Laughter]
[Laughter]
so thank you very much Melle thank you
very much for allowing yourself to
Center and of course remember once again
that your truth is the truth their truth
is the truth the truth is all
truths once again if there were only one
way there would only be one person I
assume that if that individual had a
conversation with someone he considered
to be someone else then that in obvious
fashion indicated that there is more
than one
way say that one
again I didn't that last you an
individual finding themselves attempting
to convince someone else that there is
only one way is living a contradiction
for are communicating with someone else
and that someone else obviously is
another way yeah they don't recognize that
way yeah they don't recognize that
perhaps perhaps but then you can extend
them an invitation to your party as well
actually I did a pretty good job of
that I did a nice job then I walked
away invalidating um my worth oh I did that
invalidating um my worth oh I did that
so
well in every category that you can
conceive well we have said many times
that you are a world of Masters of
limitation very thank you master okay thank you m
very thank you master okay thank you m
you may all take a short break
all right I'll see
strawberry allow us to remind you simply
all s that many of the old Ryan
s that many of the old Ryan
ideas are simply present to allow many
of you to recognize how much you have
changed and and
please remember
always that when you make the decisions
for your life based upon what you
instinctively know to be true for you
please relax into the understanding that
the infinite Creator loves you
unconditionally no matter what you
choose anyway thank you thank you baby sharing
Bashar going back to your uh opening
statement this
evening on belief
systems is an individual
actually um creating a belief as they
have a sense of who they
are yesan okay so they surround
themselves with this system or this echo
which could also be not just ideas but
individuals yes okay same thing all
right right and as you change your
belief in who you are the individuals
around you will also change guys okay
whether they remain physiologically the
same or not they will change all right
so to become more in the present
time dealing in that present moment you
would then tend to which present moment
the present moment that you are in this
present moment this moment rather than
that present moment thank
you okay being in this present
moment focusing entirely
here and forgetting the past would mean
that those Echo wouldn't have any uh
support or any in a sense okay now I'd
like to using that
idea you yourself as a belief system
what is created here in the audience in
terms of a support system in
relationship to how you change every
moment the idea is that we simply know
we attract to ourselves the individual
idea belief system structures that are
representative of our capability of
assisting you in the Transformations
that you desire to take place upon your
planet we attract no one
else what about your belief
systems you are all an expression of my
belief system okay that's why you were
attracted here or we attracted as the
same both ways simultaneously each
attracted unto each it is a
co-creation all do you people go to
chall in a
sense since I am at one right
now GA in the room and go see somebody
they are not structured in that way no
we are simply open receptive to many
different forms of communication from
many different levels of consciousness
and in that sense you can say that's a
channeling for sure yay a while ago
during the early part of the talk you
mentioned that certain vocabulary was
not available in the channels memory
system could you not use mine or someone
else's in the room it can happen from
time to time but once again we are
dealing with also let us say through the
belief system of the physical Channel as
well M and is that because say you tune
simply with that particular identity
basically it will begin to transcend
some of these ideas in time but it will
be at a rate that is comfortable for the
physical Channel as well now and then
let us say colloquially when the
Channel's guard is down we can extend
our understanding into many of the
belief systems that you represent as
well now and then that's wonderful it
will happen more often and more often
when there is more of a focus in this
direction on the part of the
physiological Channel as well as you
know you're freely uh free to use mine
at any time oh yes thank thank you for
your offering you um I was I was listening to
offering you um I was I was listening to
another Channel called by the name of
John and they were saying that since
love is the closest thing to what we are
to express it and I'm love is what you
are made of
yes is what we made of yes love is what
you are and to express it um if we're
not expressing it then what are we
doing thank you in a sense you are
always expressing it since you are made
of Love Every Act is an act of love but
the idea is that if you are functioning
in that expression through your
integrity then generally you are aware
and in synchronous Harmony as the
representation if you are not
functioning within your integrity then
nobody knows what the situation is about
consciously and in that way you run into
what you call communication gaps about
what it is you are doing as a
service because when I think about it
I'm thinking well I mean what's love to
me might not be love to someone else or
how do you know if you're really
expressing that idea all right this is
why we use the term Integrity
integration once again the ideas of
right wrong good and evil and many
different symbols and relationships and
terminologies within your Society are
simply value judgments and in this way
as you have said one individual may feel
that something is an act of love and
another may
not therefore we simply refer to the let
us say more precise definition of
positive or negative expression positive
generally being representative of that
which integrates or gathers together
into a whole and negative generally
being indicative of that which separates
segregates or
limits into
components now if you find an individual
expressing something to you in that way
that allows you to be integrative within
that relationship then it can be said
you are receiving a positive expression
if an individual is offering you an
opportunity to experience separation
segregation and limitedness then either
way the offering is one that is negative
intrinsically you follow me I gu both
are still expressions in a sense of Love
since even the negative offering can
allow you to have an experience from
which you can learn and grow but that is
your decision depends on how you look at
it how you take
it also I was thinking basically the
expression that you call love generally
is referred to as the positive
expression because once you have the
positive in integrative expression then
you are consciously harmoniously aligned
with creation rather than unconsciously
aligned love lets you
know that you deserve
love in that
sense negative Expressions usually do
not bring with it an understanding of
deserv ability or connection to a
Unity does that assist you
um yes I think so cuz I was getting
quite confused we are simply once again
dealing with semantics and the
terminology of your language I also I
thinking that um if you don't judge
someone that's not an action so in a
sense it's not really giving it's it's a
perspective of your point of view you
can have an observation so to speak
without creating an invalidation yes and
so but that's not really an act action
of giving
of what they say giving love it's it's
just a point of view in a sense yes but
in that way it is an allowance of that
being as they are and to some degree
that is an act of
Love okay identifying I Define um love
for me at this moment as a willingness
or even an eagerness to experience or
pervade that vibration all right many
individuals operating through lack of
Integrity still have an eagerness to
experience very exciting
things but you see what I'm saying
someone says I love you yes what they're
saying there
in is they're willing to be that
vibration yes it is generally speaking a
participatory action that expands
Integrity adds together so that as you have said
adds together so that as you have said
the sum becomes more
than just the parts in
combination you follow me mhm
mhm
you thanks okay um I really I looked at
the dissertation or discussion we had
about gradients guys and I realized when
it comes to the unconditional let's say
the selflove
area um it looks as if it's All or
Nothing when it comes to unconditional
selflove All or Nothing well if it's not
gradiance it's either a total self-love
or there appears that there is an
absence of self-love now I would like to
experience just for a moment for
starters or more if it occurs what it
would be like to remove all judgment all
expectation all right and for a moment or more I'm
all right and for a moment or more I'm
totally willing to have more and have it
in an infinite stand
[Laughter] up turn around three
up turn around three
[Laughter]
times sit
[Laughter] down thank you stand up sit
sit
down say something anything anything
thank you are you beginning to get the idea of
you are you beginning to get the idea of
spontaneity yes you do not have to ask
if you could take off your shoes you
simply take off your shoes you follow me
absolutely all right now the idea is
that in living in the moment that
analogy can suffice for allowing you to
Simply recognize that as you go with
your flow in a spontaneous way then and
you are simply in full trust full
centering and what needs to be there is
there do you think that when we come
through the
channel the so-called dissertation that
we give you at the beginning of the
session is something that we have
planned I what what my reality is I've
thought about that and what seems real
to me is that you are perceiving the
mass conscious of this room and what is
most pertinent at that very moment when
you begin to speak what is most needed I
have absolutely no idea what I am going
to say until I say it right and I I just
get the idea that you you just tune in
the room to the people in the room and
you get what is needed because well I
personally feel that you're talking to
me but I know all the rest all right it
is even in a sense more centered than
that because the idea is not
specifically that I tune into the people
in the room and say what is needed I
tune into myself and say what feels true
to myself to say trusting implicitly
that what I will say because I am
co-creating this interaction will be
what the people need to
hear thank you for Shing
that that is the idea completely of
everything is synchronous
that is the idea of trust acting upon
your instinct acting upon your instincts
within Integrity that will allow you to at any
Integrity that will allow you to at any
given moment know what you need to know
when you need to know it not before not
after thank you very much don't you have
an idea of what you're going to say when
something in the world happens such a b
spal dister or something like that we
pretty much have an idea that something
would be said about it if I choose to
create the idea of making myself aware
of that event in that way then there can
be a spontaneous Creation in that sense
however I do not formulate the
methodology of how I will share this
idea with you I do not necessarily even
formulate the idea that it will be
shared simply once again in the moment
of the interaction comes all the
understanding that a it is to be shared
and be how it will be
cared that does not mean I am not aware
of the idea before we speak of it but
what I am not aware of is how we will
speak of it you follow me yeah thank you
are we finished for you tell
[Music]
me I will
wait well
I'm okay I'm
wanting up I'm I'm wanting to tie
in everything that just occurred so that
so that um I can feel that we have
completed the interaction and oh what is
it that must happen for you to feel that
way what in your imagination will have
occurred to allow you to feel that the
interaction has been
completed well what I had in mind when I
introduced this idea
was find
of I would
well oh very well
said that came through the
clearest but it was a
spontaneous reflection of what you truly
felt in the moment
yes and therefore it was full of
wisdom you see you can do it perhaps
it's just being too analytical maybe
Effy all the time no maybe oh effort I
would [Laughter]
[Laughter]
just it's just just I just love to
experience the idea and talking about it
is not the same thing as experiencing it
as we both well know y yeah love without
any judgment just to see what it's like
just to see what it's like just
initially you see because once I
experience it and I'm being it all right
all right let me ask you a question if I
may oh thank you very
much can you give me one reason why you
shouldn't give yourself unconditional
love not in front of all these people
yes you see because I tell you this I asked
you see because I tell you this I asked
you that question at this time because I
know that you will not be able to come
up with one that I will
accept go ahead do your
best not one reason that you have for
not loving yourself will hold any water
with me
well I I will say oh come
on lose your imagination the things I'm
tempted to say I think all fall into the
category of backdrop backdrop what
remember what we were talking about
before background or back no I
forgot now are you simply taking the
terminology that we used and adding it
to your gradient or does it really mean
something to you well I I think anything
that I
volunteered um you would probably say
that it's not in the moment so oh so you
will not even attempt so what difference
does it make oh all right you tell me
what difference does it make the
difference it makes is that you will
have done it and that will be a
spontaneous now action have you ever
done anything in your life spontaneously
at all anything at all yes then did you
not realize that in that moment you
utterly trusted and therefore utterly
Unconditionally Love
yourself um oh maybe just a
could yes I don't think I ever put those
together well now you
can see that's what I'm talking about I
find myself living in the past so much
even in the way I'm talking you cannot
live in the past you can think about the
past all you want but you can't live in
it right and the times I have been most
centered I've had most of present past
or future I was just there perhaps the
difficulty if I may borrow that word for
a
while is in having a particular
expectation about what you think it
should feel like to be
centered and constantly judging yourself
to be out of Center simply because of
your definition I have had some I have
had a
few very very very special experiences
like that all right One Moment One
Moment let me remind you of something let's get
let me remind you of something let's get
down to Basics shall we shall we yes all
right in all reality fundamentally
ultimately you are always
centered always always always
always you have to be completely
centered you have to be a complete
Creator in order to be able to create a
scenario in which it seems you're out of
balance so you have always been centered even
so you have always been centered even
when you have used your Mastery to
create the illusion that you are not why
would I want to do that then you tell me
to learn to learn to learn what that you
don't prefer right all right then
recognize that you are centered
recognize you are centered then and stop
assuming you're not if you have learned
the lesson stop living it live something
else
does is it necessary to figure out what
the lesson was there to teach or whatever in
lesson was there to teach or whatever in
other words we just figured it
out that I don't choose to be that one
anymore yes right keep it simple if you
need any more conscious analytical
awareness than that you'll get
it keep it
simple okay again look at it the other
way if you wish simply think of a real
good reason why you simply can't go on
why I can't go on why you should hold
yourself into the idea of the old
pattern why you cannot simply allow any
reason to be good enough to change the
idea rather than say no no no I'll stay
in this format until I dig out the real
reason now there may be one that you
have manifested to be more the real
reason than any other
reason but any reason will do if you are
willing to use that reason to go ahead
and then again paradoxically as soon as
you go ahead it will probably occur to
you what the old real reason was because
you will be in a more expanded point of
view it will give you a broader
perspective and the broader perspective
will allow you to understand what it was
you were doing back
then you see the idea is all you need to
do is to keep living your life to have a
complete understanding of everything in
it but if you stop and wonder stop and
Ponder stop stop stop stop stop I will
not go on until I understand this that
and the other thing then you will never
go on when you simply go on knowing you
will ultimately understand this that and
the other thing when you need to then
you will simply go on this that and the
other thing will not hold you back and
ultimately you will understand why you
didn't know this that and the other
thing back then but why you know it
now sometimes there is so much judgment
occurring that I find myself stopped
absolutely dead in my tracks I mean I
don't even feel as if it's living or
that I am going on except by the linear
definition is that the U you still are
or is that the U you used to be that's
the you I used to be all right then
don't talk as if it is the you you still
are good it's just this is what we mean
when we say if you know you have
changed act as if you have trust it and
act as if you have changeed don't keep
talking like the old person what if the
words don't
come okay I've been going through
something similar where I'm feeling many
many different feelings inside okay and
when a person talks to me before you go
on May I remind you of something yes a
feeling comes after a
belief if you have a feeling that's a
reaction to something you already
believe to be
true the feeling doesn't come first the
feeling can show you what the belief is
that created the feeling but the feeling
does not come
first that created the feeling but the
feeling does not come first the belief
is there maybe invisibly because you
have put it in your unconscious or
subconscious mind so when you have a
feeling the feeling is the mechanism
that allows you to bring the belief to
the conscious surface
because the feeling is a reaction to a
belief you already
have now does that change something
about what you are going to
ask um no it doesn't doesn't match what
I'm feeling go
ahead
um I've been um as you said last weekend
um all the expect ations are
gone and that rigidity the rigidity with
how I was functioning that's
phys and
um so I'm open and I'm feeling feelings
and they're
wonderful and there's a part of me that
and there's a part of me that
well the feelings feel
good and there's a place where I want to
stop them
because the belief is that they're
overwhelming but they're not all right
obviously they're
not and
um when I find myself in in interacting
with people
y I get a little scared because I feel
like if I'm going to let out my mouth
what I used to let out of my mouth then
I'm going to be in an old interaction
and I don't want to do that anymore so I
but is that what you truly instinctively
feel like letting
out no all right I I bring myself more
to the interaction and I allow myself to
feel more than I've ever felt before
that's all right good so you are saying
you have a belief that you might slip
and say something you used to say well
all right so what if you do say oh well
that was the old me or or perceive that
how another person's reacting to me is
yeah is the same old way that I used to
is the same old way that I used to
perceive things well so what do you
prefer to think in those terms no well
I'm starting
to this must be catching ass
um how do you feel right
now
um here here you feel here yes all
right then would you
enjoy staying
here yes then do so yes I am all right
and remember all right I've always wanted to
remember all right I've always wanted to
say that you now you
have what did you say well bash always
said um let me tell you this I've always
wanted to jump in and say A Kiss is Just
a Kiss and now she
have
thank when you talk about yourself in
Parts you
reinforce the belief that you have a
part that can mind the rest of you when
you think of yourself as a whole then
the idea that you prefer to be will be
true for the whole of you and you will
not contain a part that does something
different right and to think that you do
means that you are wholy being another
idea other than what you say you prefer
to be
all right yes thank you
kisses the if feeling if feeling comes
from belief yes then then knowingness is
that before belief yes so then the
knowingness is that the connection to
the higher you want to call it
higher there is existence knowingness
belief emotion thought in the colloquial
sense of the term thought meaning mental
activity again knowingness comes after
existence existence is first then
knowingness then belief then emotion
then physical
thought is that a
condensation in a sense it is the First
Fundamental indication of the separation within the
indication of the separation within the
Oneness first there is the Oneness the
existence the all that is for that to
know itself invokes the first
separation because then it creates a
reflection and therefore in that Way
knowingness Comes secondary to existence
itself which is simply
Oneness then the
knowingness breaks down into different
modalities of knowing different
expressions of knowing which manifest
themselves in physical reality as the
different belief systems I know this of
myself then the emotion the energy
motion that activates it in physical
reality then the thoughts that are the
representations of your perceptions of
what you have created the reflections
The Echoes so to work our way back we allow
Echoes so to work our way back we allow
our feelings so we can get in touch with
our beliefs so we can work back through
to knowingness yes are beliefs like
knowingness with a little doubt on it
yes in one way of saying yes they
are specified knowing that as for a
particular purpose at
hand thank you thank
you I want to ask you a couple areas oh
couple of areas I want to hear more
about I want to hear more about what
what you experien things that in your
world in your life such as well things
like um uh I mean if you wanted to fly your
um uh I mean if you wanted to fly your
body around or or experience anything
like that or yes this is beginning to
occur in our civilization quite a bit as
we are transcendental for fifth from
physicality to non-
physicality can you wear Superman soup
for
sure if we wish
you know your counter selves that are
manifestations of the same
overs at this point truly in a sense in
our society everyone
is but you had spoken of Ana as a the
idea at that time was simply directed in
the sense of our particular purpose but
in an overall sense everyone in our
society is a part of the same oversold
you experience that Unity yes even
though you have
individual manifestation yes we
experience the unity through the
feelings of unconditional love that we
have for every single being in our
society you follow
me yes but I was what I was driving out
was if I could understand
your experience on a if you will day
today basis the degree to which you
experience your integration with the
mass Consciousness well it can occur in
many different ways some of which are
not dissimilar to the way you experience
it it is simply that we recognize it for
what it is when we see it whereas many
times you don't the idea simply is that
anyone we interact with is there for a
reason and we take it as a reflection
and we take it as a different aspect of
the counterpart over Soul self feeding
back to us what it is we need to look at
to allow ourselves to grow in the manner
we have chosen to be
we still respect the individual in that
sense we do not in your terms disinherit
their individuality but we also at the same
individuality but we also at the same
time recognize them to be an aspect of
ourselves that we need to
see we simply recognize everyone as the
expression of synchronicity they each
chose to be for everyone
else okay are is there a real difference
between men and women male and there is
an OD obvious to your terminology
physiological difference a how about in
terms of energy or roles in your Society
not so
much um is
it what about this whole idea of
blending the male and female within
ourselves yes as we blend them do we
then become more
neuter in one sense of the word
perhaps but in a sense not really if you
choose to maintain an individuality
expression in that sense you would still
perceive though each and every
individual male and female in our
society is the Blended marriage of the
male female principle within themselves
him or herself you would still
experience our energy as either
distinctly male or distinctly female and
why is that simply because that that is
how we choose to express ourselves
relative to the ideas we wish to be in
the universe in which we exist because
it also is very assistive in
communicating with societies like your
own that are still very much in the
middle of exploring their polarities and
it assists them in giving them an anchor
point but then that's a purpose you have
a purpose for maintaining oh yes of
course separation but in the general
progress it take away that purpose then
it would be mostly
neuter what does neuter feel
like much like the idea of Simply being
non-corporeal although you will find
that in your system at first you will
still retain a high degree of identity
to the idea of your last
Incarnation not so with us so that the
quote differences between men and women
are Anchored In
physiological differences basically they are simply
differences basically they are simply
the polarity Expressions that exist
within the soul as a
unit expressed in physical terms
expressed in the dimension that does
experience the polarities in separate
ways but in non-physical reality that
polarity wouldn't be there it would not
be perceived as such
no but is there not a positive and
negative concept or energy in the universe for a
concept or energy in the universe for a
non-physical reality in a sense yes but
it is not perceived as you perceive
polarities from your dimensional point
of view there is not necessarily exactly
the terminology to be able to explain
this to you it is simply an experiential
thing you will understand it when you
get there well for right now um my my
there well for right now um my my
feeling is if I may contribute this of
course um that as we blend the male
female energy within us we can express
both freely and we are comfortable
expressing both as the the
characteristics that we consider to be
masculine Expressions as feminine as as
well nice bash would you quickly or slowly U
nice bash would you quickly or slowly U
give us a little of your impression of
our plans for the December 31st
when we are going to
be integrating the idea of world peace
in synchronous Harmony all around the
world with everyone focusing on this
idea obviously it will have an
effect there is nothing I need to say in
that regard it will obviously have an
effect because it is an expression of
your willingness and it will make a
willingness and it will make a
difference and it will create an add to
the overall acceleration that you
experience upon your what Yes actually
my idea was in thinking about this that
it's a physical Universe expression to
show ourselves that we've already made
this decision and I think it's very
exciting and uh creative way for us to
do that thank you true also I have
another thing I'd like to share um the
idea of expectancy I was looking at
recently and it seems to me that that
idea is the feeling that a child would
have expecting a birthday they know
something wonderful is going to happen
and they just tune in the idea of
abundance they have no specific
expectations necessarily but feeling of
excitement a beautiful analogy and
expectation and I had a very lovely
present recently because my cat who was
non-physical for about a year is now
physical again and it's so exciting I
mean obviously it's a different body but
it's exact exactly like the first one
and how she did this it must have been a
wonderful co-creation because is very
natural I love it and it just makes me
realize all over again that the present
is not the result of the past thank you
one
moment there is now a bit of blending
between us it will remain in this
fashion for a while if you wish to
address the idea is through our
Consciousness to the aspect you call
dolphin consciousness of dreamer
dreamer hello old friend will we sing
your song will we sing yours um I want
to propose a little project with us the
first world uh Open Sea Marine World in
which we're going to build a little
Stadium up Beyond The Breakers and you
Dolphins can come in and agreed upon
times if you so agree we will
attend lovely lovely
um many such interactions taking place
upon your world at this time of course
and uh uh suggested uh potential
sequence uh would love to meet with you
down in the mai area with some of course
with some of your uh friends as I
realize your body is out in uh New
Zealand so would enjoy meeting with some
of your friends can you suggest uh uh
time location how we could make this
synchronous will be
arranged you will not
miss you will see lovely thank you for
that see you then a dreamer a um I feel
an S an amazing connection to you or to
some entity with the group now would
that be from the Lan times or is
connected atlan is connected serious
energy is connected AR tourus energy to
some degree is connected luran energy as
well all of these overlap and connect at
this time many different representations
of interaction taken place in time past
with regard to your representation of
us much interaction at lanting times
individuals with dreamers with what you
call Dolph and
Consciousness Early times at last
times many human many dolphins share
same dream interchange body form many
time Incarnation as each other many time
back then that's wonderful not so much
then that's wonderful not so much
now happening rare can happen more time
to
come yay thank
you do you know about the project at
Santa Cruz for Dolphin Research
University California Santa
Cruz Define uh they're going to get start a
Define uh they're going to get start a
project up there of dolphin research and
communication we in touch with
Consciousness dreamers
Malibu area will move up down your Coast
some participate in that
area some not
but some will this be a good project to
work on you
on you
enjoy yes then
good hey can you share a dream with us
[Music] dream share sign dream share
dream share sign dream share
before all right yes
W dreamer at one time be very excited
see all friends all
time swim to each friend when get there
very excited to swim off the other
friend not spend time with any one
friend so busy being excited about
seeing all friend all
time so all friend get together say we
feel your love we feel your desire for
interaction all time we decide to swim
with you together all time in same dream
original dolin say no friend that
restrict your
freedom friends say no we choose to be
same dream
we free together to be same dream each
of us go where others wish to go all be
free together at same time
synchronicity begin idea gather together all
begin idea gather together all
Consciousness
so original dolphin be with friend all
time Gathering Together Consciousness
together all dolphin become one being
manifest Incarnation you call
whale that iidea you call
well physical manifestation
dolphin representation higher
Consciousness Gathering Collective
Consciousness Manny dolphin is whale
that our story in your term me in your
term energy love
dream thank
you we share same dream more more
participation more more interaction
physical take place more more we invite
you invite we share we be together we do
we participate we enjoy have fun you
continue have fun same dreams together
share [Music] we
we
hey um I am having to face a lot of
choices in my career and I love the fact
that I have the choices to make all
right there is no need for difficult
decisions one once again simply examine
and ask yourself honestly which one
excites you the most act on that if two
or more feel like the same level of
excitement then that's your indication
it doesn't matter which one you choose
if you choose one and the level of
excitement in any of the other ones
changes then go back and choose that one
if it is in your terms greater than the
one you have chosen it is always very
simple and easy to tell which path
represents the path you chose to be
simply follow the one at any given
moment that excites the most that you
are capable of acting on if it changes
follow the
change they do not need to create
difficult
decision the one that excites me the
most is the one that doesn't appear to
offer any Financial
appear
appear appearance as you say can be
deceiving the idea is to understand again that if
the idea is to understand again that if
the one that excites you the most
excitement being the vibrational
representative of the path you chose to
be thus excitement being the thing that
will let you truly be yourself if the
one that excites you the most which is
to say the one that lets you truly be
you is obvious then by definition it
must bring with it whatever level of
abundance is necessary to allow you to
be that thing the universe does not do
pointless things you would not be
excited about something that couldn't
support you to allow you to do
it you follow me yeah all you need is
the trust that is
it it is the only ingredient necessary
to allow you to derive complete and
total abundance from the thing that
excites you the most and simply trust
that at any given moment if the
excitement shifts to something else
which on the surface may not seem to be
connected follow the excitement we do
not mean to be flighty truly listen to
the excitement make sure you are not
running from something thinking oh this
is more exciting when in fact this is
more exciting but because of your
invalidation of yourself and your
capability of doing it the excitement
May translate as great fear or
anxiety be truly honest about the idea
that is most exciting to you the one
that strikes a cord do it at any given
moment do it trust the excitement the
excitement is always there to let you
know that you are squarely on the path
you chose to be not that you can really
be off of it but that you will be in
synchronous conscious Accord with it and
let it flow most easily when you follow
your excitement you follow me yes trust trust
excitement you follow me yes trust trust
trust abundance is simply once again the
ability to do what you want to do when
you need to do it it does not have to
come in the form you call money if that
is the easiest way it will take the path
of least resistance and that will be the
way it comes if the path of least
resistance is not money then trust that
you will have whatever you need let your
life become a series of
surprises you don't want it to be
boring all right once again do not
create it to seem so for there are no
boring situations as we have said only
bored Minds let yourself recognize that
Minds let yourself recognize that
everything that will come to you by
being who you truly know yourself to be
will bring with it the same same degree
of
ecstasy that needs to be there to allow
you to continue to function as the being
you chose to be
effortlessly smoothly smoothly
joyfully
ecstatically all right yeah thank you
recognize if you wish one more time the
idea of a
wonderful wonderful coincidence in your language
wonderful coincidence in your language
once you are
moving you are
exatic you follow
me thank
you been having a lot of trouble with my
health one
moment back up that
reel you got that out so
fast I've been having a l trouble with
[Laughter] help you have been experiencing
help you have been experiencing
manifestations of your belief system you
have not been having any trouble at all
for you are manifesting exactly what is
the reflection that you believe to be
true no
trouble can you help me unlock this
belief system Maybe
what have you chosen to
experience he in what way in what form
in what
areas of my body or just yes like
allergies like allergies for how long
year a year mhm all right is that it um
the reproductive organs human organ all
right is that
it yes thank you have you already I will
assume Avail yourself of what you call
your typical medical
practitioner yes and what have you been
told stress all right do you believe
it I believe I've created it for myself
all right do you believe that what has
created it is simply
stress it's my belief system that's
created it yes we know that but it's
stress is a representation of the belief
system do do you believe you are under
stress yes
why you tell
me we will tell each other at the same
time this whole idea is not about as we
have said feeding you slices of bread it
is about allowing you to learn how to
bake bread to feed
yourself all right
now in what way do you feel yourself to
be stressed in
life what is it you believe causes you
stress taking care of myself taking care of
taking care of myself taking care of
yourself right functioning every day
functioning my
mind so you feel that you are not able
in a sense to continuously and
effortlessly reproduce yourself as you
desire to
be which I'm getting tired it's
beginning boring all right I have to do
something else now what would you like
to do be just be free to now what would
allow you to be free if you could do
anything at all that you wanted what
would you choose to do and know that
when you had chosen to do it you would
automatically feel free go on use your
imagination What would it be anything at
all pick one pick two pick three I don't
care I'd like to quit working and just
study go to school study what medicine
medicine oh all right that interests you
yes yes how will you apply your
knowledge by helping others overcome
what I'm in the process of overcoming I
see do you understand of course that A
Healer is simply someone who allows
another individual to see a reflection
of their belief system in that first
individual and allows the other
individual the typical patient to
actually do the healing on themselves
yes all right then good
doctor why not be your first patient I'm
working there is no need to work on it is that
there is no need to work on it is that
what you will tell your patient no I'm
working on
it but doter I'm in pain can't you do
something anything at all go away don't
bother me I'm working on it
it
now let's play a little scenario all
right are you willing yes will you have
a good time yes thank
you let us assume right now that you are
the Healer call it a doctor if you wish
it does not matter all right you are now
the Healer that you are quote unquote
planning to become right now you are
that healer you have gone through
whatever you have desired to go through
to become that healer it is all in your
past you are now the Healer all right a
patient comes to you with exactly the
symptoms you have now or had then before
you became this wonderful
healer what would be if you truly had
this patient before you now truly
imagine this patient is before you
speaking right to you what would be your
first idea that you would share with
them what would be your first
instinctive information to calm them down all right
information to calm them down all right
how
how I do it physically or what would I
say anyway you come up with do not
question me about the idea of giving you
a way or a methodology how do you you're
the doctor how do you feel like calming
them
down well I would use acupuncture to
bring them to bring their body energy
into balance so that they could start to
experience a sense of calmness and then
start to trust themselves all right so
you're saying that you believe that this
patient will acknowledge the idea of the
acupuncture yeah all right because you
believe that you have attracted someone
who would be similar to your own belief
system yes all right have you done
acupuncture on yourself oh myself I had
it done too me all right same
thing did it assist you at all
tremendously all right in this way then
are you saying that in your terminology
the pain has returned
it does
return and then it and then I have
another treatment and it leaves all
right in your terminology how long are
you without the pain in between
treatments it is relative to how calm I
there all
right can you at any given moment
recognize that you can give yourself an
imaginary acupuncture treatment yes can
you allow it to do the same thing yes
then why don't
you I if I will all right if that is the
way to allow yourself to cool out then
do so trust your imagination it is there
for a reason it is there to allow you to
draw from any idea you require to Center
your being now as you already know as a
being now as you already know as a
society one very beneficial and very
quick way of relaxing is to
laugh when you are under tension why not
simply laugh at all the tension You'
have gotten yourself
into thank you I remember that all right
our suggestion simply is in general when
you find yourself in a situation that
typically you say you do not
enjoy well then get into it if you're
going to have misery and and fear have
the best misery and fear you can have
really live it up become melodramatic
about it and pretty soon you will be
having such a good time that the misery
and fear will be a thing of the past
thank you I'm good if you need
some that will help me thank you very
much
you uh I'm also involved in in working
with healing in people yes and
um right now currently working with
something that I I'm holding my hands on
the most activated or depleted centers
of the body in order to stimulate the
body to balance its energy flows all
right and um I've been I've been
actually talking to patients for a long
time half an hour maybe sometimes before
I start to treat them to watch them and
they eventually activate more fully it
seems yeah it's all right their patterns
yes uh which leads me to uh find out
what most of their disease is before I
treat them I hold my hands on those
points of their body and they release
that and it's usually permanent and I
can build from there with them so you
are saying synchronistically that you
may also be able to be of service to
this individual if she is willing to
participate yes that's not what I had in mind when I
yes that's not what I had in mind when I
mentioned this but yes why not no right
therefore you can Avail yourselves each
of the synchronicity of you having the
Healer you require and you having a
patient course and um if that is enjoyable what
course and um if that is enjoyable what
of
course and recently i' I've switched
that a little bit in order to just Begin
by treating them and then communing with
them in the joy of the release
afterwards right and working with their
belief systems to a positive adrenaline
positive change oh very good and so I'm
asking a little bit at in the beginning
here of my questions um if you see both
of them as being an important part of
the of the procedure or if there may be
a way in order to streamline this to be
more effective to help more people in a
shorter period of time you are the
procedure that's true be the way you
wish to be that excites you the
most those will be the individuals you
attract who are capable of availing
themselves of the procedure that you are
and that is what will streamline your
encounters thank you that's important um
in sometimes when I'm working with
people I will have them at a certain
position where I'm treating them and
I'll project things from my conscious
mind such as love forgiveness Joy
gratitude you see projection as being a
form of hypnotism in a way that it may
not be advantageous to do for a patient
or do you find it as let us simply say
that if you believe that you are
projecting with your integrity and that
nothing is going to be forced upon them
then you will only attract the so-called
patient that will Avail themselves of it
in a manner that will be beneficial for
them and no other
way that is also a whole part of the
belief system that you are we don't have
to break this down into pieces you
follow me I understand you mentioned a
while back about whole brain and I I
have often felt that half brain I I
actually feel that left and right brain
is partly the pathological process in a
sense so that the whole brain is the way
to be it okay thank you for agreeing
with me on
that let's see
um since we are all antii lives and the
as I understand it the patterns that we
build our cage so to speak of of our
belief systems around us are basically
entities divic lives or what have you
invoked into an activity and they become
patterns in our bodies well all right
that's one way to look at it although
from our perception it is a little
perhaps backwards okay in order not in
the idea of judgment understand is it
possible to I feel it's possible to
communicate with these entities of and
release their pattern positions in the
etheric web to free the etheric body
pure communion and communication in the
cosmic human scheme yes because they are
only extensions of your Consciousness
anyway can you give some advice as to
how to freely communicate with them and
allow for us to have more three use your
imagination they are only extensions of
your Consciousness use whatever methodology
Consciousness use whatever methodology
seems releasing to you may I com
absolutely thank you if I may say so
sometimes just light visualization you
know directed light be yes yes many
different methodologies are available to
you that is why your imaginations are so
free whatever strikes the cord within
you as the w to do it will be
representative of your best way of
relating to that idea trust your
imagination and act upon
it yes I on this too all right
briefly is it a truth to you
that we if the Pres if the present isn't
a result of the past yes that these
patterns we create the patterns in the
now to experience working with them to
release them so we it's just a choice to
have the pattern that's it thank you to
finish up
um since you were so wonderful at
releasing certain energies into someone
I know closely and now he's no longer
going to work for me anymore can you
find me in your employee in
mon what about the good doctor that
sounds like a great great
idea my uh my last question you'll
attract whatever you need to attract I
understand I know
and you talked to a friend of mine about
epilepsy and brain disorders in a
private conversation which I did not
hear and I was wondering if you could
give me any ideas on how to help the
seizure and the psychotic and the
different manipulated brain patterns
guys in a physical treatment thank you
we will be very brief and general for
now upon this since there is not the
timing for specifics okay but recognize
that epilepsy and some of the ideas you
epilepsy and some of the ideas you
express as psychosis are simply
different manifestations of channeling
energy but it is being focused and
funneled inward rather than
outward recognize this we are not saying
this is so in every case but it is a
very common and typical pattern that
many of the individuals you find to be
what you call channeling in your Society
at this time have generally experienced
either a seizure a Blow To The Head or a
massive electric shock at some point in
their lives these ideas sometimes are
simply your way of creating the
necessary jolt of Revelation to realign
the neuronic pathways of the brain
towards the focus of channeling to allow
that idea into your life therefore
certain individuals that exhibit some of
these patterns are let us
say inherent channels in that sense but
they are simply focused in a manner that
is inward they are cross circuiting into
themselves and not allowing it to flow
outward in a communicative
sense many times you will find even
though you may wish to think of the
brain as a whole system and you can that
because many individuals have thought of
it as a left and right system you can
allow a balancing in epileptics to take
place if you simply utilize your flow
and direction of energy with regard to
the two hemispheres and create the idea
of an infinity symbol to to allow the
two halves to communicate with each
other rather than short Circ in that
sense and allow them to blend you may
find that while you are directing them
in this manner and
orchestrating the energy within them in
that way you can actually completely
halt a seizure in progress and you can
even extend this idea to individuals
that stutter for it is much the same
idea this is working on my Asma right
now thank
you I do this currently in my work um
with my fingers working with the
hemispheres and the um but the actually
the the energy seems to move uh
sagitally instead of corally instead
of as you're drawing it there drawing it
forward to backwards the infinity symbol
is this just as effective or is it
important to make a change for now we
would go from hemisphere to hemisphere
you can have one going forward to back
at the same time because then that will
allow them to access the nodal point in
the center of the brain that is is the
communication doorway from other
dimensions into this one and vice versa
thank you can you do one more thing and
that is I know you couldn't find a word
for us that is surrender in the actual
event but can you create a sound even
from another Society a sound that we may
interpret as this truth in new
surrender laughter is ing
ing
yes you follow me yes sir thank you oh
sir oh yes sir thank you sir you are
welcome yes back to the epilepsy would
would you say that dtin has been harmful
for people who um depends upon the
belief system of the individual in
general you will find that your
so-called drug injection in this way is
not really necessary recognize that the
majority of
individuals that you consider to be
imbalanced mentally simply are
experiencing different levels of their
Consciousness and have not been taught
any way to communicate that in a manner
that the society will accept to put it
very colloquially approximately the idea you
colloquially approximately the idea you
would call
85 to
87% of all individuals that you consider
to be psychotic
schizophrenic or disturbed in various
similar ways so to speak Disturbed are
simply psychic
psychic
channels that don't know how to express
it because they have not been taught
that it is something the society
allows therefore it implodes within them
and causes a cross
circuiting a feedback loop that locks
them into their reality with the
inability to
communicate other channels and other
psychics who are sensitive to that
energy can assist them in bringing them
out also as you have already noticed as
in the case of autism and similar
phenomena the dolphin Consciousness can
be of great assistance to those
individuals as well for they have direct
telepathic communication and can draw
them out perhaps more easily than any
words you might use using your
language so [Music]
interesting um talked with my mother and
helping her understand her epilepsy and
I was wondering if you could further
explain why it occurred um right after
she gave birth to her second child she
wasn't born with it but it it developed
like just
our perception is that the agreement
that was made with the second child is
for the second child to put that
individual in touch with certain aspects
of herself that in many lives she has
been afraid to face let us say and in
this life has reinforced those fears
with certain belief systems that she has
been brought up with she is now having
to face those ideas she can assimilate
them in this present life and can allow
herself to alleviate that idea if she
will simply once again but trust her
instincts and begin to rely more and
more upon the idea of her feelings
I think she's supposed to accomplish
with that
son and anything in particular that
there can be specific scenarios but at
this time we will simply allow the idea
that communication between themselves
with regard to the agreements they have
made in meditative States very centered
relaxed meditative states can put them
for now in touch with some of these
agreements okay thank you we will also
suggest that some of this idea can come
out in the dream
reality things can be resolved there and
they can become conscious so that when
you awaken you have conscious
recognition of what the agreement is
simply focus on the idea of wishing to
know what the agreement is before they
go to sleep and simply allow themselves
to wake up understanding that they have
now got at least another different point
of view regarding the agreement and bit
by bit they will have conscious
awareness of what the total agreement is
and bit by bit the necessity of the
experience of the epilepsy will wne
as they integrate themselves completely
for in a sense it is only an indication
of lack of integration along certain
lines those specific lines will simply
be representative of the different paths
that that individual chose to be in the
many different lives they have lived it
is also one way to allow them massive
acceleration in this
life yes I understand more thank you for
sure is that is that why uh the feelings
that I get when I when I I'm aware of
channeling it feels like the beginnings
of an epileptic seizure
yes it is very similar energy in that
way and also when the physical channel
is sometimes it it sometimes looks like
an epileptic on his
channeling interesting at this timing allow us to
interesting at this timing allow us to
once again extend our love to each and
every one of you individually and
collectively and our appreciation in
allowing us to experience the crystallin
clear gift of your
hearts we thank you for your willingness
and your sharing we thank you for being
willing to share our dream with us and
for allowing us to share your dream with
you a fond and unconditionally loving
good evening and good life to you all
good night good night thank you [Music] have everything
gone thank you very much thank you all
for being here