action with the idea once again of
laying out what you call in your Society
coincidence or synchronicity for in this
way you will find that what we will
specify within the interaction the
evening of your time will be a
simplification according to the idea and
the understanding of the mechanisms that
allow your life to work things in your
vernacular in your Consciousness are now
accelerating again and in this way we
will find that at this time it will be
to use your terminology important to us
that you have a clear understanding as
to your control of your
lives so in this way we will discuss
some of the exemplification of the idea
of synchronicity and outline and
delineate and Define in a very
straightforward as you say simplified
manner exactly how you can utilize your
understanding of this concept to
recognize that you are and always have
been in control of your life now I have
discussed with you many times the idea
of coincidence synchronicity that the
idea that is nothing happens by accident
but simply that what you are recognizing
is overlapping incidents
coincidents that describe and Define the
patterns and paths you have chosen
yourselves to
be now we
will have defined the idea of
synchronicity as this and delineate a
little further in further in
clarification
synchronicity coincidence is your
coincidence is your
conscious
perception in a physiological Time
Track spatial
reality of the of the
simultaneous
manifestation of the multi by dimensional dimensional
existence of
all in this
way we will now through your examples of
day-to-day existence indicate the following idea that
synchronicity is your recognition
your conscious
recognition that all the
events all of the
objects all of the
relationships all points of
view all perceptions all
interactions are all one thing one
thing every single thing
every single thing
that you experience every
differentiation that you create in your
reality is the same one
thing from a different point of
view the same one thing manifesting
itself simultaneously as the illusion of many
simultaneously as the illusion of many
things everything
is one thing
one therefore to put it in your quote
unquote practical terminology observe
the following give yourself the opportunity
following give yourself the opportunity
to recognize that what we will now begin
to delineate is that in order to
understand consciously that you are in
control of your life you need to do but
two things and that is it we will render
everything we have discussed with you to
date concepts of ideology
belief emotion thoughts perception
perspective interaction into
two ideas that you can utilize as the
ideas that you can utilize as the
mechanism itself of recognizing that to
are in control of creating your reality
two things very simple one
two the
first the first now before we
[Music] continue I will ask you a favor may
continue I will ask you a favor may
I this is
again because of the acceleration
because of what you have allowed us to
do and to function as in Reflections to
you of what you are capable of it is
important to us at this time that you
fully understand what we are saying if
you do not say so for we would wish that
you have full understanding before we
continue if at any time you feel like so
to speak interrup
do so do not feel embarrassed or
ashamed the idea is coming to you as you
need to understand it if you feel so
inclined as to inquire for further
clarification do so it will not serve
your purpose to not
understand all
right than you number
one everything is
synchronicity everything is syn
synchronicity now what this means is
this as you are driving as you are
walking as you are doing anything in
your daytoday
lives remember
this every single object every single
person every single sound every single
interaction action every crack in the
street every leaf on the tree the number
of the leaves the color of the leaves is
all there for a
reason no
accidents no
accidents now recognize therefore that while
now recognize therefore that while
certain interactions while certain
objects while certain people may not
have a strong direct relationship to you in a
a strong direct relationship to you in a
particular given moment it does not mean
that they are still not there for a
reason they may have quote unquote more
conscious meaning to the person just
ahead of you the person just behind you
but because you are there
too you are playing the part of being
willing to act and interact with all the
other individual so that their degree of
importance as to their relationship to
what is going on is also enhanced by
your presence just like your degree of
importance is enhanced by
theirs are you following
me degree of importance we will get to
that tell
you the idea therefore once again is to
Simply recognize to use an analogy that you
recognize to use an analogy that you
have shared with us quite often if you
are driving in your car and someone
quote unquote Cuts you off if you are in
a traffic
jam if you are in a situation that you
would usually typically label as
something negative recognize once again nothing
negative recognize once again nothing
happens by accident
nothing nothing every every single thing
if you are in your traffic
jam the car next to you how much farther
ahead or behind it is what color it is
what way the light from the sun strikes
it none of it is by accident none of
it
therefore begin to be
fascinated by how well orchestrated
everything is that you are participating
in on what you would call an unconscious
level you are drawing into your life
every single
particle of
dust every single atom that is
there everything no
everything no
exceptions no exceptions
the way somebody may look at you the way
you look at
them what they are
wearing no accidents it all plays a part
in the idea that everything is one
single event experienced from different
points of view
simultaneously one
event the idea of degree of importance
is simply to recognize how you relate to
the event in other words you may find
that let us say someone is walking down
the street and they are wearing a certain
street and they are wearing a certain
color shirt as you say now you may
simply recognize it you may simply
recognize it as synchronicity you know
that it has a
reason you may explore the idea of the
relationship for you and simply find
that it does not bear any quote unquote
reason that would stand out as anything
important to you at the moment however
the person behind you may get more
importance out of it than you do but
simply that does not mean you cannot
recognize that the reason for why you
are there is still no accident for you
are part of the enhancement of the
entire experience for the other
person you follow me that is what we
mean by degree of importance look at it
this way another
analogy you have the idea of a rotating
propeller you understand yes a rotates
at certain frequency certain rate you
have what you call a strobe light you
follow me yes if you are in a dark room
if the propeller is rotating if your
strobe light along with everyone else's
strobe light is synchronized
synchronicity synchronized to the
rotation of the propeller such that when
you decide to turn your strobe light on
and it begins to flash on off on off on
off on
off whenever you decided to turn it on
that will be the first position that you
will see the propeller in you follow me
so far yes recognize that because your
light is synchronized to the rotation of
the propeller that will be the only
position you see the propeller in you
follow me now if you were in dependently able
me now if you were in dependently able
to see your particular synchronization
and someone else was independently able
to see theirs so that your strobe and
their strob did not Clash so to speak
then they would be observing the same
propeller in a different position same
propeller different aspect entirely the
same single event that appears to be
completely and totally different simply
because of the rate and the timing of
the frequency of each individual
strobe everything is the same
thing everything is the same thing the
only reason you see the same one thing
as different is because of the rate and
the timing of your strobe of
Consciousness in physical
reality everything is one thing that is
the first point everything is
synchronous one thing everything is synchronicity
one thing everything is synchronicity
everything is there for a reason that is
point number one point number two act
two act
upon the
opportunity that your conscious
recognition of everything as
synchronicity brings you with
Integrity act upon all opportunity
Integrity that is all you have to
do one recognize that everything is
synchronicity two act upon it in that
way with
Integrity that those two
ideas is all you need to do to create
the life you desire that is it
period that is all there is to physical
reality one
one
two everything is
synchronicity act like
it that is all there is to be in
complete harmonic
resonance with your conscious
understanding of all that is as it
expresses itself as physical
reality one
two acting like it will always generate
more conscious awareness of number one
which will always then give you more
opportunity to act like it Point number
two they are self-perpetuating
one breeds two breeds one breeds two
breeds one breeds to accelerating into
Infinity what do you mean by with
Integrity thank you the
recognition to put it in colloquial
terms that if you are aware that
everything is one thing and you are a
part of it then you recognize that you
have everything you need to be anything
you want without having to force
yourself upon anyone else to do
it Integrity integrated integral
integrated Blended one Hess wholeness
you do not have to force your opinions
on anyone else you do not have to
dominate anyone else to get what you
think you deserve act upon the
opportunities that synchronicity gives
you with Integrity knowing that you are
as complete as you need to be to act
upon it in exactly the way you need to
to get exactly what you need you do not
have to in that sense rely upon anyone
else to do it for you or force them to
act with Integrity upon the opportunity
you create and it will always always
perpetuate more of number one always
because you in acting integrally with
all that is with synchronicity will
always maintain your connection to it
consciously acting outside of Integrity
separates you and stops the process
between one and
two and does not allow the acting to
generate conscious awareness of
synchronicity understand everything is
synchronicity including negative
synchronicity you always attract
the ideas you believe in that way that
you are willing to act upon in the
manner that you are willing to act upon
them negative occurrences are still
synchronicity because they are
fulfillments of your own negative
beliefs you are acting in that manner
what we are simply saying is that acting
with Integrity in positive attitude
always will
consciously maintain the connection
consciously that is what will allow you
to perceive the connection as an
acceleration and not a
stagnation so it could accelerate
negative more positive by your
recognition in a sense but the idea is
simply that if it is negative
acceleration you will find that you
first of all consider it
destruction and perceive the effect in
that for and also it may not allow you to
for and also it may not allow you to
recognize the reasons for the
destruction for the negativity because
you are disassociating from the fact
that everything is
synchronicity and then it leads to the
question why is this happening to
metim negative synchronicity creates
victimhood and so recognizing it like
you said recognizing it is forming a
conscious positive connection because
once you recognize what it is you know
you are in control of
it then you can choose what you prefer
by acting accordingly on the under
understanding that everything is
synchronicity and then acting
accordingly through
Integrity you follow me that is all
there is to it do you do you mean that
by everything is synchronicity that each
aspect as you enumerated them are
reflections of the same idea yes they
are all the same thing all of them are
the same fundamental one thing that you
call creation or
God they are all the same thing and it
is
holographic each contains everything it
is all all everything is
all every separate concept is its own
thing and its own version of the one
same thing en llarge concept that makes
sense of like understanding relate to it
and feel look at it this way then are
you familiar with the idea you call
cloning yes then recognize that each and
every cell in your body contains
information for a whole body right that
is the idea each and every single
separate concept is simply a different
manifestation of the same one thing but
when I try to apply that idea to
the teeny weeny little events going on
throughout the course of a day as we
measure time I have
difficulty understanding all of those do
not forget that we are not saying that
conscious recognition of everything as
synchronicity means you will be able to
consciously analyze every single aspect
to your conscious understanding that is
not the point then what's the point the
point is to recognize that some aspects
will have as we have said varrying
degrees of relative importance to you
the ones that do not have a great degree
of importance you will not form an
conscious analytical recognition H sure
one moment but then how do we it is once
again a matter of trust I can trust but
are you saying that we will simply it
will be obvious and you will know which
ones have the have the highest degree of
importance yes in other words
what a coincidence just what I needed
right place right time everything else
doesn't matter but you're saying that everything
matter but you're saying that everything
else although it may not matter is also
a manifestation of the same thing that
the coincidence yes and it will appear
that another variation of those same
circumstances will matter to someone
else though it may not matter so much to
you but it is all the same one
but it is all the same one
thing also aren't you saying the point
isn't the conscious recognition of the
symbolism you can just reinforce that it
means something and you will yourself
know what yes the point is not the
conscious recognition the point is to
Simply act as if you simply know that
what is occurring is synchronicity and
what stands out is what you need to know
the way you need to know it is the way
you need to know it period the way you
know it is it that is the way you need
to know it didn't you in fact say that
it might be detrimental to analyze
everything in a sense you can recognize
that many times you will allow the
synchronicity into your lives and you
will have made a decision to not become
analytical about it because becoming
analytical about it may not allow you to
live the
experience you will turn it back into
pieces instead of allowing it to be one
thing cause and effect the same event
it's all one thing all of it so you're
moving from the knowingness inad and yes
trust that is knowingness you simply
take it for granted that everything you
are perceiving is
synchronicity no accidents
and the way you relate to it is the way
you need
to plain and
simple that is all there is to
this what about those times when there's
a tremendous amount of synchronicity and
everything and acting on that and then
nothing happens
happens
again that is a
contradiction recognize that you are
postulating two completely different
viewpoints of synchronicity a positive
and a negative one mhm recognize that it
will always manifest in whatever way it
needs to and again it may not be
consciously obvious so that you can take
advantage of the way it has manifested
for to you if you were to become
consciously aware of certain ideas you
would not be able to move on
it you would be fixated on the
mechanism it would be as if all of a
sudden you became fascinated with the
concept itself analytically of being
able to drive a car and forgot how to
Simply get in and drive because you were
too fixated on well this piece or how
does it relate to that piece or how does
it relate to that or how does it how how
how how how and in the meantime you're
late for your
opponent you follow me that is putting
it into an analogy but it will have the
same effect many times you will simply
recognize that synchronicity will occur
in the appropriate time by Ming the idea
of saying it doesn't happen is a
judgment call you are putting expectations on how
call you are putting expectations on how
you think it should have happened that
is not allowing it to be
synchronicity you follow
me synchronicity is what it is the way
it is the way it is not well it should
have been this well it didn't happen I
didn't see what I expected should have
been the reflection of synchronicity I
have a definition of well then if we
have no understanding of the outcome you
do have an
understanding in the way you need to
conscious analysis is not the only
definition of
understanding you follow
me and recognize again the second you
act like everything is is synchronicity
the more obvious it will
become is everything happens as it is
meant to does that mean that there is a
sort of plan yes and
no within a plan there
is Free Will yes and it is both
simultaneous again because time and
space are Illusions and are also
synchronicity
time space is also simply another
manifestation of one
thing it all occurs now it all occurs
here for lack of a better term Char do
you understand what you're talking about
yes because that is how our civilization
lives as we have described you that is
why we do not need the idea of the tools
of government or economic systems
because we allow synchronicity to always
let us know that we are interacting with
exactly the beings we need to be
interacting with and sharing the
services with those beings and they are
sharing services with us that are the
only services at that moment that we
need mhm you follow me I follow what
you're saying yes no what about creating
something that you envision that you
wish to create how does that count again
as we have described acting like
everything is synchronicity with
integrity means following your
excitement you will then be allowing
yourself to use synchronicity in a
positive way what about those times when
you don't follow it there are often
times where you feel
like again you may be creating the idea
of beliefs of negative synchronicity and
it may not let you know that you are
following it but in a negative
way recognize the idea as this if you do
not act according to your own instincts
what you know to be true for you
then all you are saying is that you have
a
belief that in not doing so you will
create a reality that will force you to
recognize that that is what you are
doing which very often in your Society
can manifest in a negative reality in
other words I didn't follow my feelings
I find therefore that I still quote
unquote hate my job hate this hate that
you follow me you always reinforce the
choice you make it's a setback not a
setback no for in this way you are
simply giving yourself the opportunity
to learn that the choice you made is
what the reality is that you are
experiencing and it gives you that much
more opportunity to recognize that if
you redefine your choice that will be
the reality you will
experience since you are experiencing
flawlessly the reality you believe you
will experience
now you follow me
yeah this brings me to a question I've
been wondering about for a long time
everything's happening right now right
right then why can't the future be
predicted it is but not in the terms you
call prediction again recognize the idea of
prediction again recognize the idea of
the propeller and the strobe
lights the idea as we have said is not
so much that you are predicting a future
you are sensing the energy at the
present that is most likely to occur
because it has the greatest degree of
energy behind it the strobe light is on
that particular setting at the time the
sensing or prediction is made the
prediction itself might change the
setting of The strobe
light understand what your physicists
Now understand you
understand you
cannot make
a conscious decision that doesn't affect
the reality you are deciding
about you follow me every thought
changes the reality you are thinking
of therefore so-called predictions are
only sent things of the energy most
likely to manifest at the time the
prediction is made the prediction itself
can change the energy if what has been
sensed has a great deal of energy
momentum behind it it will in your terms
be unlikely to change but it is not the
future that you have predicted it is the
present and it simply doesn't
change to the point where it
manifests you follow me I little I I'll
I'll chew on it keep it simple keep it
simple I have the past the present and
the future is all now
right understand it again this way
you have a radio yes you have the idea
of being able to tune to different
programs yes just because only one
program at a time is coming through your
speaker doesn't mean all the other
programs aren't there right and you can
make a prediction that if you tune the
dial you will get another
program that is making a prediction but
it is only because you are aware of the
fact that the program already exists
that you can do so it is the same thing
you follow me yeah can I I one moment
but I express my reality by way of
answering her to see if you would agree
with my view of it
proceed if everything is happening now
there are an in and the Pres there is no
there's only the present the past and
future are created out of the present
there is a there are an infinite number
of possible
Futures and therefore
what they exist all of them exist right
now all of them so the question is not
whether they are there cuz they are yes
the question is which one you will wind
up choosing perfect
okay well thank you thank you I yeah I
was saying why why talk about the future
at all since there is no
future it is all present it's all
present but I think I really answered my
question yeah
could I ask you a question about uh
certain human emotions which switch on
when you seem to deviate from this
intensity yes uh can I just brief
descriptions of these uh what is anger
anger is alignment with what you know to
be true for you anything that lasts
longer than 10 to 15 of your seconds is
no longer anger but
judgment okay what is fear
fear is the recognition that you may be
operating on a frequency once once again
that does not necessarily represent an
alignment with what you find to be true
for you and it adds energy in a certain
way to accelerate you and bring you into
the present the negative effects that
fear can have again are only the
Judgment of the fear that it is
something that does not serve
you what is grief grief again is the
Judgment that you are not connected to a
portion of
yourself that you can quote unquote lose
something somewhere as if there were
somewhere for something to be lost to
that's very
good what is
resentment it is in your terms connected
to the idea of jealousy Envy it is a
judgment upon oneself that one does not
contain what one sees in another and
does not think it attainable but
recognize from our point of view if you
can see it you have to contain it
what is uh
loneliness again the idea of separation
of yourself from the rest of all that is
that you
are the belief that while you are unto
yourself one idea one Universe a
separate Universe in that way that the
idea does not contain automatically the
polarity that you are connected to
everything and can never be
alone very good the last one is on
something that seems to be a chronic
condition rather than a temporary
condition uh I have two girls in my
office one of them understands Insurance
perfectly the other one doesn't
understand it at all so she calls
herself stupid what is stupidity and
intelligence which seem to be fixed
during one lifetime thank you in this
way it is not fixed but the idea simply
is at any given moment what an
individual relates to as a vibration for
recognize that someone who is quote
unquote stupid at one thing is brilliant
at something else MH the idea is simply
selectivity the recognition of the
vibration that in your terms truly
excites you and
doesn't okay but um it can also be it
can also
be a conscious or an unconscious refusal
to recognize that you are complete and
do contain all the information you need
to contain at any given
moment that seems to be fixed for one
lifetime you don't get people it can be
but it does not have to be and in
particular particular because this is
the transformational life upon your
planet it is less likely that it is
fixed for the entire
life why does a person create that
problem though that for her is a very
big problem she doesn't see because they
wish to experience what it is like to be
limited to that
extent because it is one of the
experiences you can participate in
within all that is and it also may be
serving other individuals to allow those
other individuals through caring and
compassion to learn that they can be
teachers as
well what is Judgment judgment is
separation limitation it is the
invalidation of the different components
within all that is the une equalizing of
the different components that you
perceive within all that is so can you
make a positive
preference preference is simply
recognizing the vibration that relates
to you judgment is the invalidation of
what you do not prefer as something less
than what you have
chosen you can also simply have an
observation so to speak that does not
have to be a judgment you can simply
observe that someone may be utilizing
negative energy that does not have to be
a judgment because you simply can
recognize that you prefer say in this
case the positive energy and their
preference of negative energy is what
they need to learn m so that is simply
an observation not a judgment but if you
tell them that they are manifesting
negative energy isn't that a judgment
that can still be an observation as long
as the idea in sharing that with them is
not an encroachment upon their rights
and not an enforcement upon your behalf
that you think they should
change because it would be better if
they did okay then that is a judgment the
did okay then that is a judgment the
idea of Judge not lest you be judged is
that when you judge another you become
the vibration of judgment yourself it is
not that you are being judged by
something outside there is no
outside you follow me yes yes thank you
he yes um a friend of mine asked me to
to ask you um a question tonight and
actually perfect it's all in mind talk
what a coincidence
yeah her name is Teresa levit and she uh
asked me first of all the way she put it
is she would want to have a healing from
you and and it's healing of an emotional
level um and what's happening now is she
is recognizing the synchronicity in her
life however however
um while she recognizes things that are
happening and of a negative nature and
and why they happen happening and where
they're stemming from
in her past she she's having and I'll
use the word difficulty because that's
the way it feels to her difficulty in
releasing those those negative beliefs
about herself so that she can create
preservability in her life and and then
ask her what she gets out of
them how do they serve her to maintain
the negative beliefs well she knows that
too she gets a certain amount of
attention all right then simply allow
her her recognitions in her own good
time recognize that our perception of
this individual is that she is on the
threshold of allowing herself to know
she can change we have sent energy to
that effect it is up to her to use it we
cannot force the change of Honor in this
way in this way simply allow her to know
that the idea of maintaining the belief
that something is difficult to change is
also a choice right like anything else
ask her what she gets out of it and in
this way then simply recognize that if
she is going to enjoy being miserable it
will
continue um is there
[Music] any you
any you
know I've gone through this myself and
I've found that I have released some
things and I guess then you yourself can
be a reflection for this individual as
well yeah it's like I guess you know
sometimes we look for some magic word or
something that will will allow us to
release you know like just tell me how
to do it you know you form such a h we
form sometimes such habits that even
though we know there's another way of
being it's such a habit it almost seems
like like well like we use the word
difficult I know and I know what you
said and I even I understand it I'm
trying to you want a magic word yeah two
words repeat after me yes I I
am you will always be able to say that
how's that that's good I I I yeah what
I'm working with right now is is wanting
to assist her in in a way then say I am
okay all right and be it that is how you
can assist others by being fully what
you are and then by her saying I am will be
are and then by her saying I am will be
to her to others yes for then she will
cease to judge the different judge ments
she has created within
herself all right well thank you very
much well thank you well sure good I
would like to address an objective of
developing an ability to communicate
with dolphins with the same degree of um
clarification that we're communicating
to each other now go ahead and along
that line I I will and
am along that line would you please
detail for me what you consider to be a
workable approach to accomplishing that
objective emotion expound a little more please
emotion expound a little more please
feeling sharing touching physical
presence with the dolphin as opposed to
linguistic articulation you can do that as well do
articulation you can do that as well do
they use a a language an articulate
language like we do in a sense yes in a
sense what sense exp is simply not the
idea of what you call your alphabet in
that way but it is in your terms
acoustic what is it what you perceive to be the
what is it what you perceive to be the
Sonic vibrations that they create and do
those Sonic vibrations represent
specific packages of thoughts that our
words do
okay and how would we um identify what
are ways in which we could identify the
thoughts that those particular sounds
represent by spending time with them and
exchanging Concepts in such a way that
you can differentiate what they mean and
what you mean
by a simple object that you both can
identify I see similar in the way that
you would teach a child by mimicry
what's hold up a if you held up an
object to a dolphin would you make the
appropriate sound yes you would do that
naturally of course very good it's been
done please their methods of communication uh
please their methods of communication uh
how are their methods of communication
differ from
ours again in this way you will find
that have perhaps more group
Concepts than you and also the range of
the Acoustics will be abnormally high
and low for you for many of what their
Concepts relate to in this way will take
them in a Range beyond your hearing
range and thus you may not even be aware
sometimes of when they are talking
unless you can feel it what you can mhm
recognize and remember once again that
telepathy is an
empathic emotional phenomenon and it is
also once again
synchronicity now allow me
to
outline clarify we recognize within your society
clarify we recognize within your society
that many times when an individual says
well something is this many of you still
take it as well it is that this exists
within that now you may take me quite
literally in the translation that is
coming through into your language the
universe is
synchronicity synchronicity is the
universe and what we mean by this as an
even closer
connection and using an analogy that
would be not even as close is to say
well what is wood well wood is a tree a
tree is wood now it is many other things
in that way but that is a closer analogy
to what we mean when we say the universe
is synchronicity and synchronicity is
the universe it is not that the ideas of
belief emotion
thought ESP telepathy ESP telepathy
Clairvoyance
psychokinesis all of these ideas are all
manifestations of
synchronicity all of them
them
therefore relate to the dolphin as
another expression of
you as another expression of the
synchronicity you are both
representative of then your interactions
will be only the interactions that will
illuminate what you desire to know uhhuh
feel yourself as adult feel yourselves
as the synchronicity of the interaction
between you and you will understand what
the interaction is at any given moment
whether it has a consciously analytical
understanding or not does not matter
didn't fully follow that consider
yourselves to be the interaction that is
going on between you you become the
synchronicity of your relationship and
you will always understand what that
relationship is which is only another
way of saying I know what you are
talking about I know what you are saying I
about I know what you are saying I
understand you all those statements are
other ways of saying that you become the
relationship between
you the interaction between the two
opposed objects of the
interaction it is the interaction itself
the synchronicity The Exchange that
creates the object interacting not the
other way
around therefore become the interaction
empathize with the interaction itself
and you will be able to feel what is
being said so you trust yourself to be
the interaction yes okay did your
ization Evol from a verbal language to a
telepathic one yes what were the primary
steps in the evolution what I have just
described the recognition that as we
discovered synchronicity we allowed it
to be real and we understood that all of
the connections the interconnectedness
of all and the holographic nature of all
we allow that to be our real reality by
acting as if it was so you're acting so
we wish to develop more confidence in
our ability to communicate
telepathically you simply saying that we
should act as if we were communicating
tath yes and recognize again that the
idea may be most closely expressed not
by a mental activation in your terms but
by an emotional one because the
emotional one is a vibration that
incompasses quote unquote more of your
being than simply mental activation
in other words once again it is not so
much the idea although this is what
occurs as well that to know someone is
to love them but to love them is to know
them very nice that is telepathy very
nice currently much of our scientific
Community will not accept or acknowledge
telepathy or imagination is real that is
because it is still to them an
analytical process okay how would you
suggest that we go about
making uh these approaches more
acceptable to the scientific Community
it is in your terms becoming acceptable
to many individuals and in this way
again our only suggestion is to Simply
act like it and afford them an
opportunity to see it in
action for what they are doing now is
trying to learn about a process by
stopping it and not doing
it how will they be able to perceive
that the action is correct though
they're using very rigid uh of
perception when enough individuals act
that way they will get the picture they
will feel it also yes of course they
will see it all around them and finally
say well what's this all
about okay again understand that the
ideas of Consciousness originate so to
speak to use that term outside a Time
Track everything that can be analyzed
can only originate inside a Time
Track therefore once they include
Consciousness into their equations they
will get the
picture and it will instantaneously
begin to activate the series of events
that will reinforce itself into their
realation
synchronicity understand many of your
so-called scientists have you ized
synchronicity to quote unquote achieve
the understandings of physics that they
have they just don't know it some of
them do currently Rec the ones I was speaking
do currently Rec the ones I was speaking
of were the ones that were conscious of
it on their own
term currently I have some friends that
are conducting uh some experiments with
dolphins uh what they're doing is they
are um putting together sort of a
computer keyboard in which the Dolphins
can punch in various actions that result
in a change in their environment such as
water chure heat food being presented
this sort of thing is there a uh method
by which they can
accelerate the uh the learning process
only by doing what occurs to them
mhm again the idea is that we already
are aware that there are individuals in
your Society that have taken some of
these steps if you wish to join them
then take the same
steps in your own
way so it's a it's a boldness with
trouble and a doing yeah in other words
you can perceive and interact with
Dolphin Consciousness from where you are
sitting if you are so inclined to do it
that way but from what we are perceiving
you are describing it is unlikely that
one of them is going to come Swimming by
in your living room
therefore go to a place where you can
interact together or create such a place
well that's what this is the place I'm
speaking of where some friends of mine
are doing this then go and relate as you
will and simply understand that it is
not so much that you are teaching them
but that you are teaching each
other for there are going to be many
things that are going to occur between
you where you might think they are just
being stubborn and what they are trying
to do is get you to learn something
return so do not
be how shall I put it humanistically chauvinistic
chauvinistic
yeah very much so in fact certain of
this uh this line of research was
stopped prevented because of
considerations that it would not be
acceptable to the public for instance
what I'm speaking about is occurring in
Epcot which is an experimental prototype
community of tomorrow in Disney World we
have a seized Pavilion that's and the
idea that the public would not quote
unquote accept telepathy or experiments
in telepathy between Dolphins PR
prevented this type of of exhibit
demonstration are the Dolphins going to
be there yes they are there then
telepathy will
occur regardless of what the expectation
is in that way
but um how could we overcome the
reluctance to present to the public this
as a you know as a possibility why don't
we it would be nice to put up an exhibit
saying please feel free to
telepathically communicate with these
Dolphins it is possible you know um but
there is a restriction we will let you
figure out how to come to terms with all
the individuals with whom you are
interacting I already
have because one of the way in which
these interactions is going to occur is
by sending them this particular tape
we've already established and
interchange and do let me put it this
way if you will perhaps this may or may
not does not have to make a difference
from our point of you in looking at your
planet if we were to let us say scan
your world in search of what you would
recognize as alien thinking species
species we would find two on your planet
the humans and the dolphin
whales therefore recognize that what you
are doing is forming a communication
link with an alien species on your very
own
world thus recognize
that your world in many ways is unique
and unique in one more way in that the
majority the
the
majority of what you would call alien
races on other
planets bear a closer resemblance in
third density reality to a humanoid life
form you are more unique in having one
right in your own backyard that is
not as close to humanoid as many alien
races you will encounter beyond your
world therefore it is a rich
opportunity for
exchange of true difference between
different alien environments than
environments than
you sure uh I'm feeling a little bit
like a pingpong ball lately all right
that can be an enjoyable
game even for the ball even for the
ball um I'm wondering if you could um
help me kind of level it out to the
point of being a little more comfortable
I will help you when you understand you
don't need
help I felt that way for a couple of
weeks then the you you were then is not
the you you are now so do not say you
felt that way right someone else did why
are you choosing to feel the way you
feel well that's part of the question
because I feel um a definite reality all
right what is wrong with that um does
that not give you a unique point of view
about yourself can you not learn from it
can you not enjoy
it can you not integrate and absorb what
you are learning from this dual
perception of yourself in a positive way
can you not assume that every situation
is fundamentally neutral and choose to
go at it with a positive attitude so it
will have a positive effect instead of a
negative attitude so it will creat a
negative effect
yes am I being of hell no
well yes I can do that all right do you
think that that will assist
you yes why do you think
so because um always
wait because it's can't hear you back
here because it implies that thank you
for pointing out the need for
boldness okay Sy um Pro it implies
that um forgot what to
imply good welcome to the
moment all right okay let me ask you a
specific thing then which oh implies
that I don't have to worry about
anything well right and one of the
things that is happening that is still a
little bit worrying is that I seem to
have a strange sleep thing happening
where I am falling asleep dagging on the
freeway ni and I've
got oh oh let's reinforce that one
let's reinforce the negativity all
right oh yes oh we all know that's
[Music] negative oh yes you are doing a negative
thing I didn't I had myself completely
covered with white light so I Was Not
Afraid on that level but what I'm
wondering is completely covered with
white light all right
I covered myself in white light to
protect myself because I was sleep on
the fer to protect yourself which
implies that you believe you need
protection which implies that you
believe you can be
harmed by large trucks when I sleep on
on
me freaked out my mother all right
has to be more impressed by
that all [Laughter] [Laughter]
[Music]
right shine it off it's okay Al may I
ask you a
question are you fighting your
own instinctive natural
schedule well I thought about that and I
remembered what you said about 2 to 4:00
being sleepy time or being our low
energy point in general in general and I
was not able to
pinpoint these periods of suddenly
becoming sleepy in terms of that General
cycle so
what are you going to take us literally
or are you going to follow your own
instincts oh it's not between 2 and 4:00
p.m. so even though I am sleepy I will
wait until 2: 4: p.m. because Bashar
said I can only be sleepy between 2: and
4:00 p.m. so I will not stop and take a
p.m. so I will not stop and take a
nap is that what you are
saying are you giving me that much of
your power no well all right
then what are you doing about your own
instinctive schedule well I guess it is my
schedule well I guess it is my
instinctive schedule is that I should
fall asleep at 55 M hour in my car on
theway are you missing the
point why in your estimation were you
falling asleep while you were moving
well that's what I don't know because
this has never happened before I'm not
the kind of person that falls asleep on
a freeway in broad daylight and when you
fell asleep you obviously were the kind
of
person do not confident yourself
perhaps you are not that kind of person
now because a you are not on the
[Music] freeway at least I will assume we are
freeway at least I will assume we are
[Laughter]
[Music] not now the person you were then is not
not now the person you were then is not
the person you are
now what you are being shown is this
entire idea of disassociation
now recognize that you are quite all
right you did not get killed by a
truck you follow me right
therefore our first suggestion is to
stop playing what if and let's talk what
is all right
now as you the you you were then was
driving along the freeway and falling
asleep what were your [Music]
[Music]
feelings um what were your
thoughts not connected to the idea of
what would happen if you fell asleep
just your general thoughts your general
feelings about yourself at that time
well it's it was very strange because it
was almost like louder it was uh it was
strange because it
was almost like I was going into a deep
meditation all right very good very
good very good
now what does meditation mean to
you it means how connecting
with another dens all right very good very
another dens all right very good very
good thank you now may I ask you a
question yes does it mean disconnecting
from this
one is that what you have always thought
meditation to mean sometimes yes and
sometimes no like most of the time I am
semi meditative all right and it's it's
cool you know I can I can do both cool
all right I can be third and fourth at the
right I can be third and fourth at the
same time all right
uh I can be B Den right Den right
[Music]
now let me ask you
this let me ask you this
okay with regard to the synchronicity of
having your mother present oh what does
it represent to you
now oh my goodness okay well do share do
share and speak up you do not want them
to fall asleep
okay yes oh my goodness I didn't make
that connection yes my mother always
falls asleep in fact my mother was
asleep in fact my mother falls asleep
maddeningly and I feel
as I mean um yes I feel that she's
sleeping her life away so to speak I see
and so you falling asleep at the wheel
did you say freaked her out or woke her
up uh she was asleep during whole thing
until I told her I mentioned to
her after we had
arrived started to follow yes yes and
her reaction was she freaked out so you
mean she woke up she woke
up and then the next time we drove she
made sure that she stayed awake and kept
talking to
me now do you get the
picture do you see the reflection that
you were being of service
to I was being of service to her oh come
come come me and in this way also
yourself and the idea of your
relationship to her and what you think
of her and what you think of what she
does and what she thinks of what you do
and this and that and showing her
reflections of herself that are
encapsulated within your feelings of her
and vice versa were you not acting out a
scenario about her that bothered you and
allowing her to see how it affects you
yeah all right then let it be
obvious now therefore simply
recognize again there is no what if this
is not the beginning of some disease I'm
going to fall as sleep to the wheel now
all the time now that you are in touch
with the reasons or at least some of
them for why you enacted that scenario
as a reflection to her you recognize the
purpose that was served and recogniz it
can be served in other ways rather than
in ways that are
unconscious you follow
me and therefore in ways that are not
quote unquote detrimental to your
physical health sometimes you will find that you
health sometimes you will find that you
will
share exciting incidents coincidents
with someone
else so that you both will wake up to
what is happen happening between you so
you will shake
yourselves give yourselves some
excitement in the relationships par it
up a
bit yes therefore thank you for your
yes therefore thank you for your
sharing you guys uh the first thing I
want to share is uh that I uh truly do
trust you and I'm realizing that I trust
you too thank you all of you
thank you
thank uh the next now they're going what
did he mean by
that I fully trust you to be who you are
exactly you cannot be anything else and
that also means infinite possibilities
than you right whatever you do is is all
right because you're an infinite Creator
as I am nice uh we also Trust the
synchronicity of the interaction that we
are together marvelous that is what we
trust wonderful thank you thank you uh would
wonderful thank you thank you uh would
you share a title for last
week how about last
week that's a good one how
about ancient dreams thank you
which is something that
exists in musical arrangement in your
Society I have Georgia
K and in this way you will find that
some of the vibrations within that will
also bring out some of the ideas you
wish to
explore all right thank you and I have
some uh question no I will assume what
tonight's title
is thank you
we already one synch synchronicity 2
okay I have some questions for uh uh
John uh sing withth who's who's from
Dallas Texas and I'd like to ask these
for his for him and his
wife um he said several years ago in a
um he said several years ago in a
spontaneous out of the body journey to
our planet the Sun son one was greeted I
was greeted by an elder who addressed me
by the name
Arno you uh may could you offer any
insights is this excuse me is this the
name whose vibratory frequency
represents my soul self whatever in a
sense for now yes it will do there are
also some other connections that we
perceive but it will do as a reflection
to relate to from the point of view you
are now as a physical being
it will assist in the blending of the
vibration of your higher self with the
physical being that you
are thank you second
question uh he wants to know if uh he will be
uh he wants to know if uh he will be
channeling Aros
soon soon is a relative
term okay all right third question uh do not
okay all right third question uh do not
mean to be mysterious but that is the
answer right
thank you and the third one is uh that
you mentioned about 7 and a half cycles
and he in the projects that he's
involved in he wanted to know if you had
uh he's got three listed here 7.52
4 uh 7.5 38 or 7.6 46 cycles per
second what about it he wants to know if
one of those is more more uh accurate
than not more accurate they are all
variations of the same thing with
relationship to the fluctuations in the
electromagnetic field there's also a
7.86 and there are some other ones in
this way simply recognize that the
individual's own experimentation will
allow there to be the arrival at an
appropriate frequency and that frequency
will fluctuate to some degree anyway it
is not that it maintains an
exact periodicity fluctuation
uh good last question is You' mentioned
he said that youd mentioned before
uh he want to know how
long you you would might predict uh that
the length excuse me how long will it be
before organized religion as we know it
will will
change our perception is that definitely
within the next 30 of your years within
that all is malleable
it can happen
sooner is up to
you thank you that's all
sure how how do you know you have
described this interaction as occurring
not you are here in your imagination
creating this interaction not as we say
astral projection or whatever that is so
how do you know what's going on on Earth
again in this way there are many
different ideas and interactions and
type of interactions that we partake of
but do not forget that astral projection
in a sense is also within the dimension
of
imagination okay then that raises
another question that I thought of when
Steve asked the question from the guy in
Dallas he said he was out of body
[Music] experience is
experience is
that is there any such thing as quote
out of body travel is it only
imagination in your terms because you
have created a type of universe that has
the different levels in it yes it is
real there is such a thing as out of B
what we are saying is that the entire
idea of all of the levels in the
universe is within the dimension of
imagination it is a creation can you
help me and perhaps other people here
get a better grasp on how it
is because I think when you use the word
imagination and relate it to this inter
action occurring in your
imagination you use the word differently
than we use here on this planet perhaps
could you help us bridge the gap between
it is simply as we have said that what
occurs within our imagination is real
the idea is more akin to the idea of
becoming quote unquote lost in a
daydream that seems to be so very
real while it is going on then when your
focus changes back to the reality you
are experiencing
before the Daydream only you think that
you have come back to the real reality
and we're only
imagining to us the Daydream is just as
real I experience our
interaction together as a very intense
Daydream more perhaps what you might
refer to as a
hallucinations but I know it's real but
it's but it's your imagination which you
are creating it is yours too
again it is a
cocreation it is synchronicity it is the
interaction itself that creates you and
me let me come ask this question a
different way did you hear what I said
first of all what did I just say you
said that it's a Coke that it's the
co-creation it is the interaction itself
that creates you and
me yes I understand that but my
attention is on the fact that there is a
if you will a collective Daydream going
on of all the beings on Earth yes
without for sure asani there's a
collective Daydream going on yes of
course okay how do you know the sub the
content of that Collective Daydream we
do not know all portions of it but you
know some portions for example we know
the portions that have to do with the
synchronicity of our interaction with
you and only Those portions so
it's not possible for you to Simply
observe or is is OB without interacting
with us on these Monday Tuesday but do
not forget an observation is an
interaction and is actually subjective
okay well I simply may not be talking
about it but it is still an interaction
well how did you know about Chernobyl
for example or the or the challenge is
that in this way the idea is that once
again what you call the physical channel
is a part of your Daydream and since we
are connected than anything the physical
Channel knows we know because again by
synchronicity what the physical Channel
knows we are supposed to know so we can
use it in that way okay independently of
this process called channeling do you
engage in other data collection
activities relative to from time to time
yes and that is one of the reasons why
sometimes we can quote unquote come
through with information
in conceptual form that the channel is
not aware of even though the terminology
may not be according to what you use
upon your
planet for in this way we can have our
observations about the ideas that we s
are going on in the portion of the
Daydream we share with you whether the
physical channel is aware of it or not
okay here's this corollary question you
told us that you physically appeared to
the Orion entity consciousness
Orion entity consciousness
in his reality which is
175,000 years
ago not a thought projection but you
physically appeared both both but yes
what you would call a physical
appearance which means that you travel
what we would say travel through time
I'm doing that now to talk to you but
it's different because why have you
chosen to channel rather than appearing
to us physically I have explained that
before well it has to do with we would
think you were a God and we couldn't
relate but has more to do with the idea
of our energy being so different it
would force an acceleration of your
energy and force you to look at portions
of yourself you are not ready to look at
ah okay all right now the idea of our
ability to appear to the so-called Orion
in this way is simply because their
society even in the state that it was in
in that sense in what we term to be
negativity still had within their
society already the recognition that
they could travel from planet to planet
and interact with other races that was
not a shock
one last question imagine being in the
rafters of a building you know what
Rafters are guys and looking down in
many different rooms so you can you can
look and see that there are lots of
different rooms and each of the rooms is
a point in what we would call time
they're all
simultaneous and let's suppose that
we're looking at the house that
represents Earth you're up in the
rafters you can see the past and the
future of or many POS many
potential many potential
fut and so you must be able to see some
potential Futures which you might you
and your civilization Collective you
would prefer that we don't
choose in a sense therefore simply
recognize that it is our perception that
because we are interacting with you it
is representative of the type of future
you have already chosen
okay but only a select
you you are the ones that make the
selection it is up to everyone it is
your individual Choice recognize again
that the individuals who have not chosen
that vibration are not interacting with
us that's true they're not here right
how is it possible to um they certainly
do not have to interact with us they can
interact with many different aspects of
themselves to quote unquote arrive at
the same conclusion
an individual can be living in a fourth
density state without ever having heard
the term fourth density metaphysics or
any of the other ideas that we are
discussing they can still live that way
and have chosen the idea of living in
that reality when it occurs totally
unconsciously so your presence here is
not merely an origination on your part
but a the very fact that you chose to
come we had something something to do
with is that what you're saying as I
have always said you allow us to
interact with you by choosing to
interact with us in equal
vibrations that is the only way we can
interact with you because of your
willingness to recognize that you can
now interact with us but if you're
sitting in the rter being able to see a
period of time on earth when let's
suppose no person on Earth One Moment
you can proceive a one
moment everything and every aspect that
you are present to relate to has to do
with you if you are willing to look at
it that
way integrate everything you are hearing
from anyone else turn the question and
the answers and the statements around
for you and understand how you relate to
it if you find in this way that you have
already related to it on your own terms
then simply recognize that if the idea
is still something you are perceiving
then there may be other ways in which
you can learn from it it
continue
okay sitting up in the rafters you can
observe one of the rooms let's Suppose
there is a room a point in time as we
would call it in which there was nobody
on Earth that was prompted to interact
with you all right and then in another
room we can observe that probability yes
and then we can also look down and see
the room which we experience as the now
in which we're interacting with you
thanks oh I answered my own question
they going on simultaneous there was
never a point in time when you decided
to interact you're interacting here but
you're not interacting there correct we
are simply with you the definition of
the interaction thank you thank you Michelle
interaction thank you thank you Michelle
yes uh the point came up in the previous
question about the Dual nature of person
ality um if I have two sides to my
personality one of them I like and one
of them I don't like um one is positive
one is negative okay but let's say the
negative side wants to eat too many
Twinkies and he has all kinds of urges
all right if I uh if I don't satisfy
those urges I feel discomfort right if
however I do satisfy those urges I feel
remorse how do you how do you how do you
resolve this human nature human
personality by simply recognizing first
and foremost the all polarity exists as
one thing outside of the physical
reality in your whole nature and that
you do not have to continue to see
yourself as a dichotomy you do not have
to continue to see yourself as a
struggle against or between this and
that but simply recognize that you have
at any given moment Free Will of
preference if you recognize that the
idea of the ingestion of those
substances does not vibrate with the
being that you would pre defer to be
then if you act like that being you will
find you do not have the urge because
you are not of the vibration that would
contain the idea have the urge to eat
this Define yourself is that could that
be called willpower or what not
willpower recognition ceasing of Judgment of
recognition ceasing of Judgment of
yourself ceasing of the belief the
changing of the belief that changing is
difficult the changing of the
the changing of the
belief that having the concept of what
you would prefer to be is not the same
thing as being it when it
is the changing of the belief that
having the concept still implies you
have to do something to become the
concept you have imagined when imagining
it is becoming the concept believing
that is what will make the
change so what is my so-called bads side
showing to me
that you have the opportunity to prefer
something else and to recognize that as
soon as you conceive of what that
something else is you're
it so the concept I have of my so-called
good side which I prefer to be is not
really what I want to be otherwise I
would be it you are simply assuming that
the concept itself when you have it is
not being it but it
is you are assuming that the concept of
the good side to have the concept is not
being it but having the concept is being
at the vibratory level of that good side
otherwise you wouldn't be able to
conceive of
it so again you have to be attuned to
the program to hear it coming through
the radio so if you find that you have
the ability to even conceive of what the
so-called good side or positive side is
all about you are at that moment tuned
to that frequency or that notion could
never have occurred to you but why is
this tremendous interference keep coming
in from because you assume that when you
conceive of it it is not real you assume
that you have to do something special in
order to make it real to stay on the
station you mean
yes you are the one that is flipping the
dial when you have flipped the dial to
the point where you can perceive what
this so-called positive side is like
leave the dial
there what I'm sitting there and
suddenly a Twinkie switches
on you are missing the
point the station that you will be tuned
to does not advertise
Twinkies so it will never occur to you
the urge won't be there understand you
are contradicting yourself you are
thinking that one being contains both of
these urges no when you are the vibration of
urges no when you are the vibration of
the positive side you only contain what
is relevant to that you if you are
finding yourself experiencing the urges
of the twinkie you are no longer the
other you you are the you that can
experience the urge of the twinkie yeah
but how do you hold that I find it
difficult to hold that is your belief to
belief to
say this is the concept itself
understand this your statement I find it
difficult to hold that is a belief so it
is its own reality so that is what you
get a reality in which you are a being
that finds it difficult to hold the
concept so you merely assume the
Viewpoint totally yes act like it assume
that if you can conceive of it at the
moment of
conception that is how you are
born you give birth to that being and
that is the only being that exists Now
understand you may use the idea again
that we have shared with some of you the
library
analogy as an integrated being you have
the ability to be cognizantly
aware of while still being the concept
that you are of all the other probable
realities that exist you can have the
definition my reality is what I am and
it contains the ability to be what I
know myself to be while at the same time
being aware of all of the other probable
realities I know I am
not you follow me yeah therefore the
idea and the analogy is as if you are a
library you go into the library you can
read every book on the Shelf the one
about Twinkies the one positive the one
negative only the one you make the
conscious choice to check out of the
library becomes your
reality otherwise it is not a matter of
having to fight against the urge you
simply have the type of reality that
says you can think about the idea that
such a probable reality exists but
that's not the idea you are you know the
library is there but you didn't check
out that
book so the fixity of the human
condition as I see it to be fixed I see
that most people are what you consider
to be the fixedness is something that
you believe to be real that is the only
reason you experience The Human
Condition as fixed because of the
definition that it
is you follow me but what is the at what
point do you go off the rails though
let's never never never never never okay
you are never off your path because you
are never on a path a path is what you
are you can't be off
yourself you are not on a path a path is
what you are you can't be off yourself
everything you do
everything everything is an opportunity
to decide what you
prefer everything you can learn from
everything every situation is
fundamentally neutral your attitude towards the
neutral your attitude towards the
neutral situation will determine the
effect that you create in your life the
life the
idea that you can have an urge to eat a
Twinkie is a neutral situation it does
not come with any power other than what
you put into
it it is simply a string of w words if
you wish to look at it that way you
Empower it you power it up oh yes the
concept of that that concept Twinkie
that creates
urges that I cannot
fight you have just written the script
and decided to act it
out by imposing definitions into a
fundamentally neutral series of
props what is the how of birth death fit
into this concept though let's say my
next door neighbor doesn't have this
urge yes and he never has the urge but I
do have the so
um knowing that your nextd door neighbor
never has the urge is an indication for
you of a reality that you can also
choose for yourself that may be why that
neighbor is there reflecting that
reality to you perhaps you are
reflecting the same thing back that he
can choose to have an urge if he wants
to you make good
but I guess my question really is
is is has it anything to do with a
particular lifetime only in the most general of
lifetime only in the most general of
Senses certainly not with a degree of
specificity of whether you eat a twinky
or not no but that's a ridiculous
example but I just see it's not a
ridiculous example but in this way
simply the overall idea of any
predestination is only expressed in
physical life in the most general terms
in other words let us say the idea of
what you are discussing falls under the
general category that you are
predestined to explore of
self-empowerment and the creation of
what you prefer so you are using
Twinkies as
your density that have that extreme
Clarity they're string positive and
negative as yes but as we move on to you only
as yes but as we move on to you only
experience the
coin the idea of the Oneness of the coin
and do not so much see it as two sides
but recognize that you need the whole
coin in order to buy your
Twinkie both the positive and and
negative are in harmony yes blended into
one concept male female one thing a soul
is not both male and female it is
neither it is one thing it can express
itself in that polarity in physical
reality but it is not that it becomes a
blended thing
separated the male female po arities
simply only exist from a physiological
reference point of view and do not exist
within the combined soul the soul to
itself is one thing neither male nor
female one
thing you follow me so are you saying
that neither negative or positive the
concept of negative and positive
polarity is one of the defining terms of
physical reality it only comes into existence as
reality it only comes into existence as
physical reality
does or as different levels that contain
that idea come into
existence the idea of The Unbroken
Oneness is not so much literally that it
contains an actual side by side cohesive
interaction with the polarities you
experience it is simply one
thing that can create itself to become
different
things for there are many different
universes that Express The Unbroken
wholeness of the Soul when it chooses to
differentiate itself in many other ways
other than the idea of Simply positive
and negative
polarity like
what this will really have no frame of
reference for
you it almost does not have a frame of
[Music]
us you sure good I have something I want
to discuss with you but also it's break
time so can we take a break and then
discuss it with you after the break all
right you may all take a short
break all right El say B yes thank you
um yes I want to talk to you about Sona
s that I chaning for okay um number one
have two parts number one is um I
understand her uh at this point to be
predominantly serious fifth density
energy all right um is yeah I don't have
a lot of information on that at this
time is is it the timing to find out
anything more about do you wish to be
obvious about this do I wish to be
obvious uh yeah all right then in the
asking of the question in one sense if
that is the way you wish to ask the
question that is the answer is is it the
timing to know more do you know more no
that is the answer okay now is a new
time all right how have you created
yourself to be
now in your recognition of your
relationship to some I'm allowing you to
be an obvious reflection of what I
already Prett sneak all
sneak all
right one moment stand
up should I touch you don't
now rings and doorways
doorways
combination as you would call
them to unlock
different aspects different
aspects different
probabilities can be the energy that
comes through your solar
plexus the idea that you can function as
a series of Gateway rings and
doorways that reflect different
combinations of probabilities to
different individuals in that you will
can represent yourself as a
reflection with the idea of SAA and the
serious energy
as a crystal in which a series of
Reflections can be viewed by different
individuals you can think of yourself as
presenting yourself as a
series of probabilities in one
simultaneous presentation
through the intention doorway chakra so
our plexus yourself to perceive that the
plexus yourself to perceive that the
white light of your blending comes
through in much the same fashion though
it may take on a transparent ghostly
milky quality in coming through that
chakra allow yourself to view it as the
SP reflective Alabaster surface of a Mir
or in which other individuals within the
milky substance and fluid can see
reflected from you all probabilities
that they can participate with you in in
that you are constantly fluctuating
between the eye is as you are presenting
them of Quasi planar reality mass energy
conversions thus always functioning as a
timing strobe in it sense for
individuals and yourself
to recognize the many probabilities that
come with each
event
it thank you for sure now one other
thing that you may have already um
included that with the idea of the white
light but U right now I'm increasing the
energy of sancha allowing her or it
feels like a female type energy to come
through more the emotionality to come
through more and allowing myself to step
back more this is why we stay utilize
the solar plexus chakra the chakra of
intention and simply view yourself that
as the energy comes through you it will
pour out of that area and form a magic
mirror of reflection okay all right
thank you very much thank
you are we going to be able to hear from
o again soon soon oh can I ask I'd like
to ask you uh ask you a question about
something uh my big dog Mana red Haack
my little dog the New Edition all right
and do you remember what we shared about
the ideas that they represented yes but
I I couldn't really figure out in terms
of well he's done that with Jamie once
and from an obvious point of view
he must assert his dominance and I
suppose it has something to do with it
has to do with the idea of
tradition tradition he the idea that we
are now
exploring is the uprooting of tradition
in terms of the idea of what is now
comfortable the dog is reflecting that
there is a sensing that you are
uprooting tradition and in this way may
reflect some minute hesitations within
you to exemplify that completely as
completely as you may like to by
indicating that you may have
reservations and allow the traditional
aspect the foundational aspects of your
transformation to conflict a little
to conflict a little
bit with the new elements of sensitivity
mhm interesting now in terms of uh
negative emotions that we mentioned
earlier uh obviously when this happened
I got very scared obviously well I did
get very scared all right allow yourself
to give love equally to both and in this
way nurture them both and let them both
know as a representational symbol to you
and yourself within as you nurture them
you are nurturing yourself to understand
that you can
blend the idea that you are not getting
rid of anything that something that is
tradition is not losing its place but
simply in this way forming a new
tradition okay seeing a reflection of
the new within itself and coming to equal
new within itself and coming to equal
terms with it so that both are
comfortable within the Blended
environment okay understand that thank
you um the the question related to that
was that when I got so scared I was sort
of comparing that emotion to those 50c
anger kind of thing it was
like my heart was beating real fast
right and it wasn't the fear I think
that we were talking about earlier it
was just a reaction just like when you
have the 15 C second anger all right but
that energy accelerated you so that you
could form a blending of those supposed
dichotomies thank you very much so that
your fear could be channeled into the
idea of
compassion outwardly rather than fear
inwardly okay thank you very
muchy one moment
yes what's going on
well now that you have allowed yourself
the opportunity of
opportunity of
reflection of release and
centering how do you stand with
yourself um I feel well I feel much it's
more centered and much different now
than I did a little while ago all
right you have made the choice to do so
it is totally under your
control recognize that as far as life is
concerned you are not asleep at the
wheel you are going where you need to be
going exactly as fast as you need to get
[Music]
there is there any anything else you
wish to share at this
time
well I have of course a million
questions of course why of course if you
have a million questions you have one
answer for each and every one of
them questions are only answers that are
separated from
yourself again if you can even conceive
of the notion it does not matter whether
you put into a form you call a question
or not the conception even of a question
shows you that you contain the
information put it in question form is
only having the information separate
from yourself to act as a reflection to show
yourself to act as a reflection to show
you what you do contain as a
reminder simply because you are used to
receiving Reflections from seemingly
outside so you create the information
within yourself to come to conscious
recognition from an unconscious state of
being by creating something that is a
form in which you can recognize it
consciously a form you will allow
yourself to recognize it consciously in
a [Music]
[Music]
question this does not mean you cannot
ask one
oh okay the being that I that appeared
before me last week I'm I'm confused
about the being that appeared before me
last week as to whether it was outside
of myself or a higher version of myself
or an entity wantan to be channeled or
may I ask you a
question what difference would it make
well it would make a lot of difference
because then I would I would feel better
you would feel better if I knew how to
address this person I me it's impolite
impolite right that is a concept in your reality
right that is a concept in your reality
yes do you think that the Consciousness
thinks you are being
impolite well I don't know what yes you
do what they what do you think the
Consciousness thinks if the
Consciousness were something that you
would allow yourself to think it is how
would you think it would think
[Music] pretend you know what it is pretend I
pretend you know what it is pretend I
know what it is
guys right now pick one pick anything
pick anything what is
it I'll let you get away for a while
with pretending so your choice does not have
pretending so your choice does not have
to be chiseled in
steel pretend it is something anything
will do what is it okay I'll I'll
pretend that it is
a wide old being from long ago and far
away or in the future and far away all
right some an outer all right being
rather than an inner all right although
later I will ask you again what is the
difference however for now it is a wise
old being from far away past future who
knows now since it is in your estimation a
now since it is in your estimation a
wise old
being what do you think it thinks of
well I think it must think I'm pretty
swell and love me a lot right you mean
exactly as you are yes no matter whether
you know what to call it or not yes then
what difference does it make why not
simply relate to it as you feel like
relating to it it doesn't care what you
call it it will still relate with you it
won't be
offended okay I guess I have an
expectation that it's going to introduce
itself with a name like everybody else's
entity seems to have names it might it
might not everybody else's entities
don't always have names
could call it Jones yes you
could good a vibration as
any a lot of Jones IND don't have
names all
right then by simply
granting yourself the equality of
knowing that however you wish to
interact with it you will be able to
keep up with the Joneses [Music]
[Music]
simply recognize that if and when a
labeling of any type is necessary it
will be
there in whatever form it needs to be
there if it isn't there you don't need
one yet relate to it on whatever level
you are relating to it
upon Call It Whatever you will it
doesn't matter the important idea is
simply to relate to it as as you feel so
inclined let the interaction
commence I felt a tiny little bit of
fear and then I was afraid that feeling
the fear would put it off a little bit
so once again what you are receiving
because of the definition of your
understanding of what it is it is
nonjudgmental it is not going to be put
off okay but it is going to wait for you
to make up your mind whether you want to
interact or
not and not need so
many proper
formalities of etiquette before you will
let let it be all right to interact
with it will be comfortable in whatever
house you
provide oh okay that is its
oh okay that is its
nature I thought maybe I had
to abide by some regulations
only that you love
yourself and stop pushing yourself so
hard all right yes thank
you one of
the greatest difficulties I have in
opening myself up to and realizing the
synchronicity of all
is the feeling of vulnerability
vulnerability good one vulnerability is
not weakness do you think it
is um no I think there's a strength in a
strength vulnerability is
strength vulnerability complete vulnerability pay
vulnerability complete vulnerability pay
attention follow along is being open to
everything being open to all that
is being open to all that is is being
connected to all that is being connected
to all that is is a position of ultimate
strength vulnerability is
strength it is trust okay it is knowing
that you open yourself up to all that
is then you will be supported by all all
that is because all that is once you
allow yourself to recognize yourself as
an integral integral
Integrity integral part of all that
is you then create yourself to function
like an integral part and all that is
would not be all that is without
you therefore vulnerability is strength
by definition
judgment is what creates the feeling of
weakness not
vulnerability judgment on yourself right
yes there is nothing
else there is no one else to judge
Judgment of others is Judgment of
yourself judgment from others if you
accept it is Judgment of
yourself you follow me yes there are a
lot of different frequencies
energy the idea of unity is to Grant
equal validity to all the diversity
within creation again allowing all the ways all
creation again allowing all the ways all
that is has of expressing itself to be
equal on their own
terms does not mean it has to
affect your
life just because you recognize that
there are other frequencies doesn't mean
that one of those frequencies has
anything at all to do with the light you
know your frequency to be if you simply
recognize that it has nothing to do with
you okay just because you are quote
unquote exposed to the reality that other beings
exposed to the reality that other beings
have chosen other ways to live and other
ways to present their version of all
that is to you doesn't mean that you
have to feel it as being forced down
your throat
okay I personally am have been very
influenced by other energies in my
environment is that just it is your
choice to be influenced nothing
influences you but you
nothing they are
offerings how would you like to be
influenced by old
pollution yes
no yes thank you no thank
you it is up to you to be
influenced but you create your version
of that gift in your reality if you are
experiencing it you have to create it
for yourself in order to experience it
so all you are doing is agreeing that it
would be for you an appropriate thing to
create if you simply understand that the
tool you are being offered is equal to
any other tool is valid if you should
decide to accept it it will serve you
because you do not accept anything
else but if you simply recognize that it
is a tool you do not need and that you
can learn what you need to learn in
other ways in ways you consider to be
more positive then simply recognize that
it does not have to manifest in your
life that if you recognize what the
purpose would be should you have
accepted that idea then you can also
recognize that the same purpose can be
served by creating another way in which
it can manifest in your life one that is
more relevant to the vibration you know
is true for
you does that assist
you yeah
but I still have difficulty with it do
you understand that the phrase I still
have difficulty with it is only a
belief okay why do you insist that that is a
okay why do you insist that that is a
part of your
reality probably because it always has
been so
what one moment is not connected to the
next now is
now has nothing to do with the past
unless you choose to make a connection
the present is not a result of the past
now is now it is always a new now just
because you may choose to Define each
and every now as seemingly similar to
the last one does not mean it has to be
okay then what's your advice
for um clearing oneself of these fixed
ideas what I just told you recognizing
that every single moment in time is its
own separate now now is now and not the
now you used to be a moment
ago the only things you experience in
any given now
are the result of what you define your
reality to be according to what you
believe it should be redefine your
reality in other words if you simply
recognize that you have a choice between
the preference the opportunity to believe it
preference the opportunity to believe it
is difficult for me it is easy for me
which one do you prefer well
prefer well
which one do you prefer it is difficult
for me to change it is easy for me to
change which one do you
prefer you are making your choice right
now because you are choosing to make it
difficult to choose a
preference which one do you prefer the
difficult why
obviously if you prefer it to be
difficult cuz I need to learn from it it
must serve you
however you can also understand that the
opportunity to choose to prefer that it
is easy is always just as equal a choice
at any given
moment at any moment whatsoever you have
the option of saying all right I am
through with the belief that it is
difficult now I will choose that it is
easy and as soon as you truly do choose
it it will be
easy thank you understand something once
again change is the only constant in the
universe things are always changing
always transforming are they not yes
then recognize that is what happens anyway
recognize that is what happens anyway
what you think always stays the same is
never the same never every moment is a
new moment even when it seems to be the
same as the last moment it is a new
version of the idea you are creating the
idea that there is a continuity you are
creating in the new moment a continuance
of the idea that nothing has
changed that is how you create the
scenario that makes it seem as if
changing is difficult you are doing it
all the time but you are changing into
ideas that allow you to think nothing has
that allow you to think nothing has
changed but that is the definition you
are creating if I'm not the same me that
I was a minute ago okay
and come on you are getting
it well what happens to Identity and
where does memory come into play a very
good identity your personality construct
in its innocense an artificial construct
created of three things belief emotion
and thoughts it is a prism through which
the white light of your Consciousness is
broken down into the spectrum of the
physical reality your identity is always changing
reality your identity is always changing
you as a person is always
changing the person is not a fixed thing
the Consciousness is in a sense but the
person is never fixed do you not
understand that you yourselves recog
that many times individuals go through
situations and when they emerge from
these situations you say well you're an
entirely different person aren't you it
is true same Consciousness you recognize
the Consciousness but it is a different
person a different personality which is
the same thing it is an artificial
construct that now has been tailored to
fit the new
idea that the Consciousness is willing
to
be memory is created in the present as
well you may think you are dredging
something up from the past but if you
really stop and understand it and think
about it you recognize you are creating
memory in the
present therefore the idea is that you
will find that many individuals begin to
forget the so-called path in for density
because they are beginning to recognize
that they will know what they need to
know in the present when they need to
know it and do not have to have an
association with the past in order to
know what they need to
know everything is created in the
present everything the present is the only time
everything the present is the only time
in which you ever exist is it
not no matter when you are isn't it
always now
now
well can you recall a time ever when you
could say it is not
now yes or [Music]
[Music]
no yes or no I can look at myself at
other times
you are doing that now okay in other
words let me rephrase it anything you
can ever experience yourself doing is
always now you follow me yes you are
now you follow me yes you are
experiencing the idea of a memory of the
past now when you were quote unquote
living that past it was still now when
you were living it wasn't it uhhuh there
is
always and only ever will be now it is
the only time there is now is it the
same moment all the time it is one
Eternal moment that can transform into
different versions of itself
yes it does so and is so
simultaneously but because you have
created a reality in which you have the
idea of linear time is it does not seem
to be the same moment but it is as we
said all things are one thing in
different manifestations at the same
time including the perception of linear
time that is one manifestation of now
existence because the only time you ever
perceive linear time is from the now you
relate to the past and the future from
the present you do not relate to the
present from the
future you follow me yeah all is now
does that assist
you yeah choose what you wish to be now
all choices are equal all choices are
equal allowing all choices to be equal
is what allows you to choose easily
because then nothing is beyond your
reach they are all on the same level you
follow me
like
you um what I wanted to
um uh talk about was a feeling of of
danger that I have experienced a lot all
right danger danger come on everyone ooh
[Music] ooh good all it has to do with
ooh good all it has to do with
um be with Rec public recognition public
recognition yes being um like my name
being um known okay cuz I'm I'm in the
art and so so well it scares me why why
I don't know it feels like it's from
another life or something to be quite
honest what
life do you think maybe you did a bad
job once and somebody stoned you could
be I don't uh
um I had a dream the other night um that
I was with a group of people in in the
theater he and this
very golden large light Y and it was
very powerful I knew whoever stepped
into it was going to be
killed yeah right so
boy go into it and get killed guys and I
don't know where I would have that here
now but from when I was
younger I felt um here do you know what you are
I felt um here do you know what you are
afraid of being killed yeah being
somehow what does being killed
mean what is
death well not transition I don't that's
not the
fear um then why make a difference
between transformation and
death well maybe that's not the right
word may I suggest what you are afraid
of mhm your own
power yes that's
yes um do you feel that it is something
you might
misuse do you feel that you cannot feel
that extent of your own power without
the idea of continuing to function
within Integrity do you think it will
get out of
[Music] hand I never would I I don't think
hand I never would I I don't think
consciously that I
would misuse it maybe I do unconsciously
I think that
um the responsibility let's do
this right now in your
imagination imagine that you are quote
unquote sucess
successful what does it feel
like well it feels kind good all right
it feels good Define therefore now that
you are feeling good what success
represents what is going on to let you
know you are quote unquote
successful how do you know you are
successful this is let us say an
interview at a time when you are SU
successful so tell
us how do you know you are successful
who let you know this how did you find
out that you were
successful what are some of the signs
well I just know how I feel now how you
feel how do you feel what does that mean
I say what I think you say what you
think yeah I see that is being
successful then freedom of expression is that what
then freedom of expression is that what
you're saying yes that's what I'm saying
all right freedom of expression check
that anything
else are there any other signs that you
needed to allow you to know you were now
successful what other signs did you
create what other
feedback did I create now that you are
successful what's going on are you being
mobbed with adoring fans is this one of
the idas that lets you know you are
successful or is it some other side no
um I'm working with uh I'm meeting a lot
of people people you enjoy working with
yeah and um having ideas that
I new possibil each not just the things
I thought of last year
each give off U sends another person to
me and we create so new forms of
expression yeah same thing freedom of
expression H anything
else a lot of fun dancing more freedom
of expression yes this is not going to
be a very long
article I don't work parttime at the
writer's guil Ty think but
that all right so you are saying that
you prefer not to right all right same
thing mhm so it seems to
mhm so it seems to
me there for that before you allowed
yourself to know that you were
successful something within your belief
system said that freedom of expression
was dangerous mhm so
mhm so
what you are maybe saying is that you
feel that you have created a scenario at some
that you have created a scenario at some
time in your life when you got negative
feedback for expressing yourself freely
and maybe now are afraid to do it
again I didn't catch that yes oh thank
you I am not going to hurt you for
expressing
yourself I can't
no one can only you
can you think that what you have to
share is worth
sharing yes really oh yeah all right you seem
yes really oh yeah all right you seem
very sure oh
boy well I like to I don't know if it's
worth it but same thing me same thing if
that is what is your excitement if that
is what is your preference then it is
worth it for you are willing to be the
individual that you know yourself to be
now recognized if in a so-called past
life or even in the past of your present
life you found that expressing yourself
attracted let us say a negative
reaction then that is simply your
opportunity to recognize that other
individuals can recognize your power and
can can in your situation present you an
opportunity to decide whether or not
that power is something you will choose
to
keep as the last part of the sentence I
go the other individuals
individuals who may recognize that you
are willing to express yourself
freely may find that that causes a
reaction reflection within themselves
since they may not believe they can
Express themselves fully they may not
want to see anyone else do
so so they give you an opportunity to
decide whether you will accept the
belief that if they can't do it or don't
think they can do it that you shouldn't
or that you still can regardless of what
they have chosen for themselves and
recognize that in your willingness to
continue to express yourself freely you
offer them the best opportunity to see
in you reflection in which they can also
choose to express themselves
freely thank you well thank you
one moment you are a
gift your own unique
manifestation of all that
is by always being fully willing to
express yourself as that gift you will
always be supported by all that
is again saity live
live
life act it
out love
it it is what you are you are life
itself Breathe It In Breathe It
Out The Golden Globe is your own power
and it has the power to
transform you from the child that was
that was
restricted into in your terms an adult
that is
Limitless the child in a sense while
always with you is in fact
dead so in this way
recognize that if death has allowed for
the birth of an adult that is
Limitless for only the aspect of the
child that you were holding on to is
what felt
repressed you know you know children
should be seen and not heard that sort
of thing
mhm now you can be seen and heard and
you will be
enjoyed I thank you thank you thank
you um in relation to the idea that we
come to this planet as a learning planet
do we take on the uh do we choose before
coming to this planet uh as a school
room and C to certain individuals and
certain basically yes um certain yes
circumstances people yes yes so
a certain person there is no accident
okay but then at the time and point
where it becomes uncomfortable
uncomfortable uncomfortable
uncomfortable uncomfortable that may be
part of the lesson okay would you then
consider that to
be a place where you could see it
differently and send love and release
that or would you say that that's an
indication for parting can be again the
idea is that it does not have to
translate into discomfort but simply the
recognition that the vibration is not
representative of your particular
vibration you don't not have to allow it
to translate as far as discomfort so if
you had Harmony up until a certain point
and then you got you still have Harmony
you may have a different
definition of your vibration and another
individual's vibration but recognizing
that difference and granting equality
and validity to it still creates Harmony
even if it defines the physical reality
as something that will separate that is
still a harmonious
decision so but you also could you you
could create the idea of staying
together too yes you could but would you
use the IDE would you then go back to
the idea that there is a overall
predestined choice that we have made in
this planet what we are sharing with you
is to Simply allow your physical reality
to be an obvious reflection of what you
have chosen to experience and if you
follow mind that there are in your terms
unlike vibrations where there used to be
like vibration then it is an indication
that things are changing according to
the path and the plan you created
yourself to
be the way to find out if it is going to
stay around is to Let It Go for
understand that even if it seems to stay
around by changing it is not the same
situation anywhere you follow me okay yeah
anywhere you follow me okay yeah
go that a sister yeah thank
um I have myom but I wanted to ask you
um you talked one night about trust
being an activating
Force um could you reflect on that some
more I found that to be very useful to
me I've been thinking a lot about it and
I wondered if you could give some more
dimensions for me
it is simply your willingness to
understand that every idea comes
complete with all the ingredients
necessary for the manifestation of that
idea that nothing comes
uncomplete so so that if you are willing
to be an idea and know beyond the shadow
of a doubt that that is simply the idea
that represents the vibration that feels
best to you then everything that will be
necessary to support you in being that
idea will automatically
synchronistically be presented to you in
your life opportunities you can act upon
that will always reinforce the idea you
are willing to be and if you go with
your feelings about a situation and the
things that you that you think you need
for that situation aren't fair you don't
need them then you don't need
correct allow yourself to be open to the
fact that whatever you do need is there
by
definition simply assume you have
whatever you need and therefore if you
need anything else it will be there
they just go with your feelings at all
times excitement is the
excitement is the
vibration your physiological translation
of the vibration that represents the
path you chose to be follow what
exactly I like and I want to ask you one
other thing um the animal kingdom the
mineral Kingdom and the vegetable
kingdom are they all the beings or
entities in those kingdoms are they
evolving toward the Human Experience
in a sense but recognize again that only
from your point of view is time linear
right therefore this is a simultaneous
occurrence it is not that they are so to
speak exactly
evolving your concept through time is of
evolution right you may find that it is
just as valid to look at it as if you
decided in this way to have an entire
series of human reincarnations in this
way and then in its ense after the fact
perhaps project your Consciousness into
the idea of the mineral Kingdom just
speak because now because of what you have
because now because of what you have
created linear time to be once you are
in linear time you may then look at the
circumstances as having projected
yourself into the mineral Kingdom first
and then the human Kingdom later simply
because you think of it as an
evolutionary process okay but in this way there is
process okay but in this way there is
the idea of Consciousness transforming
into other types so to speak of
Consciousness yes I was just wondering
if we would experience all aspects of
the physical
experience like the mineral vegetable
anal and if we would do it if you wish
to look at it in a linear progression
you may look at it this way the idea is
that you were first and foremost
non-physical so you got used to
physicality in varying stages of
complexity arriving so to speak where
you are now and moving
on and and because the human is a more
aware supposedly a more aware or as we
that would be the end of the line it is
aware in a different way in a way that
allows for
self-reflection whereas the majority of
other Consciousness that you are
describing simply knows what it is
without the need for
self-reflection could that be a higher
form of being is knowing what you are in
a sense but recognize that it is in your
terms higher to have had the reflection
and then includeed in the knowingness so
it just goes around kind of you
experience it all and then you evolve on
other things out of the
phys okay thank you very much you you
sure sure all right you then you me you okay
sure all right you then you me you okay
thank you um could you could you talk a
little bit about the power of prayer the
power of using like your attention and
louder um the power of prayer yes it is
being in communication with all that is
it is knowing and recognizing the
connection it is recognizing that that
is what you are it is again once again
the allowance of
synchronicity that is
prayer what about like praying for
another you can always feel that you are
connected to everyone everything and
always radiate your compassion for them
but recognize that the idea of praying
for someone else does not necess barely
have to include the idea that you are
reinforcing that you think they need
it because then you are only sending the
vibration that they are something less
than what you imagine they should be the
idea is simply that you support them as
they are and Trust know that what they
have chosen to be will serve them and
that they can choose to recognize it and
then choose what they
prefer that is how you pray for someone
else you follow yes what about for
yourself we have already discussed that
the idea of Simply
trusting that your life as it
is is what you have chosen it to be that
you are in control of everything you
experience that it serves you let it and
you will see how it
does then you will choose what
prer praying again is simply being in
touch with all the different levels upon
which it exists and trusting that how
any particular level manifests itself is
the result of being in touch with all
the other levels and not the result of
not being in
touch did you catch that prayer is the
trust that in this way what is happening
in your life is the result of being in
touch with all levels of yourself and
not the result of not being in touch
trust that is direct communication to
all that is which is
prayer well that eventage your question
thank you yes this Friday um is a very
you yes this Friday um is a very
sign congratulations thank you but it's
bringing and it's bringing up a lot of
emotionality congratulations
again oh more surprise congratulations a
lot of surprise I want
toit maybe some of your help and what
are you going to do now that's the
interesting part I don't know yes you do
what excites you well I have a lot of
things that are called that I call
projects yes do any of them excite you
yes and many of them are taking the form
of businesses which or one particular
business which can happen and what's
happening is I realized the last 15
years were a struggle for me oh right
and it was a profession that I did out
of necessity to raise my family and I'm
at a point where I don't have out ofice
out of choice but not but I didn't
understand the metaphysical practice
doing now and didn't even realize how
much of a struggle it was so by choice
I'm choosing the point is I'm choosing
to not struggle in this new
congratulations okay and i' i' I'm going
through almost like a sadness because
I'm starting remnants of your judgment
that is all no but I'm starting to
remember with fondness some of the
actual struggle what I used to think was
a negative thing I'm I don't know why
this is happening yes you do you are
integrating you are allowing everything
in your life to be equal to everything
else and let it serve
you so the memories you are creating
from the present of the past are now
Bond it doesn't feel painful if feels
almost Melancholy and and something happened
Melancholy and and something happened
which I I which brought this to my
Consciousness which is why I had because
I'm sweating and telling you this I'm
experiencing not a fear but there's a
lot of emotion around it yes um you are
vibrating accelerating
combining amalgamating yesterday was my um
amalgamating yesterday was my um
daughter's sixth grade graduation and it
represented the culmination of the years
of child wearing that I feel I don't
have to be so involved in and so it's
another example of this transition where
I've accomplished something and they
have a symbol where you go through a
graduation ceremony it was very
beautiful and my whole family was there
and the whole experience was another
form of integration very pleasant
experience that night which was last
night I lit a candle um behind the
crystal that I often use for meditation
and I can see through the crystal well
if I want to open my eyes the flame
flickering and I left it on all night
which I did many times just when I was
waking up this morning in those early
hours as we speak about um I had a like
an experience which felt like I was
actually experiencing this and I was
judging it thinking about it in my mind
the experience was I saw the flame
through the candle go out and I said to
myself in my dream that's an amazing
thing I tuned into the crystal just as
the flame was going out okay in my dream
in my dream today okay I don't know how
much time left but all of a sudden I
smelled this awful smell in real life
and the whole part of the candle had
cracked the glass and the wax was all
over and huge Flames leftt up about
maybe 2 ft High and the thing was on
fire and I smelled it which brought me
awake I jumped out of bed and I blew it
out and I put the thing outside because
it was you know a lot of smoke and all
day long today I've been affected by
this thinking we bring things to us that
we have to learn from what did I bring
this to myself for what what do I need
to learn from this and I had a a an
insight into that and I want to share
that with you share well I I felt that
in my bringing my Consciousness to the
dream state of the candle in the crystal
okay I extinguished my old life okay I a
certain part of my old the past is
literally going out right but a new
flame is emerging and it really happen
Okay in real life the fire ignited and
it's it's literally knocking me I'm very
tired I'm exhausted you will get used to
it as you blend your dream reality and
your physical reality into one reality
it will ease
up you are removing the separation
between the two levels because both are
real you have Blended them in that
incident and begun to accelerate
anything that tires you out is only
Remnant judgment you will
acclimate you are beginning to live your
dream literally fourth density symptom
congratulations so the fatigue is just
part of the process for
now and I feel like I've lost that spark
of enthusiasm when you say the spark of
wanting of of motivation to live your
life I mean this is tiring me out to the
point where I don't I just want to sleep
you know s sleep yeah form the
connection that will allow you to know
that when you wake up you will still be
dreaming and always awake when you are
asleep you will blend them as you say
since you are creating it to take time
give it some time go easy on yourself
you have just graduated take a [Music] [Music]
vacation you
yay um I wanted to share something um
last week I was channeling my friends
and uh when it was all over um I was getting
uh when it was all over um I was getting
up and I realized that I didn't need to
channel them anymore that um I I just
knew and I realized since then that I
had actually integrated with him oh
thank you thank you
and uh it it it is very nice by here and
um I've also noticed some other things
happening um okay I've
noticed that um my business has gotten
very very busy and at the same time I
have a lot less time okay when you
integrate you create less time yes so in
this way simp we recognize that the time
you have is all the time you need
okay okay and then one other thing I
noticed is my
husband it's like he's grasping for me
uh like he feels like I'm
disappearing show him you are not
disappearing simply allow the individual
to see in you a reflection of the
potential within himself to know that
nothing is ever lost
okay that a relationship continues
forever no matter what the definition thank
you our perception at this time of the
golden ring the vibrational tone that
ring the vibrational tone that
represents the blending you have created
fora
good I'm so intrigued by your
definitions of emotions I just have one
more uh what is worry wor worry worry
excuse me wor worry w o r r y black
of it seems such a chronic state for
such for me chronic chronic chronic I
know are you worried about
it understand that is when you allow
yourself to trust that you can live in
the moment
now then nothing will be
chronic anymore there won't be the sensation of
anymore there won't be the sensation of
the idea of the cre of time for there to
be anything chronic
within follow me
m only separation and judgment create
time more time and allow enough time for
things to happen chronically like
reincarnation than you yeah
um I would like ask an
assistant in guidance I have a daughter
who's 14 and um I find with
the idea of judgment I find it very
difficult not to be judgmental with my
daughter simply in the area of getting
her to do schoolwork and just the
regular things that you do with
teenagers so she has taught you that it is easy
so she has taught you that it is easy
for you to judgmental
judgmental
yeah but I don't like it I I don't do
it well I feel that the area I have
difficulty is I feel the responsibility
to have
her understand Reading Writing learning
her school work if you are willing to be
responsible to her then you don't have
to be responsible for
her that's where the it gets uh
difficult is if you say so yes I
do uh what are you learning in creating
such a difficulty of
communication [Music]
[Music]
um I'm not sure cuz I'm fighting with it
all the time what I would like to do is
have her how about
discussing or have you her feelings on
what it is she is learning
uh this it's uh I have there's not a
high interest all right what is there a
high interest
in
um at this present time it there doesn't
seem to be too much have you asked um do
you think you have presented yourself in
such a way that you would feel
comfortable in telling
you not recently but why don't you find
out what the interest is that is there
and perhaps by sharing the ideas that
can be learned from that you can adapt
the interest in ways that will allow
that individual your daughter to adapt
the energy in her own ways to allow
there to be the learning that needs to
be
there if you allow the individual to
learn in their own terms with the energy
that they Define to be what will allow
them to learn rather than enforcing a
particular methodology upon them which
you may think is the only way in which
somebody can learn
I don't I I personally actually I I left
out uh the aspect of my husband who is
much has a much stronger viewpoint on
enforcing uh that she do her school work
and that stuff and I feel that I have to
carry his torch and I'm I'm very tired
getting heavier yeah I don't want to do
that all right then again you can share
with him as well the understanding that
to find out what is the driving
motivation of another indiv individual
is what will allow you to see how you
can suggest to the other individual how
they can use their own driving
motivation to learn what they want to
learn thank you well thank
you recognize you have all chosen to be
with each
other yes you are all teachers and Learners
Learners
sure then be in your terms a few moments
remaining for this interaction yet what
do you mean by being responsible too I
understand the part about that being
responsible
also being responsible to someone is
being the most complete version of
yourself you can be so that they have an
accurate reflection of you you see
themselves within being fully who you are allows
within being fully who you are allows
them the opportunity to you see within
you opportunities that they can then
choose for themselves if they desire to
that is how you can assist someone but
not taking responsibility for what they
have chosen to be or that is their
choice right with with uh children it
can be a problem I know I have a can be
a one well a challenge or whatever it is
a
situation I have a 15-year-old son I was
listening to her talk and I I um would
you like to get the son and daughter to
sh
perhaps there may be much in common for
the families to
discuss with him I realize he has a need
to Define himself now on his own terms
and I want to be comfortable in allowing
him to do that and still be harmonious
together then you can share the
understanding that you have of what is
being done and simply reflect to that
individual that every individual is as
powerful as they need to be to be
anything they want without having to
hurt anyone else to get
it
yay so Define a way and simply recognize
that if the individual comes upon a
definition that requires that they
enforce or Force themselves upon someone
else there is an easier
way okay yay I have a question regarding
the um um the animal Consciousness say
to take the animal conscious and human
consciousness now I have an
understanding from Readings of other um
channeling that the animal kingdom
represented its own Consciousness and
didn't really cross into the human
consciousness that they they could
evolve in their own densities in a sense
yes but that're also is the opportunity
for all levels of consciousness to
transform into other levels of
consciousness this is not a
reincarnational experience this is
something quite beyond that idea so then
you're saying both ideas are accurate
and Heather presentative yes um is there
any way you can expand that we would
understand the idea Beyond
reincarnational perhaps you may look at
it this way you are reincarnational in
the idea of animal Consciousness as
animal Consciousness as long as you
remain within the idea of the
identification as animal
Consciousness after quote unquote a long
time so to speaks Maybe there is the
opportunity for the animal Consciousness
or the fragment thereof to recognize its
connection perhaps to other different
levels of consciousness and form an
attachment to it and draw to itself
assimilations of different portions of
the consciousness of all that is so that
it can also interact in that way but
then it is no longer the idea of animal
Consciousness and not exactly the same
thing that made the decision to do so in
the first place so it still has remained
as animal Consciousness what has become
human is its own reality and does not
relate specifically to to the idea that
it is the animal that has become human
oh so is it look kind of like a split
like a sort of kind of okay well that's
F that's that's good for now thank you
right uh last week you U mentioned the
time of 10 13 years uh before you would
uh come here physically and I before it
was possible yes um and I take that to
mean that
our um blending into the fourth density
will uh determine that ni um whereas at
another time you would said it was six
to seven years I have to say that I like
the six to seven years then perhaps that
will be your reality I see oh great then
you be it right
out the other question I
have um is that I've been experiencing
particularly now all through the evening
almost a sense that I could um jump out
of my skin it's a it's a type of tension
that seems to originate from the solar
plexus yes and the chakra of intention
creative pressure very much so the
expansion of yourself to all different
levels of yourself in physical terms
jumping out of your skin yeah all right
then another interesting uh thing to
that is that um a year ago September I
was told that I have a growth on my left
ovary in addition to the fact that my um
uterus is enlarged now I've been trying
to trying yes trying I I I can't grasp
exactly what that represents um there
those are reproductive organs there is
something growing there it is not
malignant or anything it's just I I had
it checked by a sound scan and I wonder
if you have any insight into that do you
have children no do you want to yeah
when a few years
well anytime but are you sure think
about it well they have when would it be
in your term truly
convenient when there's a a daddy there
for starters all right and um that would
be convenient probably any
time there are numerous daddies around
but but as far as them being fathers is
another question so in this way what you
are saying is that it is entirely all
right with you to put some sort of a
regulatory phenomena upon your ability
to reproduce at this time
absolutely and that's what this
yes a growth on my ovary that's
fascinating that that's absolutely
fascinating I'm having a baby and it's a
it's it's just
thing let it say the I it is that it
represents to you the plugging of a
doorway oh it you until the timing is
correct okay that's that really
okay that's that really
indicate that's so simple that uh that's
lovely be in touch with the
Consciousness you will understand the
timing you will feel
it and in that
way the insistence will be removed
insistence
INS What insist insistent
oh got you is everything so literal many
times yes for you will find that what
you have created your language to be is
usually a reflection of what you believe
your reality to
be do different words have different
energy frequency okay they represent the
concept different
frequency many times again even what you
have said though we understand the way
in which you usually mean it the idea of
something being a
maing mhm you cannot faom it right you
are lost in that's
amazing that tell ourselves something
listen to what we're saying yeah this
will give you
opportunity to understand that many many
more things than you realize are
conscious choices if you would but
listen to what you say about your
realities I have difficulty
understanding this that is a
choice listen to yourself you are
choosing that reality I have difficult
wait a
minute why all right it has served
me I have ease of
understanding oh my
it was that easy now I understand
understand stand under
support we will at this time extend to
you the
reminder that if you are willing now to
understand the idea we have described
synchronicity one two all the
synchronicity act like it with
integrity explore the idea of
coincidence and synchronicity in the
literature that is available in your
civilization the coincidental occurrence
of all of you doing so at the same time
will increase the synchronicity in your lives
lives
explore we thank you for the interaction
of the gift of your Consciousness this
night of your time you and us all that
is is the sharing that continues forever
we bid you excited
synchron and a fond and
loving you haven't heard Dr is going to
be at my home and
also so if you can kind we'd love to
have You' got some brochures Craig has
some brochures here so if you want to
stop by one of us on the way out and
grab one lots of Flyers with maps in
Easy Direction CL the houses in near here and
Direction CL the houses in near here and
if you want to if you want to come and
know you can you can give us a check
tonight $12 otherwise it's $15 at the
door thank you [Music]