All right, I'll say how are you all this
evening of your time as you create time
to exist.
Allow us to begin this interaction this
evening of your time with a few more
ideas of sharing of the individual paths
that you have chosen to be in this
physiological life this time around. In
this way recognize once again that even
though you are as you understand it a
reincarnational being the you that you
are right now is the only time you will
ever be this you. This is the only one
life you as you are now have to live.
Therefore, in the idea that we have been
sharing with you for quite some time of
your time about the willingness, the
conviction and the expression of the
unique individual that you have created
yourself to be the unique facet that you
are of the multi-dimensional crystal of
the infinite creation.
more and more and more that you are
willing to express what you know to be
true for
you, then more and more and more do you
make as an individual, yes, as an
individual, a difference in the entire
structure of the society in which you
exist. For you will find that you are
connected to everything and any change
you make within yourself affords an
opportunity for the entire community,
the entire civilization if you wish to
call it that in which you exist to be
able to then draw upon the change you
have made. If they prefer within the
reality, the unique reality that they
are themselves, to share that reality
with you, then by you creating your
unique version of what you know to be
true for you, do you give them the
opportunity to see in you. Yet one more
way that there may be of expressing
themselves and living the lives they
have chosen to live. Thus you add to the
overall ability of the society you are
in to have that many more options of
choice that many more recognitions of
expansiveness. Recognize as we have said
in this way there is no one way to do
anything. If there is only one way there
would only be one person. Look around
you. Each and every single one of you is
one of the ways that the infinite
creation has of manifesting itself.
What you quote unquote brought with you,
what you feel to be that within you that
moves you in life
is your very simple and clear
recognition of the path that is correct
for you.
Your excitement, that which we have
spoken of with you many times, what you
call excitement, your knowingness, that which
excitement, your knowingness, that which
you know to be true for you or that in
life which excites you, which moves you,
that is your cognition of the path you
chose to be. That's what excitement is
for. It is there to let you know that if
you simply follow the idea that excites
you, you will be congruent, if you will,
synchronistically harmonious, if you
will, with the original idea that you
chose to express yourself as in this
physiological life. That is why you can
follow that excitement and recognize
that your life can proceed to unfold
without effort, without strife, without
struggle. We do not mean you will remove
the idea of discovery. You will not
remove the idea of growth. You will not
remove the idea of challenge if you
will, but you will alleviate the ideas
of struggling, of suffering, of
striving, of pain. You do not need
those. Those are tools that have served
you well in the past. But you are now a
new you. This is the transformational
age upon your world when you are
beginning to recognize that there are
many more levels of consciousness to be
in communication with than you
previously conceived of as a society.
And that cognition alone in and of
itself means that therefore you can now
transform your life, your individual
life, and therefore the opportunity of
all the lives upon your planet, you can
transform them in ways that are
indicative of your new awareness. For if
you are aware that there are many levels
of consciousness, many different beings
within creation, then you are aware that
everything can function as a whole, can
function as a unit, everything can be
shared. Individual consciousnesses and
whole groups of consciousness can be of
service to other groups, be of service
to individuals. All can be explored
together within ecstasy, within love,
within light, within life. In this way,
therefore, draw upon your certain
knowledge that there are scapes, if you
will, landscapes, spiritscapes,
consciousness scapes of existence with
which you are intimately intermingled,
intimately melded and intimately
blended. And with that assurance within
yourself, allow yourself to expand in
the representational way that is correct
for you into the understanding that you
are spirit. The idea of the so-called
spirit. The idea of the so-called
spiritual paths that many of you have
been seeking as you say upon your planet
is the simple cognition that you are
spirit. Everything you do in a sense therefore
Everything you do in a sense therefore
is
spiritual. The idea is now for you to
decide whether you wish to exemplify and
reflect and express yourself in a
positive or a negative
spirituality. But the idea is that now
you can know you are spirit. You are one
with all the different levels.
You have conceived the idea that there
are in fact
levels out of the one homogeneousness of
the infinite
creation. It is your doing. It is your
own illusion if you will. Not that that
invalidates it for it has served you
like anything has served you. It has
brought you to where you are
now. Therefore, do not deny and do not
invalidate that of your past.
Incorporate it knowing it has brought
you to where you are. Treat it and think
of it as a stepping
stone. Love it for the experience that
it brought you so that you could be
understanding what you are understanding
now. And then by loving all of those
ideas that in their own timing may have
seemed to be so painful, so negative. By
loving them now, you will then create
the type of past. For you do create your
past from your present, not the other
way around. You will then create the
type of effect coming from your past
that will support you in the present
will allow you to create whatever type
of new present you desire once again
without struggle without strife but only
within joy of expression within ecstasy
in that way.
Are you all following along? Yeah.
Now, last week of your time, we
discussed the idea of your sensitivity
to electromagnetic shifts upon your
planet. Some of which may or may not be
expressed as you call it
sismically. This evening of your
time, after what you call your break
time, we will engage, if you will, if
you are willing, with you in what you
may call, a visualization, a meditation
to allow you to begin to function, each
and every one of you, and collectively
function as a
valve, so to speak, through which the
electromagnetic field of your world can
be channeled. And any energy that you
perceive might have the potential of
manifesting in your world in a negative
way can then be rechanled through you
and manifested in a positive way upon
your world. For now you are recognizing
that because you innately deserve
happiness. You do not have to shake
yourselves up or go through trials by
fire in order to believe that you
deserve happiness. And so if you are
willing to take those steps and take
them now, you can then release much of
that energy that may be pent up in that
way, expressing itself or potentially
expressing itself in negative way,
catastrophic ways, and transform that
energy into another type of energy, an
energy that can support and
sustain and enliven and enrich the
entire society in which you live. Use it
creatively. You all follow me? Yeah.
In this way,
therefore, the idea is that all we are
sharing with you and all that any
consciousness is sharing with you at
this time is that you do have the power
to create your lives as you desire them
to be. The idea is to simply wake
up and start
dreaming and live those
dreams. Live those
desires with
knowledge with intention, with
integrity, with
knowingness, with faith, and with trust
and unconditional love.
Sharing. Sure.
You Thank you. I've been having horrend
I've been having horrendous headaches.
Guess you are not alone. There are many
individuals in your society at this time
that are expressing that particular
idea. We were speaking to one of them
just last night of your time. Okay. For
how long? This has been going on that
I've been aware of for several years.
Nice. How long?
How long has it been going on? Yes.
Several years. Can you remember the
counting? When I first noticed it was
back in
198 three or four and it was right at
the front at the time that a friend of
mine's her husband died and I started
noticing right after that every time I'd
have a headache within days to several
weeks something disastrous on the planet
would happen. All right. And it was very
painful. Nice. Again, this is some of
the idea we have just spoken of. The
increased sensitivity to the shiftings
in the electromagnetic field upon your
planet. The electromagnetic field is
what mentality or mind is created from.
Any shiftings, any major shifts that
take place within
any mass mentality in catastrophic ways
will now begin to be felt by various
individuals that are becoming sensitive
to those ideas. The two prominent ways
that you will find that most individuals
upon your planet will interpret this
energy is through the heart or through
the sinus temple area. You are simply
sensitive to it in the upper area. Your
sinuses contain a high degree of
magnetite and in this way it is very
sensitive to any electromagnetic shift
taking place upon your planet. Now the
idea is that it does not have to
continue in a painful way. But the pain
may simply be coming from the fact that
you are still harboring old ways of
doing things. And now that you have
actually expanded your sensitivity in a
new way and are allowing more awareness
of more energy to pass through you, you
are allowing more energy to attempt to
pass through you that is still
constricted by the old beliefs. Thus you
are attempting to force a great amount
of energy through a very small channel
and that is painful. The idea is to open
up, relax in love, light and trust and
faith. And may I ask you a
very standard question at this point?
Okay. Are you doing in life what excites
you the most?
Sometimes. Sometimes. All right. May I
ask you another question? Okay.
What is that thing that excites you the
most? I think the thing that excites me the
I think the thing that excites me the
most is becoming more and more aware and
more and more able and capable and
seeing things for what they are. All
right. Now you can understand that you
are receiving nothing is being forced
upon you but you are receiving guidance
from the individual that you mentioned
to some degree. The idea is that you
made an agreement to receive guidance at
the appropriate timing. But the belief
systems that you bought into within this
physiological reality are still making
it such that the agreement you are
fulfilling now to receive more energy is
going through you in a constrictive way.
All you need to do is begin to open up
in your meditation. Open up in the
realization that you are having
communication with other levels of
consciousness and begin to interact in
earnest in that way and to express
yourself in earnest in that way by
letting that energy flow through you
rather than holding on to it because you
don't know what to do with it. Most of
this is taking place in what you would
call your sub or unconscious framework.
But nonetheless, this does not mean it
cannot become conscious if you are but
willing to have the trust, the level of
faith necessary beyond the shadow of a
doubt to do in life what it is that
excites you the most and to express
yourself in life regardless of how you
may think people will judge what you are
doing. As long as you are functioning
within your integrity and you know you
are not expressing yourself at the cost
of intentionally another individual or a
group it does not matter what other
individuals think of what you are doing.
If you are expressing your integrity
then what is true for you is true for
you. You follow me? Yeah. Now in what
ways have you perhaps perhaps perhaps
imagined that you can give voice that
you can vent that you can channel that
you can express yourself in creative
ways that perhaps you have been
reluctant to do.
I don't know other than the fact that I
feel that I can help and be creative in
many different ways. I know that I'm
receiving all sorts of awareness on
different levels that physically nice I
cannot express but that I know I have
been encountering for some time as a
matter of fact all of this physiological
life um I don't know an answer to your
um I don't know an answer to your
question at this point all right when I
asked you if you were doing in life what
excited you the most and you said
sometimes what are you doing when you
are not doing what excites you the
most likes to do.
Um, there are no such things.
Uh, basically emotional things.
Basically, emotional things such as
probably anger and and grief and all of
that. All right. Now, anger in and of
itself does not have to be a negative
expression. Anger is only alignment. If
you take it any farther than that, then
it becomes what you usually refer to as
the negative anger. The rage, the
frustration, the guilt, the hate. But
the idea of anger in its natural state
is not a negative idea. Anger in its
natural state is simply alignment. You
see a situation, you interact with the
situation, you align relative to that
situation that you see, you align with
what you know to be true for you
regarding that situation. You see your
relative point of view. But the idea of
anger being an unpleasant experience
comes when you then invalidate something
in the situation.
Oh, okay. You follow me? If you accept
that you always encounter in life
situations that are there to reflect to
you different portions of yourself that
you can then integrate so you can be a
more expanded being and then be of
service in the situation. You will not
judge it. You will not invalidate it. It
will not cause frustration. It will not
cause rage. It will not cause negative
anger. Anger may still bring with it
that adrenaline rush that comes with
alignment with self-cognition. But it
does not have to last any longer than
approximately 15 of your seconds and
that's it. If it lasts any longer, you
are invalidating something. Okay. Thank
you. You follow me? Yes.
Grief in this way is generally once
again simply a habitual ritual of
supposition that things can be taken
from you that you are separated from
something at any given time which you
never can be. No matter in what way
things may transform no matter what
appearances may seem to be you are
always always
always in some way shape or form in
connection to something that you have
been in connection with at one point in
your life. Once a relationship is
formed, it goes on
forever. Now the differences that occur
in that relationship as to how it is
defined can change radically. But the
relationship still exists and on some
level you are still in communication
with anyone, anything, any place, any
idea, any situation you have formed a
relationship with. So grief is only the supposition
with. So grief is only the supposition
that you can lose something. And many
times the paradox is is that the grief
itself is the only thing that keeps you
from recognizing you are still in touch.
You follow me?
Oh, laughter.
I have that. All right. Do you have it
when you have the pain in your head? No.
Why not?
I didn't think it was something to laugh
at. It hurt too much. All right. But we
are not saying to laugh at it in an
invalidating way. The idea is to first
of all recognize that it is the product
of your belief systems and it is still
something that represents a change going
on, a transformation going on within you
that can be looked at in a beneficial
way. You are growing. You will acclimate
to the idea and it will not have to be
painful for very long. But the idea is
that if you know it is there for a
positive reason, then why not accept it
with joy? And again the paradox may be
that as soon as you do accept it with
joy your joy and your laughter may
completely and utterly erase the
sensation of pain. Okay. The idea is
that to invalidate yourself is what
continues the pain. Oh no. I have pain.
I'm doing something wrong. What am I not
doing right? Oh no. Oh no. I am
incapable. I am powerless. Oh no. I'm
not in control. Oh no. Oh no. Oh
no. All of these ideas are the
continuence of the separation of a
portion of yourself from the rest of all
that you are. And therefore you actually
create an inability for the totality of
yourself to support and send nourishment
to that particular portion of yourself.
And it is that cutting off through
invalidation that creates pain. All
pain, physical pain, mental pain,
spiritual pain, emotional pain, all pain
is the result of the separation of a
portion of yourself from the rest of the
all that you are that can nurture and
support that portion as well.
It is simply old remnant habits of the
way your society thinks of itself.
Always judging itself, always getting,
as you say, down upon itself for any
particular experience. Always assuming,
and here's the big one, always
assuming that
experiences that at one time perhaps in
your terms were negative, have to always
be so. every time they seem to
reappear. It is only that assumption
that continues to reinforce the
reappearance of those situations in what
you would call a negative
way. When you say I have
chronic pain, well listen to what you are saying
pain, well listen to what you are saying
regardless of what the experience has
been. Well, you say well I say chronic
because I have had it chronically in the
past. All right, we understand that
idea. But every moment is a new moment.
You are always a new you and the present
is not a result of the past. No matter
how much that illusion holds strong for
you in the physical reality. Linear time
is an illusion. Every moment is the
present moment. And it is its own unique
now moment. And any definition you give
to any present now moment becomes
utterly what that moment is regardless
of what your life used to be. You follow
me? Yes. I've been getting that clearly
from you for quite some time. All right.
Now the idea is to recognize in your
relaxed state also this can be of some
assistance and this can be for any one
of you that wishes to partake of this
idea at any time. You are an
electromagnetic being as a physical
being. A headache is the product of the
idea of tensions within the
electromagnetic field within your brain.
In that sense the idea therefore is to
simply recognize yourself as an
homogeneous electromagnetic field.
Envision yourself, if you will, as a
sphere of blue energy, transparent blue
energy. Imagine your body to be a part
of that idea. Not separate from it, but
merged, melded, immersed, and blended.
Simply allow yourself to balance out
that energy and allow it to diffuse
outward to a comfortable distance so
it'll be more expanded. and see within
that homogeneous sphere of blue
electromagnetic energy, no one portion
standing out from any other portion in
color or shape or any other way. Allow
yourself to very gently allow the whole
field to be a homogeneously blended
transparent crystallin blue energy
field. Let all the ideas that represent
pain, the concentrated knots of focus
diffuse into that field. That's one way.
Another way can be all right, you have
the pain. Imagine that field again.
Imagine the pain. Go into your
meditative state. Let yourself relax as
best you can
and allow yourself not in concentration
but in relaxation to focus upon the area
of pain.
Encapsulate the area of pain in a small
blue energy bubble. Focus on it. You are
not isolating it. You are simply holding
it. You are cupping it. You are
caressing it. But you have focused on it
and you know where it is. You have
located it. You have defined its
space-time coordinates within you. Then
gently, gently, gently,
gently, a bit at a time, at whatever
rate you are comfortable, move the
bubble that contains the pain outside of
your body into your electromagnetic oric
field. Let the sensation be one that
simply becomes a type of vibration
rather than the sensation you would
normally attribute to the idea you call
pain. Let it diffuse.
Let it go through the membrane of your
oric field and pop on the outside. Let
the pain that was inside the bubble
sprinkle back on the surface of the oric
field in a diffused way so that it is
everywhere, spread out evenly. Then let
yourself reabsorb it in a diffused
manner. Now that it is not focused on
any one particular pinpoint area, you
have the ability and the power and the
strength to handle the idea because it
is now so spread out, so diffused. Then
you will reabsorb it at whatever rate
you are comfortable in reabsorbing it.
And that means you can deal with it at a
rate that you are comfortable in dealing
with it. You follow me? I got it. This
is true ideas. Your imagination can
provide you with many more. We thank you
for your sharing. Oh, thank you very
much. Sharing.
You um I've got something to share. Um All
um I've got something to share. Um All
right. And I'm so excited about it. I'm
a little bit afraid I'm just going to
go. This is all right. Okay. Um, last week I
This is all right. Okay. Um, last week I
shared um an experience that I had with
the idea of polarities and exploring
that and having some tremendous areas of
and turbulence just straighten out
completely. Well, I continued exploring
that this week and decided that one area
I would like to explore polarities in
was the area of um relationships that
I've had in the past that have hung up a
bit. If you say so. Okay. Yes, I do. And
in my universe, they hung up for one
reason or another. Either because there
were, from my opinion, negative aspects
to them or something that I didn't
understand about them. Right. Or
something that I was judging myself on
or something I was judging others on.
Okay. Same thing. Yeah. Okay. Right.
Right. So anyway, I went back over
several relationships and just centered myself
relationships and just centered myself
on them and allowed myself to experience
the positive emotions and the negative
emotions that came to view with
no significances. All right, attached.
No judgments attached either self
judgments or judgments on the person or
on the situation we perceive. Right? And
I just allowed that to integrate and I
started just popping off relationships
one after the other and my self began to
expand and expand and expand and I felt
so full of the love of the experience
that I had had both positive and
negative that I was just going crazy
with the exuberance of it. Oh, very
good. How exciting. Very. And plus,
there were things that were being shown
to me about myself, like one thing in
particular that loomed up as a Oh,
loomed. Loomed and showed up as this huge thing
Loomed and showed up as this huge thing
that I have been judging myself with for
eons. And it just went ring your times.
You know, here it is in big bold red
letters and here it is. You can deal
with it. That was absolutely wonderful
and blew me out of my skull.
Thank you. And I will mention that your
synchronicity is most timely. Of course,
by definition, you will find that some
of the ideas we will be discussing after
your break will involve the idea, quote
unquote, as you say, colloquially, of
ringing your chimes. Fantastic. I've got
one more. One more. Um, one relationship
that I explored in that fashion was, and
I think this might help some people that
may have been in similar situations,
maybe. Maybe. Um, there was one
relationship that I had that was a
romantic type relationship that went on
for quite some time and was
extremely high and low. High and low.
Yeah. Turbulent and exciting and messy
and crazy and just all this stuff. All
right. And very exciting. Yeah. And
after it was over, my decision on that
relationship was to file it away in the
section where it has no value and in the
section where we know that that was a
rotten experience and you don't have to
look at it anymore. All right.
Interesting section.
Yes. And the person that was filed away
in that section was really a turkey, you
know. Turkey. Do you understand turkeys?
and not to be not to be communicated
with ever ever again and hopefully not
even ever thought of again. Well, that
is not possible. But go on. Well, I
thought I could see but it was held that
it was held into that position that
filing cabinet and anytime I looked at
it and went don't like that. Right.
Okay. Okay. That is still communication
and thought and of course you are
communicating with all individuals on
many different levels more than you
think. Right. But go on we know what you
mean. Right. Okay. So anyway I took a
look at this experience. Yes. Yes. And I
started to
reexperience visually and with
perceptions. Nice. Little vignettes of
the interaction. Nice. First starting
with some positive ones that I totally
forgot were there and then going into
some negative ones that were just from
my viewpoint some hair raising negative
ones from my experience right well I
don't have any hair to raise so
if you did you know what I mean okay so
anyway it took about 45 minutes of
reviewing and viewing this relationship
and just centering myself with it and
not knocking off any judgments that came
up and knocking off any judgments of
myself that came up in relation to it
and just letting it permeate me. Nice.
And when it was over, the most
incredible the most
love consuming love for this being just
came flooding into my space. My my is
that amazing. What a surprise. Yes. And
the it was just
like I I couldn't contain myself. I felt
like I was splitting at the seam. Yes,
you were. And because that was the real
and true emotion for that being that was
always there and was channeled and ch
not channeled changed with the
polarities of the relationship that we
mocked up to show us certain things and
those significances that I put in there
that held the thing down into the filing
cabinet that said bad lot evil wicked
nasty wrong
all those significances meant like
nothing but a piece of liver. I mean it
was nothing
absolutely I didn't say that totally
myself but it means that it meant
nothing right the significances were
nothing the polarities were nothing the
negatives and the positives were nothing
the experience of life that we
experienced together was fantastic the
highs the lows the the going nutso you
see now you are in synchronous harmony
with what may be termed the higher self
or the oversoul which sees
all experience as pertaining to its
growth. Right? And that is the viewpoint
that come out of it. And it's just like
you also therefore recognize from the
same viewpoint that there is only one
emotion, love, right? And everything is
that it's everything is a variation of
that idea, right? And the things that we
have done with it in order to experience
it and experience different things with
it. It was obvious to me when that
emotion of yuck, this being yuck turned
into fantastic love that they were the
exact same thing. They never changed.
Nothing changed except the lack of
invalidation. Right. Exactly. And the
lack of of pushing out that stuff that I
considered negative and not letting it
be a part of me and let it become the
hole that it became. Thank you very
much. Yeah. Thank you. Yeah. Thank you.
You Thank you.
Thank you.
Um last week you had um you had shared
about last week you had shared a little
bit about um how we create
um for growth reasons uh certain
experiences that
[Music] um to liven things up that that growth
um to liven things up that that growth
occurs I'm getting it confused that
growth occurs sometimes through it life
not being so dull and medioc
Mediocre. Nice. Okay. So, this week I
had the experience of
um I've been I'm feeling a little spy
today, folks. Oh, nothing to excuse.
Okay. It's a very natural way to feel.
It is for me anyway.
I am always spacey as you say. I've been
feeling real detached from everything
and I've been that is now typical
symptom of fourth density
transformation. You are unlocking from
your previous preconceived universe and
you are expanding into infinite probable
universes. You are having infinite
choices. So you feel disoriented,
detached, floating around, not anchored
to any one particular structure.
This is typical. This is the first step
in the recognition of your ability to
choose what you prefer to choose in your
life. Okay. This is a joyous event.
Yes. and what I'm experiencing right
now. I'd like to be able
[Music] to to pref well I prefer a different
to to pref well I prefer a different
reality than what I'm experiencing. And
yet I understand that what I'm
experiencing I need for my growth. So I
am happy. You have only to cease
invalidating what you are experiencing
to be able to enjoy it. Okay. Well, my
car is blown it transmission. states
and um I many of you may create that type of
um I many of you may create that type of
a reflection in your life as you shift
your own gears. Okay.
Okay. Great. That's exactly what um what
I'm coming to right to the realization
of is that my car um and as someone
shared a few weeks ago they had a car
situation. I worked at
Faithfest. Um I worked at uh loving the
car and uh thanking it very much for
giving me this opportunity to see how
um
I was judging my uh acceleration. I
wanted to accelerate at a faster rate
than what I was doing. So um my car was
saying it was stuck in second gear,
which was kind of the way I was feeling.
And um I wanted to get to third gear to
experience relationships
u male female relationships and I was
and you were given a very loving symbol
that in order to get to that next gear
you have to allow the structure as it
used to exist to completely come
apart. The structure that used to exist
cannot handle the type of shifting you
prefer to do. You have to recreate the
structure. That is why you are now in
neutral. Do you follow me? That is the
sign. That is the reflection. That is
the symbol. The old system cannot handle
the change. Create a new awareness.
Create a new
system. That can handle the
change. You follow me? Yeah. I follow
you. I I don't know where to begin to
create a new system. You have already
begun by allowing the old one to
disassemble. You create the new one once
again by simply acting upon that which
moves you, which drives you forward. You
are the
vehicle. Let yourself be moved by that
which obviously moves you and you will
be flowing into the new
system. You follow me?
Let yourself in this state of seeming
disorientation simply recognize that it
is your prime opportunity in that state
to allow whatever needs to be in your
life to be synchronistically attracted
to
you because now you are not in such a
rigidized structure as to prevent what
needs to be there in your life to assist
you from coming into your life.
True. Relax.
Okay. I I I've Oh, easier said than
done.
If you say so.
I don't mean this as a yes, but for
sure. Um what I'm experiencing is that I feel
Um what I'm experiencing is that I feel
very open to
um whatever needs
to to come into my life. Yes. to come
in. And what I've
what I have had the experience of is
that I've um a lot of my old ideas of
relationships and and men. A lot of my
old ideas of relationships and people
that um I used to be attracted to have
been becoming attracted to me. And I'm
able to see that this is not what I
prefer in my life.
Um but what I do prefer I'm not
attracting. And so but yes you are.
First of all what you prefer the first
sign of what you prefer is to recognize
what you don't prefer. And now you are
simply attracting yourself situations
that give you the definition of what you
don't prefer so that you can as you say
hone in on the definition of what it is
you do in fact prefer. So you are
getting reflections of your preference.
You are simply getting them in a way
that allows you to actually define
consciously what it is you do prefer
because obviously you don't yet know. So
you are creating that opportunity in
whatever way you can by attracting
situations you don't prefer so that you
will then have a clearer understanding
of what it is you do prefer and won't
feel like you were wandering around in
the dark. Okay. Well, I had one one
experience of of an individual um when I
went to San Francisco uh on the plane.
Speak up. I had one experience with an
individual on a plane which was a an
experience of an individual I would
prefer and
um he was very spiritually um active and
we had a lot of the same metaphysical
feelings and he was into a lot of
creative stuff. Oh, right. I was saying
this is the kind of individual he was
physically attractive. I mean we had a
lot a lot of connection and I felt that
we that he he felt the same way and he
took my card and I have yet I have yet
to hear from him and I said do not put
expectations upon this idea. If you have
already communicated in any way, shape
or form with that individual, you
already have a
relationship. You are now putting
demands on how you think the
relationship should
manifest.
Relax. Talking to that individual and
discovering each other is a part of the
relationship. Stop pushing.
I don't see how I'm pushing. I'm just
You're saying I've been waiting and
waiting and waiting for this individual.
I haven't returned my call. I hadn't
been trying to call. I mean, I don't
have his number, but I just I've just
been, you know, it was like I thought
maybe last week he Are you waiting for
this individual to call
or are you getting on with your life?
I'm getting on with my life. I'm getting
on with my life. I'm just looking at the
reflection that this individual has to
show me. Yes. And I want to glean from
it whatever. What does it show you?
Share that with me right now if you
will. Okay. Is very simple.
Keep it simple. Keep it basic. What does
it show you? Your ability to interact
with such an individual. What does that
show you? It shows me that I am
attracting um a higher Keep it
simple. What does your ability to
attract such an individual show you? I
want four words.
I want him.
Four words.
words. Um, Um,
[Music]
that is not what it shows you.
[Music] Uh, would you like some assistance?
Uh, would you like some assistance?
Repeat after me.
Okay. I I am am the the same same
Repeat it. I am the same.
That is what attracting that individual
shows you. You are the
same. You have
changed. Only by changing can you
attract an individual who reflects those
ideas to you. So what it immediately
shows you is I am the same. I have
changed.
What you actually want is to know
that. Not so much that you have to have
him. But you have interacted with an
individual that has been willing to
interact with you to show you that you
are now on that
level or more than one of those
individuals will interact with you in
ways that represent what you are
expressing your desire to be. But don't
put a demand on the timing. Simply
assume that now that you have attracted
such an individual, you know you are of
that vibrational frequency, therefore
you will in the appropriate place and
timing attract whatever is necessary.
Okay. Um at the wedding that I went to
when I got to San Francisco, I attracted
two of the same old types that I used to
attract, people who are into drugs and
drinking. And which do you prefer? I
prefer the one on the plane. Then simply
understand that that is the one you make
the conscious decision with to say to
yourself, I am the same. And with the
others, you make the conscious decision
to recognize you are not the
same. Then that reinforces your ability
to create more attraction of the first
type. But as long as you continue to get
used to the idea instead of fully 100%
trusting in the change, you may still
continue to attract for a while the idea
of the other individuals just to let you
know that you have in fact changed just
to remind you.
See what what I had taken from the
attracting the people with the drugs and
the drinking problem that I
was back in my No, no, no, no,
no. Have we discussed with you the idea
that no situation has built-in meaning?
[Music] Yes. No. Maybe. Yes. Yes, you have. Then
Yes. No. Maybe. Yes. Yes, you have. Then
why have you put the meaning that you
have in that neutral situation rather
than simply recognizing it as another
opportunity to know you have changed,
you are different? Why assume that the
situation is representational of a
so-called failure when you have the
opportunity to simply recognize it as an
opportunity to see how much you have
changed? Okay, thank you. I just wanted to say
Okay, thank you. I just wanted to say
what I had what I had shared about um
you you had told me about the rescuing
in my girlfriend situation a few weeks
back and so that was in that that same
week I was getting to see situations in
which I had
um rescued and
Mel's getting involved with alcoholics
for example were situations in which I
used to be able to play rescuer so I
said Okay, this is an opportunity for me
to see that I don't need to clay this
anymore and I don't prefer to do that.
You do not have to be a rescuer. You
cannot rescue anyone, but you can be of
assistance to them by being the fully
changed individual you know yourself to
be because then you reflect back to them
their opportunity to change as well. You
can be assistive to them in any way,
shape or form that they have attracted
you into their lives to be of
assistance. But it does not have to be
anything in any way, shape, or form that
is a reflection of the ideas that you
are actually living. Nor does it have to
be in any way, shape, or form depleting
to you to be of service to them. By
simply reflecting to them the idea of
the change you have made and the peace
that it gives you, you are then a
reflection to them of your belief in
your own self-empowerment to create the
reality you desire. And in allowing them
to understand that from you, if they are
willing to hear that from you, then you
can teach them that they are also as
powerful as they need to be to create
anything they want in life without
having to hurt anyone else or themselves
in order to have
it. Do you follow me?
No, I don't. You can be of service after
you have changed. Understand? It is
simply now that you are still reluctant
to hear this because you think that
being of service to those individuals
keeps you embroiled on that level and it
doesn't.
I'm confused of how to be of service
without getting into by being who you
are. By knowing that if you have changed
the idea you are showing them is that
the change you have made represents your
knowledge that you are now
selfowered and are not putting your
power in the symbols around you. You are
not relying on the symbols around you
for your power as individuals who create
addictions do. You are now a reflection of the idea
do. You are now a reflection of the idea
that your power comes from within from
your connection to infinite creation and
that you can create anything you desire
in life without having to hurt else or
yourself in order to have it. This is
what you can teach them. But teaching
them that through your joy and
unconditional love does not create
within you a feeling of being dragged
down. You elevate
them. You follow me? Yes, I follow. All
it takes is conviction that the change
you have made is real. And then you will
not continue to create for creating it.
You are any of the so-called negative
feelings about your interaction with
them. If you do interact with them,
recognize that you co-created it. The
idea is that when you change, if you
still interact with them, then you can
be of service to them. If you cannot be
of service to them, you won't interact
with them. But if you do interact with
them, then there is a way for you to be
of
service. It can be as simple as simply
being the changed person you know you
are. You can't be responsible for them.
You are, however, completely responsible
to them by being completely who you now
believe yourself to be without getting
in there and telling them about.
You can share ideas with them if they
seem open to the idea of that
communication, but you don't have to
force it upon them. You are simply
telling them this is one option. Take it
or leave it. I'm having a good time
saying to you
later, you follow me. If they are truly
interested, they will ask you again.
They will ask you for the information.
And that in turn will allow you to know
that they are not depleting you but that
you are simply giving of your love in
whatever way shape or form you can be of
assistance in. It is not that you are
giving your power to them. No you are
simply reminding them of their own
power. That is all. That does not tire
anyone. Do you follow me now? Yes I do. I
Do you follow me now? Yes I do. I
um I this is like, you know, I got off
on all this this stuff and I wanted to
have an understanding
[Music] um of of how to be able to create my car
um of of how to be able to create my car
to be the way I want it to be, which is
not um with a broken transmission. All
right? But do not become focused and
frustrated on that idea. Allow yourself
again to know you are open and the
vehicle you are will continue to move
and will attract if you need one a
moving vehicle. There are many many many many
vehicle. There are many many many many
many many many many many many ways in
which such an idea can manifest in your
life. Do not restrict the ways you think
it should have to manifest in order to
be viable. when I had the awareness of
how I could um of what it meant to me in
my life and the gear shifting and my
accelerating and I patted myself on the
back and said I was accelerating exactly
the perfect speed I need to and I've
done such a good job and I thank the car
for service when I went out to the car I
expected that it was not going to have a
broken but you see that is your
but you see that is your
expectation the idea does not have to
manifest that way you by all means can
go and check it anytime you feel like
But the idea again is that if that
particular vehicle continues to have a
broken transmission, then don't be
disappointed. You are then only
reinforcing the validity of that broken
transmission. You are then also keeping
away any other vehicle that might come
into your life that doesn't have a
broken transmission
because you are insisting that the only
way you will accept the transformation
as valid is to have the idea of that
particular transmission be repaired.
I'm having it repaired, but I thought I
could repair it without that through my
transformation without having to pay all
this money out. I think you are missing
the point completely.
Pay attention. You can do anything you want.
attention. You can do anything you want.
You can check that transmission as many
times as you want. An individual that is
fully in one's
selfmpowerment when you go out to check
that transmission on a whim will not
care whether it is broken or not because
you trust that if it is still broken
that's the way it's supposed to be and
that is what will allow the situation to
manifest in your life to most
easily do what comes next. Now, if you
had been willing to simply let it slide
in that way, the idea could have been
that you would have been provided
automatically with the money to have it
repaired. That is simply one way of
having it repaired. Do understand that
the idea of expecting it to be repaired
in what you'd formally call a miraculous
fashion doesn't necessarily mean that
somebody giving you the money to have it
repaired is any less
miraculous. Do not make demands upon the
way the idea of the universe manifests
itself. Let it manifest itself in the
easiest possible way. If the easiest
possible manner is to have someone
simply automatically give you the money
to have it fixed, why should you
insist upon it repairing itself?
You follow me?
Sure. Can I add something here? One
moment. Do you follow me? Yeah, I do.
Keep it easy. Keep it simple. Understand
manifestation in light takes the path of
least resistance. What you think with
your ego may be the path of least
resistance is not always necessarily the
case. The idea of having allowed that
transmission to be whole is certainly
far from
impossible. But if the idea is to simply
create it in that way so you can simply
give yourself another pat on the back,
that may not be the path of least
resistance. The idea is that if you
truly live in the moment, you will
recognize that whatever is happening is
there for a reason. and you will allow
the easiest manifestable way for it to
change to come into your life.
Regardless of whether or not that
easiest manifestable way is a way that
you may consider
mundane. Nothing is mundane. As we have
said, there are no mundane or boring
situations, only mundane and bored
minds. You follow me? Let everything in
life be a miracle. No matter how it
happens, even if it happens in the most
typical of manners, that may be the path
of least resistance.
I just wanted to be able to
what we are saying is that was confused
about how you all right the idea can
happen in many different ways but what
we are primarily saying right now is
that if you were willing to remove the
focus of the
expectation not expectancy but
expectation that the idea is that the
transmission simply had to be whole.
Perhaps you would have allowed another
avenue to manifest in your life where
the money would have simply come up
without you having to feel that you were
putting anything
out in that way. Or you may have
attracted someone who was willing to
simply fix it for free for a service for
something else. Who knows? Maybe you
would have won a new transmission or a
new car.
The idea again in recognizing what you
prefer, you must be very very very very
very honest with yourself about what you
truly believe can occur in your life.
And if you actually have an easier
belief that someone can hand you the
money to fix the transmission than you
do about the molecular cohesiveness of
the transmission reforming, then be
honest with yourself. Let it come
through the money. Let it come through
service to you. do not insist that it
has to be the molecular reforming of the
transmission. You follow me? Yes, for sure. Thank you.
You follow me? Yes, for sure. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Yes. Connecting with that idea, it
occurred to me that abundance abundance
has thousands of facets. Yay. And so
when you allow it to happen however it's
going to happen, you're never
disappointed because it always happens.
Yes. It is a matter of not only trust
but honesty with yourself about what you
truly believe is
possible. Not to say that can never
happen in your life, but it doesn't have
to happen now in order for you to feel
like you're actually making progress.
There are many other ways for you to
understand that idea. Many other ways.
And you may have thought, well, just
having the transmission pop back, well,
that would be the best way. But maybe
the best quote unquote way would
actually have been allowing another
individual to perform a service for you
because then two individuals are served
by the same idea.
You follow me? Yeah. That is why you
should not
insist upon the manifestation. Allow the
manifestation and in whatever way, shape
or form it manifests. That is the way
that is of best service to all
concerned. The idea of using as a
visualization, as a focal point, the
idea of the transmission reforming
itself is all well and good. But do not
insist that it has to happen exactly as
you have visualized it. It will get back
together one way or another. It will get
back together in the way that serves the
most individual.
Is that a little clearer? Yeah, thank
you. Happy driving. You You
then
you about four years ago I was traveling
in Australia and I met a guy there
who I was working in a hospital at the
time and we worked the night shift
together and we became very close
friends. Can all of you hear this individual?
Can all of you hear this individual?
Um, it could be louder. Okay. Um, I met
this individual in Australia and we've
developed a strong friendship and
he stimulated in me a decision or a
choice to turn my focus in life around.
And that's kind of four years ago that's
led me to be here and to be doing a lot
of the things that I'm doing now. Oh,
right. Now during that time he was had a
had a relationship with a lady there who
was married who still is married and has
a couple of
children. They had a strong relationship
and he seemed to be very attached to her
and she to him however because of her
religion and the fact that she was
married she's a Roman Catholic. She
didn't want to make the commitment to
divorce her husband who she doesn't
really love. All right. and she does
love this individual, my friend Graeme.
Thanks. Anyway, I left Australia and
until 3 weeks ago, I had no
communication whatsoever with my friend
and he came to visit me from Australia
and we talked much about our experiences
between then and now. And it seems that
his relationship now is one of he's kind
of he had pulled away from the
relationship with this woman
and had attached himself or had
developed a relationship with another
woman who has a child and who really
loves him and he also loves her but he
still feels attached to this other lady.
And they you recognize first of all if
it may be of assistance before you go on
that in our society every single member
in our society considers him or herself
to be married to every other
member simultaneously. And thus many different
simultaneously. And thus many different
types of relationship manifestation can
occur within that society without the
ideas of the rigors of an imposed
structure upon it. for each and every
individual knows that they are being
dealt with in honesty and integrity and
true unconditional love.
Thank you. Does that assist you
somewhat? Continue.
Um, so basically what I'm driving at is
that Oh, another transmission.
Thank you.
Um he's coming when he was here 3 weeks
ago he asked me before going across
country to New York if I had any
suggestions as to how he's now back with
this original relationship decided to to
get back into that and however he wants
to make some kind of a decision to pull
away from this relationship without
experiencing the pain and the suffering
that he thinks is going to That is a
foregone conclusion of totally pulling
out of this relationship. Again, once a
relationship is created, it never ends.
The definition may change. The positions
of the individuals within it may shift,
but it never ends. Yet, this is a truth
for me also.
However, he has asked me to if I can to
assist him and any information I can
give him in assisting him in pulling out
of this relationship
um that I that he's open to suggestions.
It's all right. So if you can share the
idea first and foremost is to recognize
however that this individual has been
involved with these individuals in many
different lifetimes and they have danced
around each other many different ways
being reflections for each other many
many times. Now the idea in this
particular life is the exploration of
limitation and whether or not the
individuals in these relationships are
going to allow limitations to demand or
impose the system upon what they feel to
be true for themselves or not. The idea
in this way, however, is that they have
chosen each other at this particular
timing so that they would have the
opportunity to explore this idea of
whether or not they will allow
self-imposed limitations to truly be in
a sense what gets in their way or
whether they will allow themselves in
openness and honesty to communicate with
all individuals involved in all the
aspects of the relationship and allow it
to come to the surface to light so that
it can be balanced out in a way that is
in your terms mutually beneficial
consciously, satisfactoryy. for all
concerned. The idea is to first and
foremost recognize that there may be a
bit of the idea involved that we have
discussed before where you find that an
individual though it is not so prominent
with this particular individual as you
perceive the energy of this individual
you are speaking of. But an individual
many times will in not understanding
themselves to be a complete individual
will think they need a relationship in
order to be complete and will only
therefore usually attract a relationship
to reflect their own belief in their own
incompleteness or inability to create
completeness within their life rather
than knowing themselves to be complete
and allowing themselves to attract a
relationship into their lives that
reflects that degree of completeness.
Now at this time therefore according to
the agreement that this individual has
made with these other individuals many
different ideas of limitation are
necessary to be explored. All that is
necessary is complete and open honesty
in communication. Lack of fear in the
idea that if you express these ideas and
share them with all the individuals
involved honestly and openly we are not
only speaking of the females but also
the other males. Then in this way
perhaps it will be something that can be
utilized in growth in an understanding.
And many times you will find a very
surprising thing will occur as soon as
you take the step toward opening up an
examination and honest way of what all
of the relationship is about and let it
be there for the reason it is there
rather than for what you think it should
be there for. Many times the original
impulse or the original desire no longer
exists. There is no longer a need to feel that
There is no longer a need to feel that
that relationship has to complete itself
in the way you used to think it had to
complete itself because it has completed
itself according to the reason it
existed. And the reason may simply be to
allow these individuals to explore the
idea of whether or not they will allow
the society's limitations to block them
from what they know to be true for
themselves or whether they are willing
to discuss it and perhaps with
assistance with each other with love, no
forcing to change those parameters in a
way that will allow them more expansion
of self and more expression of that
love. Once they may get to that point,
they may paradoxically find it
completely unnecessary to
physiologically continue the
relationship because the purpose of the
relationship has been
served to get them to face the idea of
the exploration of the limitations they
are facing within the
relationship. You follow me? Yes. Will
that be of some assistance to you and to
him? Thank you. Thank you very much.
Yes. Thank you.
I learned of Pauline's mental sickness
in the last few weeks since I've been
over here and I returned to Australia
next weekend. Can you speak up a bit? I
learned of Pauline's mental sickness in
the last few weeks only since I have
been over here and I return to Australia
next weekend and I would love some
advice on how to proceed. Do I tell
Anthony first? Do I confront Pauline?
What is the best way to go? There are
four children.
Do you find that you have the ability to
express unconditional love for this
individual? Not towards this individual.
No. Why not? The paranoia and the
schizophrenia is just a bit too heavy.
All right. I'm not yet a saint. Oh, yes
you are. You all are in your own way. But
are. You all are in your own way. But
the idea is first and foremost that if
that if you are asking as to how to be
of assistance the first step is the
expression of love. If you cannot muster
that you aren't going to be of much
assistance. I can at times and then I
fail dismally. Oh not really. Do not be
so hard upon yourself. Don't forget that
that unconditional love goes for you
from you as well. Do not be so hard upon
yourself first of all. All right. Yes.
Thank you. Now the idea is to recognize
first and foremost that individuals in
life attract to themselves what they
fear to be true which is the same thing
as saying that they believe it to be the
most likely reality for them to
experience. And in this way, if you are
willing to look at it from that point of
view, then you can simply recognize that
this individual has chosen a situation
that is for them an expression of
endurance, an expression of strength. In
that sense, in placing upon themselves
such severe limitation, such
severe expressions of
fear, then in this way you are actually
seeing an individual who has been
willing to explore limitation to such an
extent that it may be an indication that
they will never need to experience that
idea ever again after this particular
life or even after a particular certain
amount of time within this life. If you
can simply recognize it perhaps as the
way the individual has created their
life to be so that they can come to
terms that much more rapidly perhaps
than another individual might have by
facing all of these fears within
themselves right away all at once. Well,
it may seem to be overwhelming but the
idea therefore is to recognize that if
they have chosen this whether it is
conscious or unconscious then simply
recognize that they are attempting to
integrate themselves by facing all of
these fears it may be in their conscious
mind a bit overwhelming for them. That
is why if you are willing to love them
unconditionally and support them in what
they are doing, you will paradoxically
allow them to get it over with as
quickly as possible. The more you may
invalidate them for the way they are,
the more you actually prolong their
experience because then all they see in
you is a reflection of what they already
believe that they see within themselves
overwhelming paranoia and fear. The idea
is that if you love them
unconditionally, then they can see
within you the beacon of light that they
need to see within themselves to know
that there is nothing that they need to
fear. And in that way, they may be able
to see a reflection in you of their own
inner strength that will allow them to
put themselves right back in touch with
their connection to the infinite
creation. Are you catching this? Yes,
very much. Are the children safe?
Basically, yes, she won't endanger their
lives. We find, of course, that these
We find, of course, that these
individuals have made an agreement to
together. Do not forget that the
children, so to speak, before they were
born knew very well what they were
probably getting themselves into because
then they weren't children. Now, they
will work in our perception through this
idea with whatever assistance anyone is
willing to give them. But work through
it, they will. It is their own
self-proclaimed karma. Karma being
completely self-imposed of course, but
it is their decision to work these ideas
out with each other. They are doing it
in a very highly accelerated way at this
time. They are in a sense getting the
idea that they may have thought to
express in many lifetimes out of the way
in one.
But the idea first and
foremost is that every
individual, every individual is as
powerful as they need to be to create
anything they desire in life without
having to hurt anyone else or themselves
in order to get it. An individual who is
fearful in that
way is simply an individual who has been
taught to believe that they are
powerless, that they are a victim in
life. But they do not have to be. By
shedding your unconditional love upon
them, you can allow them the opportunity
to understand that even in the very
depths of their self-cratum victimhood,
they are still worth
loving. All that is the infinite creator
loves them unconditionally
regardless. give them the same benefit
of the
doubt and that is what will accelerate
them into their own inner light and
enlightenment. We will thank you for any
assistance you are willing to give
without feeling that you must force it
upon them just the love. If you
recognize it as what you call in your
society a
disease, then simply treat them in the
way that you would support any person
who has the disease. Let them know that
they have the strength, that they have
the ability to allow themselves to be
cured, to allow themselves to regain
their zero rest balanced state of
creation relative to the universe, which
automatically brings with it complete
and utter health on all levels.
You follow me? Yes. Anything at all that
you find to be a hesitation on your part
in your ability to share with them, your
unconditional love in all reality is
simply the reflection of the beliefs
that you have also bought into in the
society. And they may be representative
of the fears that you have within
yourself that you are seeing reflected
in this other
individual because you may fear that to
be connected to this individual may
bring up the same ideas within you that
you perhaps also fear to
face. Love them. Love yourself
unconditionally as the infinite loves
you. And you will be being of best
service to them in that way. But they do
have their own path to live out.
They can choose to do it in a positive
way, but it is still ultimately their
choice. Do understand of course that
everyone is completely and utterly at
least foundationally indestructible and
eternal and in the overall sense there
is no
ultimate damage. You follow me? Mhm.
Will this have been of some assistance
to you? Very much. We thank you. Does do
they need any conventional treatment or
there may be some balancing
of chemicals what you would call heral
intake enzyatic balancing or action that
can take place if you are willing to
send your healing energy through your
hands your electromagnetic blue white
violet light that can have some
balancing effects some ideas of
crystallization energized water may have
some balancing effects
soothingness, immersion in this water
may have some balancing
effects, but you can
heal. All it takes is
love. That's all it takes. Love and
conviction. The willingness to be that
love. Thank you. Thank you to very
much sharing. All right. you than you.
Uh, last week on the way here, I came
after it was over. Speak up. Last week
or I will ask you to stand up. All
right. Um, last week on the way here in
my car, I had another one of those
um, bizarro experiences. In other words,
uh, it was probably an integrating
experience. But anyway, uh, driving the
car, I I felt this glow, you know, like
ET. It's almost visually
visually visually the idea of of a
pressure starting from the heart and
emanating out through my shoulders. Um
like a warmth uh but but then my heart
started palpitating and my arms got very
non-physical. I got a little
non-physical and all I could think of
was um just keep the car on the road and
deep breath and all that. All right. In
addition to um the physical uh for the
past two months I have had um just
constant constant constant buckets and
buckets of draining from my sinuses to
the point where I'm almost choking on it
at times. All right. And um I just want
to know that that's just all part of the
integration. I think it is. All right.
How's your diet? Pretty decent. In what
way? Balanced vegetables. Um probably
could use a little more vitamin C. I I
have a fairly balanced diet. I do eat
meat occasionally. Um what about milk?
Yeah, I do drink it. Cut it out. Okay.
It aids in the production of the toxins
that increase the mucus in your body.
Oh, okay. I wondered about that. Um
I wondered about it, but I chose to
ignore my wonder. That's right. That's
right. That's true. Oh, thank you. Um
the other the other thing is what about
that uh stuff on the way here? First
person I ran into was Daryl and I said
hey Daryl I had another one of those.
You he goes great. They're a little
they're a little strange. I mean uh you
could all right. You are simply
traveling roads you are not used to yet.
Okay. But you are fine. Okay. The other
thing since we're all talking about
relationships, um that past week,
[Music] maybe she means all of the beings that
maybe she means all of the beings that
are her. Yeah, that's it. That's the
That's the thing. Um Oh, thank you. Uh
many many months ago, I was bitching
about not having that area in action
many many moons ago. All right. Yeah.
And um boy, I've had some ecstatic
action in that area. Oh my. Yeah, it was
I don't know what it is about two people
getting together and being open and uh
that in that way to each other. You
don't so much fun. Oh, I do. All right.
But but it's the the wonder of the
discovery of the person that is so
ecstatic and it doesn't even matter what
they reveal. But then you find out new
parts of yourself. Yes. That's always
ecstatic. Yeah. Always is. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you. So, oh, you're
welcome. You're welcome. Welcome. But
anyway, here's what happened. Um I had
some I I met uh two people uh in the
course of a couple of weeks and it was
extremely intense and very beautiful and
you know one person I met and the
conversation lasted three hours and it
was just rapid fire and it was just one
sharing one thing after the other and it
was just ah it was it was absolutely
wonderful and um there was a I I
actually the reflections I got were just
I saw how lovable I really was. I saw
how many things about my the experience
of myself and the other person was just
oh it was just really well thank you now
but but here's the thing oh the thing
here's what happened I thought was very
interesting what happened is um one of
the persons is you know doesn't live
here lives in Boston so they went to
Boston that was fine um and then the
other person who I've seen for about a
month during the First week it they were
in New York. Obviously, it was just
ecstatic, ecstatic, ecstatic. Then the
person comes back and they've closed
themselves off and I'm going, "What's
this? What's this?" I'm saying, and uh
what reflection is this of myself? And
um do I have to take it personally?
Well, I didn't, but I was just going but
I was looking at now what am I doing
creating that? I don't want that part. I
want the other part where where we have
the uh I like that a lot. It excites me.
I prefer that part. All right. And so,
but that doesn't mean you have to have
it with them. That's true. So, I had
this other person come in that was
it was it was hysterically funny. But
then then there was one day after this
person finally rolls in and says, "Well,
let me tell you how I feel." And I'm
going, "Hey, that sounds like a I've
been waiting for that for three weeks."
And not so long. No, not so long. But I
sort of knew what they were going to
say. And they said, "I'm not ready to
have a relationship." And I'm going I
don't want to you know to in myself I'm
saying why is this person saying this
and then I realize that well they're
saying that for them and for whatever
reason they're h they say that they're
saying it so okay next I didn't really
react that way right away I want want to
tell you all right I had a big loss on
it so much of a loss that the next day I
experienced such a low Bashar that um
no such a low I I was amazed at how how
vulnerable I had allowed myself to be
and I liked it. I liked it a lot. Um,
vulnerabilities, strengths. Yes, it was.
I felt very alive. Very alive. And um, I
was so I I took it as a loss at first
knowing that this isn't really a loss.
But anyway, I'm experiencing it. All
right, let it be valid. And it went way
I went way down there to the point where
I thought, my god, it seems like I
haven't even moved an inch. This is
still it. This is still the same thing
as it was before. And then what
happened? And then I even thought this
stuff that we're doing doesn't even work
and it's all hopeless and I there's no
point in living. And then the next day
and then what happened?
Well then I then the next day I just
kept integrating that and allowing
myself to really experience it fully
fully. And the next day I could static
again. That's because you are now a
different you. That's true.
That's true. And it does work. And I
have Yes. Now that you are the person
that knows that it works, it works. When
you were the person that didn't believe
it worked, it didn't. I realized that. I
did see that. And and it is kind of
funny. It is also that simple. Yeah.
Yeah. It's wild. And then the person
remaining who I see is very pragmatic.
Doesn't want to hear about any of this.
All right. You know, it's just But I
prefer D. And I'm just going what the
hell? I'm I'm just going to take it as
it comes. Thank you. And having is fine
because it is Thank you. Thank you for
being here now.
My pleasure. And our
Yes. Well, on that when you're the
person that doesn't uh believe that it
will I now do recognize on some level
you always believe something. Yeah.
Otherwise, you wouldn't be physical.
Well, what do you do to get back to what
you get in your physical reality is an
indication of what you believe is true.
If once you get it, you don't prefer it.
Use it as an opportunity to recognize
that the situation that has now occurred
in your life is your recognition of what
the belief is. Now you have the
opportunity to change the definition and
then simply believe that that is what
you now choose to believe. Then you will
allow not make not force allow your
physical reality to transform into what
you now believe according to your new
definition you actually believe in. But
don't expect anything. Have
expectancy not expectations.
Expectancy C is the emotional
knowingness that A you have changed and
therefore b your physical reality will
follow suit. Expectations is placing
upon the change that your physical
reality will go through the method that
your ego thinks should be the way it
should change to represent the change
you have made within yourself. Thank you
for clarifying. I have a question on the
32C technique.
Are you willing to hold on a little
longer? Yeah, just a quickie. All right.
Okay. The question is, in doing this 33
second technique, I found myself asking
uh with regards to another person, I ran
up against the question. And the
question is, do I really want to um like
will so I I like for example, I desire
that person to to be open and receptive.
And then I said, "But wait a minute, if
he desires to," because I thought that
was a bit manipulative in a sense. Um,
so basically, you don't ask questions
like, "Okay, I want so and so to do da
da." Um, the idea is to function within
your integrity, which recognizes that
you cannot control anyone. Okay, great.
Thank you. And the idea is that if you
attempt to control someone else, all you
are doing is placing restrictions upon
yourself. Right. Right. Thank you guys.
Yes. Sorry. Hey, I went to Kawaii uh and
just got back last night. Have a good
time. Yes. It was very beautiful. Thank
you. Some great changes. Great. One
thing I noticed when I was there, I went
I had a crystal that I gotten a little
while back and it kind of it helped to
lead me there. And what it was is it was
it was the shape of a certain mountain
on Kawaii. And it was funny because I
asked the cab driver, I when I got
there, I I hailed a cab and I asked him,
"Have you seen
this?" And he took me there and I went
backpacking up in the rainforest up
there and saw it was an exact replica of
my rock and very spontaneous of you.
Yes. And uh I went up there and it was
very rainy, but I decided that's where I
wanted to be. Nice.
And I camped by stream one night and
then I went down by the ocean and camped
and had this beautiful overlooking view
of the ocean. It was raining a lot so I
was kind of in the tent quite a bit but
uh there was a lot of meditation that
went on and a lot of changes and one
thing I noticed was um I kept getting
this especially after I landed I really
noticed um I kept feeling like I was
suffocating. Every time I felt that I
would open up like a valve and there was
a lot of energy coming from a lot and
not forget you are right in the heart of
the entire planet in that energy. It was
beautiful. It was it's like I would I
would allow myself like the condalini to
just kind of bury way into the ground
and then I would just expand and allow
it open up like a valve and very
enjoyable. Yes, it was very very nice.
Very centering.
Exactly what happened. Very centering.
In fact, I feel very peaceful. Thank
you. And uh I came
back a new person. Yes. Totally new
person. Literally. Literally. Very very
literally. I also recognized
um a connection not a connection but a
reemergence with myself
at that level when I was there guys and
also while I was there one night I was
pretty much alone there um not really
not really well as far as you know
physiologically a lot of people and um I
got different reaction on that. You
know, I I tell somebody I went up there
and they alone some of them and some of
them would go, "Oh, how interesting."
And some go, "You're kidding." You know,
there are wild bo up there. But it was
very synchronous
anyway. I figured if I added to wild
boar, it would be synchronous. But um
yeah, well said there are no boring
well said there are no boring
situations.
Not at all.
I was I was sleeping and I suddenly woke
up and I felt this well first of all I I
noticed that there was a lot of energy
coming through so I just allowed it to
come through and I felt like this ache
not a bad feeling a very strong feeling
around the third eye area and I kind of
saw the corner of my eyes I wasn't
wearing contact I couldn't see a darn
thing with my eyes but I looked out and
didn't see anything. But I kind of felt
and kind of saw like the shape of a
figure kind of a short stocky thing and
I realized that these people that are
talked about there are there on a
different Yes. level and it was
different vibrational plane and it was
actually noticing me there and seeing
what I was doing and very curious about.
That is why I said you weren't alone.
Yes. No, I was not alone at all. It was
um a very beautiful experience and thank
you. Yes. I uh anyway I came out of
there and I had lots of reflections of
um different things and the original cab
driver was actually trying to talk me
into moving there and starting a farm.
It was very interesting that uh
um I have actually decided that that
would be a very nice place to
would be a very nice place to live and
I'm I'm really looking at that very with
excitement the possibility. Thank you
for your willingness to expand into the
many facets and reflections of the
crystal that you are and for planting
your crystallin seeds.
You may all take a short break. [Music]
How's everything going? [Music]
All right, I'll see. Are you all ready
for the exercise?
At this time, therefore, allow
yourselves the opportunity to become in
whatever fashion you can be. In whatever
position you find yourself to be in,
comfortable. If you are standing, so be
it. If you are sitting, this is all
right. The idea is to simply become as you say
The idea is to simply become as you say
comfortable within yourself within the
idea that you will be presenting to
yourself. Before we
begin, allow yourself the opportunity to
recognize the following
ideas. What we will once again be
suggesting to you as the idea of this
exercise, the idea of this
technique will be our
suggestion. Your imagination you may
find may alter the visualization
slightly, may change them
radically. This is all right.
Trust that in whatever way, shape or
form your imagination sees fit to
translate the idea into your being is
exactly what is correct for you. You
follow me? Yes.
The idea in this way is to also understand
idea in this way is to also understand
this a difference you will make
regardless of what you think, regardless
of how you feel. I don't feel any
different. I don't think anything really
happened. Understand that in the state
of the exercise, you will be placing
yourself within a certain mental
vibrational wavelength that will create
an effect. Whether you think you feel
any different or not will not
matter. So simply allow yourself to
relax into the understanding that you
don't have to force yourself to feel any
particular way to make sure that you did it
way to make sure that you did it
correctly. Oh well, I guess I'll let
everyone else do it. I don't seem to be
able to get the knack. I can't seem to
be able to reach that level that Bashar
is talking about. You will be on that
level if you participate at all. You
will be on that
level. The only way you will not in a
sense overall is if you do not
participate at all.
But recognize that even fleetingly, even
fleeting participation can
instantaneously take you to that level
and you may still participate and have
an
effect. All it takes is a fleeting
participation at exactly the correct
timing which you may instinctively
do. Three deep breaths and relax. Your
eyes may be open, they may be closed. It
does not matter. Whatever is most
comfortable for you.
At this time, allow yourself to begin to
imagine the blue, white, violet
electromagnetic field of the universe
and particularly of your world, your
earth. Out of this electromagnetic
fluid is the creation of the energy
pattern. The imposition of the energy
pattern from your consciousness. The
interactions of which creates what you
call mind or mentality.
It is how you are connected to each
other on the mental level and it is how
you are sensitive to any shifts,
thoughts, ideas or feelings that take
place within that energy whether they be
from any one of you, any group of you or
the collective earth itself including
the physical planet.
For as a physical being and as a
physical planet, it is colloquially
speaking a solidified pattern of
electromagnetic energy. That is all it
is. Everything in the physical universe
is made of light in one form or another.
It is therefore simply a step down so to
speak vibratory energy represented in
electromagnetic terms. Out of that
electromagnetic sea, all solid matter is
created and all mentality for
interaction between all solid matter is
created. Consciousness, the
consciousness that you are together
creates this illusion out of the
electromagnetic sea.
Feel yourself. Imagine yourself.
Visualize yourself in any way, shape or
form you care to that you are now a part
of this
electromagnetic sea.
fear yourself to be connected to every
other individual simply because if for
no other reason that you exist in the
same sea and therefore there is a
similar medium that touches you
both. So you are connected by something
somehow somewhere everywhere. Every when
as well every when and
everywhere the different when are simply
different vibrational rates of existence
of the different ideas or aspects or
manifestations of the entire
electromagnetic sea. Visualize
sea. Visualize
This blue white crystallin clear
pulsating vibrant
magnetic
energy. Let yourself be immersed in this
idea. As you now know you are at the
appropriate level to know you are in
connection with every being within this
electromagnetic sea. Take it for granted
that you are. No matter what your habits
of doubts in your physical life, for
this moment they are all
suspended for this moment. Allow
moment. Allow
yourself to simply play in that sea. You
are in
it. Before we begin the next
phase, allow yourself three more deep
breaths. Imagine yourself breathing that
fluid in and out, in and out, and
passing with it the idea of
communication, taking in the
communication of
others and understanding it on whatever
level you need to.
The next step is to allow yourself to
feel as you now know you are immersed in
this electromagnetic sea to feel the
expansion of the hearts within you. Feel
the expansion of the idea of the heart
energy to
encompass, blend with and merge with
this electromagnetic
energy in whatever way, shape or form
feels warm and comfortable or cool and
comfortable to you. Simply let it now
diffuse and
expand, intertwine,
merge, blend one matrix with another so
that there becomes a double matrix. One
that is not exactly one or the other,
but both and yet something yet again
more.
As you do
this, three more breaths, taking in the
entire blending and letting it out,
passing it through you, feeling the
combined colors, the combined energies
in a relaxed and floating manner. [Music]
Let them blend. Let them merge as you
breathe them in and out until they are
one in the same idea that contains both
energies. That is a homogeneous blended
idea that can at any particular moment
in time become either energy yet always
contain both. The next idea is to allow
both. The next idea is to allow
Now that you have allowed your
physicality, now that you have allowed
your emotionality to
allow your
mentality, allow your
mentality to vibrate, to expand in
radiating waves from you and permeate
every single crystal and lattice work
structure within this electromagnetic
sea. You are a beacon and you are a
receiver. You are sending, you are
receiving, you are intertwined and
intershed until all is a solid sea of
communication coming and
going. Breathe this three times in and
three times out. [Music]
Now that you perceive these three ideas
to be
blended, allow one fourth idea to come
in. The fourth idea
being the total collectivity of the
former three once again that which is
more than the sum of its parts. An
envision of violet and golden
light intermixing,
intermixing,
intertwining, sharing of love, ever
expanding, ever spiraling upward,
outward, inward, downward, in all
directions, simultaneously
throughout the beautiful matrix, the
crystallin matrix you have now created
and now support.
Three more deep breaths as you
experience this
expansion of beautiful light and love. And now to
now to
anchor this matrix as your
reality, you will now send a vibration
through each one of these
levels that will
firmly fix it into place in a very
crystallin way. and at the same time
quite paradoxically allow it infinite
paradoxically allow it infinite
flexibility. Yet it will always be
representative of your ability to now
function as a valve for all
energies and a
transmuter and a transformer of all
energies that you may encounter within
the physiological universe.
The way you will radiate this energy to
the first connection you made is through
the tonal vibration, the ringing of your
chimes, the ringing of your bells in
what you term to be the sound. sound.
One
3 home. [Music]
[Music]
As that goes outward, you will now allow
a second tone to blend with the
connections you made on the second level
and to align and
reinforce the first level.
Each tone will become more bell-like,
more clarifying. No matter how it
sounds, it will be
so. More crystallin the universe will
be. One 2 3.
[Laughter] [Music] [Music]
A third
vibration will pass from your being and
radiate infinitely outward, radiate
infinitely inward. This will
inward. This will
cause the pure crystallization of the
light being that you are within your
heart, within your mind, within your
spirit, within your body.
One, two, three.
[Music] Oh, and
Oh, and
yet the
culmination of the crystallin form you
now are shines with internal and eternal
light. And this
radiance, this divinity, this
infinity of creation is now more than
the sum of its parts.
One beautiful golden violet
tone will now
completely
interpenetrate all levels with a new
understanding, a new matrix, and with
it an
accessibility of all that this new
matrix implies. eyes. 1 eyes. 1
2 [Music]
3. Three deep breaths.
[Music] Rapid breathing for a count of three. 1 1
3 Three
deep breaths.
[Music]
As you now
take not yet one
more deep and loving breath, feel the
totality of the entire idea we have just
experienced together in this last one
breath. So that anytime at all, anytime
at all, the entire idea of the
experience we have just had will
completely and utterly come back and
allow you to center exactly where you
are now with one deep breath.
2 3 in [Applause] [Applause]
and
[Music] out. Allow
out. Allow
yourselves to reemerge with the idea
that you are familiar with as your
reality. But recognize that you are no
longer waking out of a dream but waking
into a
dream. The dream that you
are. The dream that we
share together of love and light. We thank
We thank
you for having made and being willing to
create a profound and impactful
difference in your
world. For a profound and impactful
difference in your world is a profound
and impactful difference in all
worlds. And all worlds right now that
are sensitive to what you have just
done have felt that
difference. Space and time not
withstanding. We thank
you. Sharing for sure. Yay. Strawberry.
For sure, I need some assistance in
transforming situation I created myself
in. Speak up so that all may share.
Okay. I need some assistance in
transforming a situation that I've uh
gotten myself into. Oh, right. And
um it has to do with I have allowed
myself to be put into a situation where
um I'm being required to deliver a sum
of money this evening to a person and if
I don't do that um being threatened with
some dire consequences which I have
assigned dire consequences and don't
want to occur and I want to transform
this thing. I've been having a hell of a
lot of trouble with or lot of
uh fear all night terror things of this
sort. Racked myself with this kind of
situation. Haven't done this in quite a
long time. And I just came here to get
some assistance. All
right. First of all,
face your
fear squarely.
Okay. In your
terminology, what is in your terms,
starting from the beginning, the worst
thing that could possibly occur?
[Music] The
um that's fascinating. It it it alters
as I look at it. Very good. changes, but
it basically it is an ongoing um apparently
um apparently
uncontrollable terror and effect point
and constantly being put at effect.
allowing myself to be put in effect with
apparently ongoing
negative feelings and sensations on an
ongoing basis and being constant over a
long period of time being trapped into
this thing. Allow us to ask you in a
very colloquial way, are you in any
immediate physical danger? No, not
immediate physical danger. [Music]
Have you run through different
conversations, different interactions
and different communications that you
might be able to cocreate with all the
other individuals involved that may
allow a different outcome to occur.
Thousands of them. In fact, some of them
totally on automatic um occurring. I
seem to see seem to become the loser in
these conversations. And in the in this
particular reality when I went to put
forth the conversation,
um the reflection was that none of it
was being willing to be received. And so
I
just continued to be there and allowing
the person to be right in their reality.
All right.
Why do you
choose to place yourself in this
situation? I love the people and I want
to be of service. How do you wish to be
of service?
I want them to transform into
a broader,
serving, less fixed viewpoint if they
choose to. Would you please say that once
to. Would you please say that once
again? I would like them to loudly. I
would like them to transform into a more
loving, expansive, less fixed point of view if
expansive, less fixed point of view if
they choose to, which I think they would
choose to. If they choose if they choose
to to. Yes. If they
choose to. Why is it so important to you
that they do choose to?
Because it appears if they don't. Yes. I
am the effect of their holding that
viewpoint because I hold myself into Why
do you have anything at all to do with
what they choose to do? Because I put
myself into that situation. Talk to me
about physics. How do you actually have
in any way, shape, or form anything at
all to do with what they choose to do?
Are you responsible for their choices?
No. Then how does anything you
do determine what they choose to do?
It doesn't determine what should they
choose to do. All right. Then you are
not the cause of what they are
experiencing. I never considered that I
was all right. I am the cause of what
I'm experiencing. Oh yes. Trying to
transform my own. Yes, you are the cause
of what you are experiencing primarily
in a sense because you think you have to
be the cause of what you want them to
experience other than what they are
already experiencing. Once again, I'm
sorry I didn't duplicate it once. All
right. You are the cause of what you are
You are the cause of what you are
experiencing as we perceive it so far in
this conversation. Primarily because you
also desire to be the cause of what they
may choose to do or not
do. If you recognize that you are not
the cause of what they choose to do,
then how can you be the cause of
anything else they might choose to do?
I'm sorry. Hey, I I tracked with you
right around to the last All
right. These tracks are slippery, aren't
they? Apparently. So, apparently so. All
Apparently. So, apparently so. All
right. You say you recognize that you
are not responsible for their decisions.
Yes. Yes. Then if you are not
responsible for their
decisions, then that goes both
ways. Though you may reflect to them
your reality, the idea of your desire
for them to choose to share your reality
is
indirectly a desire for you to be
responsible for them to choose something
to base it on you to be responsible for
their decision. I see which you aren't
true. The consternation within
you is simply that you do in fact wish
to be responsible for their decision.
That's correct. In a positive way.
That's correct. But you never will
be. You will be responsible for your
decision. They will be responsible for
their decision. And you can be responsible to
decision. And you can be responsible to
them and allow them to perhaps if they
choose to share certain ideas within the
decision you have made but you are only
responsible to them by being responsible
for yourself and not for them.
I understand. Now, if you are
basing your understanding of your own
worth upon whether or not they choose to
understand you, then you are only basing
your worth upon the decisions they may
or may not make. And this can cause a
great deal of consternation within you.
Because then you are not determining
what your worth is for yourself, but
letting them decide what you are worth
by saying that whatever they decide to
do will be how you choose to determine
what is real for you in terms of your
feelings about the
situation. You follow me? I do for sure.
The idea is a paradoxical one to some
degree. For you will find that the idea
of the individual who is truly living
the life they know to be true for them
has a very strong
compassion that other
individuals can find out what they know
to be true and can create the same peace
in their lives. But paradoxically along
with that comes the wisdom and the
knowledge that there is no way, shape or
form that you can show that to them
until they're ready to see it. So the
best way to be of assistance is to
simply continue to constantly be that
idea. So you will always be around to
look at should they make the decision to
find someone to look at that represents
that idea.
But it will be of no concern to you
whether they choose it now, 10 years
from now, 100 years from now, 100
lifetimes from now. Because to you it's
all one and the same. Now is
now. And if you are living your life as
now is
now, then you will not care when they
change and you will not make it a point
of contention within you that will
stretch out your existence interminably.
You are creating more sense of time for
yourself by focusing upon the amount of
time they are creating for themselves to
make a change and thus you are sharing
their misery in that sense. You follow me?
misery in that sense. You follow me?
Yes, I do. If you live in the now, you
will not experience the time in a
time way. You will simply see changes when
way. You will simply see changes when
and where they occur. as they interact
with you whenever they do will be just
fine with you whenever that might
be. And you will simply live the life
you know to be true for you and not
concern yourself as to when they may or
may not make the decision to share that
same idea with
you. For to you it is all infinite and
it is all now and one in the same thing.
And you understand that they are
learning what they need to learn and you
are learning what you need to learn and
everyone is doing just
fine because everyone is their own
unique path. And again
path. And again
paradoxically the moment you stop
waiting for
them then lo and behold before you know
it there they will be. Time will have
passed as you
say like
that. You follow me? I do. And this is
very helpful. Bashar. Not I haven't
fully handled it yet, but you've
definitely given me a way to do so. My
attention tends to go back to the
mechanics of I've made an agreement.
Call tonight. Put the money or these things.
tonight. Put the money or these things.
This individual will do these things.
What things?
Um, order me into a trial situation. All
right. So, what big
deal? Can you not explain yourself to
the best of your ability in ways that
would simply allow you to then attract
to yourself whatever situations,
whatever objects, whatever symbols,
whatever tools are necessary in your
life to allow the situation to become
alleviated. Providing I don't I cease
creating individuals in that situation
that will not listen.
Will not listen to what? To my sharing.
Why do they have to listen to your
sharing? I didn't duplicate what you
said. Then
I went off on the wrong and incorrect or
didn't recognize that what you have to
say you will say from your heart because
you believe it to be true. Yes. As long
as you believe you are functioning
within your integrity, then the idea of
the situations you attract to yourself
can all be seen no matter what their
previous definitions to be opportunities
of a positive light for you. Do not
imagine that the scenario you are
co-creating with them has to be negative
and then it won't turn out to be.
You follow me? I sure do. Go through it.
Live through it. If that is what you
create, then live through it knowing
that you are exploring exactly what you
want to
explore. The more you continue to deny
it and attempt to remove it from you,
the less you will allow yourself to
learn from
it in a positive
way. You follow me? I do. It will change
and it will transform only if you go
along with the
flow if you fight it. That is what wears
you out. That is what makes it seem as
if you are not heard. What it is that
needs to hear you will always hear you.
Always. When you say go along with the
flow, you don't mean necessarily that I
would comply with their demands.
depends on the idea as to whether their
so-called demands are in line with the reality and
demands are in line with the reality and
the choices you have given yourself. If
their demands represent the only opportunities
demands represent the only opportunities
or the only paths you feel that are open
to you, then obviously they are in line.
If you find that you have attracted
other opportunities in your life still
functioning within your integrity and
they are available to you, then take
them. But if you find that you have quote
But if you find that you have quote
unquote no other choice other than to go
the path that their demands represents,
then why not simply assume that that is
your choice as
well? And go with it. Okay? Let it flow.
Flow with it. Only when you flow with
the energy can you change
it. No one is listening because you are
fighting the energy. If you flow with
the energy, then you are traveling at
the same rate and changing it is no big
deal because everything moving at the
same rate relative to itself seems to be
standing perfectly still. So you can
move anything
anywhere. If you fight it, then it seems
as if events are washing over you,
overwhelming you, going faster than you
can handle. And then it doesn't seem as
if you can change it to the way you
desire it to be. But that is because you
are not operating on the same rate or
wavelength. You are not going with the
circumstances. Okay? And I follow you. Now, let me see
Okay? And I follow you. Now, let me see
if I translate this right when I go. If
I'm flowing with it and the person says
you deliver this money tonight
or then I deliver that money then but
but if I don't really if you know in
your openness yes that if that is what
is really necessary in your life then
you will attract a situation wherein you
will have the money if you are open in
that way in love and light and act upon
whatever opportunities present
themselves to you and none of those
opportunities bring what that individual
believes to be what they need then
simply trust it does not need to be
there and whatever the consequences of
that manifestation will still represent
the flow as you need to follow it well
the truth is I don't in my integrity
want to flow that money do you have it
to flow
no I do not all right but I could engage
in actions to get it to borrow it all
right I don't wish to but I also don't
wish to counter the individual and say
no I'm not going to do this Do you
believe that the transfer of what you
are terming the money from you to this
individual is or is not representative
of the maintenance of the integrity of
an agreement you have made?
I'm not sure, Bashar. I go back and
forth on that one. I don't at times I
don't feel that it's in alignment with
my integrity at all and other times I
feel that it is and I tend to flip back
and forth. I feel that the greatest good
at times would be to flow flow it and at
other times I go that it's out of
integrity and it's unethical to flow it
and I tend to flip back and forth. All
right. Can you understand
however that the idea now we are not
saying this is the case but we are
simply setting up a generalized example
that sometimes even flowing
money or any idea to another individual
even if in your
estimation on their side it may be
supporting something that does not
function within integrity can actually
allow integrity to become in existence.
Yes, definitely. That's why I consider
doing it. All right. At any given
moment, as you simply perceive the two
ideas, relax into yourself and simply
allow yourself to come, not make, not
force, allow yourself to come to the
decision as to which one truly
represents the idea of your integrity.
Then simply act upon that. If at any
given moment you find that the other idea
moment you find that the other idea
truly truly truly truly in all honesty
with yourself represents a more full
comprehension of your integrity then
begin to act on
that. This is not to say it will
necessarily in your terms complete
itself in the way you think it might
have to. Yes. And if I isolate back and
forth, as long as that's my integrity,
that's a fine. Yes. You are exploring
what you need to. And you may simply
find that in doing that, each and every
component, what you are perceiving to be
a component of this overall idea is in
and of itself its own complete idea.
Yes. One of the things I've did is I've
judged myself negatively for not coming
to a conclusive flow. All right. Then
your first step obviously is to cease
invalidating yourself for whatever it is
you are doing and begin doing what you
need to do. Lovely as always. I wish
I'll stay in uh let it work out. Okay.
Thank you. Thank you baby. Okay.
Speak. Oh good. Um, I would like to know
if permissible if I may share a guest
entity through me and bring her in as
you talk to another as we shared in what
you call last Monday night of your time.
Exactly. As this is a new group of
people and someone specifically invited
me to do this. All right. Now, yes. One
moment. Yes.
There will be within the timing once
again briefly the
opportunity for free a triad of
interactions. No more, no less.
Wonderful. Would you care to at least
answer another question of someone else
while I allow her in? I'll bring her in
and you do what you please.
As the alignment is being
made, each and every one of you allow
yourselves the opportunity to simply
reflect to
yourselves whatever the energy that will
be presented to you will represent to
you. Recognize that anything you
perceive on any level is valid in its
own terms. And what you can glean in an
overall understanding of this alignment
is a very strong willingness for the
expression of the collectivity of the
consciousness of a total individual and
the willingness of the expression of the
spontaneity necessary for the perception
of the conviction of the things you
desire to occur in your life. There is
sensitivity. There is insight in these
interactions. Anything you choose to
make of or perceive within your sharing,
those that will be the ones that share
directly and those that will be the ones
that share in your terms indirectly will
be reflective directly of your ability
to create from yourself to yourself.
Your own input and your own recognition
of the facets of yourself that are
represented in this
interaction procedure. Bashaw, I'm so
glad to see you again. Let me introduce
myself since there are so many people.
Would you object if I stand?
As you wish. Thank you.
My name is Zura. I am not uh I am from a
different play than Bashar. I lived in
the 15th century. I was an opera singer,
a very humongous opera singer. And uh I
speak through Shireen. Um I do not do
the same type of work as Bashar. kids is
very elevated and I do not receive this
kind of information from where I live
but I am very good with seeing inside
people's personal problems and uh other
things also but since that seems to be
what much of you are hoping to
accomplish uh within yourself I am open
to like Bashar said three questions so
is there someone here who would like to
ask me something of a personal nature
that might benefit all or only
themselves or whatever whenever it is is
conducive to your asking.
Um Craig, I've got one. Yes, go ahead.
Yeah, I wonder maybe you can and maybe
you can't answer this, but um in my
family, we have a curiosity about
something. My grandfather was married
before he married my grandmother and he
had a wife and two children. The last
time he saw them was in 1903 and uh no
one has been able to trace them down. If
if my half uncles who my brother my dad
his half brothers he never met them. If
they're still alive they would be like
around 85 to 90 years old or so but no
one has heard anything about them since
19. You don't know where they are or if
they're alive or dead is the question.
They could have died in the first world
war. Right. I understand. But go back
once again and you're telling me it's
your grandfather was originally married
to someone else and not the woman that
you mean. So the blood tie or my
grandmother. Okay, I see. So it would
have been my half uncle. I understand.
And you want to find the half uncle?
Yeah. We wonder what happened to them.
Do you not have a picture of the
original grandmother somewhere?
Um somewhere there may be a picture. I I
know. I only I only ask you so that when
I ask you what when I tell
you know if we have a picture of the
original How much do you know about your
grandfather? If I describe him to you
and for the kind of man he was, would
you know this? Um, yeah, to some. And he
played with you when you were a young
child. When I was very young. I don't
really remember. Maybe three or four.
Yeah. And did he speak another language?
Um, in the house? I don't believe he
spoke another language in the house. He
he was once uh in Japan. No, no, I don't
mean that. I mean that he carried with
him a second language. I don't believe
so. And did he that you interviewed
don't recall? Let me go back to your own
parents then. He produced which one of
your parents? My father.
Your father is still on this plane. Is
this correct? Yes. A tall man? Yes.
Slender? Yes. Uh very a very uh a strong
man in his convictions, but a quiet mind
on the outside. Very very quiet. But
strong in the convictions. Yeah. Likes
to read. Likes to sit with his newspaper
and read. Yes. Okay, then I have him.
All right. I just had to substantiate
that I had the gentleman. Very nice man.
You take very much life after him. You
know that your value systems very much
like him and he's produced a wonderful
son. I'm very glad to have met you,
Craig. Thank you. Anyway, as far as
his father, which produced the two uncles,
father, which produced the two uncles,
from what I understand, they have been
um deceased for some time. Okay. Um, I
wish I could get some more
substantiation, but from what I'm
getting, there's someone on your
father's side that died about 10 years
ago. Someone that says he knew you.
Would you know who that might be? Your
father's brother, perhaps? About 10
years ago. Well, my father's mother died
last year, but my father No, this is
quite a distance. I don't about 10 years
ago. No one. It was about 1962 that my
grandfather died. That would be 20 years
ago. Somebody else. You don't know who
it is? Could be on your mother's side.
Um, no. We haven't had any deaths on my
mother's side either at that point in
time. Could be 12 years. It's not 20 and
it's not six.
I can't think of who. Okay. It seems to
be that not only there were two the
uncles. Did you trace their heritage? It
seems that one had a family. Yeah, we
don't have any idea. You know, maybe
it's one of them. They are they one may
still be alive. One is definitely
deceased. Yeah, maybe it was them who
who died 12 years ago because we had
never the last communication we had from
anyone in that family was in 1912.
That's 74 years ago. Let me let me let
me do this for you as I ask another
person. I will look. If I see anything
more, I will let you know. If I don't, I
will let you know. How's that? Fine.
Okay. Does anybody else have a question
for me? I have a question. Could your
name be Esther? Esther as the biblical
Esther. Well, I guess so. You lived in
biblical times many thousands of years
ago. Did you not know that? Okay. You
were at the time of Moses. Did you not
know that? No, I didn't know that. Well,
now you know. I knew I was old. I didn't
know I was that old. Oh, dear. That's
not old. That's the thought. That's new.
It's not really. It's But it's older
than that. Go ahead. What would you like
to know? Well, I woke up this morning
feeling better than I felt in a long
time and a feeling of expectancy.
Something really good about to occur.
And I just wondered if you perceived
anything about that. You mean you just
felt alive when you woke up? Well, yeah,
but a little more than that. The
expectancy. Are you clairvoyant? I have
a hunch you are. Not enough. Yes, but
you do. You get very uh strong feelings.
You get vibrations of people. You can
meet someone and know right away if
they're going to become a good friend or
someone that's in and out of your life.
Is this not true? Usually. Yes. Okay.
You have very strong spirit guides. Do
you know what spirit guides are? They
talk incessantly to me. They want you to
know that you need to read more books on
how to develop this power because you
were afraid of your own gift. How does
that suit you? Sounds very true. Well,
of course. And your spirit guides giving
me the information. They say to tell you
that the meditation is too ethereal for
you that you need to read concrete
things and how to get in touch with your
own um psychic development.
Drink more orange juice. They like you
to drink
orange in the morning before noon not
after that. It's a very powerful food
and they wouldn't like you to drink it
beyond that. I used to do that always
and I was told to cut out because it's
very powerful and you would extend it
into the we hours of the night
difference you see and don't dilute it
in the morning if you do have and for
all of you when you drink juice it's
very acidic very acidic you should
always dilute half water to half juice
and if you have skin allergies usually
the first cause is some kind of acidic
drink juice and orange juice is
extremely healthy for healing purposes
if you know how to use it especially
with sick pulp Anyway, as far as if
something's going to happen, it's
already happening. You're here, are you
not? Yes, I do. And you already opened
up with Deshar's exercise much more than
you can see. But I can see that you just
dumped a whole shitload on your right
side. You know, you understand me to a
degree. So, all right. If you go home,
you'll think about it. Your spirit
guides say they talk to you in dreams
and you get very good information, but
sometimes you don't want to believe it
and you go opposite and it comes out to
be. Uhhuh. Well, my dreams sometimes
seem very real, but I can't seem to make
sense of what That's because they're
talking. They intervene in the dream.
Thank you for the question. I hope I
helped you. Yes, thank you. And one more
question. Yes, I do. What's your name?
Rosemary. And what's your name? Barbara.
Let me hear each question. I'll weigh
the one that's most important. I was I
was wondering what your relationship
with. How how you found out about him? Dream.
How how you found out about him? Dream.
the person I speak to found out about
him. Oh yeah. So what I was I was trying to
Oh yeah. So what I was I was trying to
understand
uh this is a bold spirit of your own
planetary plane. Me to a tea. No, that's
just about me. You can actually read
about me later. Let me ask this young
lady. What was your name? Barbara.
Barbara. What is your question? My
question is when I return home it's to a
very tiny little village. Is writing the
way to go
as a in a journal? You mean a
career-wise? Yes, I know. But I mean as
more of a a non-fiction? Um, you want to
write fiction? Not really. Experiences.
Yes. A journal. That's a journal. That's
what I said originally. You don't
understand a journal. Um, it's very good
for you. Whether or not you can make a
career out of it is debatable simply
because you it's very good for you
because you have um it's a way for you
to express yourself and get ideas that
you can't get in touch with on paper.
When you put your feelings on paper, you
open up like a flower, like a rose. When
you don't get your ideas out cuz you're
not you don't like to face your feelings
because they come uh they become
frightening. Then you close up like a
bud. You understand? And so writing as a
journal, I wouldn't wait till you get
back. I would start a daily journal. I
would get one of those big humongous
things and start writing on it daily.
And if you keep doing eventually
automatic handwriting will begin and you
will make a contact with a spirit of a
very nice nature who would like to speak
with you. Thank you. Does that answer
the question? Thank you very much. Thank
you for your time, Bashar. I'm glad you
find me amusing. I think you deserve
always find all interactions will be one
of ecstasy and joy. We will find you
both spirit. Thank you all.
Continue, Bajar. At this
time, Rose Marie. Yes, for sure. The
idea presented in your question is
simply that you will find there are many
different levels, many different planes
of spirit form as they understand their
own growth, their own progression, their
own willingness to be of service to many
different individuals upon the plane in
which they have existed prior to this
now spiritual
existence. We will from time to time
encounter them. This is one
manifestation, one methodology for
encountering such. The idea simply is
that because in your terminology, we are
extraterrestrial. We are beyond those
levels outside of the normal
diversification of spiritual planes that
are connected with your particular
planetary sphere. And in accessing the
idea of being able to be of assistance
to your earth, we then must interact, if
you wish to put it in colloquial terms,
receive permission from the levels of
spirits that exist that are being of
assistance most closely that are
functioning as guides most closely to
your particular planetary spirit at this
time. So from time to time the ideas
that we will encounter many different
spirit forms that are indicative of the
timing of the interaction of our energy
with you and also indicative of the
timing of when the best service can be
provided for interaction and
co-interaction with those that are the
guides that are most closely associated
with your earth plane already. That is
how we meet and that is how we involve
ourselves with each other in that
way. We will thank you. Thank you for
the idea at this time that we would like
to point out as per the illustration you
have just received and the sharing you
have allowed to take place within this
gathering is that
all individuals are bold spirits of this
nature and the interaction that you have
allowed yourself to perceive can put you
in touch squarely with your own a
psychic abilities and your own b
willingness to form connections with
your own
guides in that way and reflect
yourselves as convictions of the fact
that you are your higher consciousness
and can express that idea in this earth
reality. Recognize the primary
ingredients are the idea of the
conviction are the idea of the boldness
and are the idea of the integrity all at
the same time intermingling within a
absolute shity. recognize. It is simply
understood that all that is shared has
validity in the manner it is shared. And
the idea is that for what you generally
consider to be the expression of
validity andor accuracy in that way it
takes first the boldness, the
conviction, the willingness as you say
to put it out there and then in that way
recognize that the more you are willing
to do that, the more in line your
sensitivities will become regarding each
other, regarding your ability to share
of each other with each other. your
awareness in each other and the tap that
you have between each other about what
you all are to each other. You follow
along? Yes. Each and every one of you
are capable of exactly what you have
just witnessed in whatever form that
witnessed in whatever form that
manifests. Whether it is by association
to spirit guides, connection into higher
consciousness and the simple functioning
of your own psychic awareness to which
you are all quite
gifted because to be alive and to be
emotional is to be psychic.
The only ingredient that has ever always
been not really missing but let us say
suppressed is simply the
conviction, the
trust. That's
it. That is
it. Oh, by the
way, that's it.
We thank you for your willingness to
participate in the idea of recognizing
the connections along many
timelines. For understand one
thing, that willingness
now in the interaction you have just had
with the bold spirit put you much more
closely aligned with your own bold
spirits. Boy, are you going to have some
dreams tonight.
You then you then you then you
1 2 3 4 remember your numbers. Start.
Could you elaborate on all house eve
um all souls day and all saints day at
this time? There is not much to
elaborate on as we have already said
they are the functional memory holidays
if you wish commemoratives of the idea
of the day before the day of and the day
after the submergence and destruction of
Atlantis. In this way therefore it
represents a gate an energy gate through
which your entire consciousness is now
passing another type of transformation
that you are doing together jumping
through that doorway at the same time.
Therefore, it's going to bring up many
of the ideas of that past connection,
many of the lives that you have had in
that Atlantean continent. And you are
now facing many of the same ideas that
you undertook then and are now
integrating them in a more positive
direction rather than the idea of the
negative direction you did at that time
which brought about the destruction.
You follow me? Yes. Will that be of
assistance? Yes, it will. But could you
also explain the mechanism of the
gateway? It is an energy gate. The idea
that we have discussed that when
consciousness impinges itself upon the
electromagnetic spectrum of the physical
reality. The vibratory patterns as they
overlap tend to reinforce each other in
certain areas and cancel each other out
in other areas. Standing wave patterns
of electromagnetic energy are created
within consciousness. And those standing
waves that reinforce each other function
as a gate, a level that accelerates you
to a new level, a new vibratory
awareness. The gate is a stepping up of
your energy into a new plane of
existence, a new
acceleration. You follow me? Yes. But it
represents a timing. But we don't
actually move. Nothing moves. We are
using your colloquial terminology. Okay.
But you become other than what you are
all at once rather than individually.
All right. You follow me? Yes.
Thank you. Thank you. Number two. Hi.
Hi.
How are you today? Perfect. I'm you.
I am I'm fine.
I've had a lot of I've had a lot of
those dreams again. You know, dreams of
the future. Yes.
Dreams of the alternate present. Yeah.
And today when I was outside the window
listening to you, it all came together
and I realized what my dreams were
about. Thank you. I appreciate hearing
you every week because it helps me
center myself in a way. We will thank
you for your willingness to do your
centering on your own. Thank you.
H
it's just the the What are they all
about? These dreams. Well, I dreamed
that I was at the
water with the with the my boss. Yay.
And but I did not ask you what the dream
was. I asked you what they were all
about. What they're all about? Yay. I
really didn't know until I came here
tonight. And what are they all about?
Um, are you sure you know now?
Well, my my dream was was trying to save
something in the water. Yay. With my
partner friend. Yay. And then
today it seems like I lost something
that was very precious to me. Lost.
Yeah. Lost. Lost.
Oh. Lost.
It's not there physically anymore.
Father bothers me. Oh, why? Well,
because I am in this physiological
world. So what? That's not an excuse. My
friend helps me in my physiological
world. You help yourself as well. So now
I've got I do it all by myself. You
always have.
Okay. Understand that the idea of what
you say you get from
us, you are doing it yourself. You
simply let us inspire you. But recognize
the inspiration is exactly the way it
sounds. Inspiration. It is within you.
You are doing it. You simply think you
need me to do so. But you
don't. You're doing it anyway. Yeah. I'm
on a good path. Everything. You are a
good path. You are a path.
Period. A path is not what you are on. A
path is what you are.
How do you feel?
Uh, sad. Sad. All right. If you so
desire, continue to be sad.
Well, doesn't sound very sad to me.
I don't have to be is up to you. You're
right. Whatever you enjoy the most. If
you enjoy sadness the most, by all
means. If you're going to create
sadness, then create
it. Really create
it. Get into it, as you
say. Don't do it
halfway. Get into a funk.
Let's dredge up that
misery. Let's let it fall right through
the
bottom until you can't go any further
down. So that at that point then
everything else looks like
up. Anything else? Better. Better.
[Laughter]
Does that assist too? Yeah, it does.
Because maybe what I perceive as sadness
is not sadness in the reality of the
situations of all parties involved
actually be gladness. And what I
perceive as sadness might actually be
freedom of for the other friend that I
lost. Perhaps. And if you can hook into
that, then perhaps you will be free too.
Yeah. Yeah. I mean you saw that by me
seeing the sadness it's like okay what
are you going to benefit out of this
sadness well has created an opportunity
for everyone to have a good laugh.
Thank you for that opportunity.
[Music] Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Number
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Number
three.
Yay. Sure. Um I had a question about
astral projection. All right. Um I read
Monroe's book on it. Nice. And um which
oh I didn't know he had more than one
out of body. Yes body and um in it he
mentions that um when he was astral
projecting and he was returning to his
body. He mistakenly went into someone
else's body and that kind of concerned
me a little bit. If you leave your body
when you're astral projecting can
somebody else come into your body? Well,
let's say theoretically yes, so to
speak. However, recognize that that
individual is quite all right if you
follow me. Mhm. Both of them are quite
all right. And only did they attract
themselves to another individual that
will allow everything to turn out quite
all right. You follow me? Mhm. The
experience was still reflective and
still representative of the knowing of
their trust and so still turned out that
way no matter what the experience. Do
you follow me? So it's just a matter of
if you have any fear, it's just a matter
of trusting that everything will turn
out over. Yeah. Understand that if time
coming in what you may term your
future, you will as spirit forms share
many of the same bodies. For you will no
longer have a need to continue
to birth new bodies upon your planet.
And whatever physiological experience
you may have need of will be short and
you will share bodies taking turns to
gain that
experience. So it is possible to have
that interchange. It simply may have
been something that whether they
recognized it at the time or not, that
individual needed to get them over a
certain fear that they had. You follow
me? It didn't happen by accident. That's
for sure. It was a situation that they
created to overcome the fear to face it.
Yikes. Um I also had another question. Earlier
Um I also had another question. Earlier
this evening, a woman said that she was
having really bad headaches and you
talked about that. And about six years
ago, um right after I got married, I was
having really bad um pains in my um
upper abdomen. Nice. And um it reoccurs
every once in a while. been less often
lately. But I was wondering if that was
about the same type of thing that you
discussed as blocking some energy to
some degree. Slightly different. The
idea of your abdomen in that area
represents the chakra or the vortex or
the doorway or the gateway of your
intentional energy. Intention.
Intention. Intention. Intention. Yes.
Uhhuh. The idea therefore is to examine
the idea of the
intentions that may have been brought
about or were
paramount or most prominent at the time
of the idea of the activation of that
relationship and what you have learned
from it since then about what you intend
in
life and how you express yourself and
what you have learned about expressing
your intention. how much you have centered
intention. how much you have centered
within the understanding of your ability
to express your intention. Intention
being that which you feel to be the
direction of your creative urge so to
speak. the following
um to some degree you're saying that um
the idea also of the pressure in that
area from time to time is a very strong
connection forming with what you may
call your future self whether it be the
idea beyond this physical life or in
this physical life in terms of what it
is you are becoming that is why it is
the chakra of intention what you intend
to be
you follow me
it is a direct linkage
It will assimilate more and more and
more and more and more, more easily,
more flow. Rely upon your dream reality
to do so. Be the future you now and you
won't keep putting it off.
There will always be another future you.
You won't run out of them.
You will never be the future you. Too
fast. So, I was at that point questioning my
So, I was at that point questioning my
intention. Okay. To some degree, but
also forming a link that led directly to
the idea of becoming the you you really
desired to be and using that idea, that
situation, that relationship to get you
there. It showed you what the reason,
basic reason, fundamental reason for the
relationship was to form that specific
link to awaken certain ideas within you
that would lead you to be the particular
person you are becoming now or that you
are. Mhm. I see. Thank you. Thank you,
Bashar. Number four, sure.
Uhhuh. Bashar then you
pardon. I just truly want to say even
though you already know it, I love you.
Oh, thank you. And appreciate your
sharing.
We love you all.
I do have um a question I would like to
ask. All right then you all right I've
come from a philosophy that had taught
more or less that tiredness related to
uh nothing but failed purposes and
losses and I was wondering if you had
another viewpoint regarding you can
create a physiological manifestation
physiological reinforcement of the idea
that may create tiredness within your
body the idea of what you may turn to be
dietary
or expression of energy, the way it is
expressed, the situations you attract in
your life that may make it feel as if
you are fighting uphill battles. All of
these ideas can be reflective in
physical reality of the
idea that you feel you need to be tired
in order to get anything accomplished. [Music]
[Music]
But in this way, generally speaking,
tiredness does only stem fundamentally
from fighting yourself. Yes, fighting
your own ecstasy. Believing that you
have to have a conflict in that sense to
struggle through in order to achieve
anything. That's
That's
tiring. Fighting yourself is tiring.
How is your
diet? I have thought recently of going
into being a breath a breatharian and
that was my second question. It's
interesting you ask uh
food I I don't always say the right
words bores me but it seems like a
strange thing that we have to get up and
have breakfast lunch and dinner when I
do eat I eat extremely good food but it
doesn't seem to agree with me as some
things that I experience in life seem to
equate the same way. All
right. Rely upon your energy. Rely upon
your glands in that way. For now, you
might be able to avail yourself to some
degree of the idea of juices.
Yes. Some of the lighter vegetable forms
may also be of some assistance and
milk with somebody else. You just want
that's more or less
there can still to some degree be some
of the toxicity in general for your
society. What you may call if you have a
pension for it, goats milk may not
provide the same toxicity. That's right.
All right. Then trust your cravings. It
is your body consciousness telling you
something. You follow me? Yes.
There is a need to some degree in our
perception to purge in your terms some
toxins from your system.
Lightness to some degree will do it.
Much much much much water many of the
clear juices some of the lighter
vegetables in this way. Basically
that you follow me. Yeah. Seems like
every time I walk outside I get the
butterflies. Do you remember your your
butterfly? Lighten up. Yes. Yes. Lighten
up. Fly lighten up.
Now breathing in a idea of becoming a
breathing in a idea of becoming a
bretharian. As you say, breathing will
also be of assistance to oxygenate your
system. Your system does need
oxygenation. There may be other ways
that this can be assisted or
accomplished. The idea of the ingestion of water,
The idea of the ingestion of water,
purified water, energized purified water
will be of some assistance in this way.
What do you mean energized purified?
Energize it with your electromagnetic
field. Oh goodness.
Crystals may be of assistance to you in
this way. Clear quartz
way. Clear quartz
crystals placed in the water energizing
it not to purify it. Use what you
colloquially call in your society
purified water.
Purchase it that way and energize it.
like distilled water, guys. But some are
labeled specifically
purified, though it is much the same. One
moment. to some degree
some moderation some ideas also of some fasts
moderation some ideas also of some fasts
involving the idea you call wheat grass
maybe of assistance to
you very close to all
right the water the
lightness all those ideas and the
breathing in the breathing in the deep
and relaxed breathing that will lighten
you up and oxygenate you all right yes
now as far
Could it be a futurist being literally
going into being becoming a bretharian?
In a sense, yes, that is what you are
all heading for in a sense. Anyway, oh
great, that is basically what our
society is in a sense. We simply rely
upon direct energy around us rather than
the ingestion of food. But it isn't that
it it doesn't have to be that important
or no for life etc etc. No, but do not
make it so important to become the
bretharian. It just feels natural. Oh
yes, but go with it in a natural way.
That is all right. Rely upon the energy
you have access to when you have access
to it. But if you must still ingest,
then ingest what is the closest
approximation of
it. Something light rather than getting
into animal foods and there's something
that's almost repelling. This is just
fairly recent. Then simply take that as
your body consciousness talking to you
in the same manner.
The idea is that when you do accelerate
and lighten up in that way, you will
simply lose the urge for certain
sustenances. Period. You don't have to
force yourself out of it. You will lose
the urge.
You follow me? Yes. Thank you. Thank you
very much. Thank you very much. Thank
you. Actually, I have two questions.
Mine was very much about food, too. I'm
having the same uh What a coincidence.
Oh, I have the same urge. I've been
wanting to really lighten up and then
the load, you know, do so. And Okay. I
[Music] um Okay. Um Well, I Well, I have another
um Okay. Um Well, I Well, I have another
question, too. All right. I'm I for some
reason I'm
manifesting what has been diagnosed as a
fibroid tumor and um I'd like to have your ideas
tumor and um I'd like to have your ideas
on this. In what area? In my
uterus. They are in your
terms as you have been told. The
information you have
received, are they considered in your
terms non-malignant?
Yes. Well, I we haven't actually done a
biopsy yet. I used to check it out, you
know, uh briefly kind of. All right.
Just an example. We would suggest that
you continue along the lines of your
belief system within your medical
practitioners for that is still very
strongly ingrained within you as a
belief system. It is not part of me
doesn't I don't particularly want to
have Right? You are phasing. You are
phasing. You are phasing.
Use what you can of the belief system.
Now using one part of it doesn't mean
you have to go through the whole ideas
in the same manner. But get to a point
you are comfortable with in simply
accessing the information that you need.
Then when you have the total information
according to how you understand it,
according to the belief system you are
using, then you can deal with it in
another way. Okay. All right. Thanks for
show do that first. Okay. Now my friend
wants me to ask what's this? What that
33 and a third what is it? 33 second
technique technique 33 second technique
that is available to you through the
sources of what you call taped
information from another consciousness
you call Lazarus. It is very succinct.
It is very clear. It is very impactful.
Thank you. I'll get to Thank you.
Yay. I have a question for myself and one for
I have a question for myself and one for
a friend. Um All right. I'll start with
hers then I'll go to mine. All right.
She um well I was going to say lost.
Okay. Her husband was killed last
Thursday in a plane crash. All right.
She has been um integrating this
experience and doing very well with it
with lots of support and love from her
friends. All right. And she said I told
her I was coming tonight and and would
she like me to ask you something. She
said I have so many symbols going around
in my universe. I don't know what to
ask, but ask Bashar if there's any
message that he would like to send me.
And this is for Peggy. All right. Well,
how about the idea of simply for now?
For now, which can create a stronger
link of communication between them. For
now, allow her to tap into the
understanding that soaring like a free spirit is a
that soaring like a free spirit is a
beautiful way to die.
Yes, that was my feeling. I think I
think I mentioned that to her. Then let
her soar. You are on the right track.
Wonderful. When she soarses in her
spirit, she will place herself on the
same level to
receive the information of the
communication. All right. Yes. That's lovely. Thank
All right. Yes. That's lovely. Thank
you. The basic message is really quite
simple. It is simply that where the
individual now finds themsself to be is
very very beautiful. And that is what he
wishes her to know. fundamentally
she'll be happy to hear that it is
something she actually already knew.
Yes, I'm sure that she does. But that is
the first idea. Soar with him.
Do not feel as if she has been left
behind. She has the ability to soar.
All right. Yes. Thank you.
Now um I have been going through um pros and
um I have been going through um pros and
cons about a situation that has been
developing over period of years and I
pro and con. That's right. Uh having to
do with my teeth. Now, I've been to my
dental practitioners and I have gotten
the information that what I need is
dental surgery, which consists of, you
know, cutting, reshaping the jaw, wiring
it shut. I thought that'd be a great way
to lose weight.
It's quite expensive. So, I've been
exploring all these ideas and it's it's
a wonderful test of abundance. No,
right. In one way, it's not even so much
a test because I feel that it would be I
I know that I can create the funds to do
this, but I'm I keep counterbalancing
between that idea and being able to, as
the lady back here wanted to do with her
car, create a change physiologically
um from the spiritual causal plane. So
all right, reflect to me what you will
about this. Well, you can do it. Tell me
more. Well, if you are willing to do it
from the causal plane, avail yourself of
the same technique we already referred
to. You can also understand that blue energy
You can also understand that blue energy
is very specifically impactful upon the
teeth, blue light.
This would include reshaping the jaw.
That might involve something else, but
it will allow there to be some
strengthening within what you perceive
to be the anal.
Great and within some of the bone
structures. Now the idea is that you are in a sense
Now the idea is that you are in a sense
an electromagnetic
potential and especially in the teeth
area it represents a slight out of phase
out of balance idea between the positive
and the negative poles within your body
within the cellular structures of your
being. The idea in this way therefore can be
The idea in this way therefore can be
through the visualization of allowing
yourself to be balanced
electromagnetically. Seeing yourself as
a battery in that way that is balanced.
Allow the flows to come and go as they
need to go as they need to come. To
balance yourself as an electromagnetic
being can be of some assistance in that
way and it is again connected into the
idea of simply being in touch with the
blue white light of your oric
field. This can offer some support for
you. We also perceive that you can
investigate some of the ideas of herbal
applications which may allow some degree
of some of this balance to occur within
you for the
for the
electromagnetic balancing for the
application and the idea of your mouth
and your teeth. Okay? Explore the idea
of what you may call herbal
concoctions. Keep them simple. Keep them
direct. Doesn't have to get complex.
Follow your instincts. Okay. I have a
friend who's very wellversed in herbs.
What should I ask him about that so he
would know? Tell your friend what you
told me. Okay.
All right. Yes. Anything else?
Yes. I love you. Oh, that's that's
fantastic, Michelle. I was just going to
say that to you. I know.
Thank you.
At this time
Allow us once again to remind each and
every one of you that you are
spirit. Title for tonight. You are
spirit. Wake
up and start
dreaming. We thank you for allowing us
to experience the gift of your
consciousness, the gift of your love,
the gift of your sharing that we are
together forever.
We will see you in the
dream. A fond and loving good night.
Good night. [Music]
How did everything go?
[Music] Pretty good. Pretty good. Thank you for
Pretty good. Pretty good. Thank you for
being here tonight, everyone.
[Music] [Applause] Yeah.
Anyone who would like to see Lynn right
here.