In this way, recognize that the energy
you are manifesting at this time is
allowing you to understand that the
exchange as you have cocreated it to
exist in the form it exists now is so
that you can recognize that all similar
exchanges which have usually, in your
terms, undergone their transitions
covertly, are now being brought to the
surface. And the exchanges are taking
place very blatantly in that way.
Nothing is being hidden in that sense.
All the interactions are taking place
right upon the surface. So that each and
every one of you can now understand.
There is no longer even the idea of the
need to keep such interchanges, such
exchanges under the rug, as you say. But
in this way, to bring them to the
surface, to give you the opportunity to
see clearly, consciously, whether or not
you truly do or do not wish that to be
representative of the type of reality
you feel you want to live in. Are you
following along so far?
Recognize in this way it is your
willingness to
face having such a decision in your
reality because it is now out in the
open for everyone to see in that way
and you can allow yourselves to
recognize. Now
understand this is not a chastisement.
It is not a judgment in your
terminology. It is simply an observation
from our point of view. You have
cocreated an opportunity to allow you,
we are speaking of the idea for now of
what you call your country specifically
to allow you to function and act within
the idea of strength. And in our
perspective, you chose weakness.
In this way you allowed yourself the
opportunity to become exactly like that
which you said you upholded. You follow
me? Now in this
way allow us if you
will someone anyone verbatim with what
you call your pencil and your paper.
Take this down though we recognize it
will be on your tape as well.
follows. While you are getting ready in
this way, we will illuminate that many
of you have recognized that we have
shared with you the idea that this is
activity month and active it is. Now
active on your part you can be and we
have suggested a few ideas about
recognizing that you are your
governments and that you can communicate
as your governments to other factions of
your government as you have created
them. letting them know that you prefer
peace and trusting your own imagination
to allow you the opportunity to
communicate with them in whatever way,
shape, and forth. You so desire without
judging, without chastising, without
accusation. Now, you have asked me many
times for the idea of suggestion. Now,
not that you have to do this, but I am
about to give you one.
Are you ready? Yeah. All right.
Write this
down. You You
have killed. We We
have killed. have
shown each
other that it that it
is
easy for for
us
to kill. Can We We
each
now exhibit the
strength that it takes to
love one another. We We
are willing to co-create co-create
a
reality of faith. harmony harmony
and mutually supportive supportive
and beneficial exchange.
Sign it the people of the United States. Now our
Now our
suggestion would be to take
this, print it in what you call your
language of English, your language of
Arabic on the same card and
card and
suggest to your recognizable
governmental structure, even though you
yourselves are your
government that
these cards be
cards be
allowed in this
way using what you know to be your
so-called military machinery, your
planes, your
ships, using those devices as you have
already used them for destruction.
Use those planks. Use those ships.
Take these cards with both
languages and as
many thousands as many
thousands as many
thousands of car and as many
thousands as many thousands of flowers
as you can
find and drop those on their country.
That is our suggestion.
You can
form a
cooperation and again without judgment,
without accusation,
without desperation.
desperation.
Offer not in a demanding way but with a
type of knowing insistence.
You understand the difference
that your governmental structure in this
way would then be able to find that no
one in your
world would be
able to view the
idea negatively as they have viewed what
you have done
negatively in any way that would matter
to
you if you are
willing to take the opportunity to take
the first step, make the first offering
now in your terms that you are
equal life for
life. That is our suggestion. You may do
with it as you wish.
It is that
degree of
boldness and that
cooperation that we have meant when we
suggested that you
communicate equally with your
governments. as boldly as you are
willing to, as creatively as you are
willing to, as
lovingly as you are willing
to. We thank you for allowing us to
suggest that idea, will
you? And no matter what you do with it,
we will always send you our
unconditional love.
We thank you. Sure.
What are the ramifications of the decision? It's decision? It's
April
and the
time decision.
Yes, this is it. Make it.
You are right in the middle of
it. This is the idea.
Choose how you want your world to be and
act like it. It is the performing of the
action that is representative of the
world you believe you want. That is what
will be making the
decision. Follow me. Here it is big and
bold right in front of you all.
Yes. Could the action be taken uh in
one's local spheres?
Of course. Uh well, certainly they can.
Uh but I mean I was going to say instead
of acting in a large international
sphere, act within your own neighborhood
or just the people that you know
reflecting those things that you would
like the country to reflect to other
countries. Do all you are willing to do.
Thank you. Sure.
This may sound a little strange, but I
felt I had an experience that's been
sort of going on for the last two, three
weeks. Um, and somehow I felt it was an
analogy with the Lydia incident. Oh,
right. It started out with my dog, one
of my dogs coming into the house with uh
on two different occasions eating goods.
I didn't actually see it. I just thought
it Oh, right. And I first thought, well,
that's really, you know, strange. I
didn't like it.
And last weekend um it occurred to me
that I really should think about it in
terms of myself what it meant. All
right. What did you come up with? Well,
it
reflected I've always had a problem all
my life about the food chain and the
quote cruelty of nature and I thought
well perhaps um it just reflects there
that I should accept it or it reflects a
decision I have to make. No. Yeah. And
over the weekend
um I did some planting and I planted the
tomato plants and stuff and um on Monday
I saw that the snails had gotten to my
tomatoes and had eaten most of them.
Gosh, half of them. And I got really
angry and I really sort of agonized
about what to do because I don't like to
eat poisons and I don't like to kill
things. Oh, right. And I thought, well,
gee, they're going to eat everything I
plant. You know, I have to kill them
after all. Well, this I know. Then
towards the end of the day, I thought,
okay, I'll build a trench around it to
make a barrier and go talk to the snail
consciousness up my hill. And u so
that's what I did. And then later on on
Tuesday morning, I realized that I had
sort of gone through the same
thing in in a very minor way. Not a
minor way, a private way. Oh, private
way that I represented in the United
States having to make a decision about
intrusions on my territory. Yes. And um
so I got pretty good that I decided not
to kill you. Thank you very much.
that decision whether you may think so
or not make a difference in the entire
world. Thank you. Thank you. For sure. Good.
Thank you. Thank you. For sure. Good.
Um want to relate to you something that
happened to me on the 11th of April. All
right. I was uh planning to go to work. Uh
I was uh planning to go to work. Uh
somehow my ride and I never contact we
never met. All right.
Um, so I called a friend and she picked
me up. She called her work and she
wasn't supposed to go to work that day
either. It just so happens that this
particular individual that I spent the
whole day with, right, was the most
active person I've ever met in my life.
Oh, good reflection.
I was just wondering what's significant.
Significance. Significant. What's significant? The
Significant. What's significant? The
most active person I have met in my
life. This is activity month. What
significance? 1 + 1 equals
Well, actually, what I I want to be a
little bit more specific about Well, all
right. It doesn't have anything to do
the uh blending of our energy on that
particular day or what do you perceive
about that?
Sometimes I marvel [Music]
[Music]
at not to be
derogatory. Your lack of willingness to
recognize an obvious thing and allow it
to be enough to stand on its own right.
I got that. But I thought there could be
more to it than I could perceive from
the third density. So So I'm interested.
So find out. Like how? Act on it.
continue to act on it and you will lead
yourself where you need to go.
Is that not sufficient for you? That's
fine. Are you sure? Do you truly
understand how it will give you what you
want? No, not really. Then it is not
sufficient for you. Right?
Understand the whole idea is that you
have created that interaction to begin
with. All you need to do in life is to
continue to live what life you are
creating to find out everything about
why you're creating it. You do not find
out what the process is for by stopping
it and analyzing it.
You find out by experiencing it, by
letting it flow and flowing with it.
Then it becomes obvious and you will
recognize the growth that you are
getting from the interaction. Why do we
come here and ask you questions? I don't
know.
That has always been our primary point.
I will be doing my job the best when you
don't need me anymore.
You get it?
I then it will be a gift in that
way. Beginning of the breaking of a
longheld habit, segregation in that way. And even
habit, segregation in that way. And even
though you will find that that idea was
explored in your country, the idea of
separation and that sense, your country
still is the idea of the representation
of the blending of all cultures.
Right. Does that answer your question?
Just one last right. I have this idea
that there is a master plan and that
well in a sense consciousnesses such as
yourself, your civilization, other
civilizations have an intention to lend
support to the execution of the master
plan like a game of chess and that the
founding of the United States was a
definite intentioned move in that
overall game. My curiosity is it what's
the the most imminent next move at this
point in our in time as we measure time
consider this the willingness as we have been
this the willingness as we have been
telling you for quite some time to act
as the next step as if it already
existed. It is the blending of your
entire planet into one
consciousness. Just as you had
individuals who became tribes, who
became villages, who became towns, who
became cities, who became countries, who
are now becoming one world, who will
then become a part of the idea of an
association of worlds.
Got it. Thank you very much. Thank you.
Thank you. Over the last few years, I've
come across some information. Um well,
are you familiar with
um writers on our planet? So, okay. Ruth
Montgomery. Nice. Okay. Um information
I'm talking
about talks about things like what
happened in Libya. Okay. And I feel
really concerned about it because
concerned why? Well, it's my own my own
fear. So obviously there's lessons for
me to learn about myself. All right.
Until you allow yourself to transform
that fear, that will be the reality you
experience. And that is my question. Can
you give me some suggestions on that?
Because I've tried different things and
I thought that then how about not trying
but doing otherwise if you are trying you
doing otherwise if you are trying you
are only doing trying. In your
terminology it is half-hearted.
Okay. I understand. All right. Um, where
is your trust?
Where is your knowingness that the
reality of peace and harmony is the
reality you believe to be the one that
has the most power behind it.
I have been more and more in touch with
feeling that. All right. You know, the
last few months and coming here and
talking to you and learning. All right.
And I feel really good. In that sense,
you can first of all understand that you
are doing just fine. Okay. But when this
whole thing with Livia started, I guess
it was maybe it's just an old um idea
that came up. It reminded me of an old
feeling. I'm not real sure.
Like any given moment are new.
You make the connection that says it is
old. Thank you for reminding me.
Okay. the the
Yeah.
Every idea like any given moment is
idea like any given moment is
new. Even if you choose in that new
moment to create a connection to the
idea of the past, to something you
consider to be
old. But it is never the same. Never.
You are a different perspective, a
different point of view, a different
time frame, space,
reference. It is always a new
perspective. Any connections that seem
to be repeating are the ones you are
choosing to make so that you can see how
the idea relates to where you are now.
Only because you judge that it is
something old coming up again and
feeling like you have not made progress
do you not see that it is a new
perspective and allow yourself to reap
the benefits of that point of view.
Okay. You follow the mechanism. Yes.
Um, the other part of my question had to
do with um, a lot of what her books talk
about, right?
Um, I guess I just would like to comment
or your idea on
I don't understand why those books end
up on our planet to begin with. I mean,
why they end up on our planet? Well, I
mean, I don't know how fall out of the
sky. Of course not. I know that. I mean,
you know, why do we end up with
um according to Ruth Montgomery, she is
receiving channelneled information,
guys? Okay. Why is this kind of
information coming here? That's what I
want to know. If I hear other types of
information from other channels saying
it's as you perceive it to be. So, if
you want to be involved in the fear
consciousness and then you will get
fear. And so in that way what you can
And so in that way what you can
understand is that an individual who
chooses to channel their higher self in
that way with that belief system already
intact will translate the idea in their
own terminology. Mhm. It is as simple as
that. Okay.
So maybe is she channeling are there
actual uh energies that are channeling
through her or is and she's perceiving
it as the way she feels it should be. Is
that what you're saying to a degree?
Okay, I understand. Thank you.
It is funneling through a structure, a
belief system and being translated
according to the terms inherent in that
belief system because the feeling is the same
system because the feeling is the same
and because of the way you have
structured your world in that
way. There is not necessarily the
opportunity to understand that it is
being interpreted rather than allowed
literally through. You follow me? Mhm. If you wish
through. You follow me? Mhm. If you wish
the idea of any socalled guidelines at
all, it is simply very basically this
idea. You are
self-empowered to choose whatever
reality you desire.
There is no one
way. The truth is composed of all
truths. You create your own reality
according to your
beliefs. That is
it. That is all that defines the
physical universe.
Therefore, any idea that carries
specificity within it about
how the reality in your universe can be
structured is a suggestion based upon a
perception that is the vibration that is
harmonious with the individual making
the suggestion.
You can adapt it in whatever way your
imagination sees fit because that is the
nature of the
information. It is basically neutral.
You give it the meaning that it has. All
situation, all
situations are
fundamentally neutral. Nothing carries with it
neutral. Nothing carries with it
meaning. You give it meaning.
according to your perception of your
relative position and viewpoint
regarding the situation. But all
elements of a situation are basically
neutral. At least that is how the higher
self sees it. You follow me? Yes, I do.
Very clear. Then you can understand it
is up to you to glean and create
positive manifestation from a positive
attitude and point of view or negative
manifestation from a negative attitude
and point of view about a basically
neutral situation.
So therefore then people are just going
to resonate resonate to the information
that feels right for them. Correct. That
is all there is to it. And much of the
information comes through in various
ways so that it can reach all the
different ways people look at things so
they can all feel the basic energy that
is there and understand it on that term.
But all of the trappings that go with
it, they are not essential for the
understanding of the basic
feeling. You follow me? Thank you. Thank
you very much. Thank you guys. Mr.
Bashar, um it's my understanding that
you on your planet as you create time to
exist create time more flexibly than we
have been creating it on our planet. As
such, as we have counted time, you have
been uh channeling well basically
through through Daryl here at Steve's
house for about 15 or 16 months. I'm
wondering as you count time on your
planet is three three months guys. So
ours is significantly more expansive in
that respect. Yes. That's very
interesting. Thank you. Okay. I have one more
Thank you. Okay. I have one more
question for myself. Could you help me
pinpoint the source of my high degree of
interest and facility and love of
words? The idea
as we perceive it
primarily stems from many many ideas of
incarnation having to do with the study
of the physical universe and requiring
precise formulation to describe that
idea. Oh yeah. And
also a couple of lies in which you were
very distraught over not being
understood in your communication. and so
made let us say a pack with yourself to
discover anything that would assist you
in the precise communication of your
intention. So you are highly focused in
that way primarily because of a need to
define things that were important to
you. Uhhuh. It's interesting. It comes
from a high degree of
separation which has from which I
created the idea of needing to
communicate. In other words, I separate
and then I need to create the idea of
communicating. Oh, wonderfully creative
paradox. Thank you. Yeah, I had fun with
it. So,
how you want to uh take this a little bit
you want to uh take this a little bit
further that what you said to write etc.
Uh I know some of us or quite a few of
us have been writing to the president
and I wrote the president and the
speakers of the house etc etc. Uh now uh
I would like to suggest that perhaps we
again write and those that haven't
written go ahead and write incorporate
this in their letter stating what you in
in our own words what you stated asking
them to do this and I and also we could
probably I think what we need is to join
together and get this going like contact
churches, things like that, the people
that are wanting uh the peace, the love.
Thank you for your suggestion and your
willingness to do that. Anyone else who
wishes to share that idea may join
along. Thank you. Thank you very much.
Yes. Female and male.
Um I have more than one thing, but first
of all, I want to thank that I happen to
think how to this idea of the card.
There's a that occurs though oh I think it's
a that occurs though oh I think it's
weekly or something called the exam or
something like that this little weekly
tabloid that's like read by millions and
millions of
people and they love causes and I
imagine that they would probably be
willing to print something like that and
get you know millions of people to send
in money and and get the idea going if
somebody wants to do that. All right.
Yeah. You just volunteered. I just
I just
dy Okay. Um what uh the first thing I
want to ask you is going right along the
line with what he was saying is I'm
interested in pinpointing this um for
myself this incredible this what pardon
me this what incredible what credible
you see I am becoming selectively third
density deaf.
That's great. Thank you. Oh, thank you.
Intense fasination that I seem to have
for uh physics
uh physics
and atoms and the malleability of atoms.
Yes. And things of this nature which as a
And things of this nature which as a
secretary in my in the previous history
of this lifetime has nothing to do with.
Guys, one connection that we can
perceive and this is all we can share
with you at this time. For we do not
want to increase the labeling of things
is one connection to the idea you call
scientist in Atlantis and one not on
this planet.
With the one not on this planet, you
consider that a future life or a past
life?
In our terms, our perception is that it
can be both.
Okay. to form the triangulation
the center. Yes.
[Music] Um interesting. Now I have two more
Um interesting. Now I have two more
things. One is I have a question to ask
you. I was listening to a tape of one
that you did last week or the week
before and you were talking about the
idea uh that your society calls of the
fact that if something is not going as
you expected that that's wonderful and
it some has something to do with the
fact that that means that the higher
self is taking over or in yeah taking
over. Um now we are simply saying that
it is a statement of trust that even
what you call the
unexpected is a part of the path you
chose to be. Okay.
I was
wonder at some point all decided that
that was what it was that was
[Music] now let's see oh another thing
now let's see oh another thing
actually one is I have a sharing which
is quite fascinating and I want to share
it with everybody right the um this
previous week or two weeks actually been
uh quite active in my universe that I've
judged to be negative and everything.
So, okay. And anyway, I got quite ill
bodily as far as like physical disease,
Paul, right? Flu and that sort of thing,
guys. Anyway, and so one night I was
laying Sunday night. I was laying in bed
and I was like feeling extremely
uncomfortable and had chills and it um
just really sick in our terms of sick
and laying there and I kind of dozed off
and and uh I
dreamed quote unquote that instead of
having intense terrible chills and I was
extremely cold but I was just the
opposite but I was like way too warm and
just this intense peak. Yeah. And then I
realized that I was viewing both of
these realities and I was actually in
both of these realities. I felt the body
and the whole thing and it was totally
real just as this is right here. But I
realized that both of those were a
dream, not just the one. I was sort of
the spectator although I was in the
reality. Very good.
Very good. Kind of a new both are dreams
and both are real. Well, I've heard you
say this many times and I had not had
the personal experience. Now you have.
Yeah. Thank you. Great.
Okay. Now, uh, one other thing is
briefly. Okay. Um, one of the things
I've been experiencing for a number of
months now is is a phenomena having to
do with memory, guys. And
u it it seems to be go getting worse
rather than better. No, no, no, no, no.
Wait a minute. Let me in my own
estimation. But I look at things like
something else you are choosing to
judge. Okay, that's true. But let me
think. So like for instance, um the
other day I was in the shower. I mean I
was going to get in the shower and then
uh and then I looked over and the water
was running in the shower. Now I know I
must have turned it on. There was nobody
else there. But I have I had absolutely
no memory, no recollection, no pictures,
nothing. Nothing there. All right. And I
tried real hard to remember doing it. I
had nothing to go on. Nothing. And this
has been happening. Yes. And of course
at work it's real frustrating because I
cannot remember what I'm supposed to
remember or have. You know we said that
is one of the symptoms of the
transformation. As you are becoming more
in the now, you recognize that the
present is not a result of the past and
you draw the connection to the past so
that in the now moment you know exactly
what you need to know as the now being
that you are and do not have to create
the idea of a memory to know it. Okay.
Well, the thing with the shower and in
that way recognize there can be
situations symptomatic of this idea of
recognizing that the you that you were
when you turned the shower on is not the
you you were when you went back and saw
it. So the you that you were that sought
did not contain the memory of having
turned it on because you were another
you more completely than you have ever
been before. That's interesting. Yeah.
At the moment that occurred I looked at
I thought well
Yeah. Okay. In this situation, I do not
need the memory because it doesn't I
mean the shower is on and now I'm going
to
you are allowing yourself to get used to
the idea a little bit at a time so that
you can trust it and allow it to be a
comfortable shift. Mhm. Okay. Yeah. Work
ahead. All right. Did you enjoy your shower?
All right. Did you enjoy your shower?
Yes.
I even tried to look at the fact that I
didn't need to remember having Oh, thank
you very much for your sharing. Thank
you, May. Yes, you're going to love this
one, B. Oh, thank you.
I always do. How can I best me
specifically, how can I best avail
myself of my higher consciousness?
How do you talk to it? Yep. What does it
tell you? A lot of things. Well, why not ask
you? A lot of things. Well, why not ask
it? Uh, well, I was thinking that might
maybe you'd be a good reflection from
it. Very clever of you.
But take the responsibility and see what
happens. Now, using your
Now, using your
imagination, if you are to ask your
higher consciousness right now the
question you have asked me, what does it
say? Don't think about it. What is the
first thing you get? I get a number of
things. All right. But I definitely get
something. Thank you. Then understand
you are already doing it. Yeah. Exactly
as you need to be. Thank you for your
willingness to recognize you are already
plugged in. I have another question. All
right. It seems a a being coming through
it.
The purpose of the interaction. Yeah.
It is to some degree the idea that you
call speaking in tongues. But in this
way it transcends the learned memory of
the physical being and connects into all
they have ever been or can be in that
way. So when you're talking memory now
memory all memory is now memory though. So do
all memory is now memory though. So do
you have to be in a deep trance to
channel that way or not not?
Well, not really. Although you can be in
that state and be
active, it is the same state so to
speak, but you can learn to adapt it so
that you are functional so to speak in
your terms while you are in that state.
in that I was just looking when you were
talking about that if a person even
stayed totally conscious if they were
being completely in the moment and
weren't thinking about anything that
they would have access to it the being
would be able to use the body you would
not be in any way
in that way yes and also it is the
opportunity to recognize that it does
not need to concern a so-called other
consciousness but that your own can
function in that way as well. We used an
analogy recently in your terms of time
with another individuality that if they
were in a given moment though they had
not been before willing to completely be
the idea of a musician say play the
piano as you call it. They would in that
moment, whether they had lessons or not,
by truly completely being a pianist,
know everything a pianist needs to know
and would play the piano in that moment,
whether it is in their memory or not.
[Music] uh you does the term manasha uh mean
uh you does the term manasha uh mean
anything to you or could
you have you any me
the vibration does not translate what
does it mean to you by definition I
don't know I'm asking this for someone
and we could not uh be here tonight who
seem to have they shared with you any of
their interpretation?
It seems to have something to do with
her highest self. She thinks all right.
Suggest for now that she simply act upon
that idea and see where it takes her.
Understand any arrangements, any
agreements whether with the idea of your
higher self or so-called other
consciousness will always take you where
you need to go. Once again, if you are
willing to act on whatever you have of
the information in the moment, you do
not need to have the specifics laid out
as a blueprint to be able to travel that
path. You will see it as you go.
The other thing I'm going to ask one
moment.
We can suggest this idea that the
terminology at least to our
perception which has as much meaning as
you care to give
it. Manasha can be viewed
as either child of life or child of
life. Either way. Oh, that's
interesting. This person is a very
loving kind of person who
I personally see on that level. All
right. Then in that way you may reflect
that idea too. Great.
The other thing uh
is of late not of late for for quite a
while now I've been doing a lot of
meditation. All right. And having a good
time and extremely good. Oh, thank you.
Uh it's
been interesting in that I have been
able to ascertain information through
meditation that I have not been able to
get any other way. Yes.
And I've reached the point that
um I'm not doing it as much. And one of
the things that I want to know is there
a danger or is there such a thing as
meditating too much in your estimation
to a point of nothing happening about in
a sense that can occur. Yes. Simply
recognize that the
opportunity is that you can recognize
that as you act you are meditating at
the same time. Right. Well, that aspect
of meditation I understand even though I
don't do that type of meditation as much as
do that type of meditation as much as
the quiet sitting I
um and I have the strong desire and
belief that this is taking me somewhere
because when I do ask uh just like about
five minutes before I asked the question
um I you are seeing synchronicity. Okay.
Because this sound okay you picking up.
Okay. Because it's been very
interesting. I mean it's like I'll
meditate one day and within a few within
48 hours you will get a reinforcement of
the idea you have been considering.
Okay. Like the dolphin. Yes. Okay. You
are allowing synchronicity to function
in your life to become the ecstatic
explosion of coincidence so that you can
recognize that your life as an action is
also a meditation. Okay. I want to at
some point teach this on a level that
not well I want to share this. All
right. You are doing so right now very
beautifully. Okay.
Um well I guess I don't need to say
anything. Oh thank you very much.
Well taught.
Thank you. Thank you. Yes. Michelle. Can
you tell me anything about uh the
whereabouts of um a large amethyst
crystal that I I brought with me last
week and will it uh materialize again?
I do not know.
Why do you feel you need it? I don't
need it. All right. Well, I don't need
it. Um I was um it was in my caretaking uh
Um I was um it was in my caretaking uh
for a friend and
I would like to return it to her when
she returns home.
Our perception is that there is a high
degree of probability that you will.
Where did it go?
That does not show up. What shows up in
our perception is simply the mechanics
of the interaction that there is a
process that she is creating herself to
go through that can result in the
so-called finding of the crystal and
then the returning at exactly at the
precise time or just slightly before or
just slightly after
depending upon what she wants to see
reflected to herself from the friend. [Music] [Music]
Examine the
idea of caretaking in that way and
responsibility not for something but to
everyone. All right. What is the difference
All right. What is the difference
between those two or being responsible
for someone else in a sense is
attempting to live their lives for them.
Being responsible to them is being
completely the person you know yourself
to be so that you are an accurate
reflection of who you chose to be to
them so that they can see in you the
reflection that is the service that they
can then choose for themselves if they
desire to. Thank you. Thank you. One
moment. I I just wanted to uh when you
were speaking to I believe someone in
the back room a few minutes ago about
becoming the idea
of the concert pianist does and
without that information in their memory
bay they are able to function in this
such all ideas come complete as an idea
with all the ingredients necessary for
the support of that idea in
existence if you are willing to
completely know immerse yourself in the
trust of actually being that idea the
universe will support you by funneling
to you all the information that goes
into defining what it is to be that idea
so that you can continue to be that
idea. So can you take on somebody's name
a famous pianist if you take it upon you
then you would become that person in a
sense yes but it will be your version of
that idea. It is not so much that you
will be
them but you will be exhibiting the same
ability they were able to tap into as
well in that sense. That that's why
that's why name of of why men are so uh
have so much
energy sense. Yes, you are perceiving
that it is a vibrational equation an
identification which if you make
yourself one too can exist on the same
level and exhibit the same traits. Very
good in a sense. But it is not so much that
in a sense. But it is not so much that
you have to rely on them as a symbol in
that way, but that you can recognize
that you also contain the same energy
that you are a master as well.
Thank you. So by I'm a a singer, so I'd
like to um utilize that for myself. Then
all it takes
is complete and total trust of what you
just said. I am a singer. Oh,
otherwise if you feel you have to work
at it, you don't believe you are a
singer. Oh, thank you. Thank you.
Oh, thank you. Thank you.
Dude, thank you. You said something
earlier uh about the founding fathers
had and touched on something I was
curious about for quite a while now.
When you reincarnate
before you decide to come back, do you
have a choice as to how much of your
consciousness, how much of your
beingness, how much of you bring with
you? You can make certain adjustments
and shifts in that way. Yes. So that
parts of you can in a sense be siphoned
off for other reasons in that way and
other parts added to form a new
identity. And in a sense that is what
happens otherwise you would not be a new
identity. Okay. But could you say this time I'm
Okay. But could you say this time I'm
going to reincarnate and I'll have all
the wisdom that I've had in this life
and that life and that life and I will
be all of myself. I mean you you always
say that now understand that technically
speaking if you choose to incarnate you
are by definition choosing a certain
form of limitation. You can be all that
you need to be as that definition of
that limitation.
You will not be all of yourself because
all of yourself is more than just the
physical reality. Right? I understand
that. Um but you determine the general
definition of what you will function as
well a little bit. Uh it sort of touches
also on an idea that Seth had one in one
of his books. He said that uh part of
him was in a dog. Part of his
consciousness was in a dog in a sense.
And so I was thinking well can I have my
consciousness part of it is in this and
part of it is Oh you do already. Yeah.
Animal consciousness to use your example
is an extension of your own
consciousness. Mhm. And so you can say
you are also part of you in a dog, in a
cat, in whatever. Can you explain that
further? Simply that you understand in
this way that as the creator
consciousness that you are other
consciousness that in your terms
surrounds you that does not analyze
itself that cannot forget who and what
it is are simply extensions of your
creatorhood consciousness to act as
guides and reflections to always give
you an immediate obvious physical tap
into your own natural godhood. They are
extensions of your consciousness. Not
that they do not know themselves as
their own consciousness, but when they
see themselves as an individual, they
see themselves not only as the idea of
an individual, but they see the idea of
being an individual as being connected
to everything else they interact with.
That is what defines them to themselves
as an individual consciousness. They
recognize they are extensions of all the
consciousness of your creator.
In the same way that you might
say to use an
analogy, you are a
bubble. You decide to create a physical
reality. So you snip off little small
bubbles of yourself and surround
yourself with all these projections that
are extensions of your own consciousness
but function as if they are separate to
reflect to you certain aspects that were
contained in the entire bubble to begin
with. Yes.
Yes.
Does that clarify the idea to some
extent for you? Yes.
For example, could you I mean, could I
decide well I'm going to have a life as
uh somebody who doesn't think very much
and yes, you know, so I'm not going to
put too much of my consciousness in
there because all it needs is to react
physically. All of the same degree of consciousness
All of the same degree of consciousness
will be there. But you will simply
pattern the physiological consciousness
to create the situation in that way that
the circumstances of your physical life
will go into giving you the belief
structure that will allow you to
function that way. You follow me? I
think so. Yeah. I want you to surprise
how long it takes to integrate concepts
into only because you are in a reality
that does not know you are connected to
them to begin with. Okay. Thank you
guys. I recently had an experience that
was new for me. All right.
Uh a few nights ago I was practicing
some calligraphy to try to get my hand
back and uh back from where?
before the uh characters are smooth and
and uh beautiful, right?
And I started uh after practicing for a
while, I started writing in symbols and
characters that I didn't I had never
seen before. And after a while, it was
about I guess eight different languages
or characters of languages that I had
never seen. the emotional language that
many of you are learning to speak.
Later, few days
later, I was uh I started seeing a
symbol uh in my mind and I saw it all
day long. And then that evening, I
decided I was going
to draw it out. Nice. When I drew the
symbol out, it came to me that it was
the symbol for a particular planet,
right? That wanted an alphabet created.
All right. And in this alphabet, they
wanted all the characters in the
alphabet had to contain this one
particular symbol. Oh, okay. And it was
to be a national alphabet. They had
other alphabets, but this was one that
they wanted
created as a like a planetwide alphabet.
So, I created it for them. How exciting.
And they were very pleased. There have
been other people tried to create it but
had not succeeded to their
satisfaction. Since that time I've
created about eight or nine other
alphabets for other planets. What was
interesting was that this first one
uh they said that I had won a prize.
First time out. Congratulations.
And uh what I was wondering is uh
is there such a thing as a universal
banking system?
There can be in a sense although again
on our planet we do not use the idea of
money at all.
Our banking system is in each other.
Well, this was very very enjoyable and I
would I would do it for nothing anyway.
However, they wanted to give me
something at that particular time. They
are 40 million light years from from
here. The communication link is
instantaneous. But what happens on the physical uh how
But what happens on the physical uh how
does the physical
part transmitted?
What do you think they want when he
checks in the mail?
Do you know? Yes. What? Gold. Gold.
Gold. Why? I don't know. It's what they
wanted. I see. Do you not have gold upon
your planet? Yeah. Then allow me to
suggest that if you acquire a bit of it,
you will make the identification by
allowing them in a sense and yourself to
cocreate the bit you have to be the bit
they need to give you so that it becomes
imbued with the co-created energy that
they can transmit.
And then you can explore the energy that
exists within that element that your
civilization has not yet discovered.
What's that? And this particular
incident, it was like I was the source
being channeled through another person.
Is this happening?
Yes. What's happening now? Yes. You do
form connections particularly in your
dream reality where you do function in
much the same way as I am functioning
through this physical channel on other
planets. I was totally conscious.
Thank you. Thank you very much. One moment
moment
gold has within
it a type
of one moment.
All right. After your break. Okay.
Yes. I have had a sort of a physical
I have had a sort of a physical
disability of a bad lower back and neck
and I wonder what lesson this is for how
long? Well, the back for 20 years off
and on every 5 years the neck for a
couple years. All right. But it's been
persisting for the last couple months
which has been giving me a lot of
discomfort. Yeah. Because things are
accelerating in that way. First and
foremost understand that what you call
the base of the neck between the
shoulder blade in that way will be the
channeling chakra. The opening up of
yourself to your higher self and the
energy coming through if there is the
idea of a so-called blockage can create
what you call physical pain in that area
to increase.
Now, are you exploring the
idea of being supported?
of being supported?
In what way?
In what you want to do?
Yes. Could be abundance.
Definitely. All right. What have you
recognized about this idea of support?
turn the running or the control of my
life over to my higher self.
Where does that leave you here?
It leaves me here because of my higher
self or my choice of being here. But in
what state does it leave you to
completely and utterly hand over control
to your higher self rather than allowing
the higher self to function as the
higher self and allowing your
physiological consciousness to function
in control of its own free will and then
simply synchronize and harmonize the two
vibrations rather than completely giving
over your ability to also choose. what
you are willing to experience in your
physical life. Well, I feel that I am my
higher self. So therefore, all right,
then you know you are in control here as
well. Right. All right.
Now the
idea of
support have you explored to this point
about that idea?
basically just letting things happen
that are supposed to happen. And what
had happened? I didn't support. All
right. Now, How you felt a
connection to the
idea of electricity in any way?
slightly, but maybe a sense of twitches. Yeah.
Yeah.
How does that feel?
Stimulating. All right. There There
are
individuals upon your planet who are
exploring the idea of the application of
electric current to the physical body in
certain areas to stimulate the idea of
areas to stimulate the idea of
regeneration in those areas.
Now in your terms it is a young
science. They may or may
not find an application in your
particular situation. Though we do
perceive that some offshoot of their
particular endeavors could be of
assistance to you in that way.
There are devices that they have created
that you might avail yourself of in that
sense and see if they do make a
difference in balancing the
electromagnetic field around and about
you and within your body in that
particular area of your nervous system,
your spinal
system also. Has there
been has there been
any work
done by yourself or and by others with
you on your brain?
Not on my brain. No,
only on your back.
Yes.
Why my such a network? [Music] Do you
Do you
know what in your language the word
simolacum means? No. A
model, a representation.
Okay, you follow me? Yes.
Can you create in your
imagination a
representation of a body that can be
yours that does not
feel this pain? Yes.
What does it look like in terms of its
visual appearance energy wise,
lightwise? Descriptively, surface
wise clear. Good. Translucent. Good.
Now, can you for a moment, knowing that
you will not alter the pristine
condition of that imaginary body, but
can you for a moment look at the body
and imagine that that body in its state
of transparency does have the pain that
you have? How does it show up in that
body? glowing red areas. All right.
Can you hold this image in your
imagination? Yes. Take a deep breath and let it out
Yes. Take a deep breath and let it out
while you are holding this
image. One more
breath. And one more.
Are they changing color yet at all? The
blue. All
right. Now, how does that feel if you
were to apply that idea to your body?
Soothing. All
right. Can you now
allow that blue area to become just as
transparent as the rest of the body?
Yes. Can you allow yourself to become that
Can you allow yourself to become that
body? Yes. How does it feel? Great.
Now allow your imagination to alter it
in whatever way, shape, and form it so
desire. Our suggestion to
you would
be to do this
visualization three times a day.
three times a
day for at
least three
days. Then take stock of the
image and see if it is in your terms
more difficult to
imagine those areas existing. If you
still perceive them, do it again for
three more days. And before each time
you do it, inhale and exhale deeply
three times. And as you conclude the
exercise, inhale and exhale deeply three
times. All right. Okay. That will be our
suggestion for now. There are many many
many activities taking place upon the
network you are creating yourself to be.
You are in initiating this process. It
is our perception. You will initiate
others. You will
unlock other processes that will begin
to filter into your life. Some within
you as realization and some as you call
it externally as manifestations of
interaction that will reflect the
process you are doing with regard to
assimilating this
pain. All right. All right. Do that for
now with no particular expectation other
than the understanding that you can
transform the purpose or the pain in
another way.
that you can still serve the purpose
that the pain is there for without the
pain without that particular tool
because you are now willing to all
right. Yes. And let it into your life
along all the pathways of the network
you have created yourself to
become the hub of the web.
All right. All right.
[Music] [Laughter]
[Laughter]
I have one other question. All right.
What part does destiny play in
Thank you. Well, let me just All right.
in having free choice or freedom of
choice. Thank you.
Understand in this way there are two
types of free will. The free will of the
higher consciousness and the free will
of the physiological consciousness. The
free will of the higher consciousness is
what the physiological consciousness
experiences as destiny or
predestination. But the free will of the
higher consciousness is only expressed
in the most general of terms. It is up
to the free will of the physiological
consciousness how to experience the
specifics of the free will of the higher
consciousness. For example, as we have
said, let us say in general, the higher
consciousness says in life you will walk
down this hall. Let us say you will
explore the idea of
connections. You will explore it. That
is your destiny because it is the free
will of the higher consciousness.
How you explore it positively,
negatively, slowly,
quickly, with joy, with pain is up to
the physical consciousness here because
to the higher consciousness it does not
matter what you choose because to the
higher consciousness everything is
learning everything. So understand it is up to
everything. So understand it is up to
you how to experience that idea based
upon what you choose to believe about
your reality.
Yes. Does that answer your question?
Yes.
So the higher I mean the the highest
self and that's
true. The lower self doesn't have a
choice then. Yes. How to experience the
choice made by the higher self. But the
choice made by the higher self is only
in the most general of terms. In other
words, the idea of exploring connection,
the idea of exploring abundance, the
idea of exploring relationship in that
way. How you choose to do it with whom
and in what way is up to the free will
of the physiological consciousness.
What makes the what determines the
choice of the physiological
consciousness? what you choose to
believe,
how you allow yourself to what degree of
synchronous harmony with your higher
self. Because to the higher self, it
does not care how you choose to
experience that.
Well, the higher self makes the
decision, not how to. No, no, no, no.
I'm not talking about the how. I mean
the ultimate decision the higher self is
making as to the general theme. Yes.
Okay. So, we well I guess I can say I
don't want to say
we have to still abide by the rules of
the higher self. Uh I guess what I'm
saying is that we still don't
have the higher self makes the choice
and when that choice is made even if
it's made generally then to the physical
self that is destiny.
Okay. You follow me? So being here on
your planet and dealing with the
integration of all of the separation you
have created in previous lives is the
choice of the higher
selves. Going through this
transformation in whatever way you here
decide to go through it. The higher self
doesn't care. Why does why does nobody
go I mean why do people go through it
painfully then if the conscious self has
a choice why isn't it all because they
do not believe that they can go through
it joyfully all we have to do is change
our belief yes and that changes the
experience of your reality. It is an
opportunity for you to recognize that
now you are choosing the idea of
conscious integration rather than
unconscious limitation.
the same with people. We create people
in our our life. Yes. You attract what
vibration you are. Well, as far as his
destiny goes with the people that are to
some degree. Yes. Although that also is
a wide range of ideas.
It can be that many people can fulfill
the same destiny in certain cases.
Sometimes it will be a specific one.
But in the case where your lower self,
if I say I've turned the running of my
life over to God, let's say, or the
universe, and that whatever I do is there's no
and that whatever I do is there's no
rightness, there's no wrongness. It's
okay. Yes. And I just do what I do in
integrity. Right. Yes. With with
integrity and
self-empowerment. What do you mean
self-empowerment? The ability to recognize that you are
The ability to recognize that you are
powerful enough to create anything you
desire without having to hurt anyone to
get it. Right. Okay. So therefore, if
I'm walking down the street, I mean,
it's sort of like what I mean, as far as
I feel now, where I go, what I do, what
I eat, when I go to sleep, what I choose
to read is
all sort of predestined. It's sort of
like it just is going to happen. No, no,
no. No, no.
Understand in this way when you let us
say to use your example read something
you can recognize that it may represent
a
harmonious playing out of the higher
self's choice and then go with that flow
or you can fight
it. It is up to you.
You can explore the idea of not being in
synchronous harmony with your higher
self and give yourself the experience of
limitation, separation, and pain by
saying, "Well, I recognize that this
sets up a vibration within me, but I
choose to ignore what I know to be true
for me, and I will do the
opposite." You can explore it that way,
too. Both ways are still fulfilling the
destiny of the higher self because the
higher self is still learning about that
particular general
idea either from your positive or your
negative choice. But if there's no
rightness and wrongness, then either way
would be correct. Oh yes, in that sense.
Yes. To the higher self, it does not
care which way you go in that sense. But
is in one choice is that one choice
you're saying might be an easier way.
Yes. And the other way. Well, how does
one then determine which is the easier
way or not? You can feel it. Okay. Can
you specifically say what the highest
self is, please?
If if if you could give a definition.
Well, in a sense, it can be referred to
as what has been termed the oversoul. If
you are willing to look at it that way.
Okay. Well, what's the other stuff? It
is your collective consciousness of all
that you
are as a collection of personalities
past, present and future.
Let us say it is the knowledge
bank of all that you have experienced in
all your
lives. You can look at it that way if
you wish. But if the oversoul is the all
the ultimate or the you know the head
guru you know um and he he then he or
she then knows
he gets then knows the easiest path. Why
can I not? Can I see I can say I'm
turning the running of my life over to
you? Because the idea is that the
running of your life is up to you. And
when you choose to run it consciously,
that is the easiest
path easy for your physiological self,
not your higher self. Right? In this
way, it is both.
Understand the idea is that when you are
being true to yourself as the
personality you recognize yourself to be
and are being of service to others by
being yourself by acting true to who you
know you are. Then recognize that by
your own definition being yourself
should be the easiest thing in the
world. You sure one moment? Okay. You
You sure one moment? Okay. You
understand? Yeah. Does that make some
sense? Yeah. So you Yeah. Okay. Along
the same line, if you were to say this
in terms of non seeparation, which is
without separating the what we call the
lower self with the higher self, then
what would your definition be of who we
are without the separation? For instance, For instance,
um
uh you know the labeling of the lower
self and the higher self and and the
lower self does this and the higher self
has the broader view and the lower self
has the choices. Um you
are the
self experiencing itself in a particular
mode. Okay. And that's the reason for
talking to them in regards.
Yes, you are the self
experiencing the self through a
particular perspective of the
self. But to be able to do that does
imply some sort of separation. Okay. On
your planet, how do you view it? I mean,
do you view it as a separation? We can
recognize that there is still obviously
needs to be some degree of
differentiation otherwise we could not
consider ourselves to be personalities
talking with
you and at the same time we
emotionally recognize that we are
creating that
idea. So it is not that we choose to
forget that we are doing that. Oh I see.
Okay. So yeah, when you think of like as
an oversoul of all our personalities in
order to focus onto one life within the
oversoul then we need to make the the
separation. Okay. But you can make the
separation consciously. Yeah. If you
know that the experience serves the
oversoul in that way and you will not
feel like a victim. Right? You may all
take a short break. Thank you.
All right, allow me to say gold.
The idea of that
element. It is again no accidental
coincidence that your basic
root word is orable in that way.
word is orable in that way.
aura. The
idea being that
go is in a sense channel funnel
transformer for the electromagnetic
energy of your world in that way in a
specific way. Much as the same idea of
crystals channeling energy in their own
specific way, many elements will channel
energy in their own specific way. The
way of
gold will be to
create the idea
of an
immediacy, a
nowness, the idea
of
stability, the maintenance of a
particular level of
energy, the infusion
infusion of the electromagnetic field of
your planet within an
equilibrium that can
be transferred to your bodily oric field
to maintain the type of
equilibrium that can allow you to
experience the idea of what you call
physiological longevity.
In this way recognize that it is
symbolically perceived this energy in the idea of
perceived this energy in the idea of
gold because the element in and of
itself does not change, does not
tarnish, does not decay. The gold that
exists upon your planet now is the same
gold that has existed for hundreds of
thousands, millions of years. Exactly
the same
goes. Recognize that it can be utilized to
Recognize that it can be utilized to
create an
exopplasmic projection of that energy. It is like
projection of that energy. It is like
taking the rarified vibration, the
fundamental vibration of the
electromagnetic field of your planet and
giving it a little bit of
thickening, a little bit of
substance and it can leak into your oric
field in that
way and allow there to be the
equilibrium and the
balancing to act as a balancer between
your oric field and the electromagnetic
vibration of your outer world so to
speak forming the type of identification
that can form a connection a flow so
that you can act as a flow within the
field. In that way you are flowing with
the electromagnetic field equal balanced
sustained supported and in that way you can be
supported and in that way you can be
maintained in that now
moment. Part of what you call the idea
in our spacecraft of what we have
referred to as the flash
matrix contains gold. It is transforming
light into another type of energy. One
that carries with it the type of
equilibrium that allows the
spacecraft to, let us say, color the
energy it uses to be able in that sense
to form balanced identifications with
different vibrational
frequencies. That vibration is inherent
in the amplified energy. So that the
ability to form a connection and an
identification with any particular
universe is inherent within the energy
that is being amplified by simply
allowing us to pass through the goal in
the flash matrix.
Are you following this? Yes. Innocent.
No, in this way as you can recognize
that so many of you are fond of the
metal. It can be represented in that way
because of your unconscious knowingness.
Not so much physiologically although you
have made it so but the idea of energy
wealth in that sense the longevity the
goldenness that it represents to you in
that way that is why you have made that
association to that particular metal in
that sense also you can recognize that as you
sense also you can recognize that as you
have already discovered some of you in
conjunction with certain crystallin
forms terms. You can direct specific
forms of the application of
that skip translation
amplification of that energy. In that
way, you can allow yourselves the
opportunity to experiment in combination
of crystallin form and gold to see what
effect you can feel within your oric
field and then can utilize that as
symbols to represent the different
portions of yourself that it may allow
you to discover upon reflection.
All right. All right. Thank you.
you first. Okay. Um when you the
slight ticking
uh to manifest that what what would you
uh communicate
telepathically with element?
Okay. Share it or feel with yours. Okay. Okay.
Share it or feel with yours. Okay. Okay.
Now, you don't have to have it right in
front of you to do that, right? No, you
do not.
Sure. One moment. The idea of silver is
more closely connected to the
energy that you would translate as your
unconsciousness. And that is why it was
used in the idea of the
oult. Follow me. That which was hidden
is what your term oult means. hidden.
And in that way, it was as a magnet, a
focuser, allowing you to represent
yourself a symbol of allowing that
hidden knowledge of yourself to be
channeled outward. All right.
outward. All right.
Yes. Yes.
Uh I would like for you to tell me what
hyperventilation does to the body and to
the
consciousness. In this way, you can find
there are certain balances of that idea
that can be in a sense beneficial for
allowing you to unlock from one
particular reality and refocus through
the disorientation that it may cause
into another. But in this way, you will
always also understand that your body
will regulate itself to a certain point.
If you go beyond that point, you will
simply pass out until you reregulate
yourself. It is the oxygenation of your
system. Hyper oxygenation in that way
that will reach a point of
saturation beyond which you would not be
able to translate the experience in
physical terms and so it shuts itself
down so that you can maintain your focus
in physical reality. You could in a
sense you could literally hyperventilate
yourself out of your body.
So does this help in releasing police?
It can. Yes. Okay. It is a
disorientation and unlocking. Okay. Can
pure oxygen be used instead of just
breathing?
Can be. But in this way it is also a
tool. You can simply recognize that if
you experiment with the idea of the
patterns of your breathing, you can
maintain the equilibrium that will allow
you to function fully oxygenated as you
need to be in full balance with that
system. Easy breathing rather than the
idea of fuller breathing in that
way can
become congruent and you can find
yourself perhaps breathing deeply but
less often
fully. Yes. Well, that answers your
question. Yes. I have one more. All
right. Let's say that we have a condition in
Let's say that we have a condition in
our life that we don't necessarily it's
not necessarily appealing to us. All
right. How do we know whether this is
the result of a belief system or
destiny? Understand it is always the result of a
Understand it is always the result of a
belief system to experience any neutral
situation positively or
negatively. If you find it
unappealing, that is your first clue
that you are experiencing the idea
negatively and that it is a product of
your belief system which you can change.
So if you're going along in your poor
church mouse and you find this
unappealing, right?
Then ask yourself first of all since you
know it is not an interruption in your
life but a part of the path you chose to
be in general. How does this serve me to
have this experience? So it is destiny
in an overall sense to have the general
experience. Yes experience is is
destiny. The way you view it is your
belief system.
What you learn from it is destiny and
the experience is your belief system.
Yes. And the idea of the general
situation is also destiny in that way.
Understand to explore the idea as you
have said of your own self abundance
means you can explore it physically rich
or physically poor. It is the same
general theme. You are exploring the
idea of abundance. You can have an
abundance of materiality or an abundance
of poverty. Evolve
me in that way. The first step if you
wish to make a step out of it is to
allow yourself to simply ask how does it
serve me? It can even be because you are
now considering it. It can even be as
simple as it serves me by letting me
know I don't prefer to live this way.
Therefore, I will understand that I do
not need to judge the fact that I have
chosen to live this way because it has
brought me to this understanding.
Therefore, it has served me equally to
any other way I could choose. And now
that I know every choice is equal to any
other choice, I can now choose to
experience the exploration of this idea
in a more positive way.
That's all you have to do to change it.
Trust that.
Thank you.
One moment. One moment. One moment.
Does this clarify the idea for me?
Yes. Thank you.
call you you then you
uh I want to ask about my roommate who
has a cyst uh that uh she went to have
x-rayed and talked to the doctor about
and they wanted to cut and she refused
to All right. And um she's here
presently. All right. And um I'm sort of
I'm concerned about it. Oh, concerned?
Yes. Why are you reinforcing a probable
negative outcome? Okay, thank you for
telling me that. All right. Okay. Uh,
you can have compassion for the strength
she may have chosen to exhibit this idea
within herself. Hey, listen. I'm
cheering for her making that decision.
Uh, now what I'd really like to know is
if you
could perhaps relate something that she could
perhaps relate something that she could
do to help and well, how does she feel
about the idea?
I guess she'd have to tell you. Yes. Well,
I don't think she wants to.
All right. Why not?
Can you find out?
Um, yeah. I guess it's hurtful choice.
So, of course. Yeah. Now understand
first and
foremost one of the
ideas can be that a willingness to share
the creations that you do create in your
life will then create the opportunity to
be able to avail yourself of other
methodologies that your civilization can
share with you about how to transform
any particular experience. Keeping it
all bottled up
inside is a good reflection of what is
going on if you are going to be insistent.
on if you are going to be insistent.
Excellent. I'm glad you said that
because she has been an awful good
inspiration and teacher as well as
student. All right.
All right.
The idea of
encapsulization of something you
consider to be negative is simply not
sharing a portion of yourself that you
are judging unworthy of sharing. So you
wall it off, seal it up and allow it to
become malignant. In this way, it is as we are
malignant. In this way, it is as we are
saying and again not necessarily is it
an accidental coincidence in what you
turn to be the speech pattern. It
is being
insistent in a negative
way. You would call it stubborns.
Now you have the power to
share. Listen to this idea if you wish.
One of the greatest gifts you can give
is the gift of allowing others to give
to
you. Therefore, share and expand. Do not wall
Therefore, share and expand. Do not wall
off portions of yourself you may think
are not worthy of sharing that you are
ashamed of. For by sharing all portions
of yourself, do you allow other
individuals to understand yet one more
way that all that it has of expressing
itself so that they may
learn, share, open
up, and you will not have to be forced
open.
Well, I thought with you what you shared
about Spiderman back there.
I wanted to ask if she perhaps could
apply the same. Of course, if that feels
good to
her, her imagination will always
construct the perfect scenario. If she
trusts it and acts upon it, then she
will have the result of that trust and
action automatically.
Thank you. Okay. The other thing that I
needed to to ask wanted to that I want
to ask
is in my meditation I have gotten to a
point that very much like what Daryl is
going through when he's leaving and
you're coming in there's a centering
that's taking place. Yes. And the first
time I did it, it the closest thing I
could describe to it was an orgasm. All
right. And I have been very reluctant
about telling you about this. Uh well,
you just did. Yes. But so I thought it
kind of necessary for me to do it now
because I
feel a burning desire to do it often.
All right.
understand you are simply in touch with
your own ecstasy. Okay. Well, it
has it's I'm sort of in transition to go
beyond that at this point. You mean to
use it? Okay.
Okay. Somehow I perceive if I go any
further I'm going to pass out. You
might. It'll be
fun, but you might not. Trust that you
never give yourself more than you can
handle. Otherwise, what would be the
point? Life is not illogical in that way.
Life is not illogical in that way.
You follow me? Yes. Have you when when I
keep think something's going to happen.
It's like a person is going to show up
or something. Could be. Let me know,
won't you?
Okay, I'll thank you. Allow yourself to
continue to experience your own ecstasy
and see what manifests or womans. [Music]
One moment. One moment. Yes, please.
Okay.
Yes, that's my name and that's what I
wanted to share about is my name. I've
um discovered a strength and
ascendedness in um in meditation and
also now I'm just using it whenever you
know in my daily action is my full name
Pamela Newre and
um I found last few days when in
meditation I found when I breathed in my
last name seems to work out that way
breathe in my last name and breathed out
my first name I felt uh I don't even
know how to describe what it felt
But a connection with everything I was I
am all that to the fullness of your
vibration. Dang. Yes. And uh I loved it. I just
Dang. Yes. And uh I loved it. I just
wanted to go out there and shake
everyone's hand and introduce myself.
But I was already doing that. It was
like it wasn't I knew it wasn't
necessary. It was just something that in
fact I did do. I sent out a portion of
myself. It's all right. It'll take
forever. Yeah. It'll be fine. You know,
forever. But it's already done, right?
you know, but it was just it was a fun
idea. It was a feeling of love and of
sharing um that I just I just wanted to shake
um that I just I just wanted to shake
everyone's hand. What did you
Yes. [Music] [Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] One moment. Yeah.
Yeah.
Thank you. What next?
For sure. Um, I have always had a very
unusual relationship with animals in
this life. Unusual. Unusual. Well, other
people say that it's unusual. Oh, all
right. The forms they come to me in are
unusual varieties. And five years ago, I
was well, I through a series of
incidents, I raised was given a great
horned owl baby, which I raised for five
years. His name was Sydney. All right.
And now he's free in Always has been.
Yes. But in the canyon areas. All right.
He was injured in one town permanently.
Okay. And what I was curious to know is
is he still alive?
Time frame of release. Time frame of
release was last August. No, a year ago
last year and a half.
Yes. Our perception is that there is
still life in that vibration.
So he's been able to measure. Oh dear.
Okay. And there's one other question I
have. Uh actually it's not a question.
What I wanted to do was tell you that
last week you spoke about anger. Good.
And what you gave us an information has
profoundly affected my universe. Well,
thank you for creating it to do so. You
have profoundly affected your universe.
Well, I thank you for your your
reflection. I'm very grateful.
You wise old owl. [Music] [Music]
[Laughter]
Yes.
You have a question? No.
Oh, one moment.
You remember? No, I don't. All right.
Must be a new you.
I've been having that a lot lately. Oh,
thank you, guys. You okay? Um, what did
you just said before about opening up to
me? Guys, that's just reaching me cuz I
have this thing about
um this thing. Yeah.
French Canadian. Thank you. Um
[Music] uh sometimes I like I feel open and I
uh sometimes I like I feel open and I
talk about everything I feel and then
sometimes I don't because I feel if I
talk about it it won't happen. Mhm. It's
like sometime I have a cold, you know,
and I say, "Well, I'm going to tell
everybody I have a cold and it'll go
away." Oh, right. That's the way I feel.
But if I don't talk about it, then I I
feel it's going to sick or something.
Understand any given
moment can bring with it a different way
of relating the
idea. You can create the idea of a cold
one time and feel that the thing for you
to do would be to talk about it and the
next time not to. Do not judge that you
are changing with respect to how you relate
changing with respect to how you relate
that idea. Right.
Yeah, that's great. I just want
to share that um what you just said
before really hit me was Did it hurt?
No. Not very good. Oh, thank you. Because
Not very good. Oh, thank you. Because
it's um it's something I always think
like you know this little chatter inside
that says what? Yeah, chatter.
I says well I want to talk about it but
I said no I don't want to talk about it.
Yeah I was I went no I don't want to
talk about it. Nah. Oh de I should have
talked about it here. Sounds like you
are having a very enjoyable tennis man.
Right. So I just decided to talk about
it right now. Well thank you very much
for being willing to share in the manner
you have been willing to share with him.
Okay. Also,
Also,
um I was going to say, well, see mommy's
talk about him. I don't want to talk
about it. Talk about it's just that I hit
it. Talk about it's just that I hit
myself on the wall. I cracked my skull.
And I I think it's just one of the idea
what you said just before like you're
forced open or something like that.
Otherwise, and also I feel that I went
through death regarding that thing
because it really hurt me and it was
like for about 2 or 3 hours I couldn't I
was really in pain. All right. It still
hurts a little but it's going away. All
right. So I think it goes in that uh I'm
rewinding the whole thing.
Thank you very
much for your self-realizations. Yeah.
Yeah.
One moment. Yes. Yeah. Hi. Um, hi.
I'm going to put up a a quandry about
wondering where's that
about
a
situation which I seem to keep creating
over and over. Nice.
Um uh
uh well you know like in my
pray of
uh you know that I have a 24-hour
poly and I have an agreement like which
I have my clients sign and agree to that
that it that you know like when they
can't insult any law says unless 24
hours before that time they agree to pay
for that session. All right. Well, well
know like one thing that has happened
over and over again and I'm right in the
midst of the same thing now. There's a
man who called me, you know, like seven
to 15 hours before the
session and, you know, and cancelled the
session and it was mildly
inconvenient for him like to be there,
right? And uh and like what I seem to
create is like uh you know like is to
let them um you know like is to let them
off the hook but then you know like not
you know confront them because I feel
like uh you know like this man uh you
know like I know that if I remind him of
the agreement you know with me that that
that uh he signed like he will get real
uh he signed like he will get real
angry. Why do you think so? Because I
know this man. What does that mean?
Well, it's like I One moment. Okay,
understand. I am not really asking you
to answer me. Okay, listen to the idea.
What does that mean? It is in a sense
what you call a rhetorical question.
Listen to the idea that I should even
ask you that
question and answer it for yourself. I
know this man. But understand anyone in
your reality is who you have created
them to be your version of them in that
way. That is the version of the man you
know. You do not know the whole being
nor what it could change into should you
decide to change as well. Right.
Well, well, you know what? The only
thing is that I can say is that I've
tried it both ways. you know like you
know you know in certain situations I
have either confronted
people with a a
green and and like it seems that I've
set this up so that like you know like
it's a lose-lose because people do not
like to pay for something that they
don't get you know like even if they
have made an agreement that let me ask
you a question. Mhm. Why did you create
that agreement?
Um well because my sessions are an hour
and a half long and like if people you
know cancel out at me you know like
uh you know like on me like right before
I really then you have an hour and a
half to do something else. I know
although the place that I work is you
know it's just the logistics of the
situation. six. Yeah, I I mean the uh
six. Yeah, I I mean the uh
um
I understand you are referring to a
particular framework structure reference
time case point idea but in this way
also recognize it may be your
willingness to explore the idea of
loosening that structure up just a
little bit
and functioning within your integrity.
Yes. but perhaps also functioning within
your integrity in a slightly less
structured manner.
Now, not to say that you need to create
a situation in which you feel you are
being taken advantage of, but you can
create the idea of trusting you and
trusting the idea that you will then
attract clientele that will support you
exactly as you need to be supported and
not feel that you must create a rigid
structure to reinforce what you
obviously doubt will happen on its own.
If you feel you need to enforce the idea
that they will make up for your valuable
time, then you are really in a sense
saying that you don't believe that in of
itself, the being that you are can draw
enough support. You have to take out
insurance. Well, uh well, you know, I do hear that
Well, uh well, you know, I do hear that
and and uh it is a double-edged
opportunity for on one hand, it does
give you the opportunity to explore the
idea of maintaining the integrity that
you do lay down and on the other hand,
it gives you the opportunity to explore
how you have laid down your particular
demand of your integrity.
Uh-huh. Um well, I just let me say that
one more thing. it well like when when
people you know like can't on
short it's then sometimes you know like
I lose that time lose and that money
that I could give to another person that
wants that time but understand if
another person needs to be there they
will be there
automatically understand it can work
that way if one person cancels another
one will automatically come in and Hey,
have you got a cancellation? Why, yes,
what a coincidence. I just happened to
have just gotten the cancellation and my
trust allowed me to know that if I
needed the money, something would come
in. And here you are. Thank you very
much. Life works if you let it.
You follow me? It does happen that way
if you are willing to trust that it can.
Uhhuh. Therefore, you do not have to
make those rigid demands that a specific
individual fill your needs because as
long as you know you are being of
service, you will attract
whoever needs to be there to be of
service to you back.
You are simply making the specific
demand that it be that individual or no
one. So, you are left with time on your
hand. Sure. Well, uh, and and
and you know, in this situation that's
uh that's going down like right now, you
know, like I don't you know, like I
still don't understand how to work deal
with the broken agreement and nothing is
broken. Do not make the demand and
nothing can be
broken. If you trust that someone is
going to cancel because of a change in
their situation and you know that the
agreement is still functioning within
integrity, then whatever needs to occur
will occur in exactly the right amount
of time. You won't have to worry
about. If you don't make a wall, it
can't be broken down.
Uhhuh. allow light to flow through your
office. So like you're saying that I should
So like you're saying that I should
loosen the uh
uh that I should joyfully know like I'll
loosen the structure of that
particular green movement. No, not
should. But if you do and trust it, you
may find that you will flow with enough
clientele to make you very happy. And
when they don't show up, it will occur
at exactly the time you feel like you
need a little vacation.
Okay. Thank you. You very
much find that that man never cancels on
you again. That could be, but I don't
know. You
Yes. Could you tell me the uh month and
day of my birth?
Do you not know it? That is correct. I
have discovered lately that I have not
been looking at a lie and I decided to
find out what it was. Not been what? I
have been living a lie. Living a lie.
Yes. How so? Using someone else's birth
certificate. So So I'd like to know what
day I was born on. Someone help.
Is it circumstance of your physical
situation that you do not know?
In other words, you do not know place of
your birth. I know the place. Where is
the place? Uh, Long Beach, California.
What is your physiological age? [Music]
50. How did you come to choose the other
certificate?
I was abandoned.
All right. and I chose uh to
be adopted. Who chose your name?
My new parents. All right. Did
right. Did
they when they adopted
you never tell you how old you were when
they adopted
you? Could they not tell?
That's correct. They could not tell,
right? Roughly how old were you? A
month. Then you have an approximate
idea. Correct.
What month do you assume?
March.
In your astrological terms, you are
Piscian. So it is close enough. Our
enough. Our
perception is of a 22nd
day. Now whether in your terms that is
your month of February or
March is not clear.
The aspect of your
personality carries with it the idea of
high psychic manifestation that you
associate with python
quality. You follow me? Yes.
In this way, because of what you have
created yourself to
be, I will find that perhaps in your
terms I cannot
be
accurate. But for my
perception, what you call February 22nd
would be valid.
That is the form of the assistance I can
offer you.
Thank you. Two two. Two two.
[Music] We will
We will
assume that because this is the manner
in which the interaction has taken
place, it will serve you as it needs to
should there be any additional
information from another source or
not. Correct. Thank
you for allowing us to serve you in that
way and for sharing
and we know what you mean but it has not
been a lie.
For again even that particular aspect of
your life has made you what you are. So
it is something that you decided in a
sense to
include to take yourself to where you
now find yourself.
All right. Correct. Thank you for
Yes. Um on the question of anger that we were
Um on the question of anger that we were
discussing last week, I realized one of
the things I would like to explore and
that is the idea of being invited and
therefore being of service to someone
who invites from you not from you but
the gener the generic us um a sharp
response sharp verbal response shout.
Yes. Would you comment on that? Well,
simply you do not have to accept the
invitation. True. However, when on those occasions
True. However, when on those occasions
when I do respond that way, I do feel
the idea of being of service to that
individual. Well, all right. Of course,
you can look at it that way. And then
all you are simply doing is not judging
yourself for having responded, right, in
a way that perhaps you do not
necessarily prefer, right? Are you No
more to say about that than that? Not
really. Okay, good. Thank you. I have
one more question.
What is the difference in effect between
using shortened forms of our names,
nicknames, versus using the full long
form of our names? Familiarity?
Well, that's obvious, but in terms of
the vibrational effects,
well, I am not being physicious. No, no,
no. I I realize that but there I I I
guess I perceive that there is an
additional effect that um shortening the
name has in terms of the Yes. the form
of you know it allows you to function
more as a unit with each other by
shortening. Yes. How so? Well, you
function as a team when you are
familiar. Yes. Okay.
Okay. Well, my perception is that the
full name carries the full vibrational
aspect of the beingness. I was wondering
how shortening it changes. The nickname
carries the aspect that may delineate
the specific purpose you have between
yourself and that individual
like dealing with one facet of a crystal
instead of the whole thing. When you say
that individual, you mean another
individual that you're dealing with who
may use that nickname for you. I see.
Okay. So, they are drawing upon a
particular aspect of your total crisis.
Got it. Thank you. Thank you. What if
you changed your whole name into a
nickname? Then you are simply assuming the idea
Then you are simply assuming the idea
that your vibration is focused in that
way. Thank you. Thank you.
All right. Thank you. Then you Hi.
Hi. [Music]
[Music]
My um I wanted to ask you what I how I
might be able to serve u my father at
this moment. And if you had any ideas to
help him, he is having heart trouble
quite seriously. Feeling the shifting
electromagnetic spectrum in that way.
Has there already been a weakness in
that area?
Yes. He has had several heart attacks
through his life and in the last year
he's been in the hospital three times.
As the fourth density transformation
increases and as your heart chakras
become sensitized to the electromagnetic
shifting, you may find that those that
have created the idea of a weakened
state in that area may be
susceptible. And some of them may be in
your terms pushed out.
out.
Now what does it do for you?
the idea of my father being
um or simply what you are dealing with
now. What does it do for you? How does
his choice serve you to make your
choice? It's connecting to you. All
right. All right. And your choice in
terms of how you live your life.
May I make a suggestion? Yes, please.
When sometimes we ask you to use your
imagination perhaps because of the form
you have made it in literature in your
society. It would help you to take that
statement in what you might call a
science fiction
flavor. Let the scenario as you are
forming in your imagination your
so-called connection to your father from
your heart to his heart, let the
pictures be ones that don't necessarily
make sense in your society's terms.
Let it be
imaginary and see if the feeling is not
more accurately defined.
All right. Um All right. So what do you
think?
How does the connection from his heart
to your heart allow you to make the
choices in your life that you are
making?
I I do not want to be as afraid of
emotions as he is.
Are you?
No. All right. Have you
shared the idea with him that he might
be afraid of emotion?
Oh, I have a face. I see. I think he'll
have a And so you are in fact equally
afraid just as he is.
I feel like he can I can see his fear
and he can't. So I feel like I can you
see your own? Yes. All right, sir.
Share the idea that you see within you a
fear to share your emotions and perhaps
you will allow it to be all right for
him to do so which may take some of the
pressure off his heart. Yes. Be a
reflection for him in the same way he
has been a reflection for you. Do not be
afraid of your own emotions.
All right. All right. Then you will be
being an example to him that he can
choose to imitate.
Yes. Is there anything else for shark?
Nope. Not for now.
Not for now.
No matter what the manifestation of his
choice, do not create the idea of
regret. All right.
Yeah. Yes. I I guess that is in there
that that I um regret a relationship you
didn't have or
You had exactly the relationship that
you needed to be exactly who you are.
Yes. Yes. Now that you are cognizant of
that idea, you can transform the relationship
idea, you can transform the relationship
into something else, the definition into
something else is
else is
exactly what will fulfill
you later on. All right. Oh, nice. Thank
you. Thank you.
You That was very nice of you. I really
like that. Oh, thank you. Um, you're
welcome. So are you.
Thank you.
I've had this recurring dream where um
my father and I are in his put engine
plane and we run into some kind of
mechanical difficulty and he goes,
"Well, the only thing we can do is start
at the beginning." So, he cuts the
engine intending to go through the check
sheet of how you start dies. And the
plane goes into a dive and I don't know
how it ends. Don't
It ends like this. And then I woke up.
Yeah. All right. Has it ended? No, it is still
All right. Has it ended? No, it is still
going on. I just woke up. That is all.
What's going to happen? I don't know.
In to the next exciting insult.
Will they pull out of this one?
[Laughter] Here. Oh, you do. How intuitive of you
Here. Oh, you do. How intuitive of you
symbology?
Maybe I know. Well, what do you think of
your relationship with my dad? No, the
plane to have a very intimate
relationship with the ground.
[Laughter] Well, Well,
Well,
are there a few things you would like to
go over on your checklist
with my dad? Yeah.
Well, well, do it.
Well, well, then perhaps you can pull
out of the dive you feel you are in. I
haven't been too successful at that.
Understand? It is not that you have to
fulfill your expectation, but that you
are willing to take the action to
function within your own
integrity and know that you have done
your best.
So then you can fly your own plane.
All right. Thank you very me. you.
First of all, I'd like to share a dream
that I had recently
that was synchronicity itself. Oh, how
exciting. Yeah.
Um, I was staying overnight at my folks.
I woke up
and but I wasn't ready to get up and I
thought, well, I'll go back. I should
get up and take a shower, but I think
I'll sleep a little longer. Oh, what?
The instant I went back to
sleep, I had a dream about taking a
shower. It started right away. And I
said, "Well, I'm going to take a shower
in this dream." Hey. So, I looked down.
I had this blue key in my hand. I looked
up and there's a blue door. I said,
"This key is going to fit that door."
How convenient. Yes. Really? Open the
door. And sure enough, there's a
wonderful little shower room. And I
thought, "Oh, this is great.
Oh, but I've forgotten my clothes and my
purse. So, I had Oh, no. I forgotten my
clothes and my towel, right? So, I lost
my purse in the room. Good. And I ran
off to get my towel and my clothes. And
usually in a dream, minutes action
changes, I never get back to what I
started with. How I was
However, I did
And meanwhile,
what what happened that was so amazing
to me was that all of a sudden I
realized the whole scenario. I'm in this
girl's college and I I remember that I
had classes that morning and we just had
time. We It was lunchtime and we just
had time to take a
shower. And when I when I recalled this
later, I thought fantastic. This is
exactly what Bashar was talking about.
And you create your past from your
present. It was happening right there in
the dream. Yes. So that was the first
thing. So I went back, unlock the door
again, open it up. No shower. Oh, that's
exactly what I did.
And and then I realized, oh, I've
already taken a shower. Oh, why? And the
room was wet there. And there was also a
towel and a little mat. I thought, isn't
this nice? They really do things nicely
here. This sounds familiar.
And then I
realized, oh, I've already taken a shower, but I
oh, I've already taken a shower, but I
didn't remember having done it. And I
thought, this is
great. What this is is your present is
not a result of your past. And I just wanted
a result of your past. And I just wanted
to share that with everybody. Thank you
for doing it in the same manner with the
shower as was done by the other
individual as well. Exactly. Also, I do
have a question. Another secret is I
love it. It's happening all the time. Uh
a friend of mine asked me to ask you
about the Anastasia
Indians. He likes to visit a place in
Arizona where they have cliff dwellings.
And he wanted me to ask about a
particular thought there that has some
magic significance. What can you tell me about
significance. What can you tell me about
that?
Communications took place
there. Communications from your planet to
Communications from your planet to
another
realm. The energy of the
communications still exists. The doorway
is still open. The link, the
conduit wide open.
What could be done by my friend in that
place? Could we actually
communicate? And is it serious?
It is connected to that conduit, but it
is also connected to many other places.
It is one of the direct connection
points to what you call kacina energy
and kacina consciousness.
Although they had a subtle variation of
that idea in that area.
There is a
particular ceremony in your term which
does exist for those people in standing
in that spot in having that
communication. He can find out what that
is and do it.
How would you discover that? Talk to
them. Ah okay
or
read there is information what you call
yours that he can allow himself to
synchronistically come across.
Okay. Can
you can you tell um me any more about
the Anastasia themselves where they came
Anastasia themselves where they came
from, where they went? In this way, the
majority of what you call your American
Indian culture, regardless of the
specific offshoot, have connections to
what you call
Leoria and to some degree also
communication and
existence extraterrestrially and
extraterrestrially and
extradimensionally. For that one is
their literal lifestyle to exist in both
realms at once consciously.
Now those
particular individuals that you are
referring to in our
perception have a particular fondness
for the
idea of water in a
bowl. Water in a
jug. The essence that is contained
within the shell.
allowed him to explore the idea of an
earthnware bowl with
pure spring water in it
and perform for himself the idea of
divination with that tool. See what he
contacts. All right. Yes.
All right. Yes.
I feel a strong connection with this.
Um, and it has to do with being an
Aquarian symbol.
That is why the water. Yes, exactly. The
water bears. Yes.
Can you say anything more about that?
No.
I will leave it up to your imagination
to take what we have already shared and
see what you do with it. Very good. For
sure. Thank you. Yeah. Would you share a
title for this song? connection.
Already been taken. [Music]
[Music]
synchronous showers. Yes. Thank you.
Thank you.
One
moment or showers of synchronicity. Ah,
I like that one.
More poet.
Yes. Over the last few years in
meditations, I I have seen uh crystals
and have connected with
um what I believe to be a lifetime or
they exist in Atlantis. All right.
Um, in my mind I feel I feel drawn to
crystals, although I don't use them
because my mind tells me that they're
just a symbol and whatever I put into it
is what I'll get out of it. Yes. Plus,
they do not carry the same symbology
they did in Appalantis and cannot be
used in exactly the same way because
your mentality is different. Oh, okay.
So my question was what did I what
connection did I have with crystals in
Atlantis? Well, you did in that way
create them, build them, utilize them.
They were the sources of power that
drove the machines that did exist in
that way. Their vibrations ultimately
also are what set off the chain
reactions that destroyed the island land
mass. Mhm. No,
No,
it is the reference you refer to in your
literature as the flood.
Was I a female?
Now understand you have had many
lifetimes in Appalis. It covered a wide
range of time frames. I'm referring to I
I what the information that you seem to
be a priestess. Yes. Yeah. I I felt as
though I
had this or I should say the connections
and the pull that I feel is towards the
end of that time period and you trying
to was I dealing with crystals and was I
at that time? Yes. Also, however, we
find there was a very strong connection
with a counterpart of yourself from the
same whole soul that was also made. I'm
sorry I don't understand it. Did you go
a little slow? Do you know what a
counterpart is? I I think I do. It is
another what you would perceive to be
another person that comes from the same
soul that you do.
Soulmate soulmate. Not exactly.
In a sense it can be but simply the idea
is that you understand that one soul is
responsible for having past, present and
future lives. Yes. Yeah. Understand you
can have simultaneous ones as well.
Does that count as do you call it
counterpart? Did that count is that
counterpart with me in this lifetime
now? Yes.
Can you tell me who that person is?
Maybe. In your case.
Our perception immediately, if this
makes any sense to you at all, would be
that it is someone with intense dark
eyes. Now, yes.
can be more a work associate.
You follow me?
[Music] Um, huh. A work associate.
I can't. Then perhaps you have not met
him. But he is present
and seemingly in our perception very
close.
Very close. You mean somebody that very
close as far as in time frame structure
in terms of interaction
in my life. So it could be somebody that
I know that I just not recognizing or
somebody you will meet very shortly. Ah,
that is our perception at this time. Oh,
I appreciate it. Could have dark hair as
well. Mhm. Will seem to be very intense.
May have a
beard. These guys are making
I think may have
may have a gold ring.
May have a ruby or an emerald in
it or both. Um and maybe also a diamond.
Maybe all three. I think I I have a
feeling this person has nothing to do
with my work environment. Never has. But
there is someone in my life that I'm
thinking of that resembles that. If I
was to tell you a name would first name,
would you be able to maybe
John? Best I can give you is it could
be. Okay. I appreciate that. Thank you.
Okay. I appreciate that. Thank you.
Thank you. There will be a few more
minutes remaining in this interaction.
You me? You. Oh. Oh. Um. Oh dear. Which
me? You. Oh. Oh. Um. Oh dear. Which
question?
Caught you off guard. Yeah. Um, well,
this was something personal. I've now
and then become aware of a ranch, but
it's a group of us
um doing specific work sort of
metaphysical work. Yes. And I've seen
it. I've been there. It's been shown to
me. It's even been where I I am. I mean,
I've created it in my in this body of
space, but I haven't run across it.
Um, across what? Well, in other words,
there's a ranch, and I don't know if
it's it's set up now or strictly in my
future. And I was just wondering if you
could pinpoint it or Yes. Right there.
Do you feel like taking a vacation?
Yeah. Well, well, not really. I not
really. Why not? Because I've already
been on one. Where too?
What do you mean? Oh, no. I I'm I um
just in my experience, I didn't take
anything. Oh, very good. All right.
Uh it just seems that there's a rash
that's so Sometimes it's so real to me
that I run across it. If you know that
it is within you and you allow yourself
to begin to explore the idea of creating
it, then if it exists already, you will
run across
it. Also understand it is
allegorical for the idea of the
relaxation within yourself. It does not
have to be physical. Although it can
become physical
when you act upon some of that
relaxation and form connections to other
individuals who may wish to put
something like that together but not
necessarily together for the purpose of
creating it but to do something else and
create that in the process of doing
something else. Yeah. Right. Okay. Not
that it is in and of itself an end
result. See beyond it. See beyond it and
you will find it. Oh, thanks. That's
awesome. If you only see to it, then in
that way you will stumble around and all
the different roads that might lead
there. And in this way, seeing beyond it
will allow you to already know the road
that leads to it
because it will be familiar. Yeah, of
course. Thank you for that. Thank you.
You okay? Um I'm being sued
uh for $1,600. All right. And uh
my I'm I'm not taking the idea very
well. All right. I I'm observing my
tendency to uh kind of freak out over
the idea of I deserve I deserve
paper saying I am the defendant. It's a
legal term. Oh,
never meant a legal term before.
Well, that's one now. And all right, I'm
observing my tendency to like lose sleep
and just can't think of anything else
but having to deal with it. All right.
Why do you imagine you have created this
idea? Uh well, I I imagine that I've
created it so I could observe my
tendency to do this so I can um maybe
why in this way?
Um I don't know.
Um it's uh what is their reason? Their
reason they want money.
Are you saying in this way the idea is
that you do not have it to give them?
Well, what they want to do is have me
pay over a period of years by attaching
my salary, having me pay like $30 a
month for four and a half years or
something like that. Oh my.
Do you owe them the money? No. Why not?
I don't feel I owe them anything. Why
not?
Why do they feel you do?
Well, I had a small fire in my
apartment. It did probably less than
$100 damage, but my landlord made a
claim and he claimed a whole bunch of
stuff and they paid him 1,600 bucks. Oh,
why? Have you explained this to someone?
Have you explained this to someone?
No. Why not? The
uh they came and talked to my manager
and my manager was an old lady who uh
used to accuse me of all kinds of
things. He told she told them the story
that I was negligent and that I was in a
different room and all kinds of stuff.
And so in this
so in this
way, are you saying that you will have
an opportunity to state your case?
Well, I have to now. I don't have any
choice. I have 30 days to answer. And uh
answer how? Well, I'm supposed to hire a
lawyer. Their strategy is that the cost
in lawyer fees would be more than the
$1,500. So, I'll just pay them. That's
the idea. And I don't know all the legal
things that I have to do.
Can you find out?
I tried to make some calls, but every
lawyer I called said, "No, I'll just do
this for a hundred bucks or do that for
100 bucks." And uh there are three
lawyers. There are three lawyers that
you can contact. I looked up to try to
find free lawyers and uh under what
category? At this house, they have free
lawyers. There's a number that says
legal assistance. I call the guy up. He
says, "Give me a hundred bucks." Is it
in your terms legal assistance
specifically with regard to the idea of
your situation? I don't know. I called a
whole bunch of numbers and they kept
giving me each other's numbers. Do you
not have individuals who have chosen to
be of service with regard to what you
call the idea of
renting? Yeah. Well, they said that this has to
Yeah. Well, they said that this has to
do with evictions. So they kept giving
me different numbers and I never could
find anyone who knew of anyone who could
deal with my
situation. In other words, I just got
the runaround. All right. Are you tired?
runaround. All right. Are you tired?
Yes. All right.
Then stop running and stand up for
yourself.
Without judging the other individual who
is giving you a marvelous opportunity to
state your case, your tenth. All right.
And simply make it plain as to what you
perceive the situation to be. Then see
what happens.
Without accusing. All right.
accusing. All right.
Thank you. And recognize that you may
still have individuals who may suggest
other individuals to whom you can talk.
And in this way, allow yourself the
opportunity, if you feel so inclined, to
talk to them. But recognize that if the
situation they present to you always
makes it seem that you must rely on
yourself, then take it as the obvious
reflection of what the situation,
relying on yourself. I'm coming to that.
I'm seeing that that
uh I may do a better job uh just taking
care of it myself than actually hiring a
lawyer to do it for me. One thing I'm
having to deal with is the fact that I
worry about it so much. I am observing
my tendency to worry and all right then
simply include that in your
understanding of what you are becoming
and know that at the proper place in the
proper time you will say what you need
to say as the being you happen to be at
that moment and for you it will be
perfect no matter what the outcome.
Right? All right. trust that and see
what happens. Okay. Thank you, Bashar.
Bashar. Yes. Well, my left leg is a
little bit shorter than my right leg, an
inch. All right. And so the left side of
my body compensates. It kind of goes
down to match the length of my leg.
All right. But okay. So, my back has
some mild curves in it, and I've been
working therapeutically on it for a
while, and I'm wondering if you can give
me a visualization or a key to helping
that left leg grow in length to match
the right
leg. All right.
This will be a measure of your
willingness. However, for as I perceive
the suggestion I can make to you, it
will come from the portion of your
higher consciousness that
says, "Let's deal with
willingness." All right. Yeah. Now, this
does not mean that if you don't do it
this way, you can't do something.
However, the suggestion that we perceive
the information coming from your higher
consciousness. Allow
yourself to go
around. Well, all right. Let me back up.
You have made a general agreement with
all beings in this reality to set limits
upon what can be accomplished in your
physical reality. You follow me? Mhm.
Therefore, one can do is petition to
have that agreement change. [Music]
[Music]
Oh fine. Call me
discuss with individuals who you think
will be of like mind the idea that even
though you recognize that in that way
creating this physical reality you have
agreed to abide by the idea of the
physical rules and that things can't
just automatically stretch and grow in
that way. Allow yourself to discuss the
possibility that the rule can be
changed. So you in that journey and in those
So you in that journey and in those
interactions will be changing the rule
and you will make a difference and you
may find it automatically perhaps at the
end of that journey you will
automatically be on even ke
that is our suggestion allow your
imagination to alter it in whatever way
seems appropriate for you to maintain
your own sense
All right. Thank you. Yeah, it sounds
lot like a lot of fun. Oh, thank you
very much. That is a whole idea. You saw
right through that.
I'd like to say that I I give her my
opinion permission.
All right. And understand it is not in
that way that just the acceptance but also
way that just the acceptance but also
the fun of the interaction and the
discussion about the idea soon from all
the different perspectives with whom you
will discuss it. Mhm. Not just cart
plunge. Yeah.
Can be that
way. And if you find fun in the
discussion that is all right too.
Yes. Is Shap coming through tonight? I
heard there was a possibility of that.
Yes. Thank you.
Bashar. No. Um it was
um it was told to me that I'm well I'm a
filmmaker and it was told to me that I
would be channeling um a life series
that would um be able to be projected
directly onto film and have to not go
through all the processes. now look at
making and I was wondering if you could
give me some sort of idea of a time
frame in which that might be possible
right now. If you understand yourself in this
now. If you understand yourself in this
way indeed the idea of the
electromagnetic phenomena we have
discussed many times in that way you can
allow yourself the opportunity to
recognize every single idea of
materiality in your terms including what
you call the idea of the film to see a
rearrangement of the magnetic process in
that way and to impose the idea of your
vibration upon the eye of the vibration
of the magnetic field in that way to
form an identification and to leave your
mark in that sense. Do you follow along
with what I'm saying? Yes. Can you allow
your imagination to function in this way
as the idea of your projector? The
imagination is your projector that
allows you to translate the white light
of your higher consciousness out into
the spectrum. In that way, the prism in
that sense to project the picture
through your lens of imagination onto
the screen of your reality. that may
allow your imagination to be the
projector and allow yourself to design
that projector in whatever way, shape
and form and manner that you so deem the
ability will be inherent within the
projector itself to enable you to allow
yourself to experience that phenomena,
that manifestation in your physiological
reality will then only exhibit the idea
of the form and the substance that you
give it of the script that you write for
it. In that way, as you pass that film
through your projector, that is what you
will see on your screen. Are you
following along? Yes. Thank you.
Understanding this way the idea of the
serious energy as you call the first to
ourselves in that sense is the idea of
manifested energy in and of itself. It
is its own reinforcing holographic
pattern. Allow yourself to explore the
idea of the holographic patterns of
magnetism in that way. And allow
yourself to recognize that you yourself
can even create the idea technically of
a new type of projector, a new type of
presentation that way. that will take
the opportunity to present magnetically
induced holographic patterns that will
give you your first clue into the
understanding of how even your physical
reality is impressed in that manner with
the idea of that type of projection
through your imagination. By
we exist in that way within the serious
energy in what you call a
magneticium and immersion in the idea of
the electromagnetic impulse which
creates our consciousness and allows us
to interact as the magnetic field in
which we exist as well. We view the idea
and our viewing within our own
transformation as we are concurrent and
congruent with your transformation. The
idea of our existence is becoming not
the idea that we exist within that
medium but that we are the medium
itself. You follow me? Become the medium
yourself in that way and you will be
able to imprint and impress any idea
within the manifestation of virtual
reality that you so desire. You follow
me? Become the crystallin form of your own
Become the crystallin form of your own
projector in that way so that consider
yourself to be the idea of any
particular aspect of any frame of that
film. You know your life has been chosen
to be by you. All right.
In this way, each and every one of you
allow yourselves the opportunity to
recognize this in the second half of
what you call the activity month of your
April month. Your timing frame in this
way will become more highly accelerated
in a sense and we are allowing
yourselves the opportunity to present
our energy to you to make use of
whatever shape or you so desired. Allow
yourself to recognize that we will in
communication with you many times
through the remainder of this month that
you call the idea of April and often
into the idea of what you call your May
for the renewal of the natural spirit of
yourself and the formation of what will
become the idea of identification of
yourself too. That portion of your
consciousness you consider to be nature,
the idea of your may, the idea of your
spring in that May and the idea of your
own godhood within the creation you see
around you and the animal consciousness,
the nature consciousness even extending
into the idea of the mineral
consciousness. We shall be exploring
this with you. We will thank you in this
way for your endeavor and allowing us to
expedate the idea of the acceleration by
sharing with you our consciousness as a
reflection of the acceleration you have
created for yourselves by yourselves
with us with yourselves and your
willingness to share the unconditional
love you have shared with us in this
way. We will thank you and we will in
this way vitual a fond and loving dream
life and a fond good
night. Now, as I was saying,
we will in this way extend to each and
every one of you our unconditional love
as well and allow you to recognize that
the idea of your activity
month is your
opportunity, your joy to see yourselves
in motion.
You are a beautiful sight when you are
You are poetry in motion. And that rhyme
that you create
yourself will be reflected in the
simultaneous synchronicity that our lives will
synchronicity that our lives will
become. We thank you for your sharing.
We extend our love and our appreciation
for allowing us to experience the gift
that you are and to experience all the
different ways that all that it has of
manifesting itself in creation. We
extend to you our excitement and our joy
at the sharing that you have chosen to
cocreate with us
forever. We thank you. We b you a fond
and loving good night.