all right I'll say how are you all this
evening of your time as you create time
to
exist are you all alive how are you all
this evening of your time thank you in
this way we will begin this evening of
your time with the
idea that in your society as you are
going through many of the
Transformations that are taking place
now upon your planet you change the
different methodologies the different
modes of operation that you find
yourselves exploring all these different
modes of operation are all part and
parsel of the idea of discovering
yourself to be who you know yourselves
to be in this way therefore simply
recognize that many times when you go
through different modalities when you
change from one methodology to another
in this way simply because of the way
you are used to reacting in your Society
many times you will negate or judge or
cancel the
idea or call it negative as to the idea
you have previously been involved with
now that you are involved in something
else many times you will tend to
Discount the idea that you have already
been previously involved in thinking
that it now in this way is as you say no
good and that what you are doing now is
better than what you would doing then
but recognizeing this way many times the
idea is that every single step you have
ever taken every single stepping stone
has gotten you to where you are thus in
this way you will find that it is just
as much of a break in your momentum just
as much of a stoppage of the flow of
your continuity to Discount and judge
and negate anything you have ever done
as it is to Discount anything that you
could ever do in this way the entire
idea the entire path that you
are will in this way remain unbroken and
constantly flowing to you and through
you if you are willing to recognize that
anything that could come to you is a
part of the path you chose to be and
anything you have ever done is a part of
the path you chose to be for everything
you have ever done has brought you to
where you are now and therefore has
served you in a positive way there is no
need to judge that certain things that
you used to do are invalid compared to
the things you are doing now simply
because the things you used to do
brought you to what you are now at this
point thus the more you are willing to
understand every single event in your
life every single experience every
single interaction every single
situation that you have interacted with
as a part of the path you chose to be in
your so-called past and in your
so-called future that is when you will
allow yourself to fully experience your
reality in the present moment and in
this way you will allow every experience
to be a consciously recognizable part of
the path you chose to be and you will
feel yourself to be one unbroken whole
continuous idea in every given now
moment that you create to exist
therefore when you find that at some
point in your life a certain source of
information has meaning for you and then
you simply find that the idea no longer
has meaning
this does not mean that it is an
opportunity necessarily to invalidate
that source of information for at the
time it did serve you and at the time
that is the level you were on and you
did benefit from it if only to recognize
perhaps that the information that was
coming to you may not represent the
reality you know to be true for you that
does not mean it is not valid for it was
an opportunity to recognize what is true
for you based upon allowing yourself the
opportunity to see what is not true for
you now the distinction in terms of your
outlook within these situations will
determine how consciously aware you are
of all the other experiences that come
into your life for to determine that
something in your past has been
invalid is to open up a higher degree of
probability that something coming in
from the future will also be looked at
as not valid anytime you invalidate
any portion of yourself which includes
all the experiences you have ever had
you invalidate the total idea of
yourself and therefore do not let
yourself be able to perceive that the
ideas that are coming to you the
experiences and situations that are
coming to you from the so-called future
are a part of your path many times you
may become the idea of suspicious
because of things that have happened in
the past and not allow yourself to trust
that they were a part of your path and
therefore not allow yourself to trust
that some things coming into your life
from the future will in this way also
always be a part of your path you may
become suspicious that they could be
interruptions in your path which they
cannot be unless you judge that they can
in this way therefore simply recognize
that if you find that something is no
longer true for you then simply take it
as a recognition that you have changed
or that the source of information has
changed but if it has changed if you
have changed this is simply another
opportunity to recognize what it is that
is now true for you what you have become
all you need to do once again is allow
yourself to recognize that everything
that has ever happened in your life or
will ever happen in your life is a part
of the path you chose to be having that
Outlook and having that perspective and
having that point of view and having
that attitude is what will allow you to
understand all the situations that come
into your life because you will be
willing to accept them as a part of the
path and thus you will replace your
suspicion with fascination with
curiosity with imagination and with
excitement and those faculties are what
will allow you clear Clairvoyant and and
conscious recognition of exactly what
those situations do serve you in your
life how they fit into the path you
chose to be and allow your lives to
become very transparent and a work of
ease of creation rather than a struggle
and a Strife to achieve you follow me
yes all right is very
simple you always attach yourself firmly
to the thing you
judge the idea is that you
chose this reality in which to exist do
you follow that yes in choosing this
reality in which to exist you did so for
your own reasons your own purposes and
you allowed yourself the opportunity to
Simply recognize therefore that if you
know that the life you have chosen to
live is for your own reasons then you
can simply take it for granted and trust
that every single thing you will
encounter in this life must be a part of
the path you chose to be for the
universe does not do pointless and
extraneous things you can judge that it
does and it is only the Judgment that
something is Superfluous that creates
the effect of the seeming
effect of the seeming
superfluousness but every situation is
fundamentally neutral no
neutral no
situation has builtin meaning they are
all blank neutral circumstances you
supply the meaning to any situation in
supplying your meaning positive and or
negative to Any Given blank neutral
situation you then by the choice of that
Outlook by the choice of that
perspective and attitude determine what
effect you will reap from that situation
because positive outlook in positive effect
positive outlook in positive effect
out negative outlook in negative effect
out but it is only your judgment of a
situation as something that you do not
think belongs in your life that allows
you to have the experience as if that
situation did not belong in your life
only the Judgment that causes the
effect there are no interruptions in
your life you are complete and whole as
a Creator and everything every idea you
are comes complete with all the
ingredients and situations necessary for
the manifestation and continuance of
that idea in your reality thus when you
are willing to understand that
everything you experience every
situation you attract in your life is a
part of your path and therefore can be
looked at with excitement here is
another part of me to discover to add to
the life that I am and live the path I
chose to be then that is how that
situation will affect your life and you
will be able to see how it fits in does
that clarify the idea
yes for you
sharing um I want to ask you about the
can't find the one on the
um and Reon yeah I cannot find that then
perhaps you simply do not need
it okay understand once again if any
idea you are being needs a tool in order
for you to be that idea the tool is
automatically synchronistically there if
it isn't you don't need it right I read
that book
and uh the thing that I got from it were
the eyes I we have discussed this idea
right by the way how are your
trips uh very changing very been very
changing very interesting um I've been
in contact with a um serious connection
all right perhaps to function as a
modulator in your extraction of the
information you seek from the idea of
your future noal Point yes uh I was on
the spaceship and they I got vague it
seemed like there were several of them
serious energy will usually come across
like that because it is in a sense a
collective of Consciousness okay all
right cuz that's what I got and then
they said to uh go ahead and get a
drawing pass U because then the uh the
information for sketches and all that
would come forth so I did that and uh
that's very interesting all right and
then uh just the other day there was um
I was uh uh writing automatic writing
with the serious connection and I I felt
that it was a he but he said that
um he said he doesn't have a name they
do not know no and but he said it's a
signature vibration which is O HH but
has no verbal sound or meaning in our
language and then he showed me
um he said he was not a he that it was a
combination of male female Blended they
already Blended in that sixth density
level right and um so then he showed me
my signature vibration that going out of
body um
that I would be that I'm known as or
identified as all right that looked to
me like a flower with an L um a big L
that I felt looked like a flower and
then then low all right is your symbolic
interpretation of the vibration so you
can understand it in Consciousness terms
right and um the feeling uh was that uh
I
would they would assist me and Gary's
assisting me in going out of body into
some of the future
information so it's very exciting thank
you what is the unifying force in the
universe
Consciousness and it is not so much a
force as it is the fabric of existence
itself when your scientists include
Consciousness in their equations they
will understand the unified field that
they seek
again I did not get
unifying the entirety of creation is one
thing is one Consciousness manifesting
in
multidimensional simultaneous
aspects everything is the same one
thing now if that is not a unifying
force I do not know what it is it is not
so much the idea of a force it is simply
that everything is in fact the same one
thing manifesting in an infinite number
of
multi-dimensional aspects that is what unifies
aspects that is what unifies
everything does that clarify the idea to
some extent got your answer thank you
extent got your answer thank you
sh I just want to share one other thing
that uh Gary was over the other day and
I shared with him the idea of going into
the future reality and was very excited
about it all right um so I'm that made
me feel real good all right thank you
for co-creating that excitement in your
reality so that you can recognize the
excitement as a reflection of the path
you chose to be which is what excitement
is that is why you can always trust to
follow your excitement each and every
one of you excitement is the vibration
that represents the path you chose to be
so you can trust it that if you follow
your excitement you will automatically
attract into your lives all the
situations necessary to provide whatever
you need to be the idea you are excited
about
being you all
follow sh B you venue um I'm trying to
uh what I am try I am trying to trying
trying do you enjoy trying
yes I I do enjoy struggling all
right I'm trying to uhit take okay uh I
wish to be able to
differentiate between my
intuition and perhaps subtle forms of an
analysis of thinking on my mind so I can
know what's going on you do not know
what is going
on in terms of my being communicating
with myself what do you think if I may
ask you having this differentiation will
do for
you um I'm desirous of of um becoming
more in tune with my intuition all right
and knowing when that's speaking to me
versus my subtle form of of my mind
talking to me or thinking in terms of an
may I ask you another question yes if
you cannot tell the difference what
difference does it
make I can't answer that but I think
there is
all right in this way simply recognize many
right in this way simply recognize many
times you may be assuming that there is
a difference and there may not be there
is nothing quote unquote wrong with
reason there is nothing quote unquote
limiting about reason when you simply
allow it to be when it needs to be and
simply trust that whatever tool from
your imagination you do need in any any
given situation at any given moment will
be the tool you will use if sometimes
reason is needed reason will be there if
your intuition is needed then that is
what you will be drawing from and if you
cannot tell the difference then why not
assume that they are simply Blended in a
form they need to be Blended within that
allows you to Simply Avail yourself of
whatever you need at any given moment
without the need for such a separation
and such a distinction between them in
needing such a separation you may
actually be then requesting the blockage
you think you already have but
don't you follow
me 65% you may be asking for a
limitation you think you already have
but don't
have you are saying I am experiencing
the idea of my communication with my
imagination in a way that I cannot tell
when I am reasoning and when I am
intuiting so I want to separate them so
I can see them both distinctly because I
feel that not being able to separate
them limit me but you are being
contradictory having them Blended in
this way the way you already have is the
integration and to wish to see them
separated that is the
limitation um okay I get that but and um
because of being perhaps
overly analytical I would like to be
more in tune with my intuition which is
there but all right let me ask you
another question yes can you
specifically describe what makes you
think you are not in touch with your
intuition as much as you need to
be mostly external feedback such as
people saying I'm too analytical ah why
do you choose to believe
them it's information so
just because something is information
does not mean you have to choose to
believe
it do you
regardless of what you have been told by
someone else do you truly feel that that
is true for you at times I believe so at
times at times all right what about the
other
times I'm not clear about the other
times there's some intuition there but
um I'm not clear about it can you
understand that there is always exactly
the proper amount of intuition there not
just
some you follow me yes I guess I'm
trying to I I wish to be more in touch
with the intuition all right and and
what does it feel like to you when you
are in touch with your intuition do you
know what the feeling is kind of a
spontaneous feeling all right in other
words you can at any given moment as you
have just done call that feeling up yes
or
no I'm not sure I can call it off it
just seems how did you know how to
describe it if you could not call it up
well there was no conscious thought
going on that I was able
to attach myself to ah so you were
functioning from Instinct from
intuition possibly
possibly
possibly do you think it would feel
another way
do you think experiencing your intuition
has to feel a certain way before you
will acknowledge that you are doing
it I don't know what the rules are there
aren't
any you create
them now does that make it
easier yes understand that if you
in any way shape and form can
conceive of the idea of quote unquote
what it would be like to function from
more of your intuition in the very
second you are conceiving of what it
would be like you are actually
functioning from that point of view in
order to be able to conceive what it
would be like because you cannot
perceive what you do not contain
if you can perceive it you are at that
moment of the perception the very idea
itself all you need to do is trust that
it is that simple and that the moment
you are conceiving it you are on the
same vibratory frequency as the idea you
desire to be you are suddenly the idea
instantly the idea itself all you need
to do to see it reflected in your
physical reality to get the feedback you
desire is when you conceive in your
imagination of what it is you would like
to be trust that because you have been
able to conceive it you are already it
and all you need to do to see it
reflected in your reality is act like
you know that that is what you are act
like it then you will be saying that you
it then you will be saying that you
trust that your ability to even conceive
of the idea is the same
thing your imagination is the same thing
just as real as physical reality just as
real you will recognize that your
physical reality is the product of your
imagination anyway you are simply then choosing what
anyway you are simply then choosing what
portion or what idea or what form or
what definition of your imagination you
choose to have the experience of your
physical reality as
as soon as you simply act like you know
that the ability to conceive of it is
making the choice of the reality you
prefer all you need to do is act like
that as your reality and your reality
will have no choice but to reflect that
to you and attract to you individuals
who will say you know you seem to be
functioning from your intuition
lately that's the kind of feedback I'd
like to hear for then act like that is
true for you already so that you give
them the opportunity to see radiated
from you the reality you prefer
otherwise they are only going to be
attracted to your belief that you do not
function from your intuition and so that
is what they are reflecting to you but
when an individual reflects a situation
like that to you that does not mean you
are stuck in that situation them
reflecting that to you what they see
from you is your opportunity to
recognize what reality you are creating
and if you do not prefer it change it no
therefore or that you prefer to function
from your intuition and act from that
point as if that is the reality that is
true for you then is when you give them
the opportunity to see the reality the
other reality you have chosen then you
will get the
feedback you follow me thank you it is
if I may remind you also that
simple you follow me yes thank you you
um you just talked about something that
you talked about last week and that
is that simple with trust okay well I
did that for about two days last week
and then what happened to me is what
happens a lot um in my life I operate on
a lot of times from feelings of um
insecurity worry and fear why um well do
you enjoy them well obviously I must but
I really don't it's really it's painful
and anyways I don't like those feelings Al
anyways I don't like those feelings Al
you know now recognize that in and of
themselves in a sense fundamentally they
are not feelings in the sense that they
do not represent feelings
of fundamental emotions there is only
one fundamental emotion and that is
love everything else is a
differentiation of or a judgment of your
own
selfworth Judgment of the self is what
creates worry guilt frustration
pain and all of the things you are
describing anger in a sense although
recognize that in your Society what you
are calling anger is actually
judgment true quote unquote true quote
unquote anger does not come with a negative
anger does not come with a negative
feeling
for anger is only the energy of
alignment to what you know to be true
for you let us say there is a situation
where you are presented with an
idea when you know if you recognize that
that idea simply has nothing to do with
the reality that is true for you you
instantaneously have a energy Rush that
is an
alignment so that you can see what is
true for you compared to to what you
have been offered a choice to believe in
now when you judge the idea you have
been offered a choice to believe in as
something less worse or negative
compared to what it is you choose to
believe in then you experience the
alignment in a negative way which you
call anger but natural anger does not
last any longer than 10 to 15 seconds
anything longer than that is Judgment of
the situation that allows you to
experience the feeling
when you know that something and I will
act as if every situation in your life
is a part of the thing you trust you are
doing
perfectly then you will create in your
physical reality the positive feedback
that is a reflection of your trust that
you know what you are doing and only
attract situations that fit in with the
path you chose to
be how's that thank you does that assist
you pleasant pleasant
dreams
sharing bash guys I have six questions
is that too many six
questions and I'm afraid they aren't as
afraid there is no such thing as a
stupid question everything is a sharing
everything is a gift everything is an
opportunity for everyone you are
interacting with to learn something
about themselves by experiencing the
gift that you are are do not judge
yourself share thank you okay number one are you
share thank you okay number one are you
aware of any civilization on or near the
star we call Arcturus yes what are they
like who are they to our understanding
for now as they relate to your
civilization they are a collective
non-physical Consciousness that is
involved on many different levels as
many other civilizations are with the
assistance of the transformation of your
world with specific regard to some of
the ideas of the new incarnation taking
place that you call the children that
are being born into your world now in
this way they are in a sense let us say
an emotional framework regulatory energy
that allows many of these children now
being born upon your planet to let us
say not forget as much as they would
have without that alignment without that
assistance without that
identification just births now or could
it be ones that have occurred there are
some that have already occurred for a
little while of your time yes what like
30 years 20 years
10 within the 30-year frame yes is the
ashtar command part of this group not
directly a part of the ID you call
arcturis in this way but they do
represent another level of Consciousness
that is being of assistance in different
ways although recognize that to some
degree our perception of the way many of
the individuals upon your planet have
interpreted the idea of what you are
calling ashtar command in many ways may
be being created in symbolic terms that
are not necessarily let us say
completely representative of the way the
actual Consciousness perceives itself to
be so in other words uh what is what we
call the ashtar command could be putting
in physical uh terminology the
non-physical Collective consciousness of
Urus is that right there is some
connection to that and some connection
to your own world as well and as with
any Consciousness assisting your
Civilization now they are all a part of
what we term the
association which is the collective
consciousness of all civilizations and
levels of consciousness that we interact
with do the arcturians have
spaceships that appear you may perceive
them to be such but that is how your
mentality needs to see their energy at
this time mostly it is simply a
projection of
Consciousness although in a sense that
is what any physical object is yeah I
understand um number two oh that was
number
one um when I first came here I met some
people outside who are who are giving me
a sort of capsule explanation of you and
in their explanation they said that you
were Daryl's future self innocense um
this is my question as I wrote it out
please explain the idea that you are
Daryl's future S one understanding can
simply be as you understand linear Time
Imagine That the physical Channel seated
before you dies leaves this physical
plane you call Earth you follow me MH is
Born Into My civilization as myself
myself having the ability to transcend
the idea you call SpaceTime and speak
through my own past
life so back in time in a sense this is
you a the only one life physical life I
have had on your world for the purpose
of forming the arrangement and the
agreement to be of service in the way we
are being of service
now isn't all individuality Eternal
unique and not United with another yes
and it is also all one both are true
recognize that the unity that you seek
upon your planet will be the product of
the granting of equality to the infinite
diversity within it so the strengthening
of the individuals is paradoxically what
creates the strongest single unified
mind just as you as an individual are
composed of many different personality
portions you follow me yeah if you
function most strongly as an individual
it is because you have allowed all the
different portions of yourself to be
Blended in equal strength you follow me
thus each and every one of you as an
individual when you allow yourselves to
be equal as individuals that is when you
allow let us say the over mind of your
civilization to then function as the
strongest single identity it can
function as the idea is that you will
not lose your individuality but it will
be
crystallized enhanced yes now so okay so
just to make sure I understand that uh
for instance you have someone who in
this time right now believes they are
they are The Reincarnation of Moses or
some Prophet now their individual ity
right now isn't
exactly Moses per se but it is the
carrying on the time continuum so to
speak of Moses's life see what I in a
sense there can be identification energy
there are many different ways to
perceive this idea in their one single
reality that they are recognizing that
every single individual is truly
literally their own complete univ I do
you follow me mhm then in that
individual's Universe in that Universe what they are
Universe in that Universe what they are
saying is just as valid as anything else
and for them completely true as it
relates to the rest of the agreed upon
similarities you agree to share as a
mass Consciousness then it is more let
us say appropriate to refer to it as you
already have as simply an identification
with a certain type of energy that may
be associated with that Consciousness to
to which you are referring but is not
necessarily literally a representation
of a direct reincarnation right is there
direct reincarnation oh there is direct
reincarnation yes but in this way also
recognize that even what you call Direct
reincarnation Is Not always completely
exactly direct for you are never exactly
the same
you fulfillment of his Divine Purpose
set out long ago was this citing The
Awakening for him that it was the timing
of our agreement
yes okay um number four in these
channeling sessions is there any danger
of an Uninvited Guest coming through
Daryl are you inviting them no because
Daryl is
not so there is no no because I've done
reading about about other understand
once again you are your own completely
inviolet Universe anything that occurs
in your Universe does so because of your
beliefs that it can thus in this way you
will find that while we are not
necessarily saying that even darl is in
touch with all of his core beliefs there
is enough understanding to Simply know
that the level of trust that has already
been experienced can continue to be
experienced and there is simply the
recognition that without necessarily
having to be consciously aware of what
all the single beliefs are there is the
inviolet trust that no matter what
happens is what needs to happen to be of
service to all of you
uhhuh okay do you have a language of
your own not anymore though there are
Remnant portions of this idea we are now
basically functionally what you would
call telepathic if so can you tell let me
telepathic if so can you tell let me
know what they sound like what these
portions sound
like we love you
but you don't need that anymore no for
we have understood that to love every
single individual within our society
unconditionally allows us to know them
implicitly to love them is to know
them is that the eventual communication
of our man as we perceive this is a high
degree of probability it is your choice
however okay are you in Earth space right
okay are you in Earth space right
now no you're in future time
I are you in your environs or that in my
spacecraft round about my Planet how far
away is that from here in your terms of
spatial counting approximately what you
call 500 of your light
years are you familiar with the planet
cuest to some degree
uh are you familiar with the planet UMO
to some degree although we would
recognize that not exactly as what you
would delineate precisely as a planet in
your dimensionality who UMO yes to us it
is more another type of patterned
Consciousness that may have a
representational idea of a planet but it
is slightly
different are you connected in any way
with these two um um when you say not
directly but through the idea of the
interaction that takes place on what you
would call higher levels of the
association our Consciousness is always
blended with any other Consciousness in
the same Association even though there
may not be specific interaction between
the individuals are they uh the same
density as your beings as yourself or
fundamentally with variations
yes roughly
fourth and you in turn as we are are
evolving into your own oh yes
progression of course everyone is a
learner and a
teacher sometimes it seems like more one
than the other your
choice but that is why we request the
idea not so much of questions but of
sharing for when you blend the idea of
yourself as a teacher and a learner then
you simply become an equal Sharer
all right okay thank you thank you very
much sharing y good question all right
you answered 500 light years I that's
precisely the light years of um era in
within the plean
constellation is are you saying that
you're perhaps neighbors laterally
parallel to each
other our per of the counting in this
way is that the pleadian systems in your
terms are farther than
that will you in your terms recheck your
figures
okay that's what I have in mind now but
I will all right uh next question have
you any hint when you are familiar with
UMO apparently correct to some degree some
apparently correct to some degree some
degree well all right when the umit were
in their craft
over Spain um they beheld another craft they
Spain um they beheld another craft they
did not recognize a craft that could
permeate their identity permeate their
ship but their technology could not
identify the craft or permeate their
field have you any idea what kind of
civilization or craft this might have
belonged to from your own
experiences at this point we are
scanning
probabilities it is not let us say
within our perceptions definite but
probable that it might be might be
representative of one fragment of what
you recognize to be the da
mhm it may also have been in a sense a
piercing from one universal planer
reality through what we can only turn a quasi
through what we can only turn a quasi
planar reality
membrane that does not allow immediate
recognition from one Universe to another
and so coming through that membrane in a
sense will not necessarily have allowed
an individual on this side of the
membrane to perceive from where those
Consciousness has originated are you are
you ter me membrane in terms of slight
dimensional degree differences so that
they perceived
imperfectly uh not enough of a whole
picture to in a sense
yes that is the perception at this time
we can share we find there is no name we
can associate to that phenomena or that
level of Consciousness that would make
any sense okay in the
translations all right got a last
question one moment
yes oh there is to some degree the idea
of what you call accuracy with the first
of your questions in this way the 500
like years but we are simply aware of
the idea that the extent of the pleadian
systems in this way is much more
extensive than just that okay there is
one fragment however that is in that
sense lateral okay that's interesting okay um
lateral okay that's interesting okay um
at one
point I'm talking about Billy Meyer now
when he woke
up because the whole area including his
house was bathed in a tremendous
light and uh he walked out and he was
included in that light all it I don't
recall the amount of time that it lasted
but what he saw was a bar of Light which
eventually showed up in um the second
volume pedian volume he did not
know what civilization this was asked
the pleadians they did not know and
reported back to him about a year
later this fact as to their identity of
what they represented was never
divulged I don't know why not can you
help on that we simply do perceive that
whether or not it is immediately
attached there is some degree of
correlation between that experience and
the one you have related to by the idea
of
UMO there are divisions and quasi planar
realities that from time to time will
have extensions of their Consciousness
into your Universal membrane they will
usually come along lines that are
already attractive to such types of
energy and thus appear before
individuals in many different
civilizations who are already by
definition interacting with each other
in that way thus they simply follow the
lines of least resistance as they probe
into your
Universe we ourselves have not explored
these
levels all right are you saying then
that there are
certain beings or capacities to probe
more breadth within the universe and perhaps
breadth within the universe and perhaps
into another Universe another oh yes we
have encountered a few but not
many but we know they exist is androm
part of
it ability do they ex they have some
degree of that ability within that
Galactic system a although they also
have a high degree of connection to your
and our in a sense
Universe more so than some of the others
do
but you may understand that in a sense
androma does function as a
Gateway through which some of those
other Universal consciousnesses also
find themselves most easily able to
penetrate into this universe because
Andromeda does in fact act as the
Consciousness hub for what you call the
local group of
galaxies you follow
me local group of galaxies in other
words let us put it this way as we speak
of the idea of an Association of
civilizations that you are relating to
in this galaxy Andromeda in a sense
functions as an association of
associations and this creates
reachability and impact Hey Oh yay
because of the
quality in a sense because of the
magnitude yes
okay than you hey uh in this on this
plane we we appear here in masculine or
feminine or positive and negative
is that indicative of our soul within us
to some degree but in this way you will
understand that the soul is not
masculine and feminine Blended but in a
sense it is the idea to some degree of
polarities which truly only become
manifested when they project themselves
into a dimension such as yours that by
definition will simply have that
perception of a soul a polarized
perception of a soul
but the soul is both energy yes but not
exactly in the idea that it is a blended
form it is
simply one
thing you follow me think so in this way
in other words it is not so much the
idea exactly that you have the masculine
and feminine energy and they are blended
into one Soul it is that they are
Blended but when the blending occurs on
the soul level you do not recog ize the
soul as a blending of masculine and
feminine energy but simply as one
thing you follow me you do not see the
components on that level at all you do
not recognize the soul as a blending of
things you just recognize it as one
thing you do not even see the potential
for the soul to separate into
polarities this is only a product of the
definition of the reality you have
created to be your plane of existence so
to speak MH
sure does that clarify the idea to some
extent we do realize that some of these
terminologies do not translate into your
language yes that does help me
understand thank
you um do Spirit guides exist oh yes oh
yes oh yes you have been won many times
as has all of you how can I contact
whatever spirit guide might be
associated with my universe may I ask
you a question first my pleasure why do
you want to contact them curiosity all
right uh mostly actually knowledge all
right may I remind you of something
however yes thank
you a spirit guide of course will not
live your life for
you you follow me yes therefore it is
very simple there are many ways to
contact your guides in this way first of
all simply recognize and rely upon the
idea you call your imagination for your
imagination is a dimension unto itself
that contains all that you are including
the idea of anyone interacting with you
therefore in your imagination can be any
methodology at all that you find
yourself to be comfortable with for your
imagination is the vibration that is
specifically tuned to your vibration in
physical reality therefore anything it
will give you as a method of doing
anything you desire to do will work for
you that is why it is your imagination
if it didn't work for you it would be
someone else's imagination so first and
foremost rely and Trust upon your
imagination to provide for you a
methodology that you feel comfortable
and excited about quote unquote
invoking then simply recognize you are
never out of touch with your guides
there is always communication but
recognize that it is a guide's job in a
sense to be unobtrusive because they are
not about living your life for you nor
giving you the answers they know you you
want to discover for yourself they
simply lure you to more of yourself and
in the state of being more of yourself
you discover you are your own answers
they do not have to precisely give them
to you you follow me yes that is the
function of a
guide so simply in whatever way shape
and form you find exciting create a
scenario in which you know you are in
fact talking to your guides then all you
have to do is listen and simply trust
that whatever it is you get
whether it is a vision whether it is a
feeling whether it is a thought simply
trust that that is communication do not
put a judgment upon what it means simply
trust it is a communication you do not
have to interpret nor analyze it to
begin with allow yourself simp the
experience of the communication itself
then bit by bit at whatever rate you are
comfortable you will get the translation
that goes along with it but
communication is always being sent to
you all you need to do is relax and
listen all right thank you find you sure yes
all right thank you find you sure yes
um I have a
feeling uh that there's a high
probability uh for some future um
inventions that I might run into that
material one of the materials to be used
in it would be sand silicon silicon ice
Okay now what's the difference between
sand and Sil sand blended with
oxygen uhuh in this way silicon is in and of
uhuh in this way silicon is in and of
itself the idea of an element mhm and in
this way you will simply find that the
blending of the idea with oxygen in this
way will create many of the ideas of
silica in that sense that you are used
to one of which is very common in your
society that you call
Glass but silicon itself as an element
in this way does have many glass-like
properties and in this sense the Pure
Element does have energy that can be
extracted by some of the idea of the
virtual vacuum technology that we have
discussed already oh
okay very again I'll explore that all
right it has a specific vibration that
will be
conducive to interactions with other
elements primarily lithium okay
lithium okay
also perhaps magnesium
cesium tungsten heard CI look it
tungsten heard CI look it
up cesium also has a high degree of
affinity for the substance you call
quartz oh
okay Blended together they can form
forms of energy regulation and patterns
of vibrational
resonance okay that was Gary's idea f it
great thank you sure hey is there a
difference between guides and these more
highly evolved civilizations or are they
depends upon what a particular
individual in any one of those
civilizations is doing in a sense no if
they are willing to be of service to be
of assistance in that way then they
function as gu in the same way that I
have chosen to function as a guy so to
speak you follow me mhm
now there is a difference in the sense
that many of the guides or let us say
most of the guides that you find
yourselves to be interacting with have a
higher degree of association with your
particular Earth plane more so than we
do you follow me that is the primary
difference in other words you are all
let us say more an immediate family of
energy not that anything else is not
included but by definition because we
are in a sense to you a alien we are
somewhat by definition slightly removed
from the immediacy of the intimacy
between you and your guide that are
attached to the Earth Energy you follow
me mhm that is the primary
difference so when people talk about
Spirit guides that they're in
communication with say one person talks
about their spirit guide and then
another person talks about a
communication they're having with an
extraterrestrial that comes
telepathically guys
is that the same it can be but it does
not have to be how do you know the
difference many times you will not need
to know but when you need to know you
will the energy can be different many
times the idea of the energy from a
guide will simply seem more familiar
more in a sense perhaps to put it one
way colloquially like
yourself whereas what you would call
extraterrestrial Energy may have
let us say a foreign
taste you follow me uhhuh yeah thank
you in a sense simply always trust that
you yourself are always a part of the
interaction every level of you and that
in a sense you are always your own best
guide all right
thank you
sh
yes and what
a thank
you now
wanders can simply be the idea of
individuals who are willing to be of
service in many different planes of
existence at one time or another so they
simply form whatever degree of
attachment they need to to any
particular plane of existence to be of
service in the way that they can best be
of service service but they maintain a
sort of let us say loose connection to
any one particular plane of existence a
prime activator is simply one who may
form a higher degree of Association and
degree of specificity with whatever it
is they are choosing to be of service in
and simply can allow themselves to let
us say obtain a multitude of experiences
in one plane of existence so as to
become very very familiar with that
plane of existence and carry a high
degree of differentiation and or
magnitude of impact within that
particular plane in the service that
they provide thank you very thank you
provide thank you very thank you
Shar sh yes how do you see uh the people
that we call mentally ill in our society
are they they are looking into different
realities that your Society has not
provided a structure for and has not
provided a means for them to communicate
back to you as valid realities so they
disconnect from your Society knowing
what they are experiencing is true and
just as real as anything in your reality
but they are not given an opportunity to
know that it is all right to have those
experiences and so are not allowed to
communicate them back into your society
as valid experiences so they
disconnect they seem to be in so much
pain many of them are they in pain some
of them guys for again they feel that
they are separated from a portion of
themselves in that way they have created
themselves to be in a closed feedback
loop and in a sense are cutting
themselves off from all that they do
instinctively know themselves to be
because they have chosen to project
themselves into a type of reality where
they are not let us say on certain
levels interacting with the society they
chose to be born into they are not being
allowed to be of service although that
is changing now in your Society you are
beginning to recognize that many of
these individuals are simply sensitive
to other levels of reality and you are
beginning to understand and that if you
can teach them in this way touch them in
this way with your love with your
unconditional love then you can allow
them to reform the connections they have
been taught to disconnect they have been
taught to break and in reforming those
connections you will find them to become
quite Lucid thank you thank you yes uh I
Lucid thank you thank you yes uh I
recently spent some time with uh
somebody in my family who I had to take
to a mental hospital
and spend a lot of time talking to him
all right
and there's a lot of similarity
between having
thoughts about what was going on to him
hearing voices hey um feeling delusional
seeing signs guys and in my own
experience I felt signs yes and I've
heard yes voes yes as more and more of
you will as you go further and further
into fourth density because you are
expanding your senses to include other
levels of consciousness and are becoming
sensitized to communication from
them when you allow yourself to know
that it is all right to do so then you
will not create a disconnection and
Encon yourself in a closed circuit as
these individuals have done simply
because they have never been taught how
to let it be all right to receive that
information and to let it be all right
to integrate that information into your
mainstream Society what if some of the things that
Society what if some of the things that
are being
received seem to me are so absurd absurd
well I can only give example go ahead uh
somebody Twitches their nose and it
means something to them what is so
absurd about that well when it's all
added up does that not mean something to
you means that they're twitching your
nose but do not facial expressions carry
meaning for you yes well then in the
proper context the twitching of a nose can
context the twitching of a nose can
carry volumes of information can it
not in the proper
context you see in the context that they
are perceiving it simply applies
perceiving it simply applies
but it is not the context of your mass
agreed upon reality so the majority of
individuals in your Society simply don't
know how to translate the
motion seeing a straw in a garbage can
means something yes because nothing is
an accident everything is synchronicity
everything is orchestrated when you are
functioning on the level where you
recognize everything as synchronicity
you will recognize the reasons for the
interactions of any symbol with any
other symbol
because of such an abundance of these
symbols and such an abundance of this
one means this this this the person is
unable to basically function yes without
the help or
assistance or uh the stoppage of his energy flow
or uh the stoppage of his energy flow
through medicine and I don't know if the
medicine helps or if
it detracts
because in one hand it stops the energy
from moving on the other hand it Prov
you do of course recognize that this
individual chose this reality yes all
right first and foremost therefore allow
yourself to reinforce that this was the
individual's choice this will
automatically radiate to them that you
sense that it was their self-empowerment
that created this and not a lack of
power you follow me allowing them to
know that you know it is their
self-empowerment that has created this
reality is what can assist them in
getting back in touch with the idea of
that power and allow them to relate to
all levels they experience so that they
will be able to be automatically
regulated in terms of their ability to
be of service let them know that what
they are experiencing can be of service
and then they will know that they are
desired that interaction with them is
desirable they will cease to believe
that they are cut off from their society
and then the regulation will be an
automatic thing how how does this
regulation become automatic if for
years uh when these things were
happening the automatic regulation
didn't function allow them in this way
to know that the present is not a result
of the past every moment is a new now
moment and what has gone on before has
absolutely nothing to do with what is
going on now until and unless an
individual chooses to believe that there
is a
connection so the automatic regulation
can come exactly now has nothing to do
with the fact that it has not been there
in the
past will The Taking of medicine harm
this hinder this from helping because it
depends upon the individual's belief
system as we perceive this particular
individual it will not not cause undo
harm for in this way this is an
opportunity for other individuals such
as yourself and the other individuals
that are connected to this particular
individual including individuals in what
you call the medical establishment upon
your planet to begin to learn that in
order to reach this person it is up to
them to meet this person halfway and not
expect the person to come all the way
back which is a giving up of what they
believe to be true for themselves
form a compromise meet them halfway
relax your hold upon the structure of
your reality enough to allow portions of
their reality to be equally valid to the
one you think is the only reality that
is
true meet these individuals halfway and
they will make perfect sense all
right how use your imagination
go into the dimension of your
imagination do not fear that you will
become crazy and you will not create the
Judgment that will disconnect you from
your Society you will learn how to be
crazy and still in touch thus when you
carry that knowledge with you to meet
them halfway you can share with them how
to be crazy and still be in touch
you follow me it is only fear in the
part of the mainstream of your
society that you will lose touch with
some sort of reality that is the only
one fundamental reality you believe to
be true that stops you from exploring
many other dimensions of yourself
because you think you can lose yourself
because you think there is only one
fundamental reality against which you
measure the validity of all other
realities but every reality is equally
valid and equally real what you are
experiencing now as your so-called solid
physical reality is a product of your
imagination but you give it solidity
because it serves your
purpose but this is a
dream it is no more and no less real
than any
experience that any individual
creates thank you
talking about the same subject how can
we deal with a person soal insane who
has been in a mental institution for 30
years and they don't talk you meet with
them and they don't talk how would you
communicate with them and how do you
meet them halfway ah there are still
many ways now do understand if any of
these individuals you are speaking of
has chosen unswervingly to live their
lives out in this fashion then live live
them out in that fashion they will and
you will not change their mind however
if you find that you as an individual
are attracted to assist these
individuals then it is as you say in
your civilization a good bet that they
are willing to let you into some degree
otherwise they simply would not have
attracted your
attention recognize therefore that you
can first of all trust if you believe
them quote unquote a hard nut to crack
you can simply allow the communication
to take place on whatever levels
represent let us say the least rarified
degree of physicality which is what you
call your dream reality so first and
foremost simply trust that you can begin
to communicate with them in your
dreams this bit by bit at whatever rate
they are comfortable in handling at
whatever rate you are comfortable in
handling begin to allow you to see in
the physical reality a leaking through
of the dream conversations you are
having and they will begin to be
responsive to you in the physical
reality and thus you will get the
feedback that lets you know that your
dream conversations are having an effect
use your imagination and simply trust
that if that is something that interests
you then when you are in your dream
state out of your body you can
communicate with the soul that they are
out of their body and strike up a
conversation what is it about me as a
natural person still want to communicate
with those people you wish to be of
assistance you wish to also learn about
what the dimensions they experience can
do for you and your understanding of
yourself so share they have something to
learn from you but you also have
something to learn from them it is
always a two-way
street and the time of communication
would be uh essentially
dependent on their desire to communicate
as much as my desire yes all we are
saying is that let us say you have a
larger frame of opportunities to
communicate outside of the physical
reality because outside of the physical
reality in your dream reality in your
astral State let us say there does not
have to be as rigidly held an idea as is
being experienced in the physical state
so you may find that they may be willing
to be very communicative in their astral
state but that whatever they are
experiencing in their phys physical
state they wish to continue because they
are learning something from
it in other words what you say I should
encourage the fact that I can
communicate with them telepathically and
let them be in their state essentially
yes and listen listen for the replies
that will come
telepathically learn perhaps to
communicate in other forms of
language other than physiological
first and foremost the primary
communication that they will receive
from you they will receive on whatever
level they need to will simply be your
willingness to Simply share with them
your unconditional love of them that
they will
receive all right they will receive it
unconditionally whatever I am just yes
allow it on your part to be
unconditional now they may choose to have conditions
now they may choose to have conditions
in how they receive it but receive it
they will on whatever level is necessary
to let them know that someone wishes to
communicate that can be the first
communication unconditional love that
lets them know someone is there then
they will open at whatever rate is
comfortable for them simply in your
unconditional love if it excites you be
standing by to receive whatever
communication they are willing to impart
than you may all take a short
break recognize that the idea of what
you call the break in this way for me is
the simple an instantaneous drawing
inward to the center of myself and then
an instantaneous reemergence for me no
time has passed you do not chat with
anyone from time to time that can occur
but very often I will simply go within
and reemerge when it is the timing to
begin again so you rest in essence that
way it's it is the equivalent of the
it's it is the equivalent of the
instantaneous reconnection with all the
levels of myself that constitutes the
idea of all the sleep that we
need thank you sure thanks can you
explain to me how work it is completely
self-imposed first of all
karma is your
cognition of the continuance of the
momentum of an idea that perhaps in a
sense as you say was begun in one life
and may need to be balanced and or
finalized in another life but it is
simply your recognition of the balancing
and or let us say completion of a
particular idea you have decided to
be it is completely self-imposed it is
not judgment
you follow me yeah does that clarify the
idea do you wish to explore it further
yes I would
um well it's really hard to do it is
hard to do without judging I want to get
into the subject but I have to separate
my own personal judgment but I'll go for
it anyway all right um if someone does
something in one lifetime that they see
as being negative or harmful to other
people or themselves like that
do they have to be reincarnated in
another lifetime and they do not have to be but
lifetime and they do not have to be but
you will simply find that because of the
energy associated with the limitations
you impose upon yourself in physical
reality you know that it may be the
allowance of let us say a very quick way
for in this way the degree of limitation
you experience in physical reality will
allow you to create those type of
balances perhaps more quickly in one
sense than you could in a non physical
reality because of the concentration of
effect that takes place in what you call
physical reality you follow me
yeah so you may decide to do it
physically simply because that will be
the way that will be let us say most
conducive to the very rapid assimilation
of the balance in the same way that you
created the
imbalance but it doesn't have to be that
way no it does not have to be if I
murder somebody One Life Time doesn't
mean that I'm might come back and be
murdered in another life that has
happened many times but again it can be
manifested in many different ways
perhaps you will simply be of assistance
to someone else who has had the same
experience and your willingness to
interact with that individual will then
be the balancing you require for then
you are giving yourself the opportunity
to see what it is like from the other
end of the emotional experience and
perhaps that is what to you will
constitute a balance not so much the
actual physiological Act of being
murdered though that has happened as
well can you give me any information
about my past lifetimes and any
debts why do you assume you have these
debts why do you assume it is a debt in
that way and not a
choice okay simply recognize that your
okay simply recognize that your
willingness to
know that you wish to create a balance
of the polarities within you
in and of
itself is the removal of any so-called
debt because you are now willing to be
Blended to be balanced to trust that the
life you are living is the life you
chose to live and simply willing to act
and function within service to all that
is the willingness to be of service in
that way and the willingness to
experience the life you chose to live is
the balancing of that idea and the
ceasing of the need to be reincarnated
again you follow
me thank you yes since you we talking
about reincarnation uh can you see a
glimpse to my past life experiences and
all right now listen every single one of
you many times we can share these ideas
with you but understand we are not
invalidating the exploration of your
past lives but in the
present you can know every single thing
you need to know to understand yourself
in the present from the present you do
not necessarily need to go exploring the
so-called past connections you have to
understand who and what you are in the
present again this exploration can be
valid but you will always observe the
idea within us that we are reluctant to
delineate this idea since you will
understand that the exploration of your
past lives is for the purpose of
bringing you back to the present anyway
and thus many times we simply will find
that while we will explore some of the
aspects with you from time to time that
you have
experience we will usually first of all
point out to you that the rigidized and
labeling of specifics in past lives will
have a tendency to focus you in the past
and not in the present where you
are we are not inclined to wish to focus
you in the past so it will be let us
say very very
very
irregular that we will simply dive into
the exploration of a past life now if
you right now in your Pres are
willing within your own imagination to
bring to the surface connections you
feel to be there then perhaps we can
explore some of those ideas with you for
then you will be specifically dealing
with the portions that you feel are
valid but do
understand you are creating the past
from the
present therefore the idea of any
specific past
life the one that is most valid to you
now will be the one that you simply will
be creating a connection to from now in
order to understand the idea that you
are now so if you are willing to bring
up what you feel to be a connection
perhaps we can explore it with you and
from time to time we can get a sensing
of the idea of areas that represent
strong energy transformations in your
so-called path again we will simply hesitate to
path again we will simply hesitate to
label these ideas because that will tend
to fix you in a path
instead of the
present now do you feel that there is
any specific reason for why you wish to
explore the idea of your past lives I am
bored some bored of the moment I bored
then you are not living in it right I
want to go back for the fast the future
and R around you are missing the point
if you are bored then you are not in the
moment I understand all right but
recognize in this way the idea of
seeking to create more excitement
somewhere else other than the moment
will always continue the creation of
boredom in your present
life for you will not be willing to
allow yourself to know that the past and
the future are in the
present recognize in this way you can
have a high degree of excitement in the
exploration of connections you have had
in the past and in the
future but do not forsake the present as
not being able to create the same level
of excitement as your exploration of the
past or the future because then you will
not be allowing your past and your
future to integrate into the present
granted that's exactly what I'm doing
this is exciting for me all right then
to what connections do you find yourself
attracted in the
past I'm not sure you are not sure you
have no sensation no feeling at all
about the idea of a past
life no associations no attractions no
draw not even the slightest inkling
where is your
imagination just maybe go 2,000 years
ago or and what happened then for you
what happened then what is the
experience not the number what is the
experience oh just another another
person just another oh that sounds very
exciting thought you said the idea of
the exploration of past lives was more
exciting where is that excitement you
are talking
about the moment and the past and the
future combination of all yes I was
wondering if you could see something
beyond what I see myself perhaps but
what purpose does it serve for us to
delineate that oh just to have fun oh
fun all right
here is some
[Music] fun you
fun you
were and very strongly so as with many
individuals in your Society at this time
what you call a Roman
Centurion very very
proper as you say in your present
colloquial Language by the book [Music]
[Music]
very steadfast very
loyal very strong in your
loyalty highly regarded by your fellow
centurions and respected by the populace
even though they feared you in a sense
but they knew that you
were very very in a sense Fair though
many times the the idea of your fairness
was to Simply follow the
law now whether the law was fair or not
that is another issue but you were fair
in your dispensation of the law and so
you were respected in that way at least
an individual coming under your
attention and your jurisdiction would at
least know that it was nothing
personal you follow me yes now that is
what we can share with you at this time
that's what I'm experiencing just now
thank you thank you
sure the place called
shamba s it is an another dimensional
frequency but yes it is an existence and
a level of
Consciousness what is some of their
main it is more the idea of a collection
of Consciousness that you would perceive
to be somewhat of a regulatory vibration
in a sense they feel they are
sending out caring energy to your planet
so as to allow individuals to be drawn
to their own inner Shining
Light do I have any connection to this
well since you are the one that
asked again any vibration you find
yourself attracted to anything that
comes into your Consciousness can be a
reflection of what for you in the moment
you have created that reflection is
valid if it continues to excite you follow it
if it continues to excite you follow it
if not do something else but for the
moment you asked it there was obviously
validity in it for you now you have
integrated whatever you have needed to
integrate it out of it you will continue
to do so in whatever way excites you and
attracts you okay F again yes this
you okay F again yes this
uh I have a incredible back ache what
back AE a disc is out a disc is is
slightly out all right now if this is a
result of karma how do I get rid of it
first of all recognize you do not get
rid of anything you integrate by
accepting everything into you now allow
me to ask you a question may I please
thank you how if you were to treat this as a
you how if you were to treat this as a
neutral
situation neutral
can you using your imagination perceive
in any way shape or form how the
situation could positively serve
you what comes into mind all the
different things you can think of
through which this can be viewed as a
positive opportunity uh to take things
slow and easy one what
else to uh breathe breathe into the
place where it hurts two what else
to allow whatever is
causing the pain to come out by doing
what just being open to it all right
being vulnerable is being open to all that is
vulnerable is being open to all that is
it is not weakness it is
strength being open to all that is is
being connected to all that is that is
Infinite Strength vulnerability is
Infinite Strength
now may I ask you another
question oh thank you thank you for
allowing me to have such a good
time in your
imagination if you felt that you were in
fact right now completely and fully
aligned and allowing any and all levels
of energy to move through you any and
all levels of
energy how would you feel about
that truly how would you feel about
feeling your own infinite
power as best I can imagine it hey I
think would be wonderful
why because then I would be totally in
touch with my own energy with everything
all the energy all right may I ask you
another question please oh thank you
very much in
your estimation in your terms of counting
estimation in your terms of counting
time when do you think that might
occur
roughly 10 years from now before
that yes or no before
that 10 years of your time before 10
years I would hope it to up up up up
up hope implies
despair now I am asking you to sense
within yourself when you know beyond a
shadow of a doubt that you will have
experienced enough time to experience
that level of
integration would 10 years in your
estimation be more than enough to yeah 6
years right now or you ready right now
are you sure yes all right then stand
up what is it that you
feel is the most exciting thing you
could be doing in your
life anything anything at all do you
have a preference yes no
maybe as long as there's variety oh
there will always be that then there's
no preference no
preference why not for all right then
you're saying that at any given moment
any that you are doing is just fine with
that you are doing is just fine with
you anything at all including the
situation with your back
[Music] uh when when it comes to the physical oh
uh when when it comes to the physical oh
here we
go every other level is fine as long as
it has nothing to do with this
level am I putting words in your mouth
or are you actually saying something
else uh do not let me put words in your
mouth what do you mean to
say that this back
a a I would feel much better if the pain
wasn't there I
see uh it would enable where would you
rather the pain
was somewhere somewhere out there out
there there is no out there
there you are a complete and total
Universe there is nothing outside maybe
we can transform the transform the pain
that is different
now pain is usually created because an
individual in your society and some
other societies is not willing to
receive a message from another portion
of themselves and so they create a
scenario that forces them to look at
something because they are not willing
to allow the message to come more easily
because they will not pay attention to
it when it comes more easily in your
imagination what do you imagine that
having the
pain tells you what type of message do
you think you are sending yourself that
you would have to create something like
that in order for you to pay
attention is there a message there that
you are willing to allow come to you in
some easier
way will you accept it if it comes in an
easier
way I would like to accept it all right
what do you imagine that the message
might be just take a while
again say the first thing that comes you
do not think about it to be more it does
not have to make sense to be
more to get it to get it to get it to be
more receptive receptive to what's going
on more aware more aware what is going
on what is it that you think you need to
be I don't know but if I would have been
more aware this pain would not be here
not so
necessarily perhaps the pain is there
only because you think you need to be
more aware of
something that isn't there to be aware
of
how does that idea strike
you time that all right would you like
to lie
down how are you doing uh it hurts but
is there purpose for standing up I don't
know you tell me I only made a
suggestion know how to do
it that all
right in this
way what is it that you feel could be
served by allowing
yourself to create a
situation wherein it stops you from
doing certain things and what are the
certain things you find that you cannot
do with this
situation oh I can't bend I can't run I
can't be active you cannot be active
in well running running uh physical
movement may I ask you a question yes
please since you do not have a
preference of any particular thing to do
where would you be running
to and why therefore you need to run
when exactly where you are you have said
is just fine with you uh there are times
during the day that I like to take a jog
oh uh stretches out it helps to move my
energy around it changes the gal all
right and um and I use it as a form of
meditation also all right and right now
because of this it's I can't do it all
right what has it allowed you to do
however uh well I swam today
oh all right how does that feel not as
good as running why not because
doesn't do the same thing why
not what is the difference between those
two ideas for
you running is a physical I mean it's a
certain motion it's a certain physical
oh are you telling me you actually have
a
preference yes oh so it does make a
difference to
you what you
do yes all right
then why not allow yourself to know that
you do in fact have preferences and the
idea of being so very spiritual does not
mean that you cannot prefer
something it does not mean that you have
to be Blas about
everything me being spiritual is not
necessarily just sitting around going oh
well if that happens that's all right
too it is the equalizing of everything
in that knowing it is all right but you
as a being are a different being are a
differentiated being by definition than
anyone else therefore by definition you
have your preferences it is all right to
have preferences they are not judgments
preferences they are not judgments
preferences is simply recognizing what
is true for you and acting on it a
judgment is the invalidation of what you
don't prefer but you can choose to prefer
prefer but you can choose to prefer
something without invalidating the
equality of what you don't
choose it is all right for you to have
preferences it is all right for you to
be more excited about one thing than
something else you do not have to feel
that that is a judgment excitement is
simply the recognition of your
preference of the path you chose to be
at any given
moment it is all right to prefer
something instead of something
else you follow
me now
perhaps you will now have a reason to
allow yourself to
move because you will now allow certain
ideas to be attracted into your life
that are reflective of the preferences
you truly do have that you have buried
within you
burying those preferences has simply
immobilized you because then you are not acting upon
you because then you are not acting upon
anything specific that represents the
path you chose to
be you are allowing the reality around
you the physical reality to blend to the
point of non-
cognition of
nondifferentiation you are immobilizing
your activities
you are an active being as a physical
being let yourself know that you have
preferences and that you can act upon
them and acting upon them is not a
judgment of what you do not act upon it
is simply the recognition of what is
true for
you now you also can Avail yourself of
the assistance of individuals around you
in the giving to you and the sharing of
their energy to allow you to heal
yourself in this way for there are many
individuals who have allowed themselves
to to be of service in ways that they
are excited about and prefer and some of
that is in your terms the manipulation
of your physical body you follow
me so allow these individuals to assist
you to assist
yourself and allow yourself to realign
so that the surge of energy that will
travel up and down your spine between
the Polar Opposites of your brain and
the base of your spine will then have a
reason for being there until you allow
it to have a reason for being there you
will allow there to be a
disconnection because it has no
purpose create a purpose for it create a
preference and know that you are excited
about acting upon it then you will
reconnect and plug yourself back into
the universe including the physical
one it seems
that by doing this you create
desire back inside of your what is wrong
with a
desire one becomes attached to
it
why if one is desirous and they want
something desire is not
covet do not confuse the J Desiring
something is not
coveting desire desire is
emotion energy
motion now you do not have to put
expectation on desire you do not have to
rigidized desire you do not have to
limited simply recognize that desire is
your conscious recognition again much
like the idea of
excitement it is much the same energy it
is what you recognize yourself to to
be are you attempting to become
egoless for as long as you are physical
you will always have an ego because an
ego's job fundamentally is to keep you
focused into the physical reality you
chose to be born into that is not to say
you have to allow negative ego to
control your actions but ego itself is
simply your ability to exist as a
physical being it is what keeps you
focused in physical reality there is
nothing negative about basic fundamental
ego it is simply a
conduit it keeps you where you have
chosen to be focused into the general
physical reality as long as you are physical in
reality as long as you are physical in
that way as long as you are a
personality construct you will always
have ego
ego
desire does not have to be expressed in
a negative way
simply do not limit it by imposing upon
it a particular way in which the desire
has to manifest do not make demands of
your desire but desire is emotion can be
love and can be the cognition of your
own excitement and vibratory preference
that is all you fire me in this way you
don't have to become attached to things
they do not have to become attached to
you you simply recognize that with your
desire you are allowing yourself to
become the dreams that you have you are
living your
dream desire is
dreaming it is the giving in to your
ecstasy which is your Birthright which
is what you are made of
has to be the idea of Envy of jealousy
none of that that is
Judgment was that sister
pleas question um many times in my life
um I can think of instances where I've
had very very strong heartfelt desire to
do something have certain relationship
with someone and for one reason or
another CU I usually act upon what
excites me I didn't to see in the long
run or viewing that situation from the
present now that it would not have been
good for me to have followed that
particular thing that excited me it
would not have been but understand from
the point of view in a sense that you
are looking from now there is no way for
you to know that
because you are not in the
experience you are looking at it from a
perspective of where you are now and
where you are now doesn't relate to
where you were then so it may seem as if
it would not have served you but it may
have been totally different had you
simply done
it you follow me and how that if you're
excited or you felt a very strong desire
to get to know someone let's say or
spend time with someone say hello
right but again allow yourself to make
the connection or allow the connection
to happen and then simply pay attention
to the way the connection does unfold do
not put demands upon how you think it
should let the relationship be what it
is not what you think it should
be uhhuh than you
are you pronoun all right yes um are you
you pronoun all right yes um are you
familiar with the planet reticulum oh
yes do the reticulum assist other uh
beings in their work regarding this
planet yes of late yes how do you know
in many different ways some of it has
been through some
interaction with members of your Society
so that there could be more balance more
understanding coming into access coming
into contact with your own inner fears
and thus the assistance by them of you
being willing to allow them to assist
you in balancing certain of those ideas
and polarities within you are they
fourth density beings in a sense yes or
are they more physical or fourth density
does not mean non-physical non-physical
necessarily um
um are
they do they have their separate
activities for their own interest as oh
yes oh yes oh yes oh yes so do we so
does everyone in a sense so they are not
Android beings of the new spere there
are Androids but their population in
general is not
no they are living breathing beings as
are you so can speak
thank
you guys say where are they located that
is the name you have given to the
constellation Zeta reticul find it in
your charts yes uh would you comment on
how in what way we exemplify the fears
of the Soviet
people in this way you will find that
you are their fears of individuality and
they are your fears of
collectivity that is it in
general does that answer your
question um I don't I don't perceive
why individuality would be something to
be afraid of to
them that is because you are in the
society that thinks that that is the way
to live yeah why do you put perceive
that the collectivity is fearful to you
and your
Society from their point of view the
idea of individuality is in a sense
Anarchy to you the idea of collectivity
in that way is domination
right but you are the polarities of Your
World find the commonality and blend and
then you will have a society that is is
a total Collective acting together as
individuals synchronistically right I've got that
synchronistically right I've got that
picture nice thank you live it and you
will make a
difference thanks sure nice have you
heard about theace child
conert Define um where there are like
several like 20 or 30 Soviet children
American children a Soviet band and Stu
like that they're they're touring all
over and all over the United stes
and will how do you see that that as one
will how do you see that that as one
method of allowing yourself to recognize
the commonality and equality that you
can share and one step closer to your
willingness to know that you can
interact as equals respecting the
differences within each other that
respect is what will remove all the
negative effects of those
differences that's the goal of it
yes sure is your reality thank you for
po creating it yes um on on the subject
of international relations it see it
appears to me that Gorbachev and some
other wrers be putting out a lot of
Peace fielders and yet there is a lot in
our society that wants to put that down
is always a putting down of that energy
and yet I see to sense that there is a
lot of genu about that you feel your
point of view about that
yes recognize again you as two nations
are simply pouting around each other one
takes the initiative the other takes the
defense one takes the defense and
initiative the other respond likewise
you are simply going back and forth
exemplifying the polarities in this way
without much of the idea of what you
call rationality but simply in this sense it
rationality but simply in this sense it
is an opportunity for blending at
whatever rate you allow yourselves to
feel as a comfortable rate for do
recognize once again that you and them
you are you are your governments you are
your governments you allow the
structures to exist as they exist be
willing to take responsibility in that
sense and know that you do not need the
government to protect you but allow them
to serve you then communication will be
open all right it is up to
you thank you thank you sh yes um I'm
working with someone who had a cold
yesterday and I was
thinking I guess what came to mind for
me was to surround them with green light
healing light but I really I wanted to
know what the effectiveness the
effectiveness will be according to the
agreement you have made with that
individual to be the one that they
attracted to them to do
that M okay it is always two
ways it is up to them to also decide the
effectiveness okay now let's say it to
myself it's the degree that I believe in
that being effective but you cannot
change someone else no let's say it's
myself I'm the one that and I envision
myself surrounding the degree that it's
effective is the degree that I believe
it's effective yes plain and simple yeah
thank you
sure one moment it is also the degree to
which you are willing to understand the
reason for why you created the scenario
in the first place although that does
not necessarily mean you have to be
consciously analytically aware of the
reasons but just be willing to take
responsibility for the creation evolving
whether it's myself or somebody else for
yourself well my yes thank you than uh
several of your counterparts have been
predicting a lot of earthquake activity
for us between now and like the end of
the year we ourselves have also talked
about some of that activity however one
more time there is no such thing as a
prediction of the future there is only
the sensing of the energy that exists
that has the highest degree of problem
probable realization at the time the
prediction is made it can change and
many times the prediction quote unquote
is the opportunity for you to recognize
that you prefer something else and to
change it you follow me yes I do so while there
it you follow me yes I do so while there
is a high degree of probability in that
sense you will find that there is
another possibility within your
localized area within the next 48 hours
to 72 hours
but again some of this energy has
already been transformed many times by
your Consciousness simply by your
willingness to understand you can
rechannel the energy in different ways
and that you do not necessarily have to
believe that you need such a shaking up
in order to be
awake that you are already awake and in
control of the situation so things will
regulate themselves and fall into place
themselves and fall into place
peacefully you follow me yes I do it is
not that the energy is not there it is
simply that it is your opportunity to do
with it what you
prefer very good than you
B if we cannot fori the future and how
can we as you said just
said do it is not a prediction of the
future it is a sensing of the the energy
at the present that has the highest
degree of momentum behind it if that
momentum and that level of energy
doesn't change then that sensed
situation will become material but that
is not predicting the future it is
predicting what is the most likely
reality that has the most degree of
energy behind it now at the time the
prediction is made if that energy
changes then no such prediction comes to
pass you follow me but you are not reaching
you follow me but you are not reaching
into the future to pick up on the idea
you are sensing only the present because
the present is the only reality that
actually exists essentially what you're
saying we have no power about what's
going to happen you are misunderstanding
me
completely I am saying you have absolute
and utter and complete control over the
idea because everything is right with
you right here and now
and you are sensing the energy that has
a great deal of momentum behind it if
you do not prefer that idea to have a
great deal of momentum behind it then
the sensing of the prediction is your
opportunity to change the energy if you
don't prefer it you have all the power
in the World to Change
it the idea as your society believes
predictions to be is what takes the
power away from you thinking that you
are predicting some so-called future
that you cannot avoid that is out there
Beyond you somewhere doing something
that is coming closer and closer and
closer that you cannot get away from
that is the removal of your power but
knowing that all events are in the
present where you exist is what gives
you the power to change them if you
don't prefer them you follow me well I
hear the con in what you're saying you
are simply assuming that the future is
some something that has validity unto
itself other than what you give
it the future and the past is an
illusion everything exists now and you
can change what you manifest in your now
moment based upon what you believe is
possible and what you prefer to be the
reality but for me right now is an
illusion also since by the time I the
experiences that you are socalled
surrounding yourself with to represent
the now are an illusion but the now is
not an illusion because you know you
exist you do know you exist do you not
maybe maybe all right if you are not
sure there is one very quick way to be
sure you exist well essentially I should
not say maybe I know it is then it is
not yes and no one more time one more
time do you exist or not yes and no how
can it be no if it was no you would not
have the ability to say yes and no by
the time by the time I said yes I have
changed to the now already but it is
still always now is it
not that's the turn of now yeah it is
always now
always true then you always exist in the
now always in the now we are not saying
that this now is the same now and that
the last now is the same now that this
now is but it is still now no matter
what type of a now it is it is still now
yes it's an illusion since it's changing
all the time we are not saying the
definition of the now doesn't change but
that definition the illusion of what the
now is is doesn't change the fact that
now is still now you follow me I see
what you're saying all right then simply
understand no matter what the definition
of the illusion it is still always being
experienced and only ever can be
experienced now period so all of the Power of all of
now period so all of the Power of all of
the Illusions all of the generation of
all of the Illusions are always with you
in whatever now you happen to be in and
are never anywhere else but the now you
happen to be in at any given now
moment there was one disagreement
between what you're saying and my
concept everything is the fact that I am
not in control are while you say I'm in
control that's the big difference
between our all right then in your
reality if you do not believe you are in
control then in a sense
it is quote unquote pointless you may
simply do whatever you wish to do but
know at the same time that if you are
not in control of it anything at all
anything at all can happen and you have
no control over it nor are you
responsible nor do you have anything to
do in playing a part in having that in
your life so there is in your life no
continuity no sense no connection on any
level except for one thing the
experience but the experience erience if
you do not control it in that way cannot
be applied to any other level so you
cannot grow The Experience if you are
not in control of your continuity simply
is a random experience that does not
relate to any other experience so you
cannot form a collection of experiences
that lets you think you are growing what
do you mean by growing if I am
everything the whole universe itself how
can I grow you can by having created
yourself to be in the illusion of
Separation allow yourself to remember
more of of who you are that is growing
from your point of view in this physical
reality now we understand that there may
not be a terminology that let us say
accurately translates into your language
that represents what growing May mean to
a being on a level where it does in fact
recognize that it is all that is but
that does not mean it is
static it has its own version of the
idea of recognizing that even even
though it is always now creation is
still and always will be
unfolding I recognize that in your
language it seems to be a dichotomy
seems to be a contradiction and seems to
be a paradox but that's the way it
[Music] is okay that is when you know that when
is okay that is when you know that when
you are experiencing Paradox that is
when you know you are standing in the
center of yourself because Paradox is
dichotomy that has to come from a Common
Center because you are at the center of
all polarity that you
experience you you thank you how
expanded are the
um entities that are born
as children in your Society well the
adults like when they first come into
there is some
acclimatization some what you would call
time in order for them to acclimate to
our specific methodology of expression
but generally speaking by the time that
you would call 3 years of age they are
on their
own right as expanded as you are in their
right as expanded as you are in their
own way in right in their own unique way
I see whatever definition they have
created themselves to be they are as
completely expanded into that definition
as anyone else is expanded into their
own and then it's just a matter of
physically maturing a bit do some degree
I there is that representation in our
society to some
degree and um are they fully
communicating with the adults
telepathically oh that is even before I
know I know but even when they com yes
yes there is some degree some degree of
disorientation but it does not last very
long usually no more than what you would
call three months
but there is still some understanding of
the communication at least where
necessary before we continue allow me to
also remind
you that the idea of existence and the
idea of nonexistence in your Society has
taken on a belief system and or equality
that makes you think that existence
could possibly become non-existent but
it can't
in this way recognize that all of
existence and all of nonexistence are
both real right now one does not become
the other you simply do not have an
experience of all of the non-existence
that is there because by definition it
doesn't exist therefore you can't have
an experience of all of the
non-existence that is right alongside
all of the existence of which you do
have an experience of one does not
become the other what exists will exist
forever what does not exist will not
exist forever they are already both real one
forever they are already both real one
does not become the
other continue all right I I have something to
continue all right I I have something to
share although you you threw a curve at
me by saying which you just
did um let me go on with the sharing all
um let me go on with the sharing all
right by all me and I'll take on the
curve oh right um you talked about um
weather and I there's something
wonderful that I have experienced along
that line that I just would like to tell
people oh what uh I was going through a
period of extreme I I can say is is
within tutorship and things uh ideas were
tutorship and things uh ideas were
coming out to try to manifest
dominion and um
what tantalized me one day was to
attempt Dominion of weather and this was
a period when we were having nothing but
storms constantly rainfalls day after
day after day that we're creating floods
yes okay and in our area we have a lot
of slide now um one day I had to go out
and do the laundry we don't have
facilities in the house and I normally
left freely feeling freely and got into
my car and realized that I was driving
in a blinding rain I had no umbrella I
was going to transfer clothes in the
mess and I had to go back and get an
umbrella and instantly as I had that
idea came the challenge do you need an
umbrella or are you going to accept the
picture of
discomfort are you going to mean what
you want to learn Dominion I said no I
don't accept this I want this to
disappear it isn't right
and I forgot about it and I kept driving
and parked the car and got out and got
my clothes and suddenly it wasn't until
I was crossing the parking lot that I
felt this intense sun burning down on my
back and I looked up and this was no
longer a horrendously overcast and and
rainy day is a whole Dome the whole sky
was blue there was not a cloud except
all around
360° little fleecy that looked like
mashed potatoes goes on a plate that
comes around your steak you know in a
platter all right and it
was it was I realized suddenly that was
the proof we have the Dominion in the
moment for when it's constructive and
good for the better of something we
simply decree it and it shall come to
pass like the Bible says in this way
what you are doing is simply
experiencing yourself and all the
situations around you as one event as
synchronicity itself it is not so much
literal although this does have validity within
although this does have validity within
certain electromagnetics it is not so
much literally that you are doing
something to have dominion over the idea
like the expression of energy from what
you would call a wizard but the idea is
that you are always in perfect step in
perfect timing and it was a recognition
that you placed yourself exactly when
and where you needed to and allow the
reality around you to reflect your now
realized conscious recognition of your
perfectly placed
timing everything is
synchronicity thank you for your
sharing once again every individual
makes a difference thank
you um I was wondered to talk a little
bit about the consciousness of animals
or they are are extensions and
reflections of your own Consciousness in
many ways in this sense they are here to
guide and assist you through their
unconditional love for you and they are
in this way once again primary
extensions of what you shall call the
oversold consciousness of your entire
civilization many times they will take
upon themselves ideas and or
physiological scenarios so that they can
reflect to you the ideas you are
exploring without you having to become
physiologically incapacitated during the
exploration also they will reflect your
demean ERS and your ideas your emotional
attitudes your understandings your
symbolic interpretations of the many
different levels of consciousness you
have created yourselves to be in this
sense therefore simply in the general
sense of things to give you an idea by
analogy we will share with you one more
time the simple statement in this sense
that the animals upon your world are
still mostly territorial because you
are in this sense also
recognize once again that the idea of
animal Consciousness extends to almost
all expressions of the idea you
experience upon your world with the
exception of your C in that way and with
the exception of one other race of
beings upon your planet what you call
the satation dolphin and
whale there are to us two alien species
upon your world land human water human
or if you wish water satation land
satation but animal Consciousness is there to
but animal Consciousness is there to
assist to reflect as a guide communicate
with them by simply returning the
unconditional love and allowing yourself
to take responsibility for in this way
what they are so lovingly willing to
show you at this time we will extend to you
you at this time we will extend to you
once again our appreciation for allowing
us to experience the gift that you are
individually and collectively for in the
experiencing of the unique facets of all
that is that you are you allow us to
expand our awareness of all the
different ways that all that this has of
manifesting itself within the
creation we thank you for the sharing
exciting dream lives and life dreams to
you they are all one we bid you a fond
and unconditionally loving good night