Inter IDE As You have
IDE As You have
cre be As As As have CH The Idea thei
use In You that As You
Are you not be aware that there are
other Room to be in the Idea Of The Room
What you call the wall given
in This Way recn The IDE We Are U analy
for Is that your physiological Real you have have
Just As Walls fling This many
times You will find your assuming based
upon What you believe to be about Real
based upon What have been From
Generation to Generation for
many times IDE phys comprises only the
Room you  are familiar with and that you
are not necessarily aware that there is
anything be that particular even though
it even Be a Part of the house in Are
you in This Way therefore When you
finally allow Yourself The notion that
you EX A House of Rooms and
theil being able to find and Discover
Many More of those others which have
T thousands of years you are Still to
find From Time to Time even exploration
Of The New IDE that there May be other
Rooms you May Only have The Tools you have been
used to using at Hand to Give
Yourself The Opportunity  to even know in
This Way recognize The
measurements and the exploration  that
you will undertake many
times Carry with it certain not notion
preconceived ideas based upon US Tools
and are exp New use Tools are
US to that Old ideas
you have Living to Explore to you that
is new rather allowing you to know that There are
New Tools with which you can
relate More easily to the New situation
to the New Room You are exploring in
This Way You will find that as we have
discussed many times IDE have to for that
Room It is in All Reality the
moment you Con see that there is Another
room in All Reality therefore You are  in
that other room for in This Way You Look
at it This Way The Perspective that you
know there is Another room in a Sense
means that you must of the to be
aware there is
Another Room you must already
be in that other Room And you will
restrict Yourself to using the Old Ways
of Looking at by assuming that all you
Have given Yourself is a Window From The
Room You are in Looking Into The Room
you want to be in Still assuming that
you are in the Room you do not want to be
in Looking through A window
Idea Is that Once you  are aware there is
Another Room you must by Definition be
Looking Back  upon The Room you used to be in
From the Perspective of being in that
New Room Because to be aware that
there is something else is to actually
be That's something else in This Way
This is a Simple cogn it May Sound
mysterious at first there May not be an
apparent Connection to you
butle allow to
you to physic Reality is a product of
vibratory frequency less More than any Reality you
frequency less More than any Reality you
Experience in This Way What you normally
call your physiological Reality is a
product of your Imagination is in a
Sense very literally A Dream But It  is
the Dream It is the portion of your
dimension of Imagination that you have
decided to enhance with the Quality you have discovered that
you Call
Solid that
Only that One variable Over vibration
equ that creates This physical Reality
to seem More Real than anything else you
can imag But This is a product of your
Imagination Just like anything you have
Ever conceived of in your Imagination As A
probable or possible Reality you
decide des to Experience It is Up to you
to understand that you are creating Real
From vibrational frequency and in that
any Reality you have Ever  expen that
seems so very Sol  to you has Only Ever
been The product of your belief that that Reality
is More Solid than anything
else you have Ever conceived of that is
What Makes it Solid that is What Makes
it so It is the Only Thing that creates
A difference between What you Call
materiality and the rest of your
Imagination dimension in This Way All
matter of frequency All matter
What you are tuned into you have to be
on the wav you have to be in that
Reality in Order to perceive of that
transmission of that Information
This Idea Around you can
understand that anything you do  perce
anything you Desire to Because you are
conceiving are are
are are
Only missing From equ that you do not
Believe conception is As being that
New Person All you Need to do at that
moment in having the conception knowing
that even have The conception is already being the
Idea you Think you are being the Idea you
Think you have to something to be recn are
that vibration have that
conception all you to do Like You Know having
The conception Is The Same As
being that Idea As Soon As You Are
willing to Express that degree of
conviction that degree Of certainty The
Same degree of certain you  have about
anything else you take for granted As
being Real in your Real to For
You are you all following
in This Way The Idea
Simply that in
Idea that Simply Ace ure Idea
Think
toch rather conce you are the Idea All is you
rather conce you are the Idea All is you
toes is you to Like You are the Idea you have
Now conceived Yourself to be
you remember N german Girl was abouts AG
Yeah She called Me From London today and
She Wanted me to Ask you about something
she Want to know if you had any inform
or knew anything About A Fire ceremony
something that she  about called
agra has been done on Many other
planets Fire
in This Way You will find your Planet
interpretation of Energy ceremony so to
Speak that does occur in Many different
Levels of consciousness Simply find that If It
is a vibration If It is a Tool If It is a
methodology If It is a ritual
that appeals to an individual then
obviously It is striking a Cord with
that individual and Will Lead them to
More of themselves Every ritual Every
methodology Every interaction Every undertaking Every relationship Every situation imation your Curiosity your excitement
Lead you only to the ideas that
represent The service  to you of the path
you chose to be If  It is something that
intri that indiv then participate Up to
the Point that that indiv finds they are
No longer inted and ches their Mind and
then
Fire in the
C recn The Idea pam structur does Act As
A Magnetic Lens and focuses the fire so
to Speak of electromagnetic Light ener being and
allou All are that ISIC Inter
Stronger again The Idea of ​​strength is
Inn that vulnerability is not weakness
vulnerability is being Open to All That is
being Open to All That is being
connected to All That Con
Trust and Live Now that is How thank
you have a good
time
Andy need Who
Says can Come
once again if you are acting like
The Idea that excites you The Most then
If those symbols Need to be In Your Life they Will
Be Because Every Idea is
Always supported automatically by all the
necessary symbols to allow that Idea to
continue to manifest in Creation if
you find Yourself needing The Land truly
needing The Land even though you May
Think you need it you May not But if you truly
need the Land it Will Be there
Because Everything that needs to  be
there to support The IDE You Are willing others
that will be the way so Simply
assume that Whatever is necessary Will Come to
you in the easiest fion
therefore do not Put an expectation upon
it that May represent an actually More
difficult Way For The situation to occur
by assuming that If Money is not won happy you are Come
is the Only I will Let happen Is only it Will
Be For All others which situation
could basically Just upon your
excitement and Trust that Every Idea
Comes with all the ingi necessary For The
manifestation of thata One More
Quick One I created A situation Where I
did
own What you are doing isa your exp your and
Your things yourself fre fre
can any thank [music]
[music]
you One Thing that happen Over the
years does My There
are a lot answ Pain that
expen and at the
moment not sure of What to do at this is
there anything in particular you feel
you Need to say
to
anyone No well realized that Over the
Past Few months I have struggled a lot [music ]
you mean you do not Trust that Whatever
maned SIT The Area is
Area is
some to me mean As rel other
People some ver and are you Taking
judgments upon Yourself  For The things
you are saying Yes That's Why  I'm saying
What I'm saying well Why are you
choosing to Judge
Yourself well Because at this Point I
want all right What is Going
on I find Myself noting to be Around
other People Because I tend to want to Give
them My
answers uh things have worked Very well
for me and I've gained a lot grown a lot
and I'm having a Conflict with Myself
Because there's a tendency to want to talk
to other People and Give them answers
I don't seem to be able to You Me you do
n't Look  at As aing
equ are you assuming is Nothing they can teach you they
Are Not equ teachers that you
Think that you are aach you
aach you
canare You are
From that you Think you are them The
Answer you
are equ And you nothing to Learn
From that like It's More from a View of
wanting to Just be with whoever and not all not all
right
there me that tendency is not a tendency It
is a Choice
by saying It is a tendency you are implying
that Bey that is outs of your
Choice like it continues with you or
Without You a tendency
But usually only the you have on
something like that that creates  The
Illusion of a tendency isoc
So You Are on that is all yous like
tly again that form comm do
Let them Simply see What you believe
that does not mean you cannot say
something When you feel like it But recognize
in This Way You can also
Simply do What you are doing and If they
choose to recognize in your actions that there is also do
them anw are Answer Enough I
Enough I
just that View has been hummed
to
some Leader all right But again understand
you can Create
As other AS Who
you are with
inteen Take
Care I Present
are Var  Bugs inss ants that has some The
places that I
Work They have somehow Come up with Bugs
And I have acquire This like for inss
and All Living things and having Another
conf all in This you May All your to Nature
Another Call calhan
Water intru cst ander
into can generate electromagnetic Field all the
all the
that they are hes
that May not Go with with
This Non use your owner and and
toit own are [laughter]
[laughter]
in This again you can Create harm
symbios As A PR
during Up pals After
The I was up
inwi and the Earth SH My Camper  me up
and the Earth SH My Camper  me up
and that happen I s a and
be and to Help Help enlighten
The People As to
happen can take AS
spre being of and love that to to in
Civilization ACC What excit and be
Example for others in that Way To choose
The Same vibration so they can Take That
ener that
would crust of Earth and CH through chra
also Whatever vibra that [music ]
]
with Her eyes
for having her has Double
Vision and and they cannot there's A pressure
and and they cannot there's A pressure
on Her eyes and the doctors Haven been
able to find
anything to Stop It except Now
Maybe tumor in the Brain or something And I
tumor in the Brain or something And I
was and really uncomfortable Is there
anything I was wondering why could believe SY May be
May be
Strong and May require in This Way
interaction with your Medical Person
that May be the Only Will allow herself
to Feel that something can be done that
May The Only Will allow herself to Cure
herself however you can imation [music] comm you others [music others [music
]
can
that any other
Man do AG mainer ind
andes like could you speak A
of Dreams which cemon Help
How Does blingos of Many different
Many different
cultures and assisting indiv to
understand How  they can Blend The philos
of the and Present something they can
all in Society
to does C [music]
with People Okay I have a dog and
afflicted with
allting with Another Human beses
Yourself are you to be about something and
it Will not
be it Will Be
understand your anals are reflections
and many times Take upon themselves The
manifestations of your anxiety so that
you do not have to Experience them
physically Relax Live
Relax Live
Now be in the moment that is the way  to
accelerate All des
again and that you are taking you
can Man own
there you have
that ining overy
overy
nervous and will Because EX
Because EX
and This is Where The Internal World
stops on the Border you call your Skin
those jgs Will Turn The Skin into ause
then You will know Where One begins And
The other ocus
in
thate that you Think you need As ail As A prot From the
outs Let Inn isort
again to know that you are
Many of you are going to that you are chn
What that are are Moving Back
Moving Back
are  which mum
mum
Will As The entire IDE catches Up Mon Present
Mon Present
Year of the Idea  11th 12th and First
month of your New
Year When there will be
acceleration towards the Idea of ​​the
Spring of Year
1987 and then the cation in a Mass
Energy Gate of
transformation on S
77 You are in trans7 40 40
Days you are
and 7747 7787 Cure
7787 Cure
aware are
Yes thank you One
More Personal Personal
intal [music]
[music]
challenges are that do
What Does Body to
you it varies
[music] like
like
All have you Yourself
Yourself
V is something you  are forcing on
Yourself No you do not have anything El No attempt
For a while Clear C
Trans How is your IDE Do
You Feel You Need
Order you have to have What expect to be
a Complete and Total Picture of What that
Thing is before You will Take A
Step before You will Trust that anything
in your Reality that is the Thing that excites
you The Most that you can Act
upon is the Thing that Will Lead you to
the nextel need
Whatever you can I Yes
Right Now would not One The EX
things in Life Trust
and make you not have to be consciously
be consciously
analytically aware of What that  is Where
coming From it Will Be there When You make
But that is Why You Feel The Need For
so much intimate you you May
you May
I Ask you please you please
Believe
In do not Fight Fight
First On Mat
Mat
in As do serv serv
in We Are being serv
to raer being serv
One you would Call A
there commun
US PR
to Over agre our own univ
Ways IDE are
Self ener Time Car IDE of No can can
IDE
froma Blend po formance between The
negative and positive so that Now at
this Present time  you can also
understand there is also Light in the
oran Systems Because you individuals that are connected
to that System have
begun to Learn to assimilate the
negative with posi and sending Back to
Home they can ass that IDE than you you things
things
any When are Wonderful things
Thing Taking on Color andain The All I
Real that coling My
Life than You and Another Thing I My
Skin was Breaking Out really Bad and
then One day I looked in the Mirror And I
went Oh That's Right Breaking Out I Great so
Last We Over the
We exp and
and
Yes happened was I
But you are acting It Out  Yeah exactly
and One
day I realized that What it occurs Part
of it was
Just The realization of
neutrality More than Ever Real Yes
was very very nice
and And I told My husband
After and was interesting Thing that
happened Because He He
got very upset
He got very
upset So You immediately attracted an
Opportunity tode you tru in neutral or
not That's and That's exactly What
happened so Beautiful I did
not I had
More Thank youk you Thank you and [music and [music
]
also and ious are curious so Are
so Are
You again understand you only
attract  IDE
No More need
in the Give Con you More commun
commun
thek you that is you BL are are
you has
And I have was
have was
All you
know soch All like got my
so I just
know Do you have
either an individual Who functions
As
such I have a
Yeah And I have
Someone How you feel for
indiv the one The
One
[music] have been occ Strong How
How Far Do you have are have are
[music]
Think In the
way that you find you do that even
though
you When May  I Ask you do not have to
Answer Do you  Think you will be willing to
Express conv
there Area Here lear to EX
all right May I Ask you a question you
that Will Be before
Year Mon than
you perhaps by that you will also REM
syy [music]
eas is it
smoother It's Only easier Yeah It is easier
ando Just
not Why are you Here Asking
these actually This I didn't realize What an are This was This Come
about As a
result of ours
and that creates More separat moreat
More to Experience allas
All Right  You May
forgive Yourself and them by recognizing
there is nothing to forgive
and in This Way Simply
know that From Past associations Present Someone PR More
callx Brothers and
Sisters Now
Lives interf with and Now Now
istion Now is Living Your Life As You
Feel with your integrity in
to standing your
Ground knowing that It is the Ground All for [music] will eny
id7 Do you Follow
Up What Call A
Space that is Now in the of goverment
goverment
7787 Will Be a For The  culmination of
the orbits of Time that was necessary for
orbits of Time that was necessary for
you to get used to the Idea are
Will to EX
are gover
and To exp and [music]
you are your militia you are your gover comm Open is More
EX mak ass over But in This comm vition
allou can in
own know that they are playing their
Part The they chose to you chose
To and All Will Be seen
and Sense of is aud
separation Is only
jud find and Live and
Experience All
connections are with that you will
Feel Chic that May you Every indiv [music] [music]
SH [music]
All Us
it was sign me that I One that had
mentioned a lot of things
that I Don't particular Care to get into
But it was a form Letter Pretty much
[music] and You Know I was I was Real
and You Know I was I was Real
disappointed and about 10 Days two weeks
After that More like
that More like
ied Another Letter
From which was Reply to Another Series
of letters that I had sent Out and This
One was personally typed and the
signature was in
Ink The signature itself was in Ink  And
I thought it was kind of interesting in As
much things that
mention I Put a lot of Myself On terms What I was I in to
any I got a Two
Letter you you
forn The Idea you can continue
The First Person i spoke to We had a
very pleasant conversation and heed that
his Boss would say No He did and then i
tried the Next newspaper and approach it
More from a Science fiction in Because
The man any metaphysic sugg
I Write Up The whole and mail it
inure ED and ied to Open Up to everyone
Here Great exercise of summing up and
writing their Experience of you in  a Way
that SS inri for Someone else How about
their experiences of
themselves also it seems Like L IDE are
IDE are
Close are
Open comm and are you for
As Might Di
and are in
a Sense It is basically
fundamentally the
recognition of the
vibratory patterns that represent The
Mass conscious
agreements that have been Made regarding
What you
believe inal and the knowledge of momentum
Because the entire IDE of univers
an exion of you any TH you
include The aspects that The pors of
Yourself You insc Believe because VI VI
Con
other others  UN
be intui and interaction is on  and
agreement that Made between indiv inting
and some are
always in terms of What indiv Yes more [laughter ] always the
always the
Idea and TR and do What is [music]
no no no no no
that manif in Life is a you chose are
interruption [ music] so
So if you know you are
posi intr even Experience
rine SY are do
Because that
Always areed that is Enough S [music] and and
now you things
The Idea What seems to the syb Over  and
Over again again
neal X
neal No and Trust No and
Trust than you
people I had Experience years AG I
was
And The First Time in 35 years that I've
been Up On A doing anything with
television I Start slipping Off the
ladder ladder Now I finally Found Myself on the
ladder Now I finally Found Myself on the
roof which has A pitch 15 de Now As I
Start sliding backward I figure I have to
Do something Now to save
Myself I Around and IC The Back of the
bung Little bu you know
and All I S Great on
Great on
my And I was  Out
May spiritually I don't
Out And The First Thing I knew I  was
dep in an Area about 20 feet Long and
aot And The First Thing I know that My
Brother Came around the Side Back The
House The and he gave me his Hand and
lifted Me Up I  got Nothing of
It But a little later I Start reflecting What has
happened Here Hand on my Back
and All of a sudden I Myself on my Back
in that Small Area 20 by A How could that
possibly be I should have been Dead
Because there was a BL BL Wall
Block feet High and
about in Why did I not Hit that cement Because
in Why did I not Hit that cement Because
obviously you should have not it What Hander Man Man
Con and
it was your
AC Out Of your desperation Out Great
need and
Desire forming conne Another of
All them to Come through that
and Man inic
inic
physic physical IDE
they Need to Trans
are and always
the are of cre
and
Always You own cre
form manifestation physic Reality to
that and All All others of
consciousness that love you
unconditionally to also ass inting you
formal manifestation you could to you
could US thinkers Always have you are
GR there One
He Came Back
From anding like a
War about 15 years
Old everybody hears me Came
Back and like I Said He Start Speaking
like a do Law and All his immediate
People in that Area
ased  Ay mentally [ __ ] Why is he
Speaking  like a la Because he Lives in the But
anyway there was
parents unen I don't my
my
father there and there was a More
courageous man in all the world My He Fe Nothing
He
was to give
up Money Put you
know you He I
got it Right Here you know But
He would Shot there no takers I mean
This is the kind of man He was he Fe
Nothing Nobody Right any He was there
and he Saw This happening he could
Believe It and later When He Came to
Country later 18
He was Telling me about  The
incident And I could Believe So what
they did in Fin is
called He gather ands backing
All and When You are centered in the
moment you are connected to All Levels
of existence and are able to communicate
with any level of consciousness physical
and Non physical
As was that by choosing to be
Born As What you Call [ __ ] he
ensured that that Life would Give Him
The Focus to have ty worries of that
would distract Him From the ability to communicate spe
was needed to so Little pered The
service that was in his Life and could
Get
you are All Spirit  in One form He
All youk you for your  Sharing
Is there any relation that talking
about to some degree Yes Now understand
It is Up to you to determine How You
Wish to interpret that Energy What Idea
and What Reality you Think you are All
about that determines whether you
Experience such A Shift In A positive
and or negative Way Many of the ideas
can be Taken Simply to mean electromagnetic
shifts they do not have to
be physiological ships there Will Be
some physiological ships in isolated
places Around your Planet you do not
have to be there
Over Trans cons that of
is exion [music]
that it Comes From My
From My
pressure my head Makes it accelerates that
Do You Feel
Better Why Note All
All
you that you Think that Hold you
Down you Think Hold you you are et
are
All More you refuse to acn the Idea that
you are unbounded More You will
restricted As All those ener to
Flow will you
are free you are compl sowed
you can do Whatever You Wish to do in
Life that excit you you do not have to do
anything Special to deserve existence Creation
created you you Exist now you
Always Will you are eternal you are
etern you are inou All that you
need the life you  Desire to Live And you
will allow Yourself to accelerate your
Energy so that you will in a Sense Catch
Up acclimate to the Energy you are
Feeling to be a pressure The Only Reason there is pressure is
Because You Are Not
letting it through Because You will not
Trust it You will not Trust that What Is there
Will serve you There are portions
that you have bu Yourself that you
fearing to the Surface But understand
they can Only be
Friend can Only be represent of the and
Life you chose to When you Enter
they can Only there to  support you
can Only allow you to integr to your so
that you are and vulnerable and to All
That is then you allow All That is to
any ener that Comes So You will not Feel
like you have to take The on
Yourself isolated unconditional
unconditional
Love not to
iners AS unconditional deserve deserve
deserve deserve
ity your
you All aak
Life As As
that you are All The
The
Natural Day to
experiences of a
Reality In which You are willing to
know that you are unlit that you are connected
to All of cre
In which You are willing to
know that you have  chosen to Create The
Reality you Experience according to your
own purposes
and  that IDE of was forly for Many
consider to be
conant Trans conne conne you
are that is what me not you Experience
mti exp are
you I would like I I have
have
Two of my
What you Think about having themes Out
Put have Out
and i
to What do give you not Bel [music] [music]
REM asly not One One sit Will
Will
In The eas
man you have thee RE even in difficult Take
are Come Make But But
and can
and some else
you can do Many things matter is
Energy is mal  is consciousness is what
you Think It is what you are willing to itk
Because bil material has not been distributed
generally that is to my inform and like to
these ships are
own in
in
Inn that are working Out their own Love
anding With civ
atn thats iny Are Not toly they
and that is done ass is so much A resp
to What you do But Will A Balance ACC each
reforce in This recn that The IDE of
asso mostly neutral and while there
Will responses What is done
with will AS [music] If
If
One follows The What they Is The Right
at that Time Hand
time you saying that that is allowable
allowable
in More could All Yes
Yes
that in This Way is Going Off What they
Believe to be possible for themselves so
in This Way is not that could not have
been The Creation of More awareness but
the fact that there is Whatever level of
awareness there is the that our
our
interac Take General overage
All interaction ability La
of willing integration
judgment separation unconditional
separation unconditional
lings Put The average Together and resp that
ACC How We
Feel over you
All More of them to CH through This Way Find
the Energy C you use Most often  is
chn Because You Are Not used to that
area rest Flow rest it
Will out the More you are
willing to know that What is happening is
happening For a reason and is
happening according to What you agree to have happen
You will Relax into it You
will not be so tense Is only the tension
that caus The Pain Let go
Where I feel sick to my stom and there
Feeling Where have to Get Up in midle of
drink Milk you
Milk you
are vibra
into [music]
andery EX is being jud
so Where can
Put  ende
cann
are you will You will
You will
in Trust  Will any
rest you Create in Yourself When you All
Yourself to Stop Fighting your
own Stop Fighting your intuition Stop Fighting your
excitement Stop Fighting Trust in mak
conne heed to If there He could do
He would to have so much Sleep and
can Dream One Always A
Always A
mess anyway One Area When I can talk
about
things with her Life about life and love does She
and Do you not have any
Feelings of your own As to the Idea you well do
other people I do you Think you
canare exp egy SU that
that
you get into
and
Take Just Talk rela and enjoying the bri
and Beautiful
Sun and
Let All
knowing that being
River has left you to Where You Are Now
For a
reason TH anything you Discover in any por
of any life you that you find to be
pleasant you can Transfer that
pleasantness to the Because you know
that all you experienced in the was For
The purpose of What you are can
can
As Just Asant anything you imag you Experience inly
inly
assuming The is Better The Present
anding herself of the Opportunity to
Experience The Joy of as life has
chosen in know Share Share
sharee
conne Will have
aing  isar Let Yes
One you May
also Tell
her does not have a like you [music ] sure
sure
in that SP posi and Ne so that that
would Make
arec Only attract indiv to refle your
incompleteness The Idea of ​​finding and
reattach with your soc soulmate is
knowing you are Complete already so that
you can attract thats your knowledge of
your if you need a relation
in att
that Inc
not Feel like I need relation
All Why are searching
I just thought I just thought Be
a Great question to Ask You Right You have  The
Answer that We perceive to be
the Idea that exs Most prominently in
your Society There
are Many Ways A Soul can fraction
and Because you When you are a
certain vibration att
att
vibra are att pieces of the Soul Over Soul
that you are also a Part of that do
represent The Soul you any given are
always refs and po to You And you to
them No matter what you are exping
that Idea to be reflected to you But at
the time you will also find that you
paradoxically while you recn that you do
have a Soul reflection dichotomy  that
would seem to be the Balance of your
polarity The eny
Soul and One you are you are married Every you Every you
for you Orbit
is no AC As are
tion and EX of Inter
and is a Connection to the P that is
coming Into The Present again The
instinctive and RE of the IDE you Call lum iner Love relation [music] you other Nature
All All are the you are All
gover you are
All more Still Creation on
All Create IDE
comm you have created your gover to they are they
Area The Idea so so
[music] again
This  Is The Time equation And
Communication The First
commun equ allain Us UN Love From
gover are taken [music] [music]
Let
are toose by thein
toose by thein
inform Self
form there are
lel not unreachable That's Where The
Main Resistance Comes not so much govern [music ] ]
money that AS
If You Are Not that Real you find any you
Open
and it could I don't
know like Little reon Dev
you the other Thing I
was I had a dream that
I and Is that Is that a sign of
acceleration More conne being your
Higher Self being your Future Self in
the Now  willingness conviction and Trust no
in What you call your California In You Call
New Mexico In You Call
virginia Call Oh Oh
Yes not [music]
[music]
More are you doing What you want to do
Life well do
can I Take I
mean again The Is that if you What you
know to for you you will equalize your with
the Universe Whatever
isir SIT situation equ are All
understand you are
equ All other form of and not Money
specie then you won be Only When You make Money A
Special Case Do you then
say it has The Right to  fluctuate wildly
Outside of the Idea of ​​your Normal
consideration of abundance which Is only being
able to do What you want to do
When you want to do it
All our in
that Because you Think once again that
abundance Is only represented by
the Symbol you Call Money Now understand
once again A supposedly
soc or Inc Person and a [ music]
More exactly What they Need to Idea exp
of the Idea they know themselves to be
they do not have More They have EX
Enough to the Idea they know they are so
When
you IDE are AS you you
We I was born in This Country and We
didn't Create anything Yes you did  No We didn't Why
then is Some of the
government Sleeping in
the in This Way You have created a type
of
Society that limits in Many different
Ways and your government is no Exception
As A reflection of All The different
Ways The Mainstream of your Society also
cho to All
That and Are responsible For Many of the
that you do not Think you are secondly
the longer you support an Idea that is
the As crea
it you continue to Create it byly that
there does have to can any other not equal
to not commun with that ising you
believe it is what It is have No toa
with you are not equal to it And
therefore you are creating it to
continue to be the way it was created
Long ago Every Moment of time is
different than any other Moment of Time
so Every moment is own Creation What
happens in the Next moment has nothing to
do with What happened in the last UN
you Think those Two moments are
connected that conne isus
given that you Think govern is you can commun you Think they
Run Lives you are
giving the power to do not up and Will Take
Back they are IDE and
understand The Society that
you have Many understandings And
misunderstandings of the reason Why
things happen There are VI you
happen There are VI you
Experience the real you exper
because People People gover
But you will not find One
[music] As
As
BL and will gener find
None would exp
We Are Never and
Never and
Search searching in means there is a Way
and that you will find It All you Need to do
is to Believe that there is And
you will
find aman People Great People All People
Are equ are and they are BL [music] per cana them [applause]
[applause]
and Will All  Blend and be And alls
of there is a If You Believe there is a
if you do not Believe there is a Way You
are de before SY AR
AR
archetypes Will Simply Be a
ref of ideas that you have built into A
Mass conscious
subconsciousness This is to say that
Your Mass consciousness that which you
All are collectively you have also created
to have a subconscious uns [music ]
Will Come Times In Your Life You Need to be
in touch with those levels that you
have separated From you TH out of the
Energy that is elect Field of you will
Life into A  Yourself and Will Take own
and AR SY My
My
things Experience The energ of things
you Think to be myths or Fairy or imaginary
beings or creatures Many of
these are Man of your own ener Through
The Mass conscious subconsciousness they
Take ener
Yourself could Why chose
Because R that are separated
Frag inou As One
ideate Idea All It is done in Ser of fraga
As being One Idea having
Many It is like standing in a h of
Mirrors Number Let Yourself that all One Thing manes One manes One
All
Why can
so it can consider to be One And also A
of Because It All That is it
has And of you and being in Creation all
the Ways creat has Looking exp
Yes and could Ask Personal Feel
This M
and there is something else to
do be Create Heaven on
on
Earth Act Like You are a
multidimensional being And you will
radiate As A Prime Example of One But giving
everyone else in your Reality in
your Civilization an Opportunity to see
In You a a
Method A
lifestyle that Will
allow and har
Remember you not Get He
Will Give everyone else The Best
Opportunity to also choose that Reality
for  themselves Because then they can see
In You and everyone else Who chooses to
Act like it that there is a Way To Act
that represents Peace and If they prefer
it they can then choose It For
Them All you you And I having that
having that
was of belief that
could Group could Make differ and do
some contin Idea
those that know that Peace is the
way
Always those that are As take
What Makes You Think you are not being serv are Who I
I
am not Worth can otherwise you
otherwise you
are how
can Why do I do
something El Okay And I find this
very fearful to  be doing for me All
Right to be trying to get US to it This you get US
to it If that is you TR want to do
you get US
to very Strange Feeling 25 or 2 Strange does not
Make It
negative Strange Only means It is
very different Someone like As some
As some
like Will continue to
When You Know It is noal will stoping [music ]
could Who are
as we perce at that Time was archet
representation lel of dimension
that is the Only lael We
can not exactly
Yes have a good time that
tole all right  The you Trust And you
Trust You  will
need If You understand The Idea Is that
you have Made an agreement to do What
you are saying you have agreed to do
then What purpose would serve happen any other other you
are able to handle well All
know that you are in touch with Whatever You
Need to be in touch with and Get with
Your Life acting upon The
opportunities that syron aoma
coincidentally not accident
themselves to you for those
things whether you Think they Are Not att
to all the agre you Made and
Will Lead you to Where You Need to be to
manif they seem to be
always  harmon with your
choices there Will Be No Tough decision to make
Everything Will Be an
obvious and Two things to have equil
then Trust that it does not matter which One you take
All Thank you I have a what
wee All ent All
For a reason And you do not Experience
The Pain you only Experience
the reason Why something Is there and
allow Yourself to Take That Reason use
it and All Trans that does Cause
As The things You Need to be
do what is it you do want to do anything at
All while you are
Ping all right allow your
allow your
to  that The vast maor Of any Pain you
Experience in your emotional  Lives
physical Lives Spirit Lives mental Is
only to the that you will not Trust your
excitement You will not Trust that What Is that
you want to do is what you be
doing Exit your excitement
What you Call EX Trans your that
isit friend This is
your Follow it that is what excitement Me
When you are willing to Trust that
Pain will
be you will be to [music ]
]
Over so What do
you Wish to do are
anything All be More EX Think do
then you are an AR Act like And you att Who
As
AR are  AR how can attract
anya with you As if you an
AR you do not radiate The sign I am an AR
so No One expects to be able to bu
your paintings Because they know You don't have
any She doesn't Look like arst I W Go Up
to her and Ask her to Paint all the
paintings for
is not an AR well I'll Look someone else Follow me
All of these connections happen much
quicker and on More subliminal Levels
than you imag
instant People will be attracted to you
for What you are If You  are not willing
to be What you know Yourself to be  you
are not advertising
[laugh] No One can Pick it up can No One Can you all
you all
right Let that will Only inoc
Only inoc
For Now there are Many ideas Many All
Many All
BL and [music
]
in This Because All
Iron in the of that termin asing
again that IR exp Word anding
that Out to Came can things indiv
indiv
can can it can be
connected to What you Think
you can What you Think you can it
can What you Think you can it
can Beer
something can beever [music ] and
Drill I went Back and He said I would
need  a Crown so He Put The Crown on and
When He was doing The Crown He was so it
was so roughly done that UM it was
extremely painful afterwards And I was having
so much Trouble with I went Back
and He Said well Now He needed to Drill
A Ho in the CR Ro Because Root was
traumatized or The nerve was traumatized
and
Back i to do i to get to knowing VI More More
can For You
All But Just The premise that going to
survive Said The nerve May have to can have
some M on the
upp would be  the no I had that Out I
didn't have for it  No room for
[laughter]
All When you are able to Up For and that that is
is
per own have Inter before before
Act was Care and
Care and
was so ied to get to a Place Where I
all happen in think
Looking Back understand More and More
Right something that happens with Mother
As You
have The thank you Yes That's And I have had
The thank you Yes That's And I have had
a lot
of UM explosions Real This
particular it was morning
We My Mother fell stairs And actually I
think What happened is She fell Down and
killed herself Because When I Found her
She was lying Face Down with her feet Up
The stairs  and her Head on the Tile
Floor and there was a little Cool of
blood Under her mouth And I just stopped
and Said No not Now not like this And I
I refused that Reality i went to her and
picked her Up very gently turned her
Over and She was not Dead
And I Learn Many things From This and
only later did I Real at that moment I I
Found her She was but then the minute I
refus that Reality I Switch to a
different I Switch to a different
Reality in which that did not occur and
I know that on some level isre on  some
All Now I'm sure Learn
was I Got to her mother and
Because I never her that was i to getou
so I just want to Share that with
everyone and Because was
a
fabulous that and We
do thank you you are inf are et All
All
you I doa
you All All
Us own
to IDE of Time how can
be
perception events  coming without The
Idea of ​​Time it Takes Time to occur
cannot be that is Why you created it So
You could Experience The Idea of ​​a
separation or A sequential arrangement
of
events so in No Time there is no perception
of events
allods Will transl
Comes As knowing and some
time is Real Because you cre to be
necessary to Experience The IDE have deed
When iter You will exp it
iter You will exp it
any As Enter New Age awareness You will
Time ACC that Up are
you actually Living In the moment do not Create
As
much The La
Creation
transl Up in that have
As  Call
FM it
has reming
not showing As Nota As Integra
andes As You Create
Illusion AS again [music ]
to be One that enes
you For All The Unity
that Will Be GR equ
We than you for US to
you All Us awar teach
awar teach
learner equ SH
All we than you We Send you
unconditional love We B you exciting
Dream Lives and Life Dreams We you a [music] unc L