How are you will
inter more understanding
a communication and whaticality
in this recogn that even
though you are intrally fundamentally basically
let originally to speak
nonysical
andicality is one of yourje what the way
you can understand and view and
experience the idea of ​​your nonysical
consciousness your physical reality is a
part of what you are as well it is the
idea you are being and in being that a it comes with a now communication
meaning not only what you really think of
as communication in the sense of
receiving a message back and forth communication
can  also extend into what
you call the actual
information that you are
receivingly receiving through which and
by which you create the idea of ​​the so
physiological scenario what you refer to
as feedb
back sensory experience in a sense is
also communication th recogniz that while in
communication th recogniz that while in
your nonphysical state on your nonphysical
levels communication intention of sharing
communication intention of sharing
information as knowledge and
perspectives may be or what you call
direct as you think it is in your
physicality but the idea of ​​your physical
reality because of the
definition of what physical reality is
in terms of a separating
element that separates  you from the rest
of or  more of all of what you are then
recognize that by definition any
communication that you are receiving [music]
is not so much a communication but indirect communication
and this means is
as we have said you as a physical being
create yourself to be your own
complete idea your own complete
universe. Anything at all that you
Anything at all that you
receive from someone else as a
message as a
communication what you are actually
perceiving is your version of it that
you agree to create in your so you can
have experience of the communication
that is being sent more directly on a
higher level but on the level commicate
of the idea in your own terms
according to the reflection you need to
see to understand who and what you are
as a physical being in the experience
you have chosen to have as a physical existence
it is not that what you are
now hearing for example the words
issuing from the  physical
aateysically in you
takeysical understanding of what is being said and render
understanding of what is being said and render
that understanding inysical
understandable terminology that you have agent
commicity is not so muchly from let here
but in more here up over
and so that you create your own version
that makes it as communication is here to
them and your
understand energies with is first of all you have
as we have said decided to explore
the idea of ​​separation
limitation in every way shape and form
that you can simply because that is one
of the ways you can experience that is therefore when
you  have created this
limited to you
to you
have you are to all that but at the same
time you have truly created yourselves
as individuals to truly be your own
complete and separate and total universe
unto yourself that is so you know and can discover
Everything in your
life is actually a product of your
creation in your and th you expressly
have complete utter and total contra over
everyle you experience in yourity
nothing comes upon you that influences you
anything at all that you to be influenced
over you is your choice to
believe that such influence ex to create that infusion of influence
in yourity for
yourself you  when you feel you are being
influenced by anyone else are actually being influenced
by
yourself it is the product of what you
choose to believe that is what your physicality is
Now understand
therefore that the idea of ​​what you
experience as the physiological
phenomena of telepathy of knowing
each other's
thoughts is not really so much knowing
each other's thoughts and again it is not
so much direct communication what it is
however is that you are forming what
can be called a conuous or synchronous pattern a [music ]
]
quite the way another individual may
choose to also view  their belief about
reality th what you are doing is  both of
you the two you may feel are
experiencing and expressing the idea of ​​telepathic
communication both of you are
extracting the higher communication down
and through into physicality in a
similar fashion.  So your thoughts, the thoughts
fashion.  So your thoughts, the thoughts
you are having seem to be
synchronistically conruent with another
individuals not because of direct
interaction but because you are both
choosing to operate and interpret the
higher understanding on the same wave
length. So is a
So is a
conrucy parallelism that is what to
beathicange between you nothing is changed on
the physiological level on high level
yes but on the physiological
level it is acting in parallel that
seems to be an actual exchange between
you you follow me yes in this way
therefore you can recogn
that any sit
you desire to create in
your can be as it has been discussed on
your planet for some
time created by simply recognizing that
if you wish to know anyone then become conruent
with them become synchronous
with them in a sense identify with their pattern
as we  have essed to you is to love them
is to know them when you love
unconditionally you are identifying with
another individual's pattern because you
are willing to accept them as they are
and allow yourself to be in touch with
all the different portions and facets that
they are and allow yourself to be in
linking in that sense in continuous parallel linking
in a sense creating for yourself the lines
and traveling along those parallel
similar lines you seem to be having the
same thoughts you are creating similar
manifestations but it is not literally
that you are exchanging the thought back
and forth that is why you can  understand
forth that is why you can  understand
that when your society allows to know
it does not have to have
conflict with having different points of view
but that the idea of ​​different
points of view can all run parallel
then you will understand that
at the same time you can have different
points of view you can also have
unity you follow
me
you are wonderful to back.  I have never gone
any Oh, I know that.  I
know I have coule of things.
One, I was
wondering if you perceived any
difference in the energy whatever happened
when he was in of course.  Could
you could you about
it?  In this way, our immediate
perception is that there was let us say
a type of gluing together of the
different shards or different faces of
the multidimensional cstal that you are
collectively.  that particular enery that
area of ​​your planet functions as a tie
of adhesive cohesive enery to allow the
facets to function as a unit by
providing the appropriate tempo and pace
for it to be able to do so it is as a
thickening of energy in a
sense you i you i
This
morning I was thinking about the
evolution of one moment if you will may I
each and every one of you present this
night of your time in this interaction
that there are no accidents and that
every single thing that an individual
has to ask share or  say may have
relatively different degrees of an
importance to you But it is no accident
that you are hearing it.  And you can
always utilize what someone else is
saying as a reflection for yourself to
see how in fact you do relate to what is being
said.  If you are willing to take that
opportunity then no matter what is
said you will always be able to learn
more about yourself by uing it as a reflection that
you have heard not
accidentally.  You all follow along.
Yes.  Before I continue, I wanted to say
your introduction on communication was
marvelous.  I just loved it.  I was
thinking about the evolution of mass
consciousness this morning and I was
thought to me that I thought I' like to
share with you and see what you say.  Oh,
right.  When you first when I first heard
about the triad and do you mean earth as
a son?  Yes.  Yes.  I always imagined it as
a mental kind of thing. [music] Could
Well, one I don't know exactly the shap
will you will
take for what good then you are in
you are in the moment I do not need to connect into the
right but it was exciting
any it is exciting I know I want to
share that with you thank you very
much that get in the frequency
more love you will keep it very simple
in a sense love is actually what you are
all made of the way that it might be
easiest for you to understand the idea is is
if you consider the idea of ​​all of
your material universe to  be solidified
out of a homogous background vibratory
energy perhs a simple way understand
love is to that background vibratory enery ence
out of you are all made as what love
actually is the very fabric the very
substance the very fluid out of
which you conal yourselves into
seemingly isolated solid individuals you
are made of love is the connective
vibration of everything when allow
yourself to synchronistically harmonize
with that background vibration it means
that you are automatically on the same
wavelength as the energy that gives rise
and gives birth to everything which
means therefore  you can be in touch with
anything then you  can be in touch with
anybody as long as you go in the feeling
of love for yourself unconditional love
for [music ]
you don't know question is except that I
in the process of trying to try
but not really knowing how to
go and to
myself internal disease.  All right.  First of
internal disease.  All right.  First of
all recognized by the very nomenclature
that you use of what you are referring to this ease this
ease this
the idea first of all is that this
ease is created in your society when you
invalidate pors of yourself when you
fight your own and create in you the
enery you call tion
This is aation of you from the
are and in isolating that of you you cut
it from the life flow that is birthri
the cutting of that flow is what
causes it to and toate from you and use ined manation now
is first of all  that cann truly get rid
of anything because there is nowh to get rid
of anything to however you can allow enery
that is within you to transform
into something positive recogniz you
always have the opportunity to transform enery into netive
or posi
manation in your because of the way you
have to
and you haveally into many you do not
believe it is easy to be in touch with
those portions of yourself and so many
times you will force yourself to look at
certain portions of yourself you will
force certain situations upon yourself by
the creation of ideas you call pain
and  stress and disease because you
simply have  not been taught that there are
easier ways to accept certain
portions of your consciousness and integrate them
within Now may ask you a
question are you in your life doing the
thing that excites you the
most I would say not why not use I don't
know what that is yes
you when we ask you what is
All is what
you can upon with whatever tools
are now available to you out of all the
things you could be doing life is one
thing you
acting you could more exciting anything
else you are
acting well what I'm doing
is trying to live in the moment and
there is  no trying to live in the moment
there is living in the moment or there
is not welling in the moment all right
what does living in the moment mean to
you being with myself and taking
and what I have to do.  All right.  What do
what I have to do.  All right.  What do
you have to do
?  My love.  All right.  In what ways does
it to your love and be
servety?  All right.  Do you think
about my work?
Is this something that excit you very
much?  All right.  This is something that
you love to do much.  All
right.  When you are being a what do
you give and what do you get out of
it?  Exploration.
And what do you get?  I get
the safing people get
get
all may you another
question.  Do you regard the individuals
that you assist differently than you
regard yourself?
Do you feel that you have the same deree
of unconditional love for yourself that
you do for do
you believe you act like you have
unconditional love for
your all right when do you
not get sick I see.   inck
that as how you are
why is only sit you will not to trans
into something else it takes over it takes over
it ne it are you there is
You are that power only you can create
the illusion that makes it as if
something else has more power than you
but that is giving your power away.  Now
I thought you said you love yourself unconditionally unconditionally. unconditionally so unconditionally so
any
including should not be a prerequis for
the ceasing of love to your
your
now if you are creating a
disease do you think that you created a
disease because you are doing something
wrong you are not getting something right you
proper why do you invalidate
yourself when you create a
situation just a situation which does not have to
come with nean why
chose to believe that simply
because sitation of thee is there that
you are doing something
Why not chose
to rather than a ne
while you are
will you with
me you do you do
you to have much  you very much
for now for the time frame of
this
all are fible does not have to
be any invalidation
such as oh well that will
never work that is on that is child that
will
can you create in
this even one positive reason for having thee
you
have a way
of sting
P that has
been following not having
enough my how does
the allow you to theatter notay
now you think you canay your
Yes.  Do you think that now that you have received
your attention with the disease
that you can allow yourself to receive
any and all messages that can come to
you and not choose to stop loving
yourself?
May I you
that with the background of
your one inherent belief you have ined
with yourself is that once you have a
concept of something you believe you
need a
process in order to manifest or a that
idea you recogn that this is something you have
you recogn that this is something you have
learned and something you can
unlearn and the idea can be stated this
way if you begin to recognize that your
imagination is just as real as your
physical reality and that your physical
reality is the product of your imagination
any addusion solid
addusion solid
then you can understand the
following idea if you are even able to
idea if you are even able to
conceive of a state  of being you prefer
rather than the state of being you are
in your ability to be able to even conceive
of that different state of
being means that at the time you are
conceiving
because things are things you are
vibratory level on you ex can only give
rise to the thoughts and concepts
andinations with thatevel and no other the
only that prev you from allowing
what you imagine or visualize to be a
reality or a situation you would prefer
over the one you are experiencing
as recogniz that being able to conceive
of the situation is not the beginning of
a process it is the end of a
process you following when you allow
yourself to know that what you have
imagined is now true for you then all
you need to do is to begin to anotheration when you to
you to
that you have changed into you need to
ne
do remember this
you as a society have
exed in in validation and limitation for
many of thousands of
years so it is not surprising that you
may for a little bit continue to do so
to treat your situation in that way
however this does not mean you can take
it for grant that you have changed
you
are what may not change so  quickly are
sys thatent yourity to you but do remember
thatent yourity to you but do remember
this no
symb no
situation comes with built in meaning
All situations, all symbs are
fundamentally neutral, black,
zero.  You give them the meaning and the
meaning you give the
symbol determines the effect you get out
of it.  Positive meaning, positive effect
negative meaning, negative effect.
when you imagine the scenario you would prefer to be
but that the same symbs keep occurring
all you need to do is a take
it for grant that instantaneously
in fact yourity has
changed what you need to do therefore is
start to give new meaning to the symbs
that do not appear to changing when you
new sy that is syange into
more conscious reflection of
the newness you know you actually
have but because you of linear time that
transformation may take a little of time to
not be impatient with
your if you now know for exle to your
scenario that you are now willing to receive
communication from different
portions of yourself without having to have
the experience or the symbol you
call the negative disease in order to listen
then simply take it for granted
that you actually now are from this
point forward an individual who no
longer does need to experience it in
that way if the symb should stick around
for a little while that is It
will change as quickly as it can when
you start to give that symbol a positive
meaning rather than continue to uue it
with a negative one just because of the
way it appears on the
surface.  Are you following me?
your willingness your willingness to not make not force
willingness your willingness to not make not force
a change but all it toange
then your physical will
to transform tole to you
what you now know beyond the shadow of a to be true
for you all doubt you need to do
when you know that something is true
for you is to act like is no
no
longer pain and
disease then act like a person who knows
that they no longer feel pain and
disease.  And should you create for a
little while longer the supposed outward
symbol of the pain and disease?  All you
need to know is it is not the same
meaning even though it is the same outward
expression and as soon as you
know it is not the same meaning the
outward expression will follow because
physicality is the shadow of the soul
and the soul is the body of existence
when you change the shape of the body
which is changing the idea of ​​who and
what you are the shadow must take the
form of the body but if you try to
change the shape of the shadow without
changing the intrinsic body it doesn't move this
move this
ass also recognize that from this point
for  in your dream real you will begin to recognize
that you have opened many more doorways
by your willingness to share
this communication with
as to have
anything without having tour anyone
else in order to get your dream will
expand and will be [music
]
are your life will accelerate
accordingly
we and [music ] It's been [music
know so strate recogn
that you have now in sense
created yourself to be something
different than you are blending many
levels ofer and now you find that you are limbo state
ofer and now you find that you are limbo state
in all real carry the  same
degree  of let say forignity and
familiarity at the same
time in it's been decision panicking to make decisions
but recognize
that what you are learning is that As
your life becomes more and more
transparent and more and more obvious,
then heavy decisions do not have to be
made.  Yeah, that's my that's my
solution.  I panic I'm sweating at my desk
and then I say it
just when you allow the energy to flow
you will understand that whatever
situation that comes to you will be
representative of the one you need to
act upon and therefore when the
situation gets there the decision will
already have been made it will be
obvious there will be
noy and if you find sitations to
sitations to
equal no tough decis even what that shows
you any dire you will do
it unfold
and act upon the opportunities
that come to
you unfold does not mean you and veg unfold means
youunly  attract
because acting upon that ortunity will
also be
ask yes i have my all speak
up wr it out and asked me to it as wr
How are we connect to
people with
people to are so connect to each other that our situation connects
to are so connect to each other that our situation connects
the situations
outside our
immediate exle I was not scheduled to work
on Wednesday but agreed to help out to
finish up some work my work being I
agreed for at lunch before she came back on
for at lunch before she came back on
time to receive a call from the police her
daughter had an accident to go to the hosital
it was not necessary  foray but I
did and the work picked up to extremely
I was very needed
are the in situation like this allcnect
so that if one length missing
would the other change if I had not gone to cover
would that have changed the Thank
you.  The answer is
yes.  And in this way it can be once
again let it say diagramed if you wish
on this particular level.  While on the
individualized level you can say yes
anyone that you are interacting with
closely in this life you have interacted
with many times before and th have
formed a type of relationship that is
very intimate you can also understand it
from the fundamental synchronicity level
of interconnectedness and that is simply
this everything and everyone is the same
one thing manifesting in that con that con
is
one interacting in
ways there are
no [music]
zero yes you would
after the first sentence but I what I have
the answer because I know you have the answer .
.
Remind her that also knew she has the
answer.  Thank you very much.
I have a
sh I have to David back and perception [music
perception [music
] back
oh do recogn that what you have said
does speak the vibrational truth for you
for you are
I know
any my feeling about why feeling the way I am
is partly on the account of the
idea that we all went out the group for
this spiritual background type of thing
of and all that and partly because what
happened with those people who said that they
were from walking and sending that
entity that double banger light entity
off into the light and ganger ganger and
partly because  of my channeling and
I channel so many different entities so
much in and how expanding my so many
different faces of the
faces of the
energy anyway I've been feeling
like weird but to me it's not a negative weird
I haven't had new things happen like a
little feedb on like when this was
speaking This is happening a lot to me.
I feel what I perce these differents
entities like when you speaking with her
like my shoulders sh and I feel energy
through my back and sensing things like
these ent yes
however at this time once again
for now allow yourself to recogn that it
is different levels of your own
conscious that are being activated not
different those things that I different entities
there are
connections to what you might call other
consciousness but again as we have already
discussed with you what you will
find is that at the beginning of any
opening to what you call channeling
there may be very rapid
switching from  aspect to aspect to aspect to aspect
and you may assume that
they are completely different entities
but they are
of the enery because you have many
different facets with your and you are
opening the doorways one at a
time yes well what like to know and I
know it's probably very relative to each
individual but how long months does that go on
for can be anywh in on
age as we ener
weeks to
and then it down to it will start to
these awareness I feel like one of
these um I don't know
um I don't know
types of yeah psyches of  people
that people go to like these  old people
that ti up in the hills or something
having like all these awareness open
aware they are aware what they need to be
aware right for of course by definition you
right for of course by definition you
are you and more different from everyone
else okay I'm about my previous me yes
of course that also by definition but
not different there would be no
prev that makes
sense any
What I guess the question would be
integrating all this part of me is screaming god this
is weird I don't know
about I know it I guess I'm so used to
judging myself
all relax you will understand that as  we
relax you will understand that as  we
have said one of the symptoms of density
is to begin to [music ] Joy
] Joy
you are only experiencing the
typical limbo state of transformation
once again as you have said identifying
with other individuals wherein many
different things seem to be able and at the
same time seen both foreign and
familiar. All right.  to go on when we were in ha
All right.  to go on when we were in ha
and the idea of ​​channeling was really
and I have some questions about that one
there is this question
of when entity is being people are
perceiving negativity in whatever form it
would that be the channeling it someevance
or the entity
on the other ending all this or
conglomeration of everything can be a
conlomeration byition
if you call another conscious it takes a
deree of integration to be able to do
that and if there is the experience of
negativity coming through that is
indication of lack of  integration and
therefore not
[music] specifically exha many exha many
people
net could [music
]
that is
the original r we canare that we do
perceive aspects we can also perce at
this forming
is for the individuals that are coming
into contact with that scenario
to decide for themselves what they do in
fact choose to believe to be true about
the reality and whether or not they are
willing to give their power away or not.   entingle ener
for you regard of who
says for you are all equal to any consciousness
with you [laughter ] ]
communicate all
right a question about your relationship
with up a question regarding
[music]
tak for to entrate
so let can also simply be that the
channel enjoys [laughter]
[laughter]
Weirdness that would be a trust love
I will assum all
right on the other hand you the
coming We are going to make
great.  But is there as much enjoy of
weirdness for the enemy coming for
coming to
absolutely that is [laughter
] a thank
you very much. All right.
weekend in your terminology you
call it is yeah I found out that is in what a
surprise for me I see.  Okay.
any a coule weekends
ag i channel some enery which was quite a that are
are
and a little I I have some questions I'm
a little bit confused about it
because I'm not sure where the energy
came from it seem to come throughout us and to me and it talked
it talked
about about the
children it said that it had a lot of
things to say been a long time and yeah
and that is the core vibration that
allows you to know that you are linking with
that energy specifically within
your reality at this time the emoal core
vibration but it is a surprise  an opening and a
cstalization at the same time of certain
doorways with you that are connect to
that enery ander of your intention in
the solaris and it will create the
heaving and the releasing and
theimulation and the blending of energy
simultaneously for it is that atmosphere
into which the children are being born recognizez
they are not just another
generation they are another
culture right okay
I understand that what
came through whenever this happened
was that all of the children of all the
beings on the planet are the children
just those of course and
that there was just  a lot of things that
are  going to be said
and I feel like I'm going to be a do
some of that I
mean, I'm not but I'm going to be what
you call Oh, you called it the bridge.  A
call Oh, you called it the bridge.  A
bridge?  That does not mean you are not
doing something.  Well, of course I do.
All right.  I mean, I don't what came through
me I know that thank
you for being willing to be of
cstal service.  Now, can I ask you another
service.  Now, can I ask you another
question?  All right.  You don't have to ask
if you can ask.
The what was really fcinating about it
was that the
that the
energy seem to be the of
this planet.
Yes.  And it was it is a collective.
Yeah.  And it was going through it was
like relaying through that constation
area through the energy before it got to me
I was wondering why that was only
reason I could think of was that it was
so intense that I may not have been able
because it is in a sense on many
different levels let us say just to be
in your language beyond the experience
of your physiology
in order to be able to assimilate itfory
valve representation symbol to
which you canate to which you have
already formed a degree of relationship
so that it will also carry with a deree
of familiar by the time you I
know I like there was more emality
there than I could handle for that time
but also another was
that like I know I had discovered
all that
was but I saw like in vision in my mind
a brilant brilant
star which was sort of behind this and I
think it's a future
this is representation of the
other levels we are speaking about the
idea is repres
inoc our tri earth
as on
all the enery of
the brilli conscious of
it seem to be what we are going to be this
civilization planet  Conscious is going to be in
a sense  yes you will be dealing with
it in that way and you will become immersed
in the association of that
nurturing and supporting and loving
vibration.   Thank you for
your people experience would you could you
describe that additional things would you
that additional things would you
describe
and their experiences and such on the
level that we are dealing at this time the
only description we can share with
you is what has already ener usiate usiate
in
as we can give you a symb however it is
only a symb not in a sense to be attached
to but it may function as a
focal point it is a 12 pointed white
point it is a 12 pointed white
on background circle on a background of m
that symb can represent better energy
and act as a communicative length or
identifying to the vibration of their
energy on whatever level you need to
identify with them is confused Yes. [music]
Ener I theansally and
they were very familiar
for yes recogn not as
invalidation but our point of what
thoseent is a strong
identification with that vibratory enery
enerally identification projection we
can some this idea at another time is that way
it works anyway yes okay we are
simply rearranging the symbs by which
your to okay refers So a walk in are you
would you define that for me is meant
from that perspective because I don't believe
in your colloquial terms it can be represented
as the idea  of one soul
energy let us say vacating a body and another
one coming in and taking over
where the other one left off but from our
perspective nothing really inhabits a
body because a body is the projection
of your soul inic
Nothing can be inside of it.  It is a
concept complete unto itself and full
itself with no room in it for anything
else.  It is its own concept.  Identifications
can be formed within its energy
vibratory pattern.  However, and that
from your point of view of thinking of
things with things can seem as if
something is occupying something
else but that is an illusion it is a convenience
and a symb that you find
convenient to relate to right
but that does not mean that there
is not a paralleling going on and as we
have said it is that paralleling that makes
the reality
for and for anyone else whoes toare that
you said the can from the
description you
12 you
that the idea is of If your imagination
wishes to it, then you have some reason
for  doing so according to the vibration
you are most familiar with.  What we are
speaking of however is that the idea of
focusing upon that symbol of 12 white star
on the background of an orange
circle on a black background will or
possibly can put you in touch with the
level of artist energy that you need to be in
touch with.  So it can be anywh
from very as you say profound to veryle.
Because a few weeks ag when you were
describing staring
I had a very strong feeling that
I would find such symb a piece of jewel
or something else and there was a gem
that quite often forstals and something made
me go in the other even though
I sh was a ring that I
and I have
very can you can you sense the idea of
the relationship you are forming yes in
this way therefore always trust that the
symbs that your imagination attracts you
to are the symbs that represent the
interaction best for you in your that is
your opinion  and is true for you we thank
you for your willingness
you asology from astrological
perspective planet Pluto is in align
with the
stars giving one indication of why this
energy the experience of this energy is
appropriate
space that I had to ask was saying that
the energy that is
symbolizes is on a different level the
tri that you spoke of wondering if you
could articulate a little more about
what you mean by that or what level we
can simply put it briefly that your
planet our civilization and the
civilization of Syrius together combine form
one consciousness as well
distinct civilizations within
it consciousness  finds itself being one
part  of an overall triad of which Arctur is
also one of the
overall conscious the other third Arus and the
and the
combined idea of ​​serious
and it can
beer to as for
us for you christ
what is theic
of i mean the moon lining up with at
this
recognition that the idea of ​​any alignment
with in general is simply a
representation of the idea of ​​another
threshold and a doorway that you're
going through and you will find that
your moon specifically represents in
your cosmology many of the ideas of your sub and awareness
cosmology many of the ideas of your sub and awareness
now coming to
the surface the  idea of ​​the plut
alignment generally is representative of
the transformation across a threshold
that you previously would have
considered to be the idea you call death
but now simply represents a
transformation into a new type of
life you follow I do I understand the
concept but could you give me an example
of the threshold the idea of ​​the
threshold we are referring to is simply
the transformation taking place upon
your planet from third sensitivity that is
that is
overold and every
single with your reality that has any relationship
transformation is all
generally a part of that
transformation specifics are also up to
you to determine for yourself although
as  we have said the idea of ​​your moon
does  represent to some degree the idea
of ​​your sub and unconscious awareness
coming to the surface act act
in mancribbed
the idea of ​​the myth you call
the crossing river
sticks this puts you in touch with what
you previously assumed to be the darker
regions of your
So it is another way of saying that you
enter the blending positive and negative
polar and allow yourself in the crossing
of that threshold to only a positive
effect out of the blending of the
positive and the negative.  This is why
you have
intuitively labeled Pluto's moon with
the same name as the fairy boat driver
that drives you across the mythological
river stick. when you
when you
about you mention sp and assum that is
very connect to
it is in other ways but the idea is
that as
this triad is unto itself a triad and
whole energy represents one of the
triads relative tourus and polaris in in
you how
so in ways that ser our civilization and civilization formle is the
is the
combination of the idea of ​​sp and other
cons to
It is very simple in this way you have let
say serious earth and you follow me
those three form one triangle you follow
me all right the idea of ​​the you
are from that  is another triangle and polar is another triangle
So each one of
those three compon with it and together
the three triangles form
another whole
consciousness that is also a part of
another three again and on and on and on
and does thatarify to some
deree something about that we moving
veryose
that is because once again like Arctus
it is one of the major constituents of
the overall consciousness triad that is
represented by the main group and in
this way what it basically represents as Arcturus
represents the emotional in
that way and as earth and Syrius
represent generally a collective  idea of
mentality in a certain  way.  Polaris
represents by your instinctive name the
idea also of the polarities in that
sense that you are now blending together
positive energy and negative energy in and
of itself.  So as you are now forming
an integration and making positive and
negative into one reality then you are
deriving a degree of physiological
affinity in the direction of polaris
because that is your let say indicator.
It is the indicator of your theme in
your integration the blending of the polar may all to say with
say with
any blend accept accept
with any
integration as you
become gathering together of all you have been
so
you to
in the moment
moment
in this point of space you
space you
will from time to
time all
your to
the enery that
ising with
may allow you to [music
]
experience all of the
valves that you have cl that you have ti
through the adoption of certain
relief in your physiological
life but that the of any
any
areas is only
indicative of the fact that  you are now
willing to open those
vows awaken those areas within you do not fear
anything that you will
discover within that
will be a
worthwi of your
consciousness will only add to the
overall understanding of your
momentum and your cognition of the
services that you have chosen to perform
in
this are many levels
that are willing to in
avail your that assistance
and that as
you of that assurance what
you are allowing your to is
those pors and those levels of your
as you think you are assance is communication from
that cons on
level to your cons on  level that  allows
you to create the aid and assistance you need
from your own enery
that is how you other conscious to ass
you by accepting and allowing
andcknleding their love for you and
transforming their love for you into the
love for your that will allow you to
allow your physical reality to become
the ease of without strugle
without strike
simply open to all of
and there is no
need for you to man those inful
ways for there is no need to create your to be serate
from that which you know to be true for
you this is
indication that  you no longer
to fight your
ownasy and that only the fighting of
your is what creates the scenario and
the sation of the do
the do
remember that
vulnerability is infinite strength and
indestructability [music
]
will to
all to all that is allows you to connect
to all that is connecting to all that is
allows you to experi as infinitely strong
and selfed
so your vulnerability at this
time of transformation allowing energies
to flow through you in to expand into another
idea of ​​what you are associousness
which is the same
thing need not be experienced in  a
painful way when you allow yourself to know that
way when you allow yourself to know that
you are only  discovering more and more
of the extasy from which you are
created aniety
is the same enery as excitement [music ] trans
are blending po many of you this
your time and in a sense another gateway
and another doorway and a tie of cstalization
is taking place with
individuals who specifically have chosen
their path to manifest as an expression
of polarity
some of this will have to do
with what has been termed the upwelling
and upsing and integration of oran
energies and many familial connections
are being
with each  other and with
your for you are your in a sense of your own
and now is the time that you have
allowed yourself to
begin to adopt all of the family that
you are Release
and flow enjoy
and love all that you
discover yourself to be
live in the easy of the moment of
selfovery and then none of that
discovery need to be
for our
unconditional to
My needs are against my preferences
there are physical needs to do things I
tend to run ahead run away from those
things. Yes, but
but
need grounding.  I feel why do you think
they are need?
Well, I try to ignore them.  To try.
Does that mean try to try?  I try to try.
[music] ignoring
things in a way I don't really want to
work to make a
living to be in the body to be in time now
one you our physical body in physical
time.  So you can allow one thing to be
obvious.  If you are where you are, you
obviously chose to do so.
first of all and fundamentally allow your
recogn as long as you think the
micro you truly no longer believe you have a
purpose in being physical you won be
so as long as you
Well, okay.  Thank you for that.
The feeling I get I feel as though
though
here I feel in pain.
more of ener unit
more another space another you are your own space doesn't fit
here I don't feel like I fit
and I real we understand what you
are saying but again by definition if
you truly didn't fit you wouldn't be
here so take it for granted that you
obviously do fit otherwi you would be
some yeah appreciate that and the idea
of ​​fitting however doesn't have to mean conforming oh
yeah i acknledge that I
feel as though I'm to end on a brighter
note I feel like I'maating like
something like you accelerated getting
the last little upward spiral the little
thing before no longer recadox
sitation by being now where you are is
you connect to all that you poss can become
and then I
had a realization about that concept of
the idea of ​​complete willingness to be earthly
earthly
person and many of us I know that the
years have been unwiing have awareness un [music ] ]
be and
wasing to contact the moment and this is
something I'm working for this is just
as valid as anywh else you have ever
been or could ever be exactly if  it
isn't then you  invalidate everything
else you have ever done as well right
for they are all here now [laughter
]
Absolutely in this way as we have said there is attra
and theory of many different faces of enery
theory of many different faces of enery
this evening of your
time I was noty to what went
I will listen to the I may find it some
questions that I have some questions
that I have any
all we did not imagine that you
would have had a fascinating week and a
half week and a half last week and a approximately half
last week I created  for in my
ag the answer that I to that was we are
all incompetent and we are all competent we contain both
polarities Well, was really fascinating because it has
Well, was really fascinating because it has
n't occurred to me quite this way
before, not to the intensity and I
experienced some very strong emotions
with regard to it.  Oh, why?  And then
also other things I created such as I was
supposed to get a large check and
they only sent me a small portion of it.
So you are saying they are incompetent
to that's true.  I did recognize that and
which is great you know after talking
through several people with them uh I
finally got the check that I needed
right at the last with the last few [music]
[music]
hours.  All right. butilt
around what you design for yourself in
many different ways and explore
different levels of the entire
so it was the most convenient for that
scenario I presume that it was all
right it's all perfect yes it is however
it leaves me with a
just kind of wondering willing to go for
and all this not to
go thank
you all us to su that the idea of
incompetency may simply be your
willingness to
explore the
idea of ​​whether or not you prefer to fulfill
other individuals
Incetcy is simply the idea of ​​a judg of
individual who may not be willing  to expectations including
so exercising preference carry the judg
of incetence if one didn't
measure up to expectations you
would judge that expectation guys is
there anything else any other kind of
energy flux or pattern or something
happening with
this is also to some degree the perusal
of energies that allow you to perhaps
gain more clarity on what it is that does
in
you in this
recognizing that many times the idea [music
]
of falling on expectations may
indicate well that your heart
is perhs some yeah and i that's
very very interesting.
I want to explore what I mentioned
earlier about the check arriving just
the last
minute and because with that I was able
to look at and say well now is this
something that's telling me that maybe I shouldn't go
ahad and make this investment
I made an investment and I
needed to check from somebody else to come the investment
and question well
should I really not be making this
investment is this what this is telling
me although on the other hand I just my
excit I still excited sitation [ applause] applause]
syn
excited if you are
having back
so came from  that was late but in the
final was
Yes.  Oh yes.  Yes. [music]
Yes.  So you are living in the moment
with that event. [music] [music]
very
artistic thank you very much
more I wasn't here for the first part I
get more in
here I had a dream Sunday night wean now
I really remember my dreams and that's
fine.  I like it that way.  I
remember I was standing on theet looking up
at a building which had maybe 20
floors and in two windows
one the glob that you see they kind of
hchy globes
thatch of what coming
and I was standing a guy
which lions who actor guy that I know I do
n't know why him but to be and I
looked up I watched these things happen
it was interesting and then I woke up
and my body was charged [music ] ]
ener quite quite
outside
this few weeks where I
let it say it was the raw energy
state that created  that situation but
not the same situation [music]
[music]
that toe enery andev the
you could you
us what the ener
[music] are
are
blending you that there was
a
pinch we of some ener
so there
could and them to
know that awakening
more I have something else I toare with
you and
question ever since we took the
first field trip your ship I on that that
time as I was leaving I I huggings
on your ship
ever since
Once a while I have been practicing
disolving my
environment and then  coming
your beings and I know that  it's valid
in my
imagination and I was wondering if it was valid
in their imagination of I mean are they
Yes. rec that my communication with you know
you know
myation I know we are yes
but this is because I guess not know
okay I I don't really know much
about them except that
I
to in your pr my perception is they
are there to catch
Not that you need protecting but just to
catch you when [ music]
music]
you see I actually come on and talk to
them in a sense yes now they do recogn
that you are not transforming yourself
in what you would call your bord no
right but they do know they are
communicating with okay because I a lot enjoy a
with okay because I a lot enjoy a
lot of love and a lot of them to
and my have very
happy and female is Yeah . [music] I
I
see the third is not one of what we
would call call
our permanent
members and at times at times is
female planet civilization Will you
my thank you wonderful isut as you aboutend
between myself and another person
asingar someone who immediate environ
quite some time there is a lot of t and
also strong attra over that of time
became Yes.
perception is that this other individual
represents a direct counterpart energy
to you which means you both come from
the soul
you and you gave yourself as a soul the
opportunity of interactions between two
of its fragmented counterparts so that
those counterps could explore the idea
of ​​the polar
and as it
became and unneary for
and unneary for
the physiological
I still there is some kind
ofing on my
you are notev there is con
always able again to There will be a physical
there will be a physical connection
but you will find that it
most likely will come through another
physiological now when that happens you
will not care because  it will feel
exactly like the right connection domain
and you will recogn the energy there
that represents the growth and the
integration you have made.  So there will
not be an interaction with that person againal there
may be we find that it is
let say unlikely at this time as
you however do recognize that should there be interaction
again you have changed they
will have not the personally
You will attract what you need to
attract to reflect what you are willing
to recogn with yourself as the deree of
completeness that you are that
individual may be now serving
other individuals in reflecting many of
the ideas you shared with them.
more to the space
space
yeah I understand in the future situation is already resolved
right now I guess I need to reconcile that
now I guess I need to reconcile that
idea that I know resolved with the idea of ​​that
feeling I I
guess what
would you comm
you comm
all commic are commic understand
why is that
per i don't know i there some
kind a differ there may be a differ there will
always be there can be a
greater sym sym
un
gring to div
them who they are andowing your to
you are totally andely will per commic
in if you make it have to
change in order to meet your definition
of perfect communication then you are
never going to be communicating with
them but only your idea of ​​your
expectation of what you think they should
and that's why I find thoughts of
this person someh
yes let them be who they are and
recognizez that every relationship you serves
you, let it for what it is, not
what you think should be or should have
been.  It is what it is for a reason.  Let
it be so and then you will recognize you have
never had anything but
communication. parou
parou
will because you
which is on the as
you mean it may be the same body but a
different person
yes a
person is not who or what you actually
are your personality that what you
recognize as the person is in a sense an artificial
construct of the
consciousness when the consciousness
changes the idea
out sign sy looking or not is not the
same person it is not the same idea it
in a different way have you not had
experiences with individuals where you
recogn they have changed that they truly
seem to be a different
personality they are
lerally not the are
civilizations  wherein the changing of that
idea of ​​the
willysically change the representation of the body does
not occur that way as much in
your society but it is not the same person
society but it is not the same person
regardless So recogn
that if you wish to see anything
in your identity change your
then you will exist on the
level that those individuals that that
portion of those individuals already
exists upon as well.
to have you are on a different level and
see the aspect of them that is
also but still a part of the
same so you will always recogn them as
the person
so
you think so
could in any will any when
any when
you only things are
you makes no differ becauseev
you all the
differ in that
you aremined by you thinking you apply once again
the meaning to the neutral symbol
the meaning you give it
defines the
differ that
youce when you allow yourself to recogn
everything is for a
reason then you will allow yourself to
recogn that anything else that occurs  in
your life is also for a reason and does not have to
appear to
Yes.  Thank you very much.  Thank you.  I
have one
question.  It's concerning I felt the
time.  That is only because you are
fighting your own.
It is
very much happy you
any trying is not
taxing trying is trying.
If you have been trying instead of
relaxing, it is no surprise you are for trying ising
unless of course that is what it
you would like if you do try then you
will not of
trying.  However, all you need to do is
recogniz what are the things that do
relax you?  What are the things you
enjoy?  What are the things that excite
you?  Then do trusting that doing them
will still bring the support you need in
whatever way, shape, or form you need.
Trust trust trust. [music] [music]
I
was experiencing
experiencing
nice we were speaking to you.
I real
that
you thank you for what you are sharing.
Your willingness to explore and expand
in the man you are doing now benefits
all. Thank you.
I it's interesting how the energy has
changed over the evening because
originally it started off as a mild case
of indig and as you started to talk this
evening as soon as you started to talk
about communication it became
overwhelmingly painful and I had to
go out of the room
and as I was laying down in the other
room incredible
force of energy just to feel like
flowing through me
and [music
]
electrical and I was trying to take over
me take over
simply reflect your own power to
reflect your own power to
you in
you have been
that of your own power is a
fearful  that is what makes it feel as if it is taking you over but it
but it
can for you are in control of it you are
always in contr even when you create a
scenario in which it seems you are out
of contr you are contr I [music]
other the pain all pain all pain physical pain
mental pain [music ] ]
upon
your belief you into early in your life
that you do not even know you are
carrying with you the pains you were
feeling this night of your time was your ability to
now recogn that as you
expand your energy  and make connection you have
been  constricting you that have been
not allowing you to
digest and channel through you and derive
sustenance and support and energy from
more of your but now you are opening those ways
The pain in a sense to be collal
is only there because the
doorways are rusted
shut.  The more you open them the more
they will flow the less pain there will
be.  So trust is your
medicine.  Trust.  The more you trust that
the connections of energy you are making serves
your purpose in choosing to be
alive in this life and will allow you
toil your unlimited energy to be of
service not only to everyone else but to
allow everyone else to be of service to
you and enjoy your life. moreowingerate of moreowingerate of
theorsessful
will all in your right now
isnit of judg andit that you haveeved
necessary you have been toli in this [music]
are you have any longer. [music] Yes,
Yes,
do I see
[music]
that was talking about feelingent
this week I had an experience
with that ex that I shared weeks ag I
was about
taking I have it and
so so I think
I
yesterday what I had a strong confet on my
part was scho very was invalidated by
this exam
not as confident as you thought you
were. But only you did the invalidating no one
But only you did the invalidating no one
else only you.  You set up the
expectation and according to the result
you created you invalidated yourself
according to the
result you set up the circumstances
design the exper and pred the outcome.
outcome.
Now the reason again that you areing the is
because now you areing
andning all you require is a good of self
unconditional love for what you have been experiencing
love for what you have been experiencing
in the idea of ​​the socalled selfcpetence
and selfinalidation is the complete and
selfinalidation is the complete and
total opposite of love which is guilt
Worthlessness is the opposite of
love is the opposite of love.
So love your what you have cre
you something and you are now you not
and everything you have life posi and
netive has brought you to where you are
now then do not invalidate any
circstance for if you remove any
stepping stone in
your you cann not to
the all ste when you one
me the idea simply has been for you to
recogn that it is up to you to determine
your validity no one else can ever poss
design a test that will prove your
validity to
you no one except Yes , I
and I answered the questions that I
teach without
my information. [music] harborable reality.
harborable reality.
It is simply your indication of what
deree you are willing to allow yourself
to feel unconditional love for yourself
and all that is there is no need to
continue to test your you
have passed with flying colors
everything you have ever done for
everything you have ever done you have
designed and the outcome is always perfect
you can never be found lacking
when each and outcome to be
each and outcome to be
own reason for being and do not
continue to assume that there is one
background reality against which to
measure all other experiences for their
validity then your own life will be own
experience and is not to be measured
against anyone else experience
for its validity
Yes.  All you are
doing that you need to measure and test
yourself against what society says are
the expectations you have to up to.  And
you don't you don't.
don't you don't.
You are valid as you are and you have to
pass no test to it.  You can't prove it
anywh it cannot be
done.  You cannot even prove you exist to
anyone but you.  For all the other
individuals, you may be bidding of
your existence who all
graciously their heads in acknowledgment
of your existence could
all be hallucinations for all you
know.  So you cann anything to anyone but you
so there is no need to keep on try then then
when you know you are valid
and you the idea of ​​attending to
your valid to someone
else you will be able to your [music] digest infeten
are give us jab to that we
that we
ourselves it is an opportunity in many
different directions once it can be
that you may be again using it as a comparison
knowing that you are
comparing yourself to other people's
expectations of you rather than living up
to
It can also be indication that as we have said what
you are doing is simply not
your heart is and that you can do
something else in which you know you
will automatically be completely
because you have said on
your own planet a labor of love is no labor
at
all and you do not have to live up to
any expectation when you are enjoying
everything that you are doing you are What you are doing
you will never a
perle thing that you do is a perfect
manifestation of the thing you are doing
and no business being compared to any
other thing for validity
every other thing is not better
it is only
different everything is perfectly valid
for what it is  if you do
need  as perfect you perfect you
ener
here
all st may
my question was with there was enery
for seeing
seeing
from maybe planet somewh else that was that
was trying to come in and that I
was in my fear of it taking y agare agre oficeableend
able toce upon
you but what wouldve if able to do that
it would not allow you to be who you are
and the agreement with you could not be
fulfilled because you wouldn't be there
so it serves no purpose to take
you will agreement
will 5050 it can be
5050 it can be
other
cann you will
only you are available with nothingush you
faster that interesting was that that
and it makes sense and whenever you resist
anything you
experience it gets worse doesn't get
better and as I as I wasting the pain
was getting
much and was going all
over that is because you are your own
separate unerse there is nowhere you can get rid
of anything to because there is
nothing [music] inush
in
you back that
much you let it transform and go and become thank in
bas are you Yes.
Yes.
Continue.  Speak out.  Yes. I
I
came I was really in love with my life
until I went to Hawaii and then I came back
and I realized that I was
experiencing some kind of a wonderful
spiritual peace and since I've been back realing that emoally
I'm really angry
and it's not
tolerable everything I mean
just why are you invalidating
instead of allowing the
idea you call anger not to be negative
but to
al
nower you come
backen all situations in that scenario
all constantly now reinforcing the reality
you know to be true for you so why
should you be angry don't  know it is
because you are inv that is providing
service youowing you
no unc that you have blended with
more so be joyful you have been own byle
prev that you have drtically yes
why love it not be angry
can you I
was on a channels and I have some
questions about one of the I
'm not sure I'll just use this word entities
because it seemed from my
perspective that they were entities.
One of them kissed my hand and h it and
drank from someone during the break me
that was something that does and so my
question is it was enery r
notctly in that way it was more the
idea ofing into the energy level that
may represent that consciousness but it
was also a symbolic indication
some other lives you [music]
[music]
have all end of conv
What are you doing Well,
Is it still a question or has become an
answer?  It's still a question.  All
right.  Do you wish to wait until it is
all
answer?  Academic question academic.  I
just would like to know the differ
between the heart chra and throat chra
one is in the heart
and how that
for now when you say what is the
differ what do you me do you me you s
that there is enery
differ do ener differay
att the chra are
youing i making un with
you the chra chra asn
all and th ch have to do
that and and in my case though i think have
someockage in ch which seems to be invved swallowing
things that comes when you
and what is you are
[music] swallowing your
competency your belief in [music]
[music]
I didn't hear you.  Something like
that.  I don't I don't
know.  Rejection.  Will you do me a?  Yeah.
Are you sure you will do me a stand?
How do you
feel? Wonderful.  All
Wonderful.  All
right.  Now, will you say it like you
mean it?  How do you
it?  How do you
feel?  Wonderful.
Do you believe [music]
that?  What is
confusion means all wonderful?
all wonderful?
Yes or
no?  I see.  Would
you go
ahead?  Yes.  Let it be Yes.  Let it feel
wonderful.  Will you do me another?
Will you right now pret that it does in
fact wonderful?  Yes.  Thank you very
much.  How does it feel?
Wonderful.  Thank you very
much.  So are
you now? Conviction. Conviction conviction.
conviction got feeling conviction
knowledgeness tr and the
tr and the
willingness to
speak your that
is the differ in the energy
and the block you
feel is Thank
you.  Do
[music] do you
you
feel more trusting?
A million times
[laughter] more joy to you and in your your
let
conv yourit
Yes.  Are you wonderful?
Well, you know what
I thank you very much. is tred can
tred can
you tr
is you is all there is love tr love tr
it
in to put meical your
meical your
willingness to know that you know what [music
] doing that
is tr that there is nothing
life you could ever discover canve you that is [music] [music]
trle
[music]
on this last weekend i a woman at a
convention and i a very strong
to her very strong connection and I I s
that it might have been in England from
England maybe one time many together
maybe but maybe [music ] Engle is right
I will  tell you this.  In our perception
you have been druids.
I
got which is a
derivative of practices that were also carried
out
in the druid factions are remnant
understandings of attempt to reform a
relationship and reconnection to nature
that was to be lost after the
destruction of Atlantis together
was anything else you get All
right.  Now allow me toind you your own given
connections are valid in that way and at
the same time recogniz
that whatever degree of an
importance or energy let say or momentum
you give them will only be
representative of the ideas you are
exploring in and of the moment for you
always forming different connections to
the past at any moment because you
are creating
depends on who I know my yes and that
will conce you
not you have toare at at
this we commic foref time on
other from the physiological
level we once again than
you for your willingness to be with us
the forci life and lifeam
again everything is the same one thing
manifesting in multimensional
simultaneous as we
as we
continue on other levels [applause]
[applause]
Thank you all for being here tonight.
Thank you for being here here
[music]