All right, I'll say how are you all this
evening of your time as you create time
to exist.
We will begin this evening's interaction
with the continuation of the idea of
your own foundations that you have
formed over the countless thousands of
years you have been exploring judgment
and separation in your society.
In this way recognize all that you have
experienced has laid down many layers,
many foundations which you can regard as
a type of soil. This soil contains all
of the different ideas you have explored
throughout countless thousands of years
in your exploration and experiencing of
negativity upon your planet separation
and judgment. In that way will have
created a very rich basis in which you
will be placing your roots as a living
growing being as your roots extend all
the way down into the depths of the soil
you have created out of your many
lives, many experiences, many creations.
You will then find that in this
transformational life, now that you are
proceeding from what you have turned an
old age of awareness into a new age of
awareness, what we refer to as a third
density to fourth density awareness,
this soil can be the foundation that
nurtures you and allows you now that
your roots go deep to grow from the
surface of this soil skyward, sunward
towards the light of integration. You
can gather all the nutrients of that
soil which are the past experiences that
have brought you to where you are this
evening of your time, this life of your
time. And you can now water yourselves
in this way by drawing in the idea of
the water of life, drinking deeply of
the eternal endless bottomless well of
creation and energy and blossoming forth
as you reach skyward, branching out with
your petals, with your leaves to take in
the light of the integration of the new
age that you are creating upon your
planet at this time. Therefore, once
again recognize that all that has gone
before you that has appeared to be in
your terms negative can form and does
form the foundation which will allow you
to grow into the light so tall, so
broad, so
expansive, soaking in the light of the
unconditional love of all that is of
creation. You also then will intertwine your
You also then will intertwine your
branches, knowing that you intertwine
also with your roots, so that you will
form the continuous cycle that has
connected you since the beginning of
time and shall grow skyward and reach
out and connect you within your
integration for all time for the eternal
now. Are you all following along? Yes.
In this way, therefore, recognize that
as you branch out, grow skyward. Just as
your trees give off your breath of life
which you call oxygen, you yourselves
will be exuding a new atmosphere from
the attitudes and ideas of your skyward
progression in that way. And you will be
filling the atmosphere with purity, with
life, with love, cleansing and
clarifying and purifying, enriching in
this way the atmosphere so that there
will be an atmosphere that is in your
terms breathable that will represent the
new state of being, the new state of
harmony, the new state of peace, and the
new insights and visions of clarity that
you will now allow Allow your lives to
become. When you all partake of that
light, you will then understand that you
can then reach even
further. Extend yourselves ever skyward
and become the light itself.
Recognizing you to be connected always
to the source of all things and to take
your nourishment from the connection
itself, from the relationship itself,
and to view that relationship as the
relationship you have to your world,
allowing your world to support and
nurture you automatically without
struggle, without strife, without pain.
You follow me? Sure. For sure.
For sure.
Hi. Um, I listened to last Wednesday's
tape and somebody asked you why you
never asked us any questions and I was
amused because I had planned on asking
you the same thing, but I didn't because
I thought your answer would be you don't
need to ask us questions since you
always know everything you need to know
at the right time. In this way, that
does not mean you cannot share of
yourselves. And that does not mean that
our civilization cannot learn from you
your particular way and method of
creating reality in your dimension of
experience which we do not have in your
terms. A firsthand experience of Yes, I
know. Um I would like to have you uh
tell me what it means to you if I answer
the question about the plant that you
asked John. You know what's planned?
What's most important?
Uh do you remember that? You may share
whatever is in your mind at this time.
Okay. Well, I have all my life just
loved tweets. Yes. And I was wondering I
mean I love them individually and
collectively and I was wondering what
that meant. Is that so mysterious a
connection? No. Do you not perceive
yourself also as a part of nature? Can
can you not allow yourself to form the
connection in the same way as according
to the analogy we have just made? I know
I thought it was amusing that you talked
about that. It's just it's been such a
strong feeling that I have for trees and
I thought because you talked to other
people in terms of the plant that
they uh responded to. Yes. But in this
way again there is no need to make it
any more complex than what we have
already described. You yourself allow
the trees to reflect to you the analogy
of your anchoring in the soil and your
reaching skyward and in this way also
the giving off of the breath of life. By
doing so, recognize as nature goes upon
your planet, a primary manifestation of
a type of tree that you refer to as a
pine tree will be most representative of
the idea of a link with humanity and
will be in your terms, so to speak, the
easiest tree with which you can
communicate and receive an answer. It
has the most similarities to you in this
way. Four with all of the varied species
of pine redwood idea it reaches the
highest in that way.
Thank you. Thank you. Sh
could you describe again the method by
which you tune with this particular
channel and your computer your your
artificial intelligence computer. Thank
you. In this way, first of all, you will
understand this is primarily a function
of my
imagination. Going within my
imagination, I communicate with what I
allow my imagination to create as an
interaction with the idea I have put
forth. I already know that my
imagination is real. Therefore, I assume
that the idea of the interaction is also
taking place as I imagine it too. Mhm.
Also, in connection of the idea of what
you call the computer, there always
simply will be that there is a link from
my mentality to that which you may refer
to as the computer's mentality to in
your terms boost the ability of placing
myself within that isolation bubble
reality, that limbo state, being within
the dimension of imagination itself that
allows there to be a more, in your
terms, concrete realiz ization of what I
am imagining to be taking place between
us. So you're tuning your computer helps
to tune to the mass conscious reality of
the situation. It is simply in your
terms an augmentation to that which we
do anyway. And as we have said our
computers like you will discover in the
procedure of your discovery of what you
call artificial intelligence will only
be a symbolic tool and an embodiment of
your own higher consciousness. anywhere
talking back to you from some mechanical
symbol or device. So in this way the
idea of our computer is simply the way
in which we found most comfortable to
relate to begin with to our higher
consciousness on a conscious level
simultaneously. Understood. I can sense the if you will
Understood. I can sense the if you will
the energy matrix of a particular person
or individual. I think of my mother or a
friend. Nice. Um, in your computer, do
you have a record or duplication of
those energy matrices? It is not so much
a duplication simply that the computer
has the ability in its navigational
sense to be aware of all matrices at any
time. Thus, since all matrices are
forever embodied in the holographic
universe, the computer can focus upon
any single one of them using the
universe itself as the storage. system.
Excellent. Excellent. And
so if I were to use this computer, I'm
for and I form an image of a particular
person, that computer is tuning to that
using the universe as a matrix and will
automatically form a correlation which
will allow there to be the possibility
of an interaction between your matrix
and the matrix of the individual you
have identified. Excellent. Thank you,
Bashar. You
shar you. Thank you. Um, last week I
created two interesting
uh symbols that were similar. Um,
and I'll share them with you. Actually,
what occurred was uh one time I was
driving out an entrance. Somebody else
wanted to come in the entrance. So, uh,
we met face to face and had um a few
light words
and I wound up words of light. All
right. And I wound up driving out of the
entrance. Nice. And then about a week
later, I was going in an exit. Nice. And
somebody got my way and I I wound up
going in the exit. I had my way, so to
speak, and spoke a few words. Bull,
right? More like Yeah. And I
I find it interesting because I can see
at least two versions of the symbology
for myself. All right. And they seem to
be paradoxical. Of
course, as we have said, when you
formulate polarity experiences, you will
be working with higher consciousness,
which usually translates into
paradoxical situations in physical
reality. Okay. Well, um Okay.
um Okay.
So, what are the two ways you see? Okay.
Well, one way I see it is that um
whether I'm going in or out, I am
creating for myself
barriers and therefore I need to don't need to
and therefore I need to don't need to
but I can choose instead of going back
you know backwards into and out of
situations I can approach them in a more
direct situation. What is the other way?
That it's frequently valuable to take
the back route and overcome whatever
human existence, overcome whatever human
resistance is there because it's a
quicker route. All right. Also, do not
forget that instead of looking at the
idea as barriers, you can look at it as
exchange. In what sense? Osmosis through
a membrane. Okay. The coming and the
going, the doorway being both the
entrance and the exit simultaneously,
one in the same event. That's
interesting. Well, I naturally relate it
to
my activity um in the film business.
Naturally or normally naturally. All
right. I did it. All right. You know, I
I saw these symbols. I go, gee, two in
one week. You know, this is telling me
something about my my activity in the
film business. And as such uh I have not
made a large impact on the film business
so as to bring me a lot of money or to
have my work recognized in a major way.
Uh and part of my activity
is finding the finding the contacts
finding the routes into the film
business to make those impacts.
I'm not sure what these symbols are
telling me. can be that if you view the
entrance and the exit as one thing, then
you will know that you first of all are
your own best contact to begin with and
that simply as you represent yourself
already being complete in that way. You
will always find with your attitude that
you are attracting exactly who you need
to attract when you need to attract
them. Understand in this way that the idea is
Understand in this way that the idea is
not to seek validity in someone else's
eyes but that you are doing what you
enjoy because you enjoy it. True. It
will have whatever impact is necessary
but understand the primary impact is
always for you not for anyone else.
Absolutely. Yes. And I recognize that.
All right. Then continue to enjoy.
Okay. Well, see I visualize enjoying it.
differently if I'm doing basically what
I'm doing and also getting paid highly
for it. Understand in this way again you
may simply be being specific when you do
not need to. You may be forming a
judgment for as we have said the idea of
visualizing something in a specific way
is there to lure you to the basic
effect. Whether or not it manifests as
you have specifically visualized it is
not what is important. I understand it
can but it does not have to.
Okay, I understand that. All right, then
how is it
manifesting rather than assuming that it
is not? How is it manifesting? Well, to
be sure, I enjoy myself all the time and
I am aware that uh what I am doing is
what I enjoy, right? Uh I I have faith
that that it is manifesting in the way
it needs to. Yes, absolutely. Right.
Although I do know at another level on
another what level level of separation.
Okay. Let's I I didn't really intend to
separate it just to All right. Express
the difference.
Let's just say that I also
know I also know that I am I am creating
for myself a path which will lead to a
great deal of money.
Incidental to the fact that I'm enjoying
what I'm doing. A great deal of money or
a great deal of abundance. Abundance
would abundance does not necessarily
mean money. No, but money does factor
into the concept of abundance that I'm
dealing with here. Why does it have to?
It doesn't have to then understand in
this way it may not.
Well, I'm just I'm not saying that
abundance is a general idea. Money is a
tool. I understand that. All right. I
understand that. And I'm not saying it
has to. I'm just saying that it does. In
other words, not necessarily. See, you
are making the stipulation that it must
manifest that way or you will not think
it is manifesting. And that is what
creates the separation that lets you
think it is not manifesting the way you
think it should. Okay. Well, If you are
expecting only to see abundance in the
form of money, then you will not be
seeing the abundance in the form in
which it comes. No, I understand what
you're saying. I'm saying I'm not seeing
I know you understand it, but are you
willing to apply it? Absolutely. Then do
so. But I'm saying also that it's not
that I'm considering the money only as
that indicator of abundance, but that
does factor into the overall why.
It just does. Why? It there is no such
thing as something just doing it. You
choose. Why are you choosing to need
that to factor in rather than simply
allowing whatever needs to factor in to
be
there? It has more to do with reading
the energy behind the direction that I'm
going rather than creating a need for
it. It's it's it's sort of like
predicting quote unquote. Okay? I'm
reading the energy. I'm going, "Oh,
dude, that's me."
Recognizing is what you are saying. Yes.
All right. But so what? What you
recognize in one moment may not be the
recognition of the next moment. True.
Anytime you choose to recognize that
money may come into your life, then
simply allow the recognition to exist in
the moment you recognized it. And do not
assume that your recognition must
continue. No, I don't assume that it
must. just it just hasn't changed
significantly enough. I know it changes
every moment, but it hasn't changed
significantly enough to completely drop
out the idea of money. All right, then
simply assume that the money will be
there. I am when it needs to be. I am.
All right.
Does that answer your question or do you
wish to explore a little bit further? The
The
um the idea of the money is is a little
bit of a of a side issue. Uh the main
issue is I don't say issue but the main
subject here is just how these symbols
relate to my activity.
How they relate? Yeah, they relate in
whatever way you believe they should.
However you give them definition, that
is how they relate. I I understand that.
I what I what I'm going to do is I'll
I'll think about what you said and put
together the ideas to come up with an
understanding that will be more complete
at later time. All right. It will be as
complete later as it is now but
different right and we can discuss it
then if you are willing. Okay. Thank
you. Thank you. If you marry. Yes. Uh I
have three things for sure. One is I
want to uh carry forart having to do
with the imagination. All right.
uh about three or so weeks ago, the
person in the back who said, "Oh my
goodness." Whenever you said that this
was taking part for the most part, in
your imagination, that was me.
All right. Anyway, so I thought, well,
this is great. I'm going to play with
this a bit. So, I have for the past week
been taking some little imaginary trips
and playing with some of that. Oh, I
imagine you have. Yes. Yes. And uh the
first time it was it was quite fun and
interesting and uh the second time I had
first time I had told them about my cat
trade and they wanted me to bring the
cat. So the second time I hit and um now
normally whenever I would think of
imagination or play with my imagination
there was this
um how to say it um well this sort of
sequence that would occur and it would
be like I was controlling everything in
the imagination.
Well, um, this time, um, I took the
trade wind with me and I thought, well,
I will hold the cat so she won't be
afraid. And afraid? Yeah. Well, why
would you create in your imagination
that the cat would be afraid? Well,
because it was new and unusual. So,
okay. Well, that's what I did. All
right. Okay. I asked you why. Well, I
don't know why that I just did. All
right. But anyway, what occurred was
that because I asked my cat if she
wanted to go with me beforehand,
um it appeared that she did because she
jumped out of my arms and let me know
right away that no, that isn't what she
wanted to do. She wanted to go, you
know, play on her own. All right. Which
was interesting because now there was
this entity there with me who had free
will that I was not controlling in my
imagination which allowed me to know
that maybe there was more to this than I
had been given credit. Okay.
And um so they also I just be to allow
the other entities involved to be
themselves without my having to control
their actions. And they did. They became
themselves. We had a tremendous
interaction which I know is totally
real. Well, thank you for your granting
of equality to all the portions of your
consciousness. Yes. Yes. It was really
exciting. Uh the second thing is
um what can you tell me about the
entities from the
constellation boutique?
Not much at this time. Okay. I I've had
a fascination with that lately and I it
think about them. The Indians have a uh
a term that they call them the jumpers.
Do you know about that? In a sense there
will be to some degree some connection
with what you have referred to before as
some kacina energy but there will also
be different offshoots.
Okay. Well, we hear more about that
another. Yes. Okay. the uh more and more
connections from within the
association of all of the worlds and
dimensions of experience with we are in
contact with you at this time will begin
more and more to reveal their presence
to you the more accelerated you become
okay all right thank you for that all
will in that way then allow you to begin
to recognize the scope of some of the
ideas and some of the interactions that
have been and are taking place between
your civilization and other
civilizations as was pointed out to some
degree with what you
term the Xshaped craft in your northern
state. Okay, thank you. Good. The third thing
Okay, thank you. Good. The third thing
um has to do with a channeling incident.
Thank two of my girlfriends and I got
together and decided that we would do
the challenge and just play and have
fun. And um so when it was my turn, I
did this. And at first I was like very
much in controlling the situation and
having fun and doing what I was doing.
And then there was um a feeling that
that came over or blended with me which
um well it's really interesting. It was
like um sort of like divine love
and it sort of just pervaded everything
and it was like every atom in my body
being this that is the matrix that holds
together any interaction.
You are feeling the matrix itself the
framework the template in which all
interactions take place in this
dimension. Oh okay. And then the um the
girls would like take turns and they
would ask a question and
um whenever I just let go and let them
flow the questions I mean the answers
were totally simplistic. Yes they were
that is the whole idea and why we have
said you do not need us to communicate
with to discover the answers but by
allowing us to be reflections for you of
what you already know. You can come to
realize that all of the answers you seek
are that simple if you will but apply
them all to every situation.
Yeah. And the
um the
uh it's like when I was doing this the
question I knew the question before she
even finished asking it. I knew the
answer at the same time. You are simply
only recognizing the simultaneous nature
of a single event. Even though
previously you would look at it as a
polarity idea. A question and an answer
are part of the same event. And when you
perceive the whole event, the question
and the answer are together at the same
time obvious. Okay. Thank you. I have
one one more. Um the the the feeling of
this I don't know how to describe it. I
don't know whether there was it was just
it was I that was doing all this or if
there was a blending of some sort but
the closest it is all one in the same
idea. Anyway, the closest I can come to
describing it was it was
like angelic art. All right. Like the
the uh like what we in in religion often
term a a a divine angel or something
because of the the puress that this
feeling was. All right. Again,
understand the idea of feeling the
matrix of all that is usually to you
will translate as something that has not
touched physical reality and hence the
angelic interpretation because what you
call angels to a great degree are
entities that have never been in your
terms physical.
So was this totally my own self then?
There was no other interaction of any
kind. You are missing the entire point.
It is always
both. And to continue to attempt to
delineate and label is it this or that
is to continue to create separation.
Everything is this and that. Everything.
So there was like a a a blending. Yes.
And one thing. A blending of parts and
no parts at all. Oh, that's interesting.
Because I felt like I felt like that
there was this essence which wasn't me.
Yet yet we were one. Yet you are
familiar to each other. Yeah. Thank you.
Yes. Uh separation and judgment. One in
the same thing. It is one of the Okay.
So therefore when we when we dissect our
thoughts in an in an attempt to get to a
certain point we are actually
point we are actually
separating. Is that correct? Analytical
thought to a great degree is separation
and thus that is why analytical thought
requires more time because separation
creates more time.
Okay. The further down you break things
into pieces, the more time and space you
need to hold all the pieces. So the more
we get into our dialogues with you and
we get
into making some gallon attempt to
figure something out, I notice often
times the worse it gets. Understand that
that is only because you are judging the
process you are using. There is nothing
wrong with analytical thought. Yeah. And
if that is your way, that is your way.
Okay? It does not in your terms have to
be a negative experience. You can enjoy
analytical thought. It is only negative
when you begin to judge that you are
judging. Okay? So to expedite or for
this thing to be more expedient, it's
just a matter of integration the whole
thing at one shot. Yes. Okay. Then
integration requires little time. That
is why all of the separation as we have
said that you have been experiencing in
life after life after life has taken
tens of thousands of
lifetimes. Whereas the integration you
are now forming will instead of giving
you a future of tens of thousands of
years only be necessary to create a
future of 2 to 3,000 years. Then you
will not need to be physical anymore. So
living it does it. Yes. Very simple.
Very precise. Very good. Thinking it
makes it just go on and on and on in a
sense. Yes. Although that is a very
simple analogy but it will do. Okay. Got
it. Thanks. Thank you.
Thanks. Love to you. Love to you all.
I heard beautiful, beautiful bells uh
chimed from the top. I don't know. I
can't explain. Oh. All right. It's gone.
And I wonder am I ever going to hear
this again? Maybe. Oh,
understand that the idea in allowing
yourself to extend your senses and be
aware of the background tonal vibration
of all that is and your specific tonal
signature vibration within. It can
always be something you know, something
you feel, something you hear. It is
always there. Apply it and you will hear
it all the time. I have one more
question. All right. A new friend gave
me some owl feathers because he he has
some mystical feeling for them. Owl
feathers. Owl feathers. They're very beautiful. I
Owl feathers. They're very beautiful. I
love birds and just they love you too.
Coincidentally, when I held them, they had a vibration
when I held them, they had a vibration
like a wonderful strong crystal. Gave me
a piece of this. And I Does this have
any meaning for me in my life? Why would
you have it if it had no meaning for
you? I want to know a human. You want to
know the meaning? Do you not already
ascribe symbolic meaning to the idea you
call an owl? No. Wise one. Nothing more
than time to American
Indian type of All right. Just that sort
of is that what applies to you? I don't
know. Why do you not know? I use your
wisdom. Do I have wisdom that will tell
me this? By definition, you exist. Yes.
Therefore, you have all you need to know
anything you need at any given moment.
Thank you. For you are connected to
everything by definition. As soon as you
believe, you do not have to search. I
don't have to search. That's right. I
know already. Yes. Understand everything
you need to know. You mean in the time
frame? I know. You know right now. I
understand. That is your choice to
believe. You do not understand. I
believe I understand. Then you have it.
Thank you. It is that simple. Allow
yourself to simply know that whatever
vibration, any particular symbol you are
choosing to create in your life feels
like to you. Whether you consciously
apply a label to it or not is not
necessary. Simply act as it makes you
feel and you will have the same effect.
I want to be able to know what my birds,
my animals, my friends are
feeling, thinking. They are all
extensions of you and I should know what
these things are. You should not should
anything. I do know. Yes.
Ask them. They will tell you.
Feel them. I've been trying. You have
been what? I am. Yes, you are. Yes, you
are. In exactly the way you need to be.
When you stop judging that you are not,
you will feel as if you are. Thank you.
Thank you. I've got it. Yes, you do.
Sure. You um I have a question. In my
You um I have a question. In my
channeling, I've been aware of a cloaked
figure that has a like a purple collar.
And he's also very much a part of
several lifetimes that involve
um uh moments in which I've had death
experiences that were painful for me and
also involve my head. I was wondering is
this an entity or is it just my fear and
why would he wear the same thing in all
those? It is in a sense an entity. It is
also connected to your fear and it is
connected to the idea of your chosen
embodiment of the archetypal energy of
your fear. It is a companion you have created
fear. It is a companion you have created
to be with you attracted to you in that
way and it has been experienced in
physicality in certain lifetimes. It is
acting as a mirror for you, this
consciousness, and allowing you to
create for yourself the symbolic
representation you need to relate to to
come to terms with the night side of
yourself. Okay. Now, what is the night side to
Okay. Now, what is the night side to
you?
Um, what is the darkness to you?
Well, there's a combination of a lot of
trust and a lot of fear of the night
side. I don't like being closed in rooms in
I don't like being closed in rooms in
the dark or rooms in the
dark. Rooms in the dark. If you have the
idea that you do not perceive in the
dark an end to things, why perceive that
there are walls in the
darkness rather than the infinity of the
dark, the depths of the dark, the
infinity of yourself expanding into
foreverness. You can look at the dark
that way and allow it to be positive for
you. Well, I can when I'm outside. For
some reason, I don't experience the
terror when I'm outside. Do you feel in
this way that there may be connections
to the idea that this figure was present
at your inment?
[Music] Well, um I think in one
Well, um I think in one
lifetime I was killed by him in in I
don't know whether they were tombs, but
they're dark corridors of solid like
solid rock like Egyptian
And um can you not smell the rock?
Sulfurous. Flinty. Yes. Flinty. Um very rough.
Maybe that's the smell of the sear. And
also, can you smell what was in the
inunement with you?
I smell it like parchment
in a sense or maybe the wrappings uh
around bodies or something like that.
Very good.
That's what I'm smelling. Why do you
think that
individual wished you there?
You mean wished me murdered or wished me
in those places? Same
thing.
Um well I associate it with a lifetime
that Ozarus talked about in which I had
uncovered a great some mystery. I see
through my research and that the high
priest wanted me murdered because I had
very good. Okay. The purple robe of the
high priest.
You mean the high
priest? M
okay. What is so strange about that? Our
high priests not capable of murder.
Well, I thought he had me done in rather
than doing me. But you know who is
responsible and that is your projection.
Oh. Oh, I get it. Okay. You follow me?
Yes, I follow you. Now, can you create
for
yourself resurrection from the tomb?
Can you cast aside the blocks of stone
and allow the shafts of the burning sun
of the desert to pierce into the chamber
and flood you with light so that you
know that in any enclosure there are
doors to other dimensions, doors to
freedom, that you are never trapped,
never into tuned without your agreement.
Yes, I can visualize that. Thanks. Thank
you. How do you feel? I feel much
better. Then travel the sands without
fear. Thank you very much.
Sure. For sure.
For sure. It's million. Hey, I want to
know more about the X-shaped spaceship
that came over Northern California. All
we can say at this time is that it was
involved in
electromagnetic readings, balancing,
fluctuations and to some degree involved
some idea that we cannot go into
regarding what you call time travel.
It was a particular type of survey craft
specifically designed for the idea of
the affectation of electromagnetic
fields of planets and shiftings that are
occurring within.
Did they intend to be spotted?
I did do they have a relation to the
types of spaceships that George Lucas
portrayed in Star Wars the ex? So
in your term it was in one plane a flat
cross.
Where did they come from?
Not now.
On the same time there were all we can
give you on that as we have said for now
we do not mean to be mysterious. There
are connections to the idea of time
travel with that graph. Maybe
Maybe
cuz it comes from our future,
all we are allowed, etc., etc.
All right. What were the ping pong ball
shapes on remote eyes? Oh, so they were
the same. Same kind. I mean, okay.
different sorts different different let
us say projections into your reality but
they were the eyes of a consciousness
last Wednesday you said there would be a
cosmic event involving children and my
my thinking was it could either be death
arurous energy in this way is becoming
prominent in the interactions and
connections and will in this way
interact with you this night of your
time after what you call your brain
Right. Now on the day of hands across America,
Now on the day of hands across America,
there was also a
worldwide conscious raising event in
which millions of people in 78 other
countries were running for Africa.
Um did that entire energy of perhaps 30
to 40 million people all doing something
on the same day approximately the same
time? Are you going to ask if it had an
effect? Are you going to ask if it made a
Are you going to ask if it made a
difference? Listen to yourself and catch
yourself before you do, for I will
surely jump down your throat.
Okay, given that
given that you already created an
acceleration in consciousness so that
those things act as symbols reflections
of an effect and a difference that has
already occurred, right?
The question is are are those kinds of
world participatory because this was the
first time that people actually
participated. And before with live aid
we watched any other the whole idea is
as we have said many times action doing
interaction participation willingness
and conviction.
You are giving yourselves the
opportunity to state in any way you can
what you believe and what type of a
world you desire. So of course it has an
effect. one person has an
effect in that sense. Therefore, what
you created with that will be in your
terms geometric. Thank you.
Thank you.
A friend of my roommates.
Oh, first your roommate now. Friend of
your roommate. All right. That was two
weeks ago. Get peasant back. All right.
a friend of your roommate now. Now,
um she's pregnant. Hey. And uh now now.
All right. Now. Okay. And her pregnancy,
she says, is a result of an interaction
says, is a result of an interaction
with something other
than a being on this planet. On on this
planet. Stop.
[Music] There will be
There will be
some explanation from the Arcturus
energy. That is all. Okay. Okay.
[Music]
Um Daryl's voice is extremely loud
tonight. It seems like there's a great
deal of energy coming through in the
morning. The blending of the different
levels is already taking place. I see.
Are you in physical close proximity to
the planet to our planet? No. Okay. Next
question. Um I have a question from a friend Chris
Um I have a question from a friend Chris
White who was here last week asking you
about the actually he he demonstrated
the u he calls them water wands. Yes.
u he calls them water wands. Yes.
And
u is there a name for the for the energy
that that these wands glaze? We're
looking for a name to call these these
water
wands laser because uh laser has such a
limited connotation in our reality
connotation in our reality
here. But we want to construct a name
similar to laser without the L but with
another initial there. Ecstasy or Ecstasy or
energy channeling simultaneous Temporal or
extreme can give you
some
variations to use symbolically if you
wish.
The energy channeling of simultaneous
temporal
oric structures or
streams can allow you to turn
them in that sense. Ecstasy You
You
can allude the idea of crystallin
biomagnetic fluctuation fluctuation
flux flux.
Oh, but flux amplification to simulate
emission of rad radiation which would be
phasers.
Stimulated not simulated. Oh yeah,
simulated right.
We perceive in this way that it will
carry a negative connotation in your
math cont. Yeah,
those are our suggestions. It's up to
you. Okay. Thank you. Thank you. Uh,
another two more questions. Actually, I
think we can make these brief though. I
think we can. Good.
I believe we can do you. How does the
grade of a stone such as an emerald
affect the energy field? In other words,
if it's a very rough uh stone versus a
clear emerald, clarity and precision of
cut can in your terms make a great deal
of difference in the effect. Okay. All
right. That answers that question. And u
next question is regarding the symbols
that we uh were spoking of
earlier. I feel like these
symbols many symbols for that matter
would be able to suggest action on my
part. See it's neat to go through life.
I do go through life and I um have faith
that what is occurring is exactly what I
have chosen for the moment.
But a symbol suggesting an
action does not necessarily relate to
the idea that your energy motion, your
emotional activation of the essence of
that symbol needs to take the form that
the symbol represents.
Okay? It is only there as a lure.
Okay? To activate the proper stream
within you. Do not assume that the
stream will head into a logical
manifestation of the symbol that
activated the stream to begin with. Say
that again, please. There is no need to
assume that the energy stream will flow
towards a manifestation of the symbol
that activated the stream to begin with.
Always allow the unexpected
to of course. But as regards my career,
my activities in the film business, I if
I'm going in exits and going out
entrances, I'm wondering if these
symbols are suggesting that I maybe take
a different route. Maybe take a That is
what your imagination seems to be
suggesting, then follow it.
Do not wonder. If it occurs to you, act
on it and see what happens. Well, it
only goes to so far as to uh suggest
that that might be possible, not to
suggest which back route to take. It's
like you go, okay, well, where are the
backgrounds? Follow your feeling without
needing a picture. See, at that point,
it ceases to
exist. It does not cease to exist. It
simply transforms into something you
will not allow to be real. I'll accept
that statement. All right. No, I I don't
I'm not saying that it transforms
something into something that I'm not
allowed. May I ask you a question? Sure.
Can you
imagine that you can have a feeling
without a picture? Sure. Can you imagine
yourself simply following a feeling much
in the same way that what you call a
magnetic needle would simply follow the
flow of magnetism? Simply finding
yourself feeling like going this way,
then stopping, then going that way, then
stopping, then backing up, then
stopping, then climbing those stairs,
then stopping, then knocking on that
door, then seeing who answers. Sure,
that's what I do. All
right. And who has answered? Well, uh, I
I I don't have I don't want to run down
a list here. It would take But in
general, what type of responses are you
getting? Well, recently I haven't been doing a
Well, recently I haven't been doing a
lot of knocking because I haven't been
has I has hasn't felt like I should be
knocking. It feels like I should be
knocking, but now I'm I'm translating
the feeling to what specific activity
I'm going to do. I'm I'm going to
actually be doing, and I'm I'm still in
the process of formulating those
activities. All right. Okay. Although
one thing that did occur is I met a
woman here at the channeling who was a
producer expressed interest in my script
right and we're going to set up a
meeting right but aside from that I
don't I don't create my life around that
one particular incident I continue to
act in life oh right on a variety of
things so I am doing these things but
I'm as I go through life I I see
something I go oh gee it feels like I
might be able to take a hint from these
and that's as far as the feeling goes
all right then let it emerge to whatever
level it will and act on what you give
yourself. Okay. At this point in the
middle of the process there is nothing
more we can share. Okay. Great. Thank
you. Thank you for you. I on Monday
night um I was
I was present um when the Alurus energy
came through and I heard you say that
that the beings were not experiencing
sorrow that they they were reflecting
the sorrow that we as a mass
consciousness held but that the being
itself was not. How come the facial
expression that Daryl was because the
physical channel is a part of your
society is enough and thus was
experiencing the release of those
sorrows that have been held in simply by
virtue of existing in and among your
society. Okay. So yeah, I don't know what the
Okay. So yeah, I don't know what the
problem is the being some person are not
carrying sorrow
about just the love. Ace
um approximately three weeks ago, I was
too ill to make it here on a Wednesday
and I asked a friend to come in and see
if there's any enlightment on the
illness that you could shed in my area.
Thanks. And I would like to say this. He
brought the tape rack. I was ill at the
time and you gave me more than two to
three minutes and I have over
approximately $50,000 in counseling and
doctor bills as far as enlightening me
on the illness. And believe me, I do
thank you. Thank you for co-creating the
reality in your existence and for
switching on your own life. Well, you
also mentioned something and all you
said was a brass bell and that's all you
would give on it. What so happened that
the a lady in the same house that I live
just happened to have of course a brass
and I I had no I all I did was get it
and uh I I
U all I can say is the frequency my body
started shuttering it was the most
aesthetic something about the frequency
of the brass fell and it was I don't
know whether what it was like physical
mental spiritual yes I got goosebumps
again but it's it's that whatever that
but it's it's that whatever that
frequency wasn't the noise it was the
frequency the per all is vibration yes
and you were forming a vibrational I'm
going to
a harmonic resonance to the vibration
that lets you know you are on an even
keel. So that it felt like it was
actually a healing process. Oh, an
instantaneous identification with your
zero rest state of perfection by
reflecting that tone to yourself that
represents the vibration of your
existence and your being in and at a
zero rest state of peace.
that harmony, right? Well, the the the
spiritual sensation I mean the body you
kind of forgot about. In fact, I was in
bed and I decided that's the end of that
and I got up and resumed my all are
blended in the one tone. Fantastic. That
well again that I do appreciate and
believe me. Thank you for chiming in and
I
also also this is on another subject
which I would like to ask anything that
you have on it. Quite a few of us went
up to the the place that I mentioned to
you, a mountain top up in the
motherboard country in Lake Tahoe. And
we went up there for the three-day,
4-day weekend.
Uh this is where the spaceship, as I
commented to you at one time, and you
said yes, I would be on it, which I've
been in ecstasy ever since then. But we
all went right up. It's like there was
three of us, one of the ladies here now.
We went to an area up on the peak of it.
It's a whole plateau. And I don't know
quite how to explain it, but one lady
had put a a crystal over. She didn't
know where the the area was, but she put
it around all around the area. And when
it hit right over the mountain top, this
crystal started making a big circle. And
I was watching her fingers to see if she
was moving it. She was I didn't quite
know what was going on. But there's
something I don't really understand it,
but all I know is when we got up to this
peak, the sensation of unity I have
never experienced this lifetime. This is
an energy vortex, a doorway and a
gateway to all probabilities like any
forces energy upon your planet. And that
a free zone
the unity that I mean there's like no
difference in bodies. It's like I said
belong to all is one in the vortex.
Now we plan on putting a community up
there and this is where gohead have a
good time. And also as I mentioned the last
time. And also as I mentioned the last
time in a spaceship idea it seems like
I'd like to to to establish the words
that you've given us here and establish
the same concept of the polarity etc etc
into more of a spiritual is your concept
created with your help.
We are always willing to reflect to you
what you are already capable of. Trust
your imagination. That is all the help
you need. Any other guidelines you can I
mean you've given me guidelines. I hate
to even ask the You've got it all. Thank
you. Bashar, is it all right? Uh we've
had a a a film crew and you have uh on
the channel's body a microphone and they
want to leave. Is it possible to remove
it or shall we take a break without
disturbing the connection?
You may all take a short break. [Music] Children
alike that you may recognize
yourselves in the mirrors that you
created each other.
Children but nurture
yourself. Nurture yourself.
Don't your children are your children as
well. That That
is your
seeds of the transformation
of that which comes to
you are the
children. Not what we have fashioned
ourselves to be. of
children. As you are born of you, you
are your own gateways. Your own gateways
into the realities that you wish to be
where we are. We are since
we your children go
out. So let people know who they are. Your society
society
now to go. Why not kill? kill?
neither
male nor female.
But the gateway. The
gateway. You do not want to
release yourself from that which does
not nurture
you. But all the connections you
form are your children. You are your own
children. You are creation. Give birth
to
everything. The creation loves you as
it's true. One
moment shall continue for
now so that the energy has opportunity
to
acclimate as it comes from different
dimensional plane in this way and
associations at this time can allow
there to be energy levels that are felt
by the emotional bodies of yourselves
and the physical channel that will be
not maintainable for length of your
time. The idea is that they form a
gateway, a matrix through which your
children are being born in a sense to
you, reorienting themselves to the
transformational experience of your
earth. And that many experiences that
you have had of what seem to be
pregnancies that are
not in a sense
there and all different variations of
consciousness coming into your physical
reality and not remaining for very long.
Pregnancies that start and do not
finish in this way are simply the
testings of the
waters. The projections of energy and
the initiation on your part of the
initiation on your part of the
surrounding of that energy with the
consciousness so that it may become used
to your level of
experience. But allow that level of
experience to also alter itself. So that
now that the children are being born are
the same energies that were being born
before that did not complete physical
lives in those early terms of birth.
And in this way allow themselves now to
manifest full lies in your
transformational age with the complete
identification of the matrix through the
gateway of Arcturus which is assisting
you in this way in the clarification
identification and
purification of that which represents
your divine
energy your divine matrix and brings
upon your plane of existence the clear
light of creation truth. Those children
being born to you now now
as
communication continues in what you call
your days and your weeks ahead from our
turns. As it in your terms crystallizes,
so shall you find that there are
tonalities, harmonic
vibrations opening and igniting and
crystallizing ideas within you
emotionally, emotional doorways within
you are being touched primarily by that
communication. And you may find
beginning tonight of your time that the
qualities of your life and the qualities
of your dream realities may take on more
of the recognition of those emotional
tones. As you begin to allow yourselves
to remember, more and more of who you
are, you will also then recognize that
this is a primary activation for those
emotional portions of your doubt, the
emotional quality of your being. That is
what will allow you to nurture
yourselves as children of all that is.
In the same way you will nurture your
children and they will nurture you to
remember that you are children of all
that is. So that your entire
is. So that your entire
civilization will then exemplify itself
as children of
all. There will
be acceleration in the
communications and solidifying and
crystallizing of the communications from
our course
continuing again in the next days and
weeks of your
time. We thank you for your sharing in
that particular level of openness and
expansion. And in this
way, we will also continue to extend our
love to you and our energy in all the
openings of all the endeavors that you
feel, think, and know and believe.
think, and know and believe.
Sherry
there has been in fact a definite change
in what I am beginning to perceive or
hear physically in my head.
uh and it it has taken on a very real
whistle and at various times during the
day it's it's recognizable even it's
beginning to be recognizable even when
I'm in a lot of noise physically
does that have anything to do with that
particular energy it is connected now
that you are beginning to open up to the
reception of that energy which pours
forth and bases your plane of existence
and you are opening up to recognizing
the background so to speak tone of all
that is and your identification to its
primal matrix you
matrix you
I have three or four questions I'd like
to put out at this time may they are all
one all
right first of all you've probably
covered this with some of the others but
I haven't been here that much could you
explain how we change our frequency so
that we are able to tune in more. By
simply knowing that you are now a
different idea than you previously were,
the frequency automatically shifts to
match what in your imagination says you
are now the idea of
by definition. If you can conceive of an
idea, you are that idea. You are that
frequency. You are operating on that
frequency automatically in order to be
able to perceive the concept. Well,
that's pretty good. Very simple. Uh what
Don just spoke about about a noise I
have had a ringing in my for a long
time. Is that a a physical or a
frequency? Well, it has a physiological
counterpart, but it is simply tuning in
to the mass electromagnetic
consciousness of your world. The carrier
wave of creation.
Thank you. Okay. The other questions I
had have to do with the property that my
friend talked to you about up in Grass
Valley. Um we were on this mountaintop
and we perceived uh she told you a the
feeling of the vortex. We observed a I
don't know whether call it a ditch or
whatever and we sort of got the idea
that this was made it was at the
mountain top so it could not have been
created by water. Uh we got the idea
that it was created by a landing
craft many years ago and there was it
formed a circle although we didn't find
the completion of that circle. Is there
a central depression in the middle of
the circle? Uh yes. Yes, there is. And
the other thing that we were trying to
locate, perhaps you can give us a little
perception on this. Three of us
independently got the idea of there
being a rock as a marker. Uh I got the
idea that it was glazed and there seems
to be a symbol on it, either a cross or
a plus or an X. I wasn't sure which. And
I wondered if you could shed some light
on what that might be. Not at this time.
Search within yourselves.
And it may assist you to form an
emotional idea or link with what you
call the seven sisters.
Elaborate on that. Plleades.
I guess we'll have to do some study on
that one. Uh the last thing I had was
about the water on this property. Um
there are some feel that it has some
healing qualities.
It is electromagnetically in that way.
It talks align with the primal matrix.
Thank you very much. It has crystallin
qualities. That's what we got. Thank you very much.
That's what we got. Thank you very much.
Bashar. Bashar.
Last week we chatted about uh my
counterparts. Hey, I'm wondering if I
were to give you a name of someone who I
I have a sense that is one of my
counterparts, would you be able to No
more. Okay. Still in the middle of the
process. Ah, okay. That's fine. Another
question. Uh, I I'm in a relationship with a
Uh, I I'm in a relationship with a
10-year-old
girl wherein I am finding myself or
placing myself in a parental position.
Hey, and uh it's quite an interesting
progression of events. And um I observe
the purpose for it obviously being our
interaction as we have it. Now I'm
wondering um can you give me any
reflection on what connections I might
have with her in a past sense?
Mother whose mother she was my mother.
Yeah. That's
interesting. What the hell is uh how
long ago is
this? Our perception is that it has
happened a few times. There is no
perception of the exact time flow. Okay.
When I first uh came into contact with
her, I knew that that there was
something happening in our relationship
immediately. I didn't know what was to
come, but I just I knew that we were
there that she had attracted me and I
her for a purpose. What did I do to piss
her off so much?
That's actually a joke. But if if
there's something to say about that, I'm
interested.
You were unruly.
I detective con in there.
Think of lace.
Okay, I'm thinking about lace. All
right, then
what? See where that goes.
Okay, this is interesting because she is
reflecting of the polarity of what you
indicate was my unruliness because she
is expressing that or has been
expressing that to some degree. Although
we've been chatting and she seems to be
um aligning with a positive flow.
Very nicely. Hey ladies,
I get a sense of nobility. Very
nobility. Very
good. You got a number. 17.
17. Very good. 17. What?
What?
Years. That figures in.
However,
17 I what? What what I'm thinking about
is um centuries
centuries
17. Is that what ice? Okay.
[Laughter] Okay. Okay.
Yeah.
view riding in an enclosed
carriage. See, smell,
taste, the air, the sights, the
sounds. Uhhuh. You
Uhhuh. You
are to some degree in this life
attempting to live up to her
expectations of you.
or in that life you will want to hang
around with [Laughter] [Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music] rabble home.
rabble home.
I know. That is what we can share with
you at this time. explore that symbology
and those feelings. See where that takes
you from here. Thank you very much.
Thank you guys. I was wondering what the
Arcturus energy meant by the children uh
not being male nor female.
Arturous energy was referring to itself
and but but they said that the children
would be neither male nor female. Are
they just talking about the energy?
Arcturus energy was referring to itself.
Okay. [Music]
[Music]
Yes. In a way. Remember
way. Remember
that none of
you are in a sense male and/or
female until that combined energy
translate out into a polarity within a
particular frame of reference where that
idea is
needed. It is not that you have male
female energy that channels through into
physicality. It is that you are energy
that channels through into the idea of
maleness and femaleness. Sure. Hey um
how would we perceive um their energy
otherwise say if um if they never told
us that say if um many of you will find
that to you it will seem to be female.
Many will think it to be male and it
will fluctuate at certain times hitting
fluctuate at certain times hitting
whatever point of your polarity you are
exploring and that is one of the ideas
of the emotional keys it is hitting in a
sense its energy is playing your
emotional keyboard.
Yes. Is the Arcturus energy associated
at all with the Leorian reemergence
to some degree? But for now, allow
yourself to maintain a symbolic
idea. Follow me. No, I'm not sure.
Keep what you are calling an
emergence as an analogy.
rather than a physical literalness. Oh
yes, I assume. It's all right. Yes.
Would you comment on the organization
awakening and what we can do to
facilitate it progress? Organization of
wake and what is your
perception? We teach metaphysics and
spirituality. Is it fun? Indeed it is.
Is it fun? Indeed it is.
In this way, if you are being of service
in that sense is not your own opinion
more valid to you than mine.
What do you need to know from me then?
Perhaps there's something that we have
not become consciously aware of that we
could facilitate its growth with.
Do you know it is of service?
Yes. [Applause]
[Applause]
Do you know it attracts individuals as
it needs to?
Yes. And can only attract the
individuals that are functioning on the
same wavelength.
Yes. No. Maybe. Yes. Yes.
Do you know that it is reaching
everyone everywhere on different wavelengths as
everywhere on different wavelengths as
they create themselves to know it
whether physical or not?
I have that side.
All right. carry that view and you will
simply allow yourself to know that
everyone is getting the idea in the way
they need to create it for
themselves and all of you together once again are
and all of you together once again are
interacting much in the same way when
you are out of your bodies so to speak
in dream reality
anyway move yes so that it is the
paradox of being awake when you are
asleep
Follow me. Yeah. Well, I've been up
some shark. I have someone here very
dear to me. This is my son in his
lifetime. And when he was an infant,
when I brought him home from the
hospital, uh, at one point,
um, he looked when he was just a newborn
right home from the hospital. He looked
at me from the crib with the eyes of
such wisdom that it frightened me. I
literally had to go into the other room
and hide behind the corner. Could not
stand to see your own reflection.
But it seems that he was fullblown and
all wise and all knowing and a total
person. You all are. Yes. And of course
the child has not yet forgotten that.
What occurs around the approximate age
of between what you call seven and nine
to me
to you. to me to him to him
that you would recognize as the idea of
something quote unquote out of the
ordinary.
Do you have recollection? No.
Does he? No. No. Close your eyes.
Think of yourself at the age of
seven. Feel what it is like to be seven.
What do you feel? All
feel? All
right. Anything else? Curious to do
things. I I'm I want to be active. Very
good. Do you find that in your
imagination a specific idea?
comes to your consciousness that allows
you to exercise your curiosity in a
specific direction. And if you follow
it, where does it
lead? Do not think about it. Say what
you feel immediately toward creation.
All right? Creativity.
Creativity. Do you find that as you
allow your curiosity to move you towards
the idea of
creativity that you are not
alone? Yes. Who is with
you? What is with you? Describe it as
you
can. Do not think.
simply say
um more or less a feeling. Um it's hard
to
say. I'm really Does it have an
inonation? How does it make you feel? It
makes me feel happy
and
it all right. Hold on to that feeling
for now.
Move
yourself in a sense
ahead in your time frame to what you
would consider a strong psychic
experience or intuitive or telepathic
connection. When did that occur?
When I was a child. I don't remember
when, but it was before I went into the
military. I had a a dream of being in
the military just before I went in. And
when I got there, I felt that I knew all
of most of the people in my platoon.
Like, we all knew each other. We knew
that we were all supposed to be there.
Very good. And we were all there. Yes.
Now, do you have some idea of who you
before? who you sensed surrounded you and lured
who you sensed surrounded you and lured
you with your
curiosity. Can you sense the idea of you
and them acting in this light as a truth
so to speak? Whether you are in physical
contact or not, no matter how far you
may seem to diverge, can you not feel
the parallel
connections of energy?
Not so much anymore. All
right. Allow it to be a background. We
are not saying it should become primary,
but simply allow yourself to know that
as each and every one of you diverge,
you are altogether drawing from the
group, the strength, the pool to allow
you the opportunity to experience the
offshoot in your own way. You will find
that as you proceed and
progress, there may be in your terms
interactions again with some and or all of those
again with some and or all of those
individuals in different ways, crossing
paths, intertwining, interweaving,
forming a
cable made out of many interwoven
threads that can in and of
itself become a line of strength, a
conduit, and a communication link in
time yet to come when you will need it
and when your world will require
it. The following. Yes, there
there
have been many
types of warriors.
Now is the opportunity to apply all of
that in this sense to
become in your terms a soldier of life
life
and one of
peace. For there is the strength and the
connection to all that you have ever
been. Call upon
the ideas and the
ideals that you created in what you call
Rome of ancient time in your
civilization. Not that you need apply
once again. The ideas in negative ways,
in warlike ways, but the ideals were
clear to you
then and are clear to you
now. Centurion
continue to walk your path.
Yay. Um, a number about 6 months ago, I
had a dream that uh my friend was just
ready and before we could get her off to
um a
facility, I picked up her shirt and
there was the baby pit. So, um, we just
got on with it and when the baby came
out, she said, "Does it have all fingers
and toes?" And I said, "Well, yeah, and
it also has three
nipples." So, the energy felt male, but
it was not a male. And the the nipples
formed a triangle.
So, in the dream, I was thinking that's
weird. And just then, I woke up and I
felt that it was a star seed child.
and one that recognizes very distinctly
the connection of the
triad in your civilization, our
civilization and that of Syria.
Okay. And
representationally brings nourishment
from all trees.
Well then um how does that how was that
connected with me? Why was it birthed
from my friend or was that just
significant? Just significant. Well, was it
Just significant. Well, was it
significant rather than uh prophetic?
In a sense, it is both. Although
understand again, there is no such thing
as prediction of the future. It is a
sensing of the energy of the
consciousness to be born now. It is a
sensing now, not so much a prophecy. For
you are not reaching into any future to
know what you have just shared. You are
sensing what exists now of the
consciousness to be born.
Yes. And it will allow you once again to
reflect upon your own connections to
triads to interactions to relationships
and once again allow us to remind you
the children and this is one example
will remind you who you are.
That is one example and you may take it
as a communication from that
consciousness. It is also the beginning
of your ability to be in communication
with the consciousness before it is
born. So that you can create communication all
So that you can create communication all
the way through birth and into
life and know each other and know your
one moment. Uh, I have a great pull to
go to Africa and I'm going to go. How
wonderful. Is that there's a a feeling of going
Is that there's a a feeling of going
home and is that a feeling because I'm
going to reexperience energy from the
other place that I came from or
experience the entities
from another place. Search out the idea
you call in that general area of your
world. The don
and also allow yourself to experience
whatever else you create your path to
be. Uhhuh. I also totally appreciate
your love and your patience. I have no
patience. I have no need of patience.
I am enjoying every moment far too much
for me. Thank you.
Thank you.
Yes, Bashar. I wanted to share the
synchronicity that our son who was born
two years ago also has three nipples.
No. Right. Uh something else. Uh oh.
What density is uh Arcturus? No
correlation at the time. Okay. Thank
you. Uh this weekend I went on a camping
trip to Joshua Tree uh National
Monument. You may consider it seventh,
but that will do as a standin. Thank
you. Thank you. uh and I uh was drawn to
a particular area and climbed through
some rocks and I my attention was drawn to
rocks and I my attention was drawn to
this uh huge rock formation. And as I
looked at it, I became aware that it was
it was an an a weatherworn but
ancient carving of a huge what looked
like Mayan
uh head very very large. What uh was
that Mayan or what could you share with
with us? Most Mayan, Most Mayan,
Leorian,
let us leave it as a symbol for that
idea for right now. So it it had
connection to the the uh American
Indians in that area. Yes.
And it was an
actual carving of us. Yes, I know. It is
the product of the carving of mentality.
product of the carving of mentality.
Mhm. It is
It is
the shifting into position of the
elements necessary to create the
image. So no direct idea of carving was
necessary. more uh in the in the general magic
more uh in the in the general magic
sense. Yes. Very good. Thank you. More
in the representative sense, the energy
essence sense and the archetypal
embodiment sense of nature spirit.
Thank you.
One moment.
It is all right to simply refer to this
evening's session as our tourist if you
wish. Thank you,
Y. Um, I have a question. In this last
week, I've woken up several times with
the message that there's three types of
dreams, and I can't or I haven't as
yet really identified what those three
types of dreams or what the message
means. There is the dream
reality that you consider to be the
dream when you are asleep.
There is the dream of being awake and
there is the dream of the dimension of
imagination which is in a sense the
blending of the two.
Good on this the dream. I think you just
answered my question. I'm not
sure. You mentioned uh about several
weeks ago that I would be a visitor in
my dream and I haven't paid attention to
dreams for so long I don't even think
about them. So I can hardly wait to get
to sleep and have a dream.
And this has been about three weeks now
that I have the dreams and it's like
it's almost like somebody pushed a
button on fast forward. As soon as I
wake up, it's so flashy. I it it's so
frustrating. I've not been able to get
the concept of any of them. And this has
been nightly a
dream. And as you just mentioned before,
the there are waking dreams. It is all
there. Your opportunity to allow it into
Your opportunity to allow it into
consciousness is to allow your physical
reality to become a dream. To allow your
dream reality to become
awake, to blend the two in the
imagination. And also our
suggestion is to allow yourself to
continue when you
awake to remain
laying down for a while and simply
drift. Do not get up
and it could see what comes back. Very
good. Give yourself five to 10 minutes.
Do not be in a rush. Oh dear. Pace yourself
Pace yourself
accordingly. All right. Very good. Thank
you. Thank you.
Good. I have another question um about
the devices that I've been seeing or in
particular this one device. Um I've been
visualizing a copper tubing in a spiral
that forms half a sphere. Then in the
middle is um a plate that has some it's
I don't think it's brass, but I don't
think it's iron either. It's sort of
like a combination of the two. the I'm
not sure what the continue. Anyway,
okay. And then on the bottom is another
coil um copper coil that finishes this
the sphere to complete it. And then
there's a
central um there's a central um column or tube
um there's a central um column or tube
that goes through a crystal in the
center. Hey, and I was wondering this is
a variation of the idea we have
described recently of your time. Uh-huh.
In this way, it is a disperser, a
collector of energy. We simply described
it in the fashion of having a central
spherical crystal through which is a rod
and having a central layer of gold wire
spun in spiral patterns but in a flat
plane in what you would call a Fibonacci
spiral double spiral counterclockwise
clockwise. In this way, four strands
from the clockwise spiral will
interpenetrate the crystal sphere which
also the rod interpenetrates
perpendicular to the plane of the
Fibonacci spiral matrix and will touch
the rod in the center four from one
direction four from the other direction
forming the whole cross in that way and
there will then be insulative layer
above the Fibonacci matrix and below and
then another plate shape of gold with a
hollow hemisphere over the crystal in
the center through which the golden rod
will interpenetrate and attach to and
extend up and down and is pointed to a
diameter in that way to a length of what
you would call the eye of approximately
three diameters from the center of the
crystal. Mhm. This will draw forth and
allow there to be a transformation of
electromagnetic energy in a way that
will allow there to be the infusion in
your oric field of
eternalness of harmonic synchronization of
of harmonic synchronization of
longevity of stasis.
The entity that gave me the the
figure says he's from your
planet and or the device, right? And he
says he's not on your ship. No, he's on
your planet. So,
um he also he said for the time being
that I might as well just consider it a
toy. Yes. And that it would help with my
headaches. can when it balances the oric
field and allows it again to bring you
back to your zero rest point. Okay. And
then someone other some other individual
mentioned that it might be similar to a
magic wand. Well, in a sense, but in
this way it is a more specific variation
of lens of magnetic electromagnetic
riveting lens. Uhhuh. So it's not like
what you just described
um at Marggo's house more like a what
was it like generators or conductors or
something? Okay. It is similar to that
idea but having different effects
because of its slightly different
configuration. Okay. And the um follow your own
Okay. And the um follow your own
description for you. Okay. It is simply
that I am letting you know it is a
similar variation. Okay. Of the same
idea using the same energy in different
ways. Yeah. Because my vision of it has
like the plate has holes in it but I
can't. It doesn't seem like a spiral.
No, not your version.
The spiraling in your version is in the
coil on either side.
Right. So I could create this and it
would really Yeah. You can also simply
create it in your imagination. It will
do the same thing. Okay. And then I have
one other question. Um although it may
be in your terms fun to physically
create it so that in this way others may
also receive benefit from the effect.
Yeah, that's what I was thinking. Um
um a couple years ago I had a dream that
involved unearthing
or you know like a dig or an
archaeological dig that May I ask you a
question? Yes. Did the information on
that device seem to come from within the
idea of being within Crystal Dome?
No. All right. Follow that and see what
you get.
So, place myself in my imagination
inside of a crystal dome or simply trace
the information back to the being. Okay.
And see where they are. Okay.
Um in this dream that I
experienced um there was a woman who initially when
um there was a woman who initially when
I met her was standing in like a
um I guess a hidden crypt that had been
hidden for
centuries and she was wearing like a
real I don't know schmaty a real sort of
messy dress you know and then And the
next day and I asked her, I said, "Since
you've been here for centuries, have you
read all these books?" And she said,
"No." And the next day I came back and
she was fully nine months pregnant.
And she said to me, "Thank you for
suggesting I read the
books." And she then explained a little
bit of how she got pregnant and
said, "Um, I'm now I'm going to go home
to Yugoslavia."
And the next morning I saw her walking
across the ocean and she was a giant and
she was on top of the water. I was
wondering it all it came to me that this
was the goddess energy in one form and
it said yes. And I've had other dreams
that [Music]
[Music]
involve a urgency to get back to
Yugoslavia and dream find the oracular
grandmother within you. miraculous
grandmother. Okay. Also, I've had dreams
that involve the use of a
snake on the body for healing. And the
snake comes from Greece andor Egypt.
Egypt. And has and some in this one
dream I'm supposed to lead others back
to Greece or Egypt in order to use this
snake. Understand this can all be taken
symbolically. You can literalize it in
that way and at the same time allow
yourself to simply know the whole idea
will be attracted together when the
timing is correct. It is not something
that in this way you need to create in
the form of being a leader with
followers. Right. I understand that.
stolen. You tell me anything more about those
You tell me anything more about those
dreams in terms of the snake cuz it was
a very literal snake, physical snake.
But in this way, though it has
connections into what you call past
lives, it still at that time also stood
for the idea of ancient wisdom. Oh,
okay.
And if you explore the
idea far enough back, you will also find
connections to the archetypal
dragon along another offshoot of what
you call your qualian connection.
Okay. Thank you very much. I really appreciate
Thank you very much. I really appreciate
all your help.
Next week of your time a little bit
further idea of Jac Shadrach.
Thank you from the source.
Thank you.
Hey, this last week has been for a
while. Yes.
And somewhere in that though is my
stepfather. And I know he's there and
yet I can't get a sense of where and how
he fits in with Why do you need that
first in order to proceed?
I wouldn't be first because I I felt
uh myself in his
physiology at in one of the Spanish past
lives. All right.
And I feel that there's a connection
between that and the the nun. And my two
sisters and my other son Colin are also
connected somehow with the monastery or
the the nun something there connection
there and
um it just makes it regret if I can
understand these connections. Why do you
think so? It has in the past and then so
what is now
it feels unfinished change the idea of
yourself you are finished you are complete you
you are finished you are complete you
are ever growing ever changing you will
never be finished you are finished now
you are in a sense once again though
again it may be your way if you prefer
it but you are breaking down into many
many components that will then create
much time in which to
research. You do not need them first in
order to
proceed. Oh, proceed. And you will know
what you need to know when you need to
know it. You will see it. You will
recognize it in the
present. You will not need to search the
past to create your future. the following.
the following.
Are you sure?
Yes. Disappointing, but it's Why?
[Music] Because I felt like I was just right on
Because I felt like I was just right on
the verge of seeing how it all
connected. May I ask you a question?
Are you sure I
may? Why are you upside down?
Well, why am I upside down? Yes. Why are
you upside down?
Because you're upside down. I'm upside
down, but I perceive you as upside down.
You perceive me as upside down. A little
sideways. All
All
right. Does that mean we are both upside
down at the same time? Yes. Then if we
were both upside down, why do you not
appear to be right side up to me?
I don't know.
Is it all not a point of view? What is
What is
your perspective in life of life as
life?
What is life?
What is life? What is life? We'll start
with the easy one. What is life?
You see, we have learned to appreciate
your sense of humor. Life
Life
is the opportunity for us to life is the
opportunity for me to you can keep the
answer just as simple as the question.
What is life?
Life light. Life
light. Life is a simulation of life.
It sometimes is.
Oh, why not go for the real thing?
In the process of doing you are what? In
the process of doing in the process is
why it is like life
live. Live,
Live,
just live. Enjoy. Attract,
create, inter relate as you feel any
inter relationships you form with any
other so-called
identities. Act upon them as you will
within your feelings and simply know
that whatever comes to you is all that
is necessary.
Okay? You will always only create
exactly exactly
precisely perfectly the amount of
knowledge about any particular
connection that you need to know to be
who you are in that given moment. No
more, no less. Perfect. One for one. act
on that and you will add that idea to
yourself, become another idea and
attract more information to represent
the new idea. You now happen to be but
no more and no less than the new idea
you are.
Okay, got it. One step at a time
in the now. Each step not being taken so
much because of what it will lead you
to, but for what it
is now.
Then what you are heading for will come
to you.
And you will not have to walk so far,
nor be so
tired, nor search under every rock.
All right,
you. Thank you. I wonder if you could
tell me what past relationship I've had
with my present husband and what lesson
it is that I'm there to learn.
Lesson. There's got to be some lesson
here. Really? You think so? It just
seems that way. Seems that way. Well, if
it seems that way, then you tell me.
What is the lesson? I haven't been able
to figure it out. Figure it out. It
should be obvious. What are you refusing
to allow to be conscious?
Something I don't want to admit to. Be
honest.
We both have to be right all the time.
Ah, right. What is being right?
I guess it's the feeling of superiority.
Superiority. If you are creating the idea of
If you are creating the idea of
superiority, how can you share a
relationship with an equal?
That's a good question. Thank you. I
will leave it to you to figure out.
Could you tell me what relationship we
might have had in the past? Many,
hundreds, thousands.
Is the current one
um maybe working out something that did
occur in the past? You can make that
connection, but it is also for its own
sake right now. What you want to work
out in the
present, what you want to learn and
understand about yourself in the
presence. Yeah, that's what I was hoping
you'd sort of shed a little more light
on. Click.
I think the bumps were done. [Music]
[Music]
So you are then groping in the dark. I
think so. Yeah. All right. Now we have
already brought to light the
idea of the game of playing
superior. Is that not enough to learn?
It doesn't seem like that's the whole
thing. Oh, what else might you imagine
it might be?
You don't know. I was looking for a
relationship that was uh a little better
exchange between Oh, it is a perfect
exchange. It is an exchange of exactly what idea
It is an exchange of exactly what idea
you have of yourself and everything else
and what idea he has of himself and
everything else. Perfect reflections of
what you both believe about each other
and your
reality. It is a perfect exchange.
If you do not prefer what you are
exchanging, change the idea of your and
you will see the reflection change.
All right.
Understand again the idea of
soulmates is the idea of already knowing
you are complete in ecstasy so that you
can attract a reflection to show you
that. Not that you need someone to complete
Not that you need someone to complete
you because then all you will attract is
someone to reflect your belief in your
[Music] incompleteness. That is a soulmate too.
incompleteness. That is a soulmate too.
But what you will exchange with that
soulmate you may not
prefer. But you will learn something
from you will learn how to prefer
without
Yes. Preference is the recognition of
the reality and the vibration you simply
know yourself to be. Judgment is the
invalidation of what you do not
prefer. And when you invalidate what you
do not prefer, you attach yourself to
it. Because to invalidate is to exchange
energy with it and put you on the same
freeway. That is what you are
invalidating. and so invalidating your
Italian. Thank you. Thank you very much,
Masher. Yay. I uh along that same line
as sharing, I realized
uh uh the recent weeks that everyone
that you're sharing with and know that
you're sharing with at that moment is
your soulmate at that moment. So So
everyone's a soulmate.
cuz you're sharing that that vibration.
That's all a soulmate is. Yes. Right.
For you. Thank you for your sharing and
the creation of that reality in our
interaction. Any
Any
suggestions on where I might be able to
buy a piece locally?
You can make one. How? I'll make a pipe
and call it peace.
Allow yourself to be attracted to one
that already exists that will call out
it to you. All right? Or make one. But
does it have a particular shape? You
will know it when you see it. You will
feel it. Do not be in too much of a
hurry. Okay.
Thank you for
have your you personally or your people
applied anything that you have learned
from us on your planet. Oh yes, we
applied in forming the model of the
simolacum by which we interact with you
so that it can become more
blended. That is one way. Okay. And now
that relates specifically to your
interaction with us. Is there anything
that you apply simply
for enhancement of of your reality for
your own fun on your planet?
In this way, it is an opportunity to
form in a sense, let us say, a
holographic model of the interaction of
your energy so that any being interested
in all the different ways that all that
is can manifest itself through your
civilization can tune in and learn from
that. Do they tune in and learn and and
don't take it any further than that? Or
do they actually act? They apply it as
they need to, but in this way recognize
that many of the ideas of how you apply
simply do not apply to our civilization.
Yes, I do realize that. And that's kind
of what I was getting at. What does
apply? What can you use? What do you
use? The idea of how intention can be
The idea of how intention can be
applied. Intention. How so? In the way
we are using it to communicate with you.
Okay. All right. That is the primary
tool that we let us
say actively
apply which you don't normally apply in
your society because it's not necessary.
Say yes. Well, you cuz we're hard cases.
That's why it's a
why it's a
joke. Put people here.
That does not apply either. Right.
However, you are also a bunch of
softies. You're definitely limitation.
You're definitely limitation.
Yeah. I I really enjoyed that last week.
I guess it was last week that you stated
that. I really got a lot of strength out
of that. I mean, I was feeling strong
before that, but it it really put the
cherry on the cake, you know, or
whatever you put your
I also wanted to ask you uh you're
uh you're
right. Do you have flying animals? Yes.
Similar to our birds.
Yes. Okay. And
Okay. And
also some of what you would
call mammal that sword.
Nothing so large as a horse. [Music]
[Music]
Okay. Um I'm going to get I'm going to
get back to relationships. I I find the
interweaving of um I can't spell
synchronicity in relationships
fascinating because I see I'm seeing
this relationship that I'm having with a
10-year-old as a parent and a
relationship that I have with her mother
as a lover with me.
Obviously, I have purposes with both
that are very very strong. One didn't
just happen to come with the other one.
But I which is viewed as which is viewed as you
one of the one of the things that I'm
exploring with with her mother is uh
I shared warmth and love that I hadn't
shared before. die. Now I'm wondering
what can you reflect to
me past relationships with her
mother and how they interact and there
have been many love relationships in
that way
and you can also find that one of them
as applies to what we have already
talked about was in that particular like
wherein the mother disapproved of the
relationship.
Oh yeah. Okay.
make some sense. Makes a whole bunch of
sense. Oh, good. Now, can you suggest
me? Maybe you will enjoy this process of
Maybe you will enjoy this process of
acceleration so much of having more than
one individual at a time that next life
you'll invite the whole family.
All right, I'll do that.
I was going to ask
can you suggest to me uh a physical
symbol that I can relate to the child
with that will
help say uh resolve whatever disapproval
or judgment she might have had. I can
say no more than a single word leace
although you already have that one and
that can be of assistance. Okay. There
is another word
chaperone. [Music]
Can you argue yourself?
It is being explored by you and by the
child from the ways in which it was explored
from the ways in which it was explored
in that other life.
Okay, that is all.
that is all.
Okay, thank you. Thank you.
Nice. Uh I'd like to know um if you could
Uh I'd like to know um if you could
comment on what has actually occurred
when someone meditates and when they do
meditate there well there is a faction
of yoga called sitta yoga of which the
guru does an act called shaktipa and I'd
like to understand what is actually
occurring alignment of all of your
bodies with each other
all levels of your consciousness align
aligning, blending, comingling so that
there is a clear path of communication
through all levels to all levels from
all levels. Is that with meditation or
shakta? Both. How does the guru do that
or what? Create an atmosphere in which
you suspend your disbelief and allow you
to create it for yourself.
Again, a master is the first one to tell
you you are your own master and simply
may reflect to you an idea that you find
to be representative of what touches
your core. And so you do it for yourself and
core. And so you do it for yourself and
create the effect for yourself in your
own life by following what you see.
You following? Yes. Thank you. Thank
you. Yay. Can you tell me please what planet
Yay. Can you tell me please what planet
I may have come from before coming to
Earth? Why? Why?
To uh
verify some information from another
source and I'm not sure whether it was
symbolic or or
real. That's why I asked.
Does it have validity for you?
It's a matter of curiosity. Yes. There
is no such thing as idle curiosity.
True. If your curiosity is activated, it
is for a reason. Yes. If it has touched
off a vibration within you, then in all
reality, it does apply on some level
somehow. In this way, many of you will
have many connections. Primary among
some of the connections right now are
ones to the idea of
Sirius, are ones to the idea of
Plleades, are ones to the idea of
Orion. There are offshoots and blendings
of this idea and in a sense you are all
connected to all of
them. What stands out for you?
I'm from the other source. It was the
planet Venus. All right. In this sense,
what you are forming a connection to is
something that is of assistance in this
particular planetary system on another
level, not physically. It is another
dimensional aspect of that idea. And in
your terms to us, though it is in your
terms another planet, to us it does not
represent another system. Mhm. And thus
you are forming a connection of
assistance to another dimensional aspect
within your own system. And this is
valid in that way.
But the connections that you form are
being formed in this life to serve
purposes of your own. For you are
connected to everything and come from
everywhere and nowhere.
Okay. You follow me? Yes.
Now do you find that this allows you to
reflect this connection in terms of
assisting others through ideas such as
let us say sharing of energy healings.
It did at the time it came up. Yes. And
I can see how it could enhance my
willingness to to move ahead. Right. It
is again in your symbology and in your
reality the vibration of love. Yes.
Therefore, share that love, share that
energy, heal yourself and radiate that
energy for others to dream deeply of so
that they can heal themselves. It is
part and parcel of a connection to the
idea in an archetypal symbolic way
of the mechanism of faith that was
spoken of and the energy that to some
degree was utilized by what you refer to
as the Christ consciousness.
Very good. Will that have the review?
Yes. Thank you very much. Thank you.
Thank you.
Um, a few moments ago, um, sometimes I
have the noisiest imagin. I know.
Thank you for recognizing the intention
of the noise.
You are welcome, Strawberry.
[Laughter] On your mind.
starting to pull it on now. Okay, baby.
A little while ago, sweetie. Um,
yes. I had an awareness
of exactly what I was
doing. And would you care to enlighten
us? I lost
it. And that distant phenomena has I
went, "Oh, that's it. Yeah, that's it.
Oh, yeah. That's what the hell was it?"
Act on the feeling you have retained and
you will find out. Understand? The more
you accelerate, the more opportunity you
give yourself to align with all of
yourself. Then you will, because you are
focused in physical reality, form what
seems to be a disconnection so you can
apply it. Otherwise, you would simply
sit in the radiance of the connection
and not do anything with it. You do not
lose it. In a sense, you set it aside so
you can do something with it. Integrated
practice on the spot. Absolutely. It has
to do Okay, I'll give more of the
application. I'd like some assistance in
this. It is
um consciously I vision uh and imagine
some preferences of the way that I like
things to be. And then I find things
appear that I I I know I judge
negatively. I go, "Oh, like this."
Things you didn't expect. Things I
didn't expect. Yeah. Well, where the
hell did this another traffic ticket
come from? You know, right? Or uh this
lousy feeling or this uh this unpleasant
sensation. Perhaps if you choose not to
judge those experiences, you will see
where they fit into the path you chose
to be. You will never find out where
they fit in as long as you judge them.
Because to judge them is to separate
them from the consciousness of your
past. Okay. Okay. I'm not consciously judging
Okay. Okay. I'm not consciously judging
them. I'm actually trying to answer that
question. You are. No. No. No.
All right, sweetie.
Sir, I still need some more. I'm not
done for Christ. Many many
Many many
things, all things in that
way are far more conscious than you
allow yourselves to believe. If you but
listen and look at yourselves and what
you say listen you will recognize that many
say listen you will recognize that many
times you are in the moment you say
something making the conscious choice as
to how to look at the fundamentally
neutral situation.
Say that was more pleasing. As we have
said all situations are fundamentally
neutral. That part I got. Then in this
way, if you listen very carefully to
yourself and all that you say, you can
become consciously aware of what you say
may be what immediately puts the
judgment on a fundamentally neutral
situation. Very nice. Thank you. Sure.
Simply listen to yourselves more often.
Yeah. It is all right there on the
surface. Listen and recognize that many
times what you say is an indication that
you are taking for granted that certain
things are inevitable results of what
you believe to be a fundamental
background existence to your reality.
That fundamental background existence is
also an illusion, my friend.
So do not base an illusion on an
illusion. On an Very nice. Very nice. Very nice.
On an Very nice. Very nice. Very nice.
Thank you for uh being neat enough to
allow me to throw out that emotional
response, which was I haven't done that
in a long time and that felt good. Oh,
thank you for his turn.
Then we will come to you. All right.
Then we will come to who?
Talk about the physical universe as a
holographic universe. Um our holograms
are based based with um three
projections to form the image. I was
wondering um in
two I thought it was three. One to
retrieve the image but two to form.
Okay. a initial beam and a reference
beam. Okay. And I was wondering um in our
Okay. And I was wondering um in our
holographic universe do our projections
of who we are in a three-dimensional
hologram um does it come from in a sense
uh from a spark of light or a point of
light in the in the present?
It comes from the permeation of life
through all that is. What you are
perceiving as your holographic universe
is only one dimension of a greater
universe. It is one side.
In other words, by analogy, what you
perceive to be your solid physical
universe is much the same to the idea
of let us say for example what you call
a shadow on the wall on the ground. You
follow me? Now what you are seeing as a
shadow is two-dimensional.
Although the shadow is dimensional, you
usually do not see except for certain
circumstances the three-dimensionality
of the shadow. who only perceives that
facet of it that intersects the surface
which is
two-dimensional. So the shadow is also
in that sense
holographic. But what you are seeing of
it is only what relates to your
particular dimension. Your entire third
density dimension is but the shadow of
the higher dimensions of all that
is. Therefore the reference beam is
the beam of your consciousness as it
streams through the prism of your
artificial personality construct and is
split into all the reference beams that
give credence and reinforcement to the
illusion you are creating.
You follow me? Yes.
Does that answer your question? Yeah.
Thank you very much. Thank you. Yay.
Yes. Bashar, I would like to ask you
about um past life connections I have
with a with a being who's my brother
this lifetime. Why?
Well, because I have certain senses
about it. Then tell me what they are. Do
not ask me.
Well, so much for that question.
It has gone from a bent over question
mark into an exclamation point. This is
true. Share, share, share, share. Okay.
Um I feel that we've had many many
relationships of mother and son. Yes.
Yes. Yes. That is generally true for
every single one of you. Yes. I've often
um realized that it's marvelous this
lifetime to have him as a brother
because we have been we've been through
many love affairs with other people but
that relationship always remains
constant. All right. And that's what's
really ser.
Thank you. You are simply seeing the
unconditional love that has always been
there in every type of relationship you
have ever had now being able to
exemplify itself symbolically to you in
a form you can relate to that you call
brother. Yes.
Yes.
I'd like to share something else. Oh,
please. Uh it's been my perception more
and more recently that as the this
transformation accelerates and I see it
accelerating on every hand. I see
examples of it constantly. synchronicity
abounds. Yes, that time is speeding up
enormously. It actually Yes. Although it
is not so much speeding up as simply you
are not creating as much of it.
Yes. I So things happen in less time,
right? Um that creates the illusion that I
Um that creates the illusion that I
don't have enough time to do everything
I want to do. No, you do. Again, you
will always manufacture exactly the
correct amount of time to do whatever
idea it is you are being. Again, by
definition, it really can't be any other
way. Yes. At some level, I know this and
Yes. At some level, I know this and
every once some level, well, I keep
coming back to that realization and then
I lose you not come back to anything.
You are always dead.
That's the viewpoint I have often and
then sometimes I have another one that
it it doesn't matter because there's
always plenty of time. Yes. Because as I
create my life explore your polarities
as you move and I like very much what
you said um several months ago about the
the worst thing that can happen to you
is that you will still have more life to
live and the best thing that will happen
to you is that you will still have more
life to live. You know what to thank you
for that. I thank you for the blending
of the polarities within your being.
Good that is happening so
um holographically I I suppose more and
more I'm gathering up facets of my
consciousness and awareness and I love
it. So thanks for helping with that.
Thank you. For sure. For sure. day. Uh I
understand I have a I feel I have a good
understanding of the uh triad with
Essistani and Sirius but the the I'm
wondering how does the Plleades fit into
that equation or or does it fit or how I
know it is another connection alto
together and it is more the idea of the
direct offshoot linkage lineage in the
sense that they are very literally your
brothers, sisters and cousins.
I see.
That's that has been the uh spaceships
that I've had been seeing for for some
20 20 odd years that I'm aware of has
been mainly Plleadian.
Yes. Although there are overlays. What
does that mean? and other interjections
from time to time just to spice things
up a
bit to add to the equation the necessary
interactions that will allow you to form
the connections you are forming. So
there have been others as well. Could
you tell me you simply may not be as
aware of them because they have been
unobtrusive I to allow you to focus on
what you need to focus on. Could you
tell me what what those are?
As I said,
they want to remain. Oh, I see. Thank
you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
Oh, yeah. Are you catching on? I I got
it before and I'm getting it more.
Thank you. Think the vibration for now.
Simply play with it for now. Do not make
too much of it. Neon.
Okay. N A M O N. Thank you.
What is first and second
as relates to the idea of what you call
the mineral reality consciousness and
the animal plant reality consciousness?
Sure. You've said that um your
civilization is undergoing this
transformational time as we are from
third to fourth institute from fourth to
fifth in our case. Ah well that makes
more sense
to me. Thank you. Yeah. Would you like
to master limitation as well as we have?
I have in the life I have before you. Oh
yeah. Thank you very much. It has served me
Thank you very much. It has served me
very well and has allowed me to perform
this interaction with you
very wellrel.
Why? Why not?
be really why won't you tell us all
right I will tell you why I will not
tell you
because in your terms we have been
contacting other civilizations in this
manner for thousands of years and we
know what we're doing trust us
how's that well I do trust you actually
know allow me the opportunity to express
to you that when the information needs
to be known, I will share it with you.
Right now, it will only impede the
process for many reasons that have nothing to do
for many reasons that have nothing to do
with
you. There are others who think about
it. Well, you know, it's nothing being
Well, you know, it's nothing being
selfish.
Allow yourself to learn from that. And
I'm sure it will serve you. You're a
good captain.
So, how are you?
Thank you.
Um, just last week I had a dream with
lots of bridges in it. And now what
could those possibly
symbol across the river?
I was thinking there was lots of things.
Oh, yes. But I was I was not so much
asking about this the bridges themselves
in the general sense but in specifically
how they related in this dream because
what I saw was a picture
of a lot of bridges and interconnections
and it seemed to be like I guess the
symbol that came through was marinand
where when you look what
marine plant right and when I look at
the photograph breath of
it. I could not. It was like before the
water was there. much serious energy in
that area. the dolphins and I couldn't
tell where the bridges whether the
bridges were for the physical I mean for
the human beings or for the you are
seeing a symbolic interpretation of the
matrix and the understanding that the
bridges all lead to each other and that
all reality is only in existence because
of the
interactions going on. It is the
interactions that create that which is
interacting. The bridges is all there
is.
The bridges are what in a sense give
rise and reality to the places they
connect. Oh,
Oh,
it is all one and the same. The
structure itself
is all of the realities upon it.
Oh that yeah it is self supporting.
You are looking at the matrix itself in
your interpretive symbology.
One thing leads to another in every
direction. That is the holographic
nature of all that is. All is connected.
All is gone. All paths get you
there. Whatever battle you
The other aspect of that dream was I
didn't at that marineland area there are
both in in our world there are both the
dolphins as well as the whales. Nice.
But in my dream I only saw the whales or
felt whales. And I was wondering if
they're similar to the dolphin energy or
different There is differences in their approach
There is differences in their approach
and obviously in their manifestation.
But it is all part and parcel of a
similar idea and a similar sharing. Are
they also like the
dolphins like our human counterpart?
Yes. Doesn't matter whether it was dolphins
Doesn't matter whether it was dolphins
or whales.
Um from my part of the country that I
was born in this lifetime we have we
have poes.
What are the
differences in uh is there a difference
in uh intelligence? Not so much.
It is again simply another manifestation
of the same idea in a different way. All
form of corpus dolphin whaleation ideas
are much the same.
Could could you tell us if there is any
specific reason why there there are
differences so that more can be loed all at once in
so that more can be loed all at once in
the same reason there are differences
between all of you.
You simply have created your differences
differently. Thank you.
briefly. Oh yes. Uh I felt very very moved by the
Oh yes. Uh I felt very very moved by the
artillerian people that person or energy
that came to that is the point. Yes. And
um a long time ago when I spoke to you
about my friends from space, you
suggested to me that they some were
plleadens, some were Syrian, some were
friends of
plleadenss. And then later I found that
some were from the Orion uh connection
and I feel very strongly that the
Arcturans might be the friends of the
Canadians which was the only ones that I
didn't know about you know in a sense it
is all connected in all parts of the
association. Again as you unfold you discover more
Again as you unfold you discover more
connections more bridges.
allows at this time.
Okay. Briefly, uh earlier when I asked
you for a symbol and you gave me the
word chapron, it's what I was looking
for was some kind of a physical symbol
that I could relate to the youngster
with. Not so much for my purpose, but to
trigger something in her to white
gloves. Long white gloves. All right.
Thank you very much. And we thank each
and every one of you individually and
collectively. Throw in a lace handkerchief. Okay.
And in this way,
we will in
this meaning mother.
Oh crap.
And your own relationship to all that is
that nurtures you that you
nurture in that way will allow you to
experience consciously all of the birth
that you are eternally. We thank you. We
wish you exciting dream lives and a fun
and loving good
evening. there.
Wonderful. Thank you very much, Daryl.
Thank you so much.
[Applause]
Anyone who would like tapes of tonight's
session, you may have them tonight. We
have a high tape dislocator.
Yeah. Ask Lynn over here and he will
pick you up. What time is it? It's 10
out of 50.
Yeah. The second the second section.
I think you
just see you later.