all right Al say how are you all this
evening of your time as you create
time we will begin this interaction this
even give your time with a little bit
more illumination of an idea you have shared
illumination of an idea you have shared
with us from time to time questions that
you have asked concerning the
fundamental existence of all that
is these are ideas to degree we have
shared from time to time with you
regarding what you normally consider to
be the questions you ask when you are
exploring the portions of your
Consciousness that create in you the
need to ask well why does this all exist
in the first
place now recognize many of you have
translated some of these ideas into the
notion well what is my purpose what is
the purpose of the existence of all that
is and so forth and we have discussed
with you many times that the idea first
and foremost of purpose is something that is
foremost of purpose is something that is
created within existence existence is
not subject to purpose purpose is
subject to existence therefore that
which has existed before the idea of
purpose was created does not necessarily
need a purpose to continue to
exist however an even more quote unquote
fundamental question as we have just
said in this way many times is simply
that you find yourself from time to time
asking well why why doesn't exist at
all in this way recognize we can share
with you the idea as for our
understanding but also recognize this it
is not that in the discussion and
sharing of this idea with you that we
mean in any way shap and form to be
mysterious in that way to be mystical no
but the idea the question in that form
is dealing with Prim
fundamentals and when you find yourself
dealing more and more with primary
fundamentals you will find that the
answers are more and more
simplified now the idea as to why many
of you have thought that there is no
answer to that question is simply
because it is in a sense so simple you
have not recognized it but the idea in
many ways of your Society has created a
type of structure that will not allow
answers of a certain degree of
Simplicity below your complexity
threshold to be acceptable or to be
valid in this way now
therefore again this idea may as we
present it seem to your habitual way of
thinking perhaps to be an
oversimplification but this is the way
that it will translate into your
language there is nothing we can do
about that therefore the idea as you
have asked it well why does existence
exist in the first place can simply be
viewed from this point of view first of
all you are asking that question based
upon a preconceived assumption as if
there was a
choice you are creating the idea that it
could have been that existence existed
or it could have been that it didn't now
recognize you are assuming that only one idea only
you are assuming that only one idea only
one side is real existence itself
nonexistence is just as real but
recognize this it is that you are dealing now with
this it is that you are dealing now with
primary fundamentals and when you deal
with primary fundamentals the basic
foundational ideas of creation then
those ideas is are in and of themselves
their own
definitions that is how they are
experienced as their own definitions
what this simply means is that it is not
that existence is real and non-existence is
existence is real and non-existence is
not it is simply that they both are real
but by definition
existence is the only thing you can
experience nonexistence because of what
it is by definition doesn't exist in any
way that you can have an experience of
recognizing its
reality thus the idea is that what you
are experiencing is simply that portion
of creation that brings with it the
definition that you can experience it it
is not that it could have been
non-existent for non-existence is right
now now real but by definition it
doesn't experientially exist to
you thus both realities are there are
present but only one carries with it the
ability to even create a cognition of it
that is why it only seems that one side
is all there is but it is a primary
fundamental polarity simply that on that level its
polarity simply that on that level its
own definition is the reality you do or
do not
experience you all follow along yes yes
Shing B uh there was a very strange I had a
B uh there was a very strange I had a
very strange experience last week
strange yes very
strange uh an individual uh misplaced
his keys and
misplaced right and I was aware of it
but I didn't think anything of
it and the following morning as I was
emptying my
purse I found a strange set of keys in
the inside pocket of my purse or Strang
and I and I immediately assumed there were
I and I immediately assumed there were
his but my first reaction was total
surprise my second reaction was
embarrassment and my third reaction was
that I knew exact I knew I had not taken
those keys that they there was no reason for
keys that they there was no reason for
me to put the strange keys in my purse
all right and that they had probably
gotten there um on their own so to speak
because I know that this can happen it's
happened to me that I misplaced things
and suddenly they were there when they
weren't there
before and so I thought they are not
misplaced okay no but I didn't perceive
them at one point we understand okay and
so I thought well this I mean I I was a
little embarrassed but I knew that I had
nothing to do with it
and um then I said well that's very
interesting you know we been talking
about synchronicity there must be a good
reason for it can be what do you think
well I never did find out because you
never did find out what the reason was
no I I really see I would like to know
from you if you can perceive whether in
fact they were physically put in my
purse by somebody or whether they just
materialized in there
because the person who misplaced his
keys didn't believe me he thought I had
taken them which doesn't make sense and
it doesn't make sense that anybody else
would have picked up strange keys and
put them in a strange
purse then in this way what does that
allow you and your friend to find out
about each other well I didn't find out
anything except that he he thought I
took them which tells you
want well I I wasn't I was a little
upset that he was angry but uh I thought
well you know that's that's his
perception if I had been in issues I
might have gotten angry too maybe um and
I I what are you unlocking for each
other in that
way uh really for me it just never got
resolved in terms of this particular
synchronicity which I at first you may
simply be attempting to make it more
complex than it needs to yeah I'm sure
do you feel or have you felt that you
can be a reflection in certain ways for
this friend of yours I I thought so but
uh I did not uh sense that he was
willing to discuss it with me what does
that have to do with the fact that you
may still be willing to be a reflection
oh nothing nothing I really would like
to know if those keys got there on their
own or if somebody or see he was sitting
behind me but my out of perception in
this way is that there was in your terms
what you call an assumption made on
someone's part when the keys were found
and deposited where they thought they
belong but in this way simply recognize
that no matter what the agent of the
transference is it is still
synchronicity and it is still
magical okay you follow me yes um it
still serves the purpose to allow the
recognition of the interaction that is
going on between you and your friend to
come about but there wasn't much of an
interaction there
wasn't no you said that your friend in
your terms accused you of taking the
keys well he didn't accuse me accuse me
he said well he said did you say your
friend created the idea of anger that's
my perception when he called me on the
phone oh right then you have created
your own perception of your friend's
anger whether the friend had anger or
not your creation of it the involvement
is an interaction right but I don't know
what it where it got us or what I got
out of it why don't you ask your
imagination I did
and what did you get not very much the
idea that you got not very much is a
judgment again you may be assuming that
it is more complex than it has to be
what did you get well
get well
actually for myself I really felt that
those keys got there on their own and I
thought it was exciting all right very
good very good and I thought it was a
shame that a shame well okay that's a
judgment I thought I thought he would
perceive it as being exciting too but of
course I'm not the one that was put out
by so what does that tell you well he
wasn't what else does it tell you what
does it tell you about
you about
me about you well all that I had
expectations all right what
else but I didn't let it bother me for
very long all right very good and that
you can recognize that
your creation of a situation and someone
else's creation of a situation and a
third explanation of a situation are all
their own complete realities they're all
different from each point of view yes
and all equally real for what it does
for you in terms of allowing you to
create yourself in the image you imagine
yourself to
be so in this way you see that the ey
idea of this
key can unlock many locks simultaneously
allowing you to experience your portion
of the idea and someone else to
experience theirs even though they may
be very different
good the tools that you have in your
Society can all be viewed as keys they
fit every blck one key changes and
transforms to fit every
lock that there is so you use the key in
your way they use the key in their way
and in a sense though it is transformed
it is all the same one key basically
good true thank you very much thank you
the Shar the
shark last week you were talking about
different chakras of the Earth can you
tell me what significance Big Mountain
has big mountain yeah which it's in
Arizon on the Four Corners
reservation in this way it will be once
again more what is in our terminology a
free zone rather than what you would
recognize as one of the major chakras
but in this way all the chakra points
and energy vortices upon your planet are
beginning to blend so every free zone
energy vortices will carry within it the idea
vortices will carry within it the idea
of energy from all the
vortices in this way that particular
energy is not dissimilar to the idea of
the energy vortices in what you call
Sedona and it will be one that will
carry within it many different
Reflections so that when you place
yourself in that energy what is
Paramount within you that you wish to
face will be brought to the surface it
is by the idea you have described it and
by the location it appears in your idea
of geography
indicative of the idea of a Crossroads
of sorts where all these ideas come
together so that you can know that you
are in that energy vortices an
integration of all the directions of
energy that you
are you follow me MH it will also be one
of the balancing points for what you
call American Indian culture in this way
one of the doorways of extra
dimensionality through which many of
their consciousnesses have communicated
to many other levels of
consciousness right now there's um a
public law which says which is trying to
relocate the Indians there on that land
and take over that land to dig out the
minerals and oil and coal there I um can
you say something about that what do you
wish to do about that well I wish to
stop the process then in your terms go
in love and light without accusations
and educate individuals and give them an
opportunity to recognize the idea of
what the energy can be used for and how
there is in your terms far more energy
naturally in the area than anything they
could extract from the
land you follow me yes is up to you is
your planet you decide how the balances
go if um if the federal government isn't
stopped and they do you are the
government
when you equalize yourself and open up
equal communication with that portion of
yourselves then it will not be something
outside of you that has control over
you it is not that it will become
stoppable it simply will never
start okay when you equalize the idea
and do not accuse do not judge but give
that portion of yourself an opportunity
to
recognize that you are the government
and that you all together will decide
but it will take action on your part the
willingness to show that you have the
conviction that this is what you prefer
and not something
else I just went there on a delegation
from Santa Barbara oh right students did
you have a good time yes all
right um they're preparing for their
Sundance ritual right now yes and I met
a 7-year-old boy who had
gone his name is
Joshua I was wondering if you could tell
me anything about him has been in your
terms American Indian many
times has been Shaman many times
is connected to the
idea of what may be Loosely termed
symbolically rainbow Consciousness or
fan Consciousness
fan has been and still to some degree is
within the dream state what is tered
hopa thunder dreamer we
dreamer we
and can
be focus of much
energy in a very gemlike way it is a
very crystallin
individual here for its own specific
purposes I say it's because it is a
blended individual rather than he or
she that is what we can perceive at this
time thank you thank
thank you thank
you hello to you and all of esani and to
you I've miss chatting with you the last
two weeks you have not been
chatting well actually I have all right
then are you wear specifics only
specifics only
sporadically yes uh on a few occasions I
imagined myself to exist on your planet
in physical form in the way that you
describe the virtual
personality and in that imagination I uh
imagined basically saying greetings to
you and uh on a few occasions our
perception is that you also worked with
the crystal
sheets
wow I will uh I'll take your word for it
on you don't don't have to I I like to
I'm I I like it
all right he up to yeah I that is simply
our perception of the energy sounds good
to me I enjoy that uh it seems that uh
on the second occasion that you you took
the group up to your face your
spacecraft I chose not to participate by
not being here and um I'm becoming
convinced that I am creating a reason
for that oh I'm also creating puzzlement
as to what that reason is you have any
you have any more to share with me about
that now in a sense as you have said you have
now in a sense as you have said you have
been creating it
yourself you are recognizing that you
are as unlimited as you wish to be and
the idea of any particular time has
nothing to do with the timing in that
way you are quite capable of recreating
the experience any time uhhuh in this
way it may simply be an indication and a
reflection for you that you are not
necessarily bound by any particular
schedule that is very true uh it's
particularly reflected in my life nice
so that's true that's terrific um all
right I had a I had a really neat
experience uh oh do share oh about a
week ago and as I was coming over the
hill from Kathy's house to my own
domicile nice I uh spotted in the valley
a tremendous amount of looked like Haze
or
smog I thought to myself wouldn't it be
neat to move this out of there and clear
up the day so I contacted the mass
consciousness of the area in my
imagination I just said hey guys you
want to bring up some wind and move this
stuff out of here and I got this kind of
uh chorus of voices going hey yeah that
sounds neat do so by the end of the day
um the wind had come up and cleared out
the smog it was really terrific thank
you
switcher my pleasure do you understand
the term no I don't valve gate oh okay
link connection Point
Terminal for communication or for
air same
thing oh that's neat uh activator
Catalyst ah now it's now it's hitting
home thank you yes thank
you um hi B I'm new here my name
do you mean on
Earth um I don't know
yet um I'm going through a lot of
emotional pain right now sure emotional
pain which means judgments of
yourself yeah I guess so all pain is the
result of judgment there is no need for
pain and it does not occur until you
judge portions of yourself and SE
separate them from the rest of all that
you are now why in this way would you be
are now why in this way would you be
judging yourself at this
time well I'm very much in love with
someone right now um I've taken a choice
to may I ask you a question yes what
does in your definition the term in love
mean I don't know I
see um may I ask you another
question sure oh thank you very
much do you love yourself I'm trying
trying then you are doing trying yeah
now do you wish to love yourself yes are
you sure yes
unconditionally I do not hear
anything you cut me off before I can um
I myself
unconditionally do you think you can
love others unconditionally anyone at
all it's a struggle
why what do you think it entails that
makes it a struggle for you to love
someone unconditionally cuz I have so many
unconditionally cuz I have so many
expectations a in other
words you are not trusting that the
situation as it occurs is the way it
needs to you're
right you may also be under the
assumption that you need a relationship
in order to allow yourself to be
recognized by you as
complete you're right and in this way
recognize that if that is your belief
about yourself since belief creates
reality you can only attract someone
into a relationship that will only
reflect your sense of incompleteness
about yourself
follow me yes I do it is very simple the
idea of your so-called soulmates can
appear in your lives when you know you
are already complete and are operating
on a vibrational level that attracts
someone of equal vibration to reflect to
you that you know you are complete and
thus that is the relationship you form
but the idea is not if only my soulmate
was here I'd be happy but since I am
happy I allow the idea of someone to be
in my life to reflect that happiness to
me
[Music] so I can reflect their happiness
so I can reflect their happiness
today if you believe you are in complete
in that way in that sense then you will
usually attract someone who refle like
that incompleteness to you and in that
way it will usually be someone who will
also derive benefit from having you
reflect incompleteness to
them I have another question for you um
did that assist you definitely all right
um what connection do I have with this
individual what P have I had a past life
experience with this individual his name
is Edison more than
one has it been based on
dependency um
once little girl and father father
disappointed disapp
appointment what what is
the what is the um I you say past life
but what is it in this life right
now this is the transformational life
upon your planet all that you have ever
been all that you have ever experienced
with anyone in your terms is now blending
anyone in your terms is now blending
into one understanding the idea that you
are as powerful as you need to be as an
individual to create anything in your
reality you desire without having to
hurt anyone else to get it or rely on
anyone else to have
it therefore there may be still some
remnants of the idea of dependency in
that way but you are being given an
opportunity to shake that off to be
complete so that you can
interact completely and not
completely and not
interdependently how I want to be with
this individual how can I make that
happen you want to be with an individual
that represents the vibration you desire
to have in your life
now maybe that can be with the
individual you recognize and maybe it
won't but the idea is that even if it is
with the so-called individual you
recognize when you change the vibration
you are if they decide to let us say
stick around they will need to change
the vibration to match you if they
change their vibration then they are not
the same individual
anyway literally therefore the idea is not so
literally therefore the idea is not so
much that it has to be any specific
individual but that the idea of the
vibration you are is
matched if your vibration is matched in
Perfect Harmony by someone else then all
of your needs so to speak are filled and
you don't care who it
is now it may be that you are
recognizing that that particular
individual may be able to share that
idea with you but if so they will still
change into another individual in order
to do it when you
change you follow me oh yes and you
find when you change whatever individual
needs be there to match your vibration
will be there whether it is the same
individual or not will not matter to you
because it will feel
right you follow me many times an
individual depending upon the timing of
what they are learning May interact with
you simply to get you to a certain point
but it may be that the timing is not
that they will continue to interact with
you as it may be that they need to
interact with someone else to get them
to a certain
point then whoever needs to be
interacting with you from that point
forward will automatically be there you
follow me it can be the same individual
but it does not have to be and you will
not care because it will feel
right one more question all right why
are why are newborn babies so powerful
because they have not forgotten so much
yet [Music]
[Music]
you follow me oh definitely oh thank
you um on your
planet you have two people get together
you said you have sex and procreation
sort of like we have but how structured
is that relationship if children only
children get reoriented and are on their
own by the time that their body is free
in this way as we have said
relationships will
transform into whatever the purpose is
that is being served while everyone will
still always recognize the idea of the
biological child and the biological
parent everyone in our civilization is
married to everyone else every child is
everyone's child every adult is every
child's parent thus in your terms it is
not very structured at all in other
words two people you were you ever
married I am married to my entire
civilization if you mean do I have
physiological will Offspring no okay
however I have had relationships in that
way right but let's suppose someone on
your planet has a physical relationship
and there is Offspring yeah but there is
no
cultural um pressure or I don't know what the
um pressure or I don't know what the
right word is we understand for the two
of you to remain together correct so
that the relationship May evolve and
you'll now next week or next year be
with someone else perhaps but do not
forget that we never lose track of any
relationship that is once formed then it
is altogether highly likely that the
individuals you have had relationships
with will remain in your life more or
less in some way shape or form but not
necessarily as we would say the primary
relationship perhaps in your terms as we
understand it correct not
necessarily although once again we do
understand what you mean but we do not
necessarily look at a relationship ship
as more primary than some other
relationship all are
equal it is simply a different
definition but that does not make it in
a sense more primary just because you
are assuming that quote unquote more
physiological time may be spent with one
individual than another but that doesn't
make that relationship more primary not
really to other Rel makes it the
relationship that it is which changes
nothing about what all the other
relationships are right except that
there's in the physical Universe there's
a limit that you have days just like we
do to some degree yes I mean it gets
light and it gets and so there's a limit
if you will to the amount of time in any
one day if you're spending in that sense
we understand what you mean we simply
mean that it is not Primary in terms of
energy okay another thought I've had in
exploring this for myself about sort of
answering the question you asked the
young lady what does it mean to be in
love I it seems to me that the Sensation
that most when people say they're in
love what they are meaning is that they
are experiencing a particular
physiological sensation it's in some
part of their being and the part will
differ if you do a survey of individuals
which is itself interesting but it's it
just struck me today that that that the
basis of that physiological sensation is
separation that on this planet when
someone says that they're in love
they're experiencing separation from
that individual rather
than um integration
howeh well I'm also now I'm not denying
the possibility that some people
experience a Oneness and call that love
I'm not denying that I'm merely in my
experience I'm I'm trying to describe
something which I have observed and
experienced that I think more often than not the
that I think more often than not the
average
person are you saying that the idea of
quote unquote being in love is that when
you are not physically together you miss
them is that what you are to saying no
that's not what I'm saying I'm there's a
quality of intoxication that
occurs easy well no
because I think that it's it's nearly
ident identical to the excitation that
occurs when you take drugs when one on
this planet takes drugs and I have
perceived a distinct
similarity approaching
identity between the experience of
taking a drug what you mean is multiple
orientation no I don't understand that
multiple orientation
disorientation the idea that when you
are quote unquote in love that you are
blending that you are integrating and
opening up more of yourself connecting
into more levels so that there is
multiple orientation which many times
can feel like disorientation to you let
me come at this another way um perhaps
what you are referring to as giddiness
or
intoxication well let me maybe I can
come at this another way right I have
observed Within Myself he um that my
relationships that I've had are formed
on the basis of of different parts of my
physiological being if you will in other
words I would say there are some people
I have loved with my head and I sense
kind of a source point of the
intoxication with my head whereas with
we understand the idea to our perception
is simply that when you have that kind
of differentiation that kind of
Separation yes it is not that you have
not created the relationship out of an
overall unconditional love but what you
are recognizing perhaps is the specific
vibration representative of the specific
purpose that you are with that specific
person yes but I okay I Noti I do follow
you I've noticed for myself a distinct a
dramatic of light years apart difference
yes between the quality of the
relationship and the particle of
excitation if as I would describe it to
myself it's a relationship the
connection is with my head or the
connection is with my heart yes in this
way you may understand that the idea of
being connected in a total way will be
more representative of what you say to
be feeling and thus it may be that
simply the relationship you are having
allows you to connect with more of
yourself than other relationships so all
we are saying is that when you find that
the quality is more differentiated it
may simply be that that particular
relationship is for a more highly
specified reason okay it but
it's in my
experience and of course this I don't I
I want to find it's not a judgment but
it's an observation that it would seem
to me in retrospect that all of the
relationships I've had that were
connections of the head were interesting
they served purposes etc etc etc but but
in all of them I was having a
relationship the other person at the
other end was less capable of the of
achieving and understanding the kinds of
ideas we're sharing here of a Unity
among all per people in other words it
was a person who existed more in
separation whereas the relationships
I've had with my heart are with people
who are capable of experiencing a
greater Unity among people well again
that is only in your terms logical
because in this way when you attract an
individual for a specific type of
interaction that is limited in that way
then that is the level on which they are
going to relate to you and you to them
you are simply attracting what defines
the vibration you are at any given
moment for the purpose of co-creating
that relationship therefore when you create a
relationship therefore when you create a
relationship with more of yourself
obviously you will attract an individual
that will also be able to share with
more of
themselves I got it thank you I'd just
like to tie in the what I said about
drugs we live in a society which this
particular civilization here in the
United States which places a tremendous
emphasis on things of the head
analytical reasing analytical by
definition is a taking apart into its
pieces which is obviously part of
Separation so whether it's true of other
people or not the thought occurred to me
that um because of that cultural
environment uh and a great attachment to
form perhaps the majority of many people
who knows the majority many people are
are led to focus attention on having
relationships of the head if you will
which seem to me to be almost by
definition divisive we understand in
other words it can be the result of the
idea of the habit of the way you have
created yourself to do things yes and it
is the connection of the head rather
than the heart that struck me as having
a distinct near identity to a drug
experience thank you and that drugs are
a a dividing when you take drugs you are
individuated I think from the mass
Consciousness because it's a in a sense
it's a shutdown although there are
portions of the idea you are sharing
within the mass Consciousness to have
the experience anyway but do recognize
in this way that the primary portion
that you are sharing with the math
Consciousness is that it is the drug
that is creating the experience when in
fact it is you that is creating the
experience okay one last thing so you I
could I what perhaps a direction I
should consider evolving in is up to you
no it's up to me but would be I mean it
sort of fascinates me that there are
these different parts of my
physiological seeing that is why you are
here exploring this but but there'd be a
possibility of somehow integrating all
of those so that my experience would be
having a relationship that encompasses
all of me rather than just focusing on
one point or all you need to do is be
that kind of being and act like it and
that is what you will
attract thank you thank
you you thank you Pas I just returned
from 3 weeks in Sedona where I had
communication with the space Brothers oh
and um I would like to know I found
myself looking at land buying at land up
there with an individual called Michael
I would like to know if my work in the
future involves this proposition you
mean you don't know no I don't you don't
no why not doesn't it excite you attract
you I found myself sitting in the real
estate office having the deja vu feeling
that I created this on the inner plane
and now then in that way does not that
allow you to recognize your own
signposts where you have laid them I
felt it was true but then I had a
channeling up there which said no this
individual is not to be in your life in
the future but in this way recognize
once again that every individual is
never the same individual in the the
next second all predictions are readings of
second all predictions are readings of
the energy that exists at the time the
prediction is made there is no such
thing as a prediction of the
future is this individual of the earth
plan I get the feeling that he is one of
his fake Brothers everyone in a sense is
I know but there is a feeling about him
that he's not like other people who is
take back your power and be who you are
it may be that if this individual quote
unquote is not physiologically in your
life it is to Grant you the opportunity
to recognize that you are complete as
well I feel that now all right then do
what excites you so is this a good idea
to buy land and Sedona good bad is it
what you want to
do yes no maybe maybe all right then as
long as you are maybe you will
wonder when you know whether it is
something you prefer something that
excites you then you will have your
answer it is as simple as that trusting
that what excites you the most is the
representational idea that is the path
you chose to be that's what excitement
is the vibration of the path you chose
to to be that is why you can always
trust that if you follow your excitement
you will always be automatically
supported because you are being the path
you chose to be excitement is your
barometer and follow me yes can you
comment on the um future of the context
that I'm having with the space
pleas only that like everything else it
will accelerate in perfect
timing there may be as we read the
energy now
more individuals coming into your
surroundings and that there is a large
energy gate so to speak for your entire
civilization which you may be able to
take advantage of in the area you call
Sedona since you will be in an energy
Vortex during what you call the spring
of
1,987 of your Counting
Sal it is up to
you thank
you um I have 15
questions but I'll just ask a couple now
um right just keeping everybody on their
um one uh a couple friends of mine were
sharing a dream that we all of a sudden
realized that we had had the same one
and what that dream was was um we we
would be out in a field somewhere and we
would play this game of seeing how high
we could jump and then the next thing
like you know up toward the telephone
poles and we we sort of kept at about
that level and then the game was to see
how how long we could stay up there and
then we just started floating around and
I remember uh actually telling people
you know how easy this is this is great
and it was a very very exhilerating
wonderful feeling and it was all the we
just simultaneously realized that we had
had the same dream
and that you were the same dream that's
right well I mean it's not really a big
significant thing but I don't know there
is something
there I don't know it's very light and
and I don't mean to make a big deal out
of it but so if you can make a big deal
that I mean if you can
do it is not at all uncommon to be
communicating with many of your friends
in your astral State oh lovely and the
interesting thing was that uh I did not
even recall it wasn't like I woke up and
said well she had this great dream last
night it was something that I actually
did not even think of and the reason
until someone mentioned it or something
triggered at night and we and the reason
for that that's very wonderful to me
uh is that this week I have had people
tell me things like one guy actually
walked up to me and he was a person who
who tended to really take himself very
seriously and you know Revere things and
all that and was very sweet but he sat
there and told me that I need tools and
all that intensity and energy well you
should really channel that and I was
just thinking what makes you think it
isn't Channel I mean this guy is amazing
he's coming up and telling me all these
things and what I need and oh I need
tools and I need this
and I was getting a little angry for a
second until I
realized I don't need any of it and he
was there to tell me that oh and so you
allowed the idea of your anger to be
natural so it simply aligned you with
the belief that you knew yourself to be
that is what anger is for and I actually
told him how I felt in a very nice way I
mean he was almost confused a it it was
confusion Co Fusion yeah it was terrific
because he couldn't understand how much
I could express my liking for him
while at the same time not taking him
seriously keep them
guessing thank you for being such a
loving mirror oh it's my pleasure yes
may I ask one more thing you do not have
to ask if you can ask all right that's
right um this is a this is a fun thing I
had a a realization that I was actually
my father hey that's right actually my
father yes
I mean physically here's what happened
and I don't know I don't know if this is
true I don't even know if I care if it's
true but I if you can tell relative all
right yeah I know but let's just have
some fun in World War II uh see I feel I know
fun in World War II uh see I feel I know
him really really well he has the same
sense of humor same handwriting you know
he's one of those uh Charming irish
guys and um anyway he was killed in uh
in the invasion of Normandy on the beach
by a landmine and then a week later I
was born now you tell
me so so all of a sudden I had this
flash but I was him different aspect of
the Same Soul well that I can see but I
was wondering if actually pH physically
that is the same thing different aspect
of the same whole soul oh I see if you
were not a different aspect you would
once again literally physically be your
father oh I see yes I do see what you
mean of course yeah
yeah all right that that that's
good um one other thing
yes it's all wonderful it's all I don't
care what answer I get it's all great
the the the other thing is exploding one
way one life exploding another this
life okay all right the other thing is
we recently recently um things
changed yes things change most
change most
profound yeah yeah um the theme for this
week is um this week well I'm just
making a euphemism you know I'm do that
um is that I in with regard to
relationship since this subject came up
I have been attracting to me like five
people male people and and experiencing
a reflection of myself in these people
that is extremely full and Rich and
beautiful but they're
married now I really don't mind that
except that I want one that I can jump
on I'm being very C about it but but you
know what I'm saying I don't I think
it's very interesting to pull have this
sort of situation occur but I don't it's
probably perhaps you are
simply in a sense not in a literal
ending sense but in a sense touching
Bass with many previous relationships
and saying
bage thank you thank you thank you that
is a feeling there is gratitude yeah but
I want to say um
hello when you have finished saying
goodbye you
but AR say both the same thing in a
sense but recognize what we are saying
as you evolve into the idea of a now
combination that is in of itself
complete on its own conscious
understanding then you become what
attracts what you are seeking and the
idea for you simply may be that you
become complete when you detach from all
the different ideas of the
past which is what you may be doing with
them in a sense okay
thank you
relax oh
okay so
exciting you know I get I get worked
up I I just get excited you know that I
mean there is nothing wrong with fo
simply live every moment of your life as
if every moment is what is supposed to
be happening okay do not be
impatient you do not need impatience
patience is only created when you think
you need to be patient to wait for
something you do not need to be patient
if you are enjoying every single second
of life for you are never waiting for
anything better to come
along well I definitely appreciate that
be in the now and all that you desire
can be in the now with
you that's it's getting like that that's
that's it's getting like that that's
true all right thank you thank you
yeah your opening statement you
mentioned existence and nonexistence
hilarities and I was thinking this I beg
you part I was thinking that perhaps on
the have
to how about how about a little
part that is nothing to
par please continue oh thank you in any
case what my thought was that perhaps
well we create mystery unknowingness
it's and oh yes all all these things in
an effort to experience something that
is quote unquote unexperienced
to do it yes sure the way I
[Music] have that is what the idea of this
have that is what the idea of this
particular reality you are experiencing
has been all about M the idea of
forgetting that you created it so you
can play the game of limitation if you
did not forget you created it you
couldn't be
limited you you are so unlimited you can
even create the illusion that you have
forgotten that you are
unlimited time to buy out of that one it
is the ending of the cycle buying into a
new reality money well [Music]
[Music]
spent your investment will only go up
and the game hasn't been that bad not
reallying no for you have learned from
everything you have ever been it has all
gotten you to where you are and so it
has served you in a positive way change
the
past thank you for thank
you guys uh I'd like to have a beach
house all right and go ahead
uh I was wondering if there was a chakra
or a Vortex or something on the
California coast Malibu
Malibu uh any specific
Malibu okay very good uh you also do a
lot of movements with your hands I
wonder I do not oh excuse me the idea
isly that you will find I am in what you
would call a state of repose my
mentality as it links with the
physiological channel before you my
energy as it translates through the
physiological Channel translates through
in more than just what you are receiving
as the vocal communication so what you
might turn the spill over activates the
bodily mechanism to let you know there
is more communication going on than what
you may perceive with your
ears is uh is there something uh in my
uh creation is holding me back than
you the assumption that there is
something holding you back is holding
you back is that that's
it the only thing that can hold you back
is the definition and the belief that
there is something that can that is it
when you make that a law of the universe
that something can hold you back held
back you will have the experience of
being okay is the uh by the way yes held back
okay is the uh by the way yes held back
from what from where from uh obtaining
uh what I uh my house on Malibu
first nothing holds you back okay except
perhaps the idea that you may not saying
this is the case that you
may have expectation that if what you
specifically imag imine does not
manifest exactly the way you think it
should you will not accept anything else
therefore you not allow anything else to
come to even though the something else
may quote unquote be more than what you
are already wishing
for now utilize what you are
visualizing it can manifest very
specifically no doubt about it it can
however simply use it as a model for the
energy know the energy is released and
know your real ity will do its best it
always does to reflect what energy you
are truly willing to
be then it will manifest in the way that
is necessary for you to feel that the
idea has been fulfilled whether it is as
specifically as you have imagin it or
not does not matter you will not care it
will feel right you are simply using
what you visualize as a model to hang
the energy on but it may transform by
the time it becomes
physical according to what it needs to
be I
see assist you yes thank you very much
yes on on that topic uh I've been
wondering about being an idea of
something let's say you have generated
the energy
necessary or or you have used like the
beach house as a model okay now once you
have become the idea you generated the
energy and it takes have you said it
takes usually between three weeks and
three months relatively speaking can be
as little as 3 days oh three days but
actually it can be instantaneous however
we are perceiving that the energy of
your mass Consciousness at this time
will usually relegate itself to
somewhere between 3 days and 3 months
maximum uhhuh but during that time you
do not have to keep being the idea you
oh well in a sense yes you are all you
do is simply act upon what opportunities
come to you whether it seems that those
opportunities are part of the idea as
you think they should be or not they are
you simply take it for granted and trust
that once you have recognize what idea
you are then everything in your life is
a reflection of that idea whether it
seems to be or not right you simply act
upon the opportunities that present
themselves and you will be led to the
idea that you know you are okay
right just a similar question or a
related question if I if I told you I am
the idea of such and such and there's a
concept in my mind and I tell you what
it
is um could you perceive to what extent
I'm successful in being that idea can
you not no sometimes one moment allow us
to remind you of something many of you
have created the scenario in your
mentality that what you wish to do in a sense is a
that what you wish to do in a sense is a
piece of an idea and not its own
idea in this way many times there may be
what you turn to be confusion in a
negative sense about what it is you are
defining yourself to be as an idea now
let us use this
analogy if you say you are doing a job
as many have said that you do not really
find exciting and you desire to do
something else that you know is more
exciting something you prefer well many
of you say well all right I will begin
to do that other thing but I'll hang on
to my job just in case now it is not
that that is not a valid way to proceed
but recognize this the idea of the job
you had and what you want to do then
becomes the definition of one idea not
two ideas so recognize that if you are doing
ideas so recognize that if you are doing
your job and you are doing the other
thing and saying well I try and I try
and I try why doesn't it become
100% it doesn't become 100% because you
are already using 100% of the idea you
are to maintain a balance between the
definition of what that idea is so your
job may be 30% still you therefore how
can the other thing anything more than
70% you are assuming that you can do
this to 100% And that to 100% you cannot
be
200% the idea is to Simply recognize
what portion of yourself is still quote
unquote attached or still being another
idea or another part of the definition
within one idea not so much another idea
in this way therefore take the entire
activity as one 100% idea if you are
doing your job and doing this then
simply understand that this will be
quote unquote as successful as this is
not it is a balance and it may Simply Be
Your Way of quote unquote weaning
yourself comfortably so that bit by bit perhaps
comfortably so that bit by bit perhaps
the old job will become 10% the new
thing 90 the old one one % the new thing
99% until you are comfortable with
allowing the new thing to be Its Own
100% definition and feel successful at
it but you are eminently successful at
balancing the whole equation you are
always successful always it is simply
that the definition of your success is
70% this and 30% that so you are
successful as that definition that one
idea sure thank you than you yes it
seems this might this is not absurd um I
this might this is not absurd um I
thought it was absurd it's not thank you
okay um we're talking about 100% we're
talking about that as a whole and an
agreement in this universe that 100% is
a whole that you cannot be more than a
whole now are there levels I know there
are levels but if you could expand on
something where you can be more than the
whole no no everything is only
100% you may simply have different
portions of that one idea receiving
different percentages of the whole
energy but it is all
100% so no matter how many 100% you make
out it still makes at 100% guys yes in
this way no matter how you define
yourself and redefine yourself you are
simply redistributing the 100% in different
redistributing the 100% in different
ways Sometimes some of it can go into
not knowing it is
there in other
words you are always using 100% even
when you are using 90% to make it seem
as if you are only using
10 it is still 100%
there with everyone else but me of
course thank
you I brought my 15-year-old son last
week he sat over here in this corner and
the next day he loved the session by the
way his name is Alie um the next day he
had a like a migraine headache all day
long um it didn't occur to me to connect
those two until later was there a
connection between him being here and
having that
headache the idea simply can be put the
that individual
not so much that they were interacting
with us but simply that they have now
become willing to interact with
themselves with more of themselves
simply you will find that many times in
your Society because of the belief
systems you have bought into when you
begin to open up different portions of
yourself you may find that at first it
may be a painful experience because of
all the Judgment within you it will
release oh and one other thing for sure
thank you um allow him to become a valve
a channel for himself so that the energy
can flow
through and not push against walls that
he may assume still have to be
there we have a real interesting
situation going on right now it seems
that it's some kind of control battle
and I was wondering um I feel we've been
together before yes and I feel like once
again do not forget that individuals you
feel close to in any particular life you
have been with many times I feel like
there's a that he was either a Tyrant
and I was a subject or a tyrannical
father or something there something
we're working out right now all right
and this may be part and parcel of the
idea of the migraines also for in this
way it is that he may be fighting quote
unquote the idea of control and finds
that all the pathways he is now
releasing through are constricted how
could I help him that as we have said
communicate to him the idea that he can
simply be a valve
trust that whatever energy he's
experiencing is allowing him to become
whole in his mind complete to himself
and under his own
control remind him that every
individual is under
control even when it seems like you are
not you mean under your own
control okay it's because um the last
couple of days he's he's been doing a
disappearing act and I'm wondering how I
can best be a mother and have I don't
know how much control that I should try
to exercise over him you cannot have any
control over him what do you do as a
parent when when they just disappear and
you worry about them you unconditionally
love them and trust that they know what
they are doing even if they think they
do
not yes do all right then relax oh no
no patient is waiting for something that
represents an expectation on your part
you are not being unconditional in your
love what they are doing is what they
need to do now you can ease that for
them by being Unconditional by letting
it be all right to experience those
things anywhere including in your
presence yes I think I've you know been
pretty open about that all right then
simply take it for granted that what is
going on is a reflection of your
openness and nothing
else that will be felt by
you can you help me reflect on some of
the ways we have shared in past lives
I'm curious It's but not
curious It's but not
now our perception is that you need to
be focused in this
world Al well is up to you
Al well is up to you
to decide whether or not this is going
to be judged by you by him to be silly
or not however that never stopped me
from suggesting
anything therefore what I will suggest
is that you give to him a
gift the gift can be what you call a
brick or a small block of hard
Stone give him this gift and suggest to
him that if he so desires he may smash
it into as many pieces as he wishes to
pulverize it into
dust then sift it through his
fingers and blow it away into the
air and he will know that all of his own
barriers have been broken and
dissolved this will relate to a specific
interaction that you you will refer to
as a past
life when walls were what kept you
aart I like that oh than you think
you'll
enjoying would you please tell him I
said have a good time okay than
okay than
you you refer to me as Switcher earlier
this evening could we explore that term
a little more you finally got around to
um saying Catalyst which which I did
understand I realized that the reason I
didn't understand switcher was because I
didn't know what I was switching what
the substances or the I use the term
figuratively what it was I was switching
from what to what in what
way the idea of allowing different
levels to blend through you within you
in a sense like what you would call a
switchyard traffic coming and going in
every direction I
see okay that that helps Define that uh
concept now what I did um with this
thing that I described to you I have
conceived of doing with other things
last time I was here we were talking
about the Sun and how the mass
Consciousness determines that the Sun
causes Sunburn and and whatnot and I did
have the idea idea that I could get in
touch with the mass Consciousness and
suggest that we change our minds oh uh
how much of this is being done by
various individuals on the planet in a
sense quite a bit really yes consciously
some of them yes uh because it seems
like a conscious approach to it with a
great deal of energy behind it uh could
can create quite a bit of um change yes
it already has
uhhuh well you know I can go wild this
idea have a good than
good than
you second if I may all right many years
ago I conceived
of what I would cons consider a matrix
of um a sperical matrix about the
planet of robotic Battle
Stations and the idea was that they
would either keep something in or keep
something out primarily keep Us in and
uh although I don't believe it's exactly
that uh there was a movie a couple years
ago which had a similar thing they
called the frontier was a robotic battle
station which kept them in or kept
others out and I'm wondering obviously I
channel the same thing or similar thing
that the person who wrote the movie our
perception is that let us say for now
the most likely definition that will
suit is a probable parallel
reality oh okay
um par parallel Earth reality or okay
well that sounds really
intriguing would you like to visit it
I'm sorry would you like to visit it
sure go
ahead along the lines in a sense
obviously you already have yeah
certainly I I do recognize that rock
back your own postcard so to
speak what postcard postcard oh yeah
on the subject of channeling um things
that other people have
channeled I believe that I channeled an
idea from motion
picture um that somebody else channeled and they
um that somebody else channeled and they
got theirs done before I did
synchronicity abounds was it is it synchronicity or
abounds was it is it synchronicity or
that I channeled something that it's
synchronicity well I do understand that
yes but I'm wondering if there was a
connection such as a counterpart who
wrote this particular screenplay that
was actually produced it was a movie can
be we will let you explore that
according to your own feelings okay all
right thank you well thank you b y um
I'm a Pianist I came last week all right
and um I've noticed I started practicing
a lot more recently and well playing all
right and I'm enjoying it a lot oh thank
you um however I've noticed that my
right hand is having a lot of difficulty
there's a lot of pain that develops in
my forearm oh that has slowed down my
fingers and weakened my right hand and
the bulk of my music is done with my
right hand [Laughter]
[Laughter]
oh I will I would like to um figure out
a way for this to not happen anymore
play with your
left well I play classical music and
it's written a lot for the right hand I
see Turn the Page upside down
[Laughter] okay now you might think but I am being
fous however you will find that if you
do perhaps in fact Turn the Page upside
down you will begin to form Connections
in different portions of your
brain and this will rebalance the neural
circuitry all right
okay become a little less structured all
structured all
right have some
fun take a break go on vacation with the
idea of your music
all right okay do not
push let it
flow loosen it up a little bit for now
okay when you feel the
balance when you become the music it
will flow without
strain without the need to feel that it
must be controlled
right yes thank you thank
you you may if you wish right the
right the
idea of what may be refer to as the as the
channeling
somata that contains within
itself the idea of the blending of
polarities within the tonal vibrations
of
music all right I got it fine
fine
yes um everything is going really well
um yes I just have one question all
right um I have recently been in quite a
bit of contact with someone who started
an organization which I was a part of
for a while and had quite an interesting
experience U during the last week or so
I I realized that my exploration of this
particular organization
was a reflection of my negative self all
right you like interesting to realize
that all right and uh did you have a
good time discovering that yes I do oh
thank you now also I have been having
some different experiences it's like
this particular person I think that this
person is exploring it as well as myself
like the the different um angles on
different people who have who have been
and are with this
organization and um
I've been having some U very interesting
experiences one has been that I am um
I've have been very
tired uh another one is for a little
while I had an allergy which has gone
away you know I think I I aligned with
that pretty well um one thing that has
not gone away is um my eyes are very
sore and red and I was wondering if you
could give me a little bit of a a helper
on um this particular thing kind of give
me a better understanding of what's
Happening use your integrated self for now this is
use your integrated self for now this is
what we can suggest and energize with
your blue white lights on purified water
and in this way immerse your eyes in
that water
water
okay okay I'll try it while you are
doing that relax into the understanding
whether it becomes analytical or not
does not matter but relax into the
understanding that everything you are
doing you are doing for a
reason let it come to you soft
gently all right okay thank you this is
our suggestion according to what we
perceive of the idea of your
Consciousness to be at this
time and along with
that perhaps one tonal vibration of what you
perhaps one tonal vibration of what you
call a
bell idea that as you
ring the bell and listen to the
crystalin clap ity of the
tone use your imagination and imagine
that that tone crystallizes the
water all right
okay than you for sure yes what happens
when something really excites you and
yet you have obligations to do things
which don't obligations who creates
those obligations um it's a co-creation
obligations um it's a co-creation
between you and the other individual yes
s well change this operation you can you
can still function within your integrity
if you simply recognize something is not
your vibration then simply utilizing
your integrity rearrange the things that
you are doing so that you do not have to
do those things
anymore you can also understand that
many times when you allow yourself to
act upon your excitement and begin to do
what excites you the most many of the
things that previously may have seemed
like obligations may come back in
different forms that will not seem like
obligations okay you follow me mhm
trust all
right yeah okay also another question
about relationships relationships
um I
found this past 6 months or so that I've
been in tune with with many different
individuals and um feel a lot of love
for of them
B so um well it's great the problem that
I have
problem for
what you feel love for all these
individuals and you have a
problem on this planet
yes on your planet yes [Laughter]
[Laughter]
to the wall
wriggly um yeah dealing with the set
standards of the society set standard of
the society I see or things that you believe
society I see or things that you believe
are written in
[Laughter] steel well I feel that they've been
steel well I feel that they've been
me since I was born so if you know that
that is the only reason you are
following them then because you can have
the conception of why they are there you
are automatically released from
them otherwise you wouldn't be able to
conceive that there is something
else the perspective being able to see
that there is another way is in and of
itself the
release because you have to be in a
sense outside or beyond the idea you
think you are trapped within in order to
see that idea right it seems difficult
to seems difficult another unwritten
law recognize that many of the things in
your society that you base your reasons
upon for not doing what you would prefer
to do have no more substance than the
reasons themselves well I'm doing this or not
themselves well I'm doing this or not
doing this because of this but this is
just as vague nebulous and insubstantial
as the reasons you are only creating
more
reasons follow me sort of there is only
one fundamental reality for everyone the
fact that you exist period now we do
recognize that you have in a sense made
some overall
agreements but you can also recognize
that to a very great extent your ability
to even recognize that there can be
transformation into something you would
prefer is an indication to you that it
is probably all right within the mass
Consciousness agreement to be able to do
so yeah that would be nice it is nice
would be keeps it in the future okay
nice thank you then have a good
time I still feel
like to be truly in line with myself yes
as if you could be out of
alignment did you hear me yes what does
that mean to
you it means that I'm not integrating
all the parts of
myself as if you could be out of
alignment with with
yourself as if you could be out of
alignment okay what I mean is to be the
vibration yes that I
desire if you are not that vibration how
do you even know that such a vibration
exists then then where from whence
cometh the the sensation of being out of
alignment with oneself by creating the
vibration with your Bel
by believing that it's possible that
it's possible to be out of
alignment by
believing that your imagination your
conceptual ability is not as real as
your physical
Reality by continuing to separate them
into two different things instead of one
I have conceived of it therefore this is
what is I am that I
am whatever you can conceive of you are
at the moment you conceive of it but you
can have many different conceptions one
after another choose which one you prefer and
another choose which one you prefer and
act like it knowing that the one you
prefer is what your reality will reflect
and trusting that everything in your
reality therefore from that point
forward is a reflection of what you
prefer to be do not judge that it is not
well I I feel like I
can't live in this environment and be
how I really want to be you are
missing if you simply take it for
granted right now right now that the
idea you prefer is in effect right now
if you exhibit trust to that effect then
you will begin to allow what is going on
in your life to be a part of the idea
you prefer to be so that at whatever
rate you are comfortable with bit by bit
all of the reflections that you have
that now let us say or used to seem so
negative will be to transform into more
positive Reflections stop judging Where You Are
Reflections stop judging Where You Are
so that it can function as a stepping
stone to take you where you want to be
if you judge where you are you can't use
it to go
on you follow me everything you have
ever done in this life or any other life
has gotten you where you are if you
invalidate any portion of it you can't
keep going because you are removing a
stepping stone by invalidating
it let what is happening be what is
going to get you where you want to be
and the sooner you have that attitude
the sooner it will seem like that is
what is
happening remember every situation is
fundamentally neutral until you supply
the meaning no situation has built in
meaning no situation has built in
meaning the meaning comes from
you okay find you
okay find you
what happens when one individual is
benefiting from relationship and the
other is not you are always
benefiting if it is your choice to
benefit from the relationship by being
shown an idea you do not prefer then you
have benefited because that idea has
given you an opportunity to decide what
you do prefer once again you are
choosing to look at the situation as
something that doesn't benefit you so
you are putting the negative connotation
and meaning into a neutral situation
okay so once you understand that this is
showing you something you don't want to
be or you don't want to then you can
turn it around and recognize that it is
giving you an opportunity to decide what
you do want to
be then you will recognize that the
situation has served you and it will
immediately lose its negative impact in
your life it will slide right through you
it is that simple that is what you do
not believe it is that
believe it is that
simple you follow me
mhm like you guys um Do You Believe In A
guiding Spirit guiding
Spirit guiding
Spirit we do recognize that there are
levels of consciousness that do wish to
be of aist to other levels of
consciousness in a sense that can be
tered a guiding Spirit however from our
point of view guiding Spirits are doing
their jobs when they lure you to more of
yourself not to
them someone told me that my guiding
Spirit was from
madira all right can you elaborate on
that simply that there are many
Connections in many different levels or
densities of Consciousness which you
have co-created an interact with for the
purpose of allowing them to reflect to
you portions of yourself that you need
to be in touch with so that you can
integrate so that you can know that you
are the path you chose to bead
bead
well that I guess you answered
it those that US
History well yeah the person that told
me that that my guidance was from adir
was somewhat of a pirate likee person
who pirate yeah who was very spontaneous
and freespirit
and crazy and and you know they were
saying that you need to just let
yourself go and just do the things that
you want to do because you're a very
powerful individual everyone is okay
now has that individual allowed you to
become your own guiding
Spirit um the individual that told me
this
yes I'm beginning to recognize it um
that you all are your own guiding Spirit
first and
foremost then you can recognize the way
in which guiding Spirits work they get
you you follow
me everyone is a reflection therefore
everyone is a guiding spirit for
everyone else to allow everyone to know
they are their own best guiding spirits
that is the job of a guiding Spirit
physical or non-physical it doesn't
matter you follow me yes I do oh thank
you very much now you might find maybe
this in our perception can go many
different ways but you may find that the
energy in our perception that was
referred to by that that individual is a
non-physiological what you would call
higher density
Consciousness that you have formed a
co-arranged with whether or not it needs to manifest
with whether or not it needs to manifest
in any more symbolic physiological terms
than that will be determined by you you
may not need that blatant of a symbol if
you already recognize that you are your
own Master you will simply do what you
want to
do all right have a good time I will oh
thank you you Mar
you you Mar
oh take a short
break all right allow me to bid each and
every one of you a bond and loving good
morning good morning
for at this Junction in our
interaction it is where I am upon my own
Planet Dawn
Dawn
therefore in this way allow me to
proceed with another
idea the idea you have discussed once
again of recognizing your own existence
of psychic potential
integration and connection and linking
to the idea of other mentality which as
we have said telepathically speaking is
always emotionally activated and thus
you understand the idea as we have said
of individuals you recognize to be
loving to each other most often exhibit
the idea of understanding each other's
thoughts no therefore recognizing that
the idea is that to love them is to know
them in this sense what you call psychic
functioning again is your natural birth
right it is a spontaneous connection to
more of yourself in that way and to the
recognition of the interaction you are
having with another
individual the idea many times however
of your society's let us say
attempts to categorize the idea of
psychic functioning within its standard
structure of scientific
analysis many times will in your terms
not yield the results you expect for
several reasons first of all it is a
spontaneous interaction and many times
not subject to the idea of rigorous
control for it is a living process a
living interaction and many times the
idea of the
sterilization of the conditions in which
the idea is attempted to be forced to
exist will not be indicative nor
conducive to the idea of the spontaneous
emotional surge that is usually present
when psychic interaction takes place in
your day-to-day occurrences
spontaneously recognize also these two
things therefore the idea of psychic function
therefore the idea of psychic function
will always
yield to the simplest way to access
information and will always contain
activity based upon the degree of desire
for the
information thus you will find that
while it is not impossible in many cases
for circumstances to be enacted as you
wish them to as you call upon them
consciously recognize many times that
very often when let us say to use the
example you have used in your
civilization many times someone wishes
you to quote unquote tell them what they
are thinking what they have in their
pocket or what they did that morning
recognize simply that the first criteria
of the fact that psychic function will
always yield to the simplest way to
access the information will simply yield
to obvious someone there already knows
the information therefore psychic
information therefore psychic
functioning will bow to the
understanding that the easiest way to
access the information is to Simply ask
or say the idea if you already know it
the second idea will be indicative of
when it is possible for an individual
who simply know those type of things is
because they immediately have the idea
of a spontaneous desire to link with the
identity of that individual in that way
and if the individual is open enough to
allow such a link then the other
individual can know what the so-called
answer is in that way but the idea of
the ease of the flow and the desire must
be present or there will be no
connection in that sense so you will
find that many times the idea of asking
someone well what did I eat for
breakfast today May simply yield a
response well I don't
care so the idea will not elicit enough
desire for the other individual to
function psychically with regard to that
particular circumstance this does not mean that
circumstance this does not mean that
that same individual may not all of a
sudden spontaneously know what that
other individual may have had for
breakfast if for some reason the desire
or the need is strong enough for that
individual to know perhaps even
sometimes beyond the interaction later
on when the idea of the pressure is off
and the first individual has once again
lowered their
screens for in this way many times when
individuals request that another
individual's psychic function on command
they are actually creating a challenge
and in that way what they are doing is
taking all of the accessibility of the
information and closing it all all up
and saying I'll bet you can get this
WOW therefore there is no ability no
opportunity for the
emotional exchange that is the
fundamental necessity of psychic
functioning that is why once again you
recognize that individuals who exhibit
the quality as you have said of being in
love will very generally always know
what the other is thinking before the
other one says it it is because they are
flowing together with
empathic understanding all telepathy and
psychic functioning really in a sense is
more or less
empathy identification with if you cannot
identification with if you cannot
identify if you cannot become innocent
congruent with someone
else then the realities will more often
than not remain separated in that way
you hold
me
sure [Music] [Music]
guys all
right it was about a question I was
going to ask you I was going to ask I
was going to ask you what
rest restlessness and the reason why is
restlessness and the reason why is
because um I'm a painter my living as an
artist and as far back as I can remember
that was always what I wanted to do
there was never any question in my mind
yes and um lately I've noticed when I'm
painting I I'll start working and I get
very restless yeah it's like I'm what
else is it you think you should be doing
inste what I got was it suddenly
occurred to me that I thought Carol the
reason why you're feeling WR is because
you're painting for money I'm thinking
that if I allow myself to take time off
B then I won't make enough money to pay
the bills and the rent and so it's like
pushing myself to all right instead of
flowing them yes and allowing the
universe to support whatever you do by
allowing enough money or any other tool
that is necessary to continue to be
there in whatever amount it needs to be
there to Simply support you in the idea
that you are right it's like I I feel
like well I just can't take time off I
mean how long can I take off you know
there won't be any money and all kind of
thing but understand it is not that you
are taking off from something it is that
you are doing what you wish being the
idea that you prefer to be and allowing
Universal abundance to support you in
whatever way is necessary to allow you
to continue to be the idea you prefer to
be if money is necessary to do that then
it will automatically be there in
exactly the amounts that are necessary
to do so but all the other tools of
abundance that will allow you to
continue to be who you wish to be will
also be there sometimes money sometimes
not right there has been a lot of
abundance that isn't necessarily hey
just want to share that well thank you
very much for your own
self-cognition thank you you have
painted a pretty picture thank
picture thank
you than you you mentioned um we've
discussed a couple of times the
communications with the dolphin
civilization had with others
civilizations hey was this primarily um
on an emotional empathic telepathic
level or was yes and how do these
interchanges occur are they consciously
aware that they're talking yes with
another civilization yes and the
sharings are in terms of feelings or
concepts or basically yes can you detail
that for me a little bit give me some
I'm interested in the kinds of
interchanges that occurred or do occur
simply there is what you would call
first of all the basic education or
simply learning as to what the other
civilizations are all about and the
teaching of what theirs is
about and there is also the recognition
that since they are being of assistance
to you in your transformation then there
is also the let us say correlation or
coordination of information to allow
them to do so at the same time that
everyone else is also doing so mhm now
would a specific dolphin pick out a
specific individual and civilization it
can yes there are many opportunities for
many different ways of forming those
connection and the dolphin Consciousness
is consciously aware of being able to do
that much as I would contact someone in
your civilization if that is what they
are doing they are conscious of it and
is that what they are doing that
not all of them and do you have a
varying scan of interests and
uh talents among the dolphins that to
some degree yeah to some degree although
they are a little bit more in a sense
homogenous than you
m okay thank you thank you one moment
yes I finally got my Emerald mail hey
several weeks ago you recomed
you suggested I get an emerald up you
suggested I get an emerald to assist
with the slipping of the plates of my
skull which were reflection of was
slipping of the plates of the Earth all
right and so I got the Emerald 2 days
ago yes and then I didn't know what to
do with it you don't so I used my
imagination oh then you did know what to
do with it okay and so I taped it on my
third eye whereas
right does it like being there it does
is a very a good view of
[Music]
everything my son thinks it looks like a
green booger all booger all
[Music]
right so
um it's been on my forehead two days and
I feel connected with my energy and I'm
wondering if you have any other
suggestion or what I do with it what
happened to your
imagination kind of ran out of ideas ran
out of
ideas perhaps that is only because now
is the opportunity to do something with
the energy that you have fly
you
yes sure you going to pick me up again
continue um I've had an interesting
phenomenon occur and it has to do with I I think I
occur and it has to do with I I think I
understand this I make a conscious
decision to have everything go extremely
well to know that everything always goes
extremely well right and then I have
things occur like flat tires so what so
what so what why can that not fit in to
the definition that you know it is still
something that represents the idea that
you are and is still a reflection that
everything is going perfectly because it
wasn't the products that I envisioned to
complete that as we have said is not the
point when you put expectation on your
visualization then you only make the
visualization you have had the only
acceptable one you are simply using your
visualization as a model for the energy
whatever it is that does happen is still
a reflection of the energy that you had
in the visualization whether it comes in
an unexpected form or
not that is the whole point not that you
cannot have a literal manifestation of
your visualization but you don't have
to it will come in the way that truly
does serve you best in the easiest
possible way and it comes along and you
judge it to be not part of the path so
do not give it an opportunity to serve
you that's seems to be I can understand
the concept I can let's put it this
way you have let us say a visualization
that you are driving your automobile
that you are on your way to meet someone
who will be of benefit for one of the
ideas that you are very excited about
doing following while you are driving
you have your flat
fire you
trust that it is for a reason according
to the idea you know you are and lo and
behold the person that stops to assist
you is someone who can help you better
than the one you were going to
meet interesting concept when you let
that be the synchronistic reality it
will be more been a concept to you it
will be your reality so it's it's the
trusting yes what occurs that is all
that's necessary to allow it to become
the physical reality just the trust
that's it I fig if you put it out about
more finally get oh thank [Music] [Music]
you
expect expectation as we have been
discussing it is usually once again more
judgment the idea that something must
happen the way you specifically conceive
of it or it won't be valid putting
expectations in that way now recognize
you do not want to be
bored thus the idea of the visualization
again while it can be literal will
usually think be a model a template for
whatever it is that does in fact need to
happen to bring you the
effect of the visual this will give you
an indication of the pulse rates of
different time frames
yeah thank you very much oh thank you
for co-creating the
timing may I ask may I put this to you I
have recently been in Sedona and while
there I was a new name for myself right
and uh I was I was I went there to open
my my myself to start to write a book
that I feel is necessary all right and
while writing um I was Chanel the name
some a voice came to me and said you're
doing very well ta t a yo all right and
I said my I like that name and they said
that is your name and I of course been
going by a name that I have not been
comfortable with all my life so child my
name is f f a y all right and I was this
name Tao came to me and I feel very
comfortable with okay that is because
you are now forming alignments to the
concept and idea of your higher self
vibration and losing connections to the
archetypal symbology of your
physiological self thank you no thank you I've done
self thank you no thank you I've done
nothing
the idea means that the vibrational
signature F has to do with putting her
energy in symbolic representations
according to what is drawn from the mass
subconsciousness of your physical
reality the idea of Teo which is also
very similar to the idea of
Da will be more of an alignment to the
vibration that represents her fourth
density celf so it is the revamping the
reidentification of the vibration of the
being knows herself to be so that now
she can recognize that she is a
different idea a new reality then you
suggest then it would be to my
betterment to use the name Tao from here
here on out it is up to you if you feel
comfortable with it so inclined then
simply utilize it it is not so much for
the betterment but simply that you find
it is what represents the signature
vibration of your being if it is what is
comfortable utilize it as a
tool thank you thank you once again
yay um my relationship with my mother is
filled with much disharmony oh repeat
after me yes my my relationship
relationship as as my mother my
I if you are also your mother and your
mother is also
you why have you co-created the idea
that it is disharmonious
disharmonious
well I don't know but in what way do you
perceive it to be
disharmonious well generally when we
whenever we get together for
communication it tends to be for stri do
you mean
because you are are accepting the belief
system that you must convince them of
your point of view and that they must
convince you of
their I would
some all right
simply as you are a reflection to other
individuals if you know what is the
vibrational Truth for you be that
whatever they wish to offer you in
return take it as an offering M and say
thank you no thank
you that is all there is to it there is
no need for disharmony in that way and
the more willing you are who simply
reflect that you are being what is true
for you the more opportunity you give to
another individual to also recognize
that they can simply choose what is true
for them and that what is true for them
and what is true for you are both real
realities there is no
background one real reality it against
which other realities are measured for
their degree of accuracy or
truth the truth is composed of all
truths so simply it is your opportunity
to recognize that what you hear from her
are other truths in the truth if some of
them vibrate according to your truth
then integrate them if they don't
don't okay great thank you well find you
you can still be unconditionally loving
because she is presenting you with
opportunities to view that many more
ways that all that this has of
expressing different truths so it rounds
out your ability to recognize other
points of view and to let them serve you
and to serve them in return
H for sure yes tomorrow morning hi
tomorrow morning I'm sending my body
over to Salt Lake City oh have I'm going
to show up with it and uh
we're going to take part in the
International Convention of the society
for the preservation and encouragement
of Barber Shop quartet singing in
American corporate and I would like to invite you
corporate and I would like to invite you
the people of eani and everybody here to
uh join in at any time and I'll be
channeling through various highly
enjoyable harmonies you might enjoy having
harmonies you might enjoy having
vibrating in the universe so I just want
to offer that as an
invitation our energy is always present
wherever you wish to partake of it we
will enjoy the idea of the
tone yeah we'll add one more person to
your Triad and get a little
[Music] Harmony Triad when combined forms the
Harmony Triad when combined forms the
concept of a for
right that is
harmony thank you
talking about um this Society this
parallel society that was like soil
green or whatever I started coughing oh
and um and I just have this like this um
itch maybe you are a street sweeper sweeper
K
maybe yeah I do have a strong I guess I
feel like my heart chakra is you know
something about my heart soer about that
kind of society cuz I don't I don't
share his um love of it all right you
have had exposure to some of those
things and you may have found them
distasteful so you are trying to spit it
out but in this way again simp we
recognize you are only aligning with
more portions of yourself so that you
can integrate them and that has been a
synchronistic service to you to see that
reflection MH lately that I've been I find myself
MH lately that I've been I find myself
though when um somebody else has
something going on in one of their
chakras I will feel it in mine okay
again the
empathy the recognition that all is one
right that you are all connected and
relating to each other you are all in a
relationship [Music]
[Music]
together is there anything to do with
that just just love it I is there any
way to
more easily or just the same way you're
allow let's see as you say
[Music] G I don't know maybe there is what do
G I don't know maybe there is what do
you
think um I think that
um you think it's already
done what's already done it is
integrated yeah you will not sound too
true I just thinking of certain other
things that have occurred within the
last couple weeks where this has
happened and like in one case I just had
this tremendous swollen gland right
after family somebody and it lasted for
a whole week until something occurred in
their own space and then and I felt it
in my SP and then my vanished you are
once again forming an empathic
identification simply realize you can do
so without necessarily taking on the
symbolic negativity of that way I'd like
oh you
simply realize once again that all that
is allowing you to create it to that
extent is the belief within you that you
can be of assistance to them at the same
time there is a little bit of
Remnant no offense
martyrdom yeah so for
thank you so in this way you
simply have not yet completely
consciously integrated the understanding
that to help them to assist them to help
them help themselves you do not have to
take it on as a burden
yeah all right but you are being loving
so simply love yourself as as well then
you will Channel it into the type of
energy that does not need to manifest in
that way right thank
way right thank
you
[Music] yes how would you define the opposite of
yes how would you define the opposite of
love not hate repat the question how
would you define guilt it is the
opposite of love not hate is the
opposite of love but guilt and what is
hate hate is another variation of the
idea of Love after having passed through
Judgment feeles of guil like you feel
like maybe let someone down not done
what was expected now there are
different types of the idea that you may
be recognizing one of them may Simply Be
Your cognition that perhaps you were
functioning outside of your
integrity and in this way it is simply
an opportunity to recognize the
alignment that can reenter you
but guilt of judgment as the opposite of
Love since Love Is The Knowing deserv
ability and worthiness of all guilt is
the belief in
worthlessness lack of deserv ability I'm
probably closer to what I
get okay that's very helpful oh that is
loves you
unconditionally proving it by creating
you
now why should you not Grant yourself
the same respect and unconditional love
that is given to you automatically by
all that
is all that is thinks you deserve it why
don't you I don't know why do you think
we do that we again perhaps simply
because once you decided to explore
limitation one of the things you forgot
is that you are worth loving that you
are actually love
itself that is all all you need to do is
remember that you are made of
love and then everything will be an
active
love are those this little remnant of
past judgment over when you feel a
little twingy yes in a sense
yes I know it's getting a lot better it
is what it is yes right thank you thank
you one moment
1978 I speak up in
1978 I spent a year in
Creed writing a
book and something about that time is feels
and something about that time is feels
like L end
unconnected loose end loose end yes and
the book was the
book wow I sound loud to myself yeah but
those people can't hear all the book the
book involved it was a science fiction
book and the book involved a a crystal
Planet a planet that has been
crystallized uh the other planets
involve the high technology in which the
so the super structure of the planet
were embedded in Crystal um sort of beds
so there and the crystals had been over
Evolution taking on lives of their own
and so there was this whole thing about
crystals on both of these worlds the
people lived in um of the one had a
configuration of nine instead of a
family structures we know it they lived
in eight they were eight almost
functions or participa in sort of spot R
positions or something an Octor oh okay
yes and an implied ninth point then the
blending of it all
a okay well anyway the book had all
these kinds of things in it that I just
finding out now have all kinds of
connections as you have just said I
didn't finish the book I only got half
of it
done and then it's sort of been a a
loose end a sort of dangling loose
end and there was a lot of perhaps
simply because you not ready at that
time to understand that you can totally
and do totally create your own reality
for the idea of the symbolic
presentation of the crystallin world is
in a sense a literal rep
representation the idea is that there is
such a world and in that world is where
individual beings can go from many
civilizations to have manifested while
in the influence of that world
everything they imagin while still
physically alive in other words it is like actually
alive in other words it is like actually
living physically in a dream
instantaneously created in the Crystal
World it lets you know beyond the shadow
of a doubt that you create your
reality does that have any relation to
the Dark Crystal moon
no not as you mean
it thank you
for one
moment thank you thank
you this is my first meeting with you
your definition of love all that
is does that assist you yes are you
sure yes in all that is way a how
convenient why we refer to the idea all
that is we are referring to what your
Society usually labels as God
all that is is
love everything is Created from love
everything is love that is what love
is it is the
substance itself of
existence so when you feel that
vibration is when you know you are
creating the idea of yourself to be in
harmonious synchronized alignment with
all that
is will that suffice as a definition for
you or do you wish to explore this idea f e e
I to experience like almost being blown
backwards with the enormity of what you
just say
say
yes that may be the Sensation that is
common when you make a connection from a
particular re reality that has been used
to
limitations the experience of rushing
headlong to meet
yourself infinite
acceleration however you will find that
also infinite acceleration means you are
everywhere at once being everywhere at
once will and can also feel like
standing perfectly still and therefore
gives you the sensation of ultimate
PE and love
about then simply love that says it
all thank you all right okay what does
it mean when you click your teeth
together I do not click my
teeth the
idea is one physiological translation of
my mental
l i I listened to a tape of last year
where apparently you opened your eyes
that time and somebody asked you about
it you mean the physiological Channel's
eyes there will be flick from time to
time to allow there to be more blending
of the Consciousness between us that we
have become I have asked you once before
but uh ask again do
you do you do you think that in time um
D will be opening his his
eyes well if it was outside of time he
probably wouldn't have eyes to
open so in time it will be but in this
way the idea for this particular
physiological channel will be therefore
a sign of the idea of more utilization
of his own higher
Consciousness ah and that's of you in a
sense yes but in another sense more
because we will be in that sense more
Blended even though we will still remain
as distinct
beings we are forming a Third identity
right and then
and then
um oh I forgot if you are his future
self then are both of you aspects of the
same higher Consciousness yes the same
whole soul the same there are different
definitions of the idea of higher
Consciousness we are simply referring to
the idea of the portion of the whole
soul that is given the job of
functioning as the higher Consciousness
relative to your Earth system in other
words the potential of what an IND idual
can become within for sensity on your
world that higher self that future self
well I'll use your term whole whole soul
is that your term in a sense yes so that
you and the physiological channel are
just two different aspects of the whole
soul of the same whole soul and this and
that whole
soul then has the job of functioning as
a quote higher Consciousness in a sense
for both of us but the higher
Consciousness I was specifically
referring to is what the physiological
channel will view as what it is he is
becoming relative to your time track and
the yeah got it and then when you form
this Third identity identity you still
are yourself
Onan is just a third part of your whole
soul in a sense it is yes a co-creation
to allow to be a type of
reidentification so that the individual
you would functionally recognize as the
physical channel will become another
type of individual another Persona okay
but then he won't actually need to to
Chann go through the process of a trend
correct okay great thank you thank
you um I was wondering uh since you was
talking about parallel reality or yeah
multi-dimensional Universal yes yes well
there's something that sometimes happens
or there's documentation of people
finding this on this planet where ships
are found at se and the crew is totally
some of those are instances of going
through dimensional warps of different
types yes uh what happens to those
people like different things according
to the differences in the warps some of
them will transfer to other parallel
realities the majority of them will
simply become instantaneously
physical is there any particular reason
is
it that is according to those
individuals there are as many reasons as
there are individuals who co-create that
experience well there's apparency that
it happens in certain areas because you
have a mass conscious electromagnetic
awareness that fluctuates in relatively
regular patterns those energy vortices
represent the doorways from your
dimension to others
it pulses with a certain type of
regularity because your dimension like
any other dimension has a certain
crystallin quality and so it will have a
regularity structure to its pattern in
an electromagnetic sense how about uh
this there's been stories that some of
these people like during the war planes
have um disappeared and then like many
years later the plane has appeared again
and the same crew is on it and they
don't recognize where they are they
picked up on radios and stuff like that
is that this is in your terms relatively
rare yes it is it's not doed what has
occurred at that point simply the idea
once again that they have skipped over
the intervening moments that they would
have considered to be the normal
Continuum of time flow so in their
experience time didn't pass
correct one other question
um there's various
uh well ideas of what happens to a being
in between lives okay U could you
comment on that well I have various um
you have co-created there to be many
so-called different levels of
non-physical existence and the primary
understanding is that whatever beliefs
first of all you carry with you into the
idea of death will be what you
immediately experience the after life to
be therefore you will find that as you
gain more and more understanding
understanding of where you now are it
will become more and more malleable
allowing you to recognize that you are a
thought form in a world of thought form
and that what you imagine is
instantaneously reality to you you also
gain the idea of an overview of all you
have ever been on certain levels and in
this way can incorporate these
understandings of yourself and decide
whether you wish to or not experience
another physiological life or do
something else there are many different
else there are many different
experiences in those different levels
and Realms in general however it is
simply the
recognition that you have created all
the lives you have experienced and are
now free to create whatever else you
wish on any level of experience physical
and non physical many individuals
however because of the belief systems
that they have had in your Society May
for a time not in a sense even know they
are dead these are what you call the
hauntings or ghosts so to speak
basically are going on as if they are
typically physically alive and as we
have said the original purpose for what
you have come to call an exorcist is to
Simply Be a Ghost
psychologist to let them know they are
in fact dead and they are fine and they
can go on about Better Business and
don't have to remain attached in that
way to the physical
plan now also because of the different
belief systems once again you will find
that because their thought is the thing
individuality who have had beliefs about what the
who have had beliefs about what the
afterlife will be will you experience
that idea immediately now if it is
something that they have believed would
be unpleasant then it probably will not
take them too very long to change it
because as soon as they have the idea
that they wish it were different it
is and many times the idea of
individuals so to speak that you will
meet in the so-called
afterlife that you would quote unquote
recognize as someone that has gone on
before you can be portions of that
Consciousness but also many times you
will find that simply other let us say
neutral consciousnesses will also be
there to take that reflection if that is
what you need to assist you
over then as you begin to understand
where you are they will become more and
more neutral more
themselves sure be sure does that answer
your question yes I just had one other
thing to ask um when uh okay person uh
has died and picks up another body um
there's children that they they know who
they are and then they forget hey uh is
that me not that you have to right well
it's very it has simply once again been
The Habit because of all the limitation
and separation now this is the
transformational life you will find that
the children being born now are more
prone to
remember and not
forget many of them will remind the
parents thank
you thank you um before you got to the
neutral personality nice uh you were
saying something and
I and it was in you mean the idea that
what you believe the afterlife is is
what you experienced and then you went a
little further and neutral something
about neutral personalities to exist
well simply the idea that many times you
will find that as you quote cross over
you will meet the Consciousness that you
may expect to meet of people that have
gone on before you in this way in a
sense many of them may be the quote
unquote original consciousnesses but
many may not many may be the idea of
Spirit guides or levels of consciousness
that simply know that the best way to
assist you over is to represent the
reflection you think you need to see to
let you know you're all right then once
you become stabilized and your new
environment they will take back their
old identities thank you you yes you thank
identities thank you you yes you thank
you I just uh a few minutes ago
connected uh with the idea of myself as
a crystal oh yeah I've I've heard you
talk about that concept several times
over the last year and a half but I just
got another perspective that I've never
gotten before each and every one of you
is your own master
Crystal your own best tool in that way
uh is there a uh particular gemstone or
Crystal that that uh after I just told
you you your
master I don't believe in you Smoky C
thank
you has there been an Invader force on
this planet
Invader Force yeah I've been L
[Music] into understanding of a an Invader force
into understanding of a an Invader force
that uh would implant beings with the
forget uh
to yes there has
been you [Music]
[Music]
you implanted your own
for there been civilizations from other
planets come
here like is there a mar
Confederacy in a sense to some degree
but recognize this any ideas of any
so-called negativity that you may feel
you may be able to experience is only
because you would co-create an agreement
to do so no one can for anything upon
your follow me
yeah so did these take
place to some
degree but most of the idea is mostly in
terms that are more symbolically
representative than physiologically
literal because once again the idea is
simply that when you
agree to create to co-create those type
of
interactions you yourself become a part
of that so-called Confederacy of
negativity and therefore an agent is
already there you become that
there you become that
agent that is how the idea spreads
through fear the fear that it is more
powerful than the reality you know to be
true for
you that is how the idea quote unquote
of conquering
of the civilizations
occurred the fear on the part of the
civilization that it can be conquered
turn them into extensions of the ones
they fear the ones they fear automatically
fear the ones they fear automatically
know that and therefore are
instantaneously bonded in negative energy with them is
bonded in negative energy with them is
that how a principle way that Orion
operates yes we follow me yes
yes we follow me yes
what reality are you do you wish to feed
the idea of such interactions or simply
recognize that they are offerings that
have nothing to do with your
vibration their offerings that have
nothing to do with my vibration thank
you you're here here
you I
um I have three things I want to ask you
about um speak up please okay
um what is can you tell me if this
mountain which there's such a
controversy over right now in Arizona
with regard toi was that always an area
for U evenor to when they started being
there being there has been some fluctuation
being there has been some fluctuation
but yes there has always been energy in
that area to some degree of the type
that they claim that it is basically yes
although again there has been some
fluctuation okay I was curious about
that because when I heard about this
controversy I saw
that actually as an opportunity for the
Indians even though they moved to find
that they could create that type of an
environment wherever they go that is
correct it is also an opportunity for
them to remember what it means to be an
Indian and to Simply recognize that the
event that they may fear is what will
create it to happen to fear it to Simply
know that they are who they are will
create them to be
immovable yes it is an opportunity for
them to regain the idea of who they
are okay the second thing is I have
several which I purchased because I
thought they were pretty and I
like okay and um I noticed that recently
they're beginning to have speak up again
tremendous rainbows in them all right
which they did not have before all right
and uh I'm curious about that I you are
we'll have a good time exploring
it next
okay the other thing is
um uh I
remember last time no a couple of times
ago when I all right all right all right
what is a
rainbow what is a rainbow yes well it's
a um it is all the frequencies is it
not color color band Yes the
representation of all the different
levels reflected in every single facet
next oh well the question the thing that
I wanted to know about that somebody
told me they thought it was because that
I was creating that in in the Crystal
but I thought maybe the crystal
conscious was developing those things on
their own it can't do it without
you let's put it this way what reason
has it got without
you for it own for its
own it is completely and totally of
service oh it is
yes okay I understand than you okay okay
the other thing last thing was
um a few times ago I asked you about the
boo consolation you said later okay uh I
say that now yes I know that but the
thing I want to ask you is that uh last
year earlier in the year at Margo I
mentioned to you an energy that I had
experienced which was like a great bird
and you told me that it was Thea energy
is that a connection to this to some
degree yes this more later on yes you
yes this more later on yes you
will will we do it as a group
[Music] maybe thank
maybe thank
you you uh very quickly uh these past
few days been very hot around here and
um I've responded to it in unusual way
for me and that is that I I drink a lot
of water I've taken potassium and
calcium and no matter how much water I
drink my mouth is really dry and I have
trouble swallowing and I was wondering
if there's some minerals that I'm that
you might perceive that is missing or
something one moment
do you like citrus
yes you may increase a little bit your
intake along with the water of the juice
of idea orange idea lemon idea lime tomato raw raw
corn okay some ideas
some ideas
of clear fruit
juices not an
excess in this way not the idea of what
you would call in terms of the
orange so much the orange juice but
simply some of the orange added into the
water the same with the idea of the
lemon although a little bit more of that
can be ingested and the same with the
lime a little bit more with water yes
very life okay
yes our perception is that you will also
leave yourself to some literature that
will contain some other
ideas that you may or may not find that
you identify
with okay to valy in the GRE all
right thank you thank you hi
you hi
like a title for tonight a title
relationship sounds good to
me comes from an [Music]
[Music]
expert thank you thank
you for participating so actively in
this
relationship um Bashar is there any
validity to the concept
nope I say that because there is always
validity always validity validity simply
is what is true for you okay let me it
another way all
right could you help me with the idea
with the concept of what is the validity
to a being feeling that he must create
retribution for some qu unquote mistake
created in a past
existence again is it a continuation in
this way of the idea of Judgment of
guilt of
separation for in this way what is being
recognized in a negative sense in a
judgmental sense is simply the desire to
have a polarity balancing experience to
something done before this does not mean
it has to come in the form of
Retribution it does not have to be
looked at as
judgment nothing judges you there is no
outside judge upon you there is no
outside in this way simply recognize the
idea you call Karma is a completely
self-imposed by you on yourself and B
does not have to represent a retribution
or a judgment but simply a balancing of
energy a continuance of a momentum
begun somewhere else somewh else so
basically you could approach it in such
a way that instead of trying to develop
some retribution that you just look at
the particular experience gain or
integrate what you need to integrate
from that experience let it be a choice
not a
punishment right right and then get what you need
right right and then get what you need
to get from it and then you can let it
go good the whole
idea of quote unquote
breaking the karmic cycle so to speak is
the simple recognition that you created
here you could choose not to experience
it at all
correct or if you're if you are
experiencing that your experience for
your chosen reason therefore is under
your control you are not being punished
by someone unless it is yourself right
thank you very much well than you for
sure yes um it's a little unusual for me
but oh very good yeah nice I don't
normally reflect these things oh I've
had a sore left foot for a while I see
yeah could you help me are you playing
the piano with your feet [Music]
[Music]
I used to play the organ with it quite a
bit all right and that's what I kicked
the wrong note thanks for
reflection now in this
way do you feel as you are walking along
now let me remind you of something
however the you you were that was
creating that soreness is not
necessarily the you you are now so I'm
not necessarily speaking to the you that
had the sore foot
anymore but recognize that the idea may
be that you have been
feeling a little
imbalanced so that you would put more
weight on one side than the other and
cause it to be much of a burden to walk
along now that does not necessarily mean
that that is the you you are
now after you have this night of your
time become cognizant of your ability to
treat every situation as fundamentally
neutral that can keep you on an even
kill very nice thank
you than you oh thank
you
um since for about three months now I've
been trying to drawing oh here there we
go thank
you to um recall the dreams and I
mentioned before they were flashing
through so quick that I couldn't get the
act the actual concept of them oh now as
the 5:30 this morning I finally had a
full concept uh and I'm almost I know if
I say something you're going to say what
do you think and I'm going to be stck
for an
answer I'm going you anyway oh all right
uh it was so real it was as real as I'm
sitting here right now and all I
remember was looking down and my body
was filled with acute puncture needles
oh and I'm thinking and it was it was so
real I thought what am I doing who's
doing acupuncture on me and the next
minute me you the next second my eyes
are open and I'm actually starting to
feel if they're still there or whatever
but they weren't and I decided but you
are simply recognizing in a symbolic
conscious way the idea of all of The
Matrix points that you are as a
vibratory entity you opened up all the different
entity you opened up all the different
vortices that go into making up the idea
of yourself as an energy
being symbolically represented by the
idea of the needles of acupuncture which
create a connection of the flow of all
those points to each other you recognize
in a very creative way your own
holographic nature that every
nature that every
Point contains the totality of the whole
is connected to every other point you
became in your own eyes an energy Matrix
but you simply gave yourself a
physiological
representation you follow me
yes that's what it is then little
unusual ni I'm not not bad or good it's just
ni I'm not not bad or good it's just
been different
yes congratulations thank
congratulations thank
you I thank
you J I wanted to share something that
came up when er was talking earlier
about love etc etc yes um then you
mentioned that love was everything yes
okay and at that point um I thought
about love being everything and
duplicating the frequency of
Love um in this particular experience
there was no or virtually no vibration
no physiological manifestation was only
the knowingness yes and I didn't know it
was love oh and so and my mate partner
lover whatever whatever uh demanded more
quote unquote more
or and so I
decided after a period of time that I
would give myself some physiological
manifestations and quote unquote fall in
love right and that was the start of the
deterioration of the
relationship that's it oh it's you know
not acting within my own Integrity oh
thank you okay thank
you Bashar
yes the last time we spoke you told me
to follow my ideals and walk my
path yes and
um I have come up upon a question oh uh
a large part of my ideals has to do with
discipline a yes and discipline to me
is limitation concentration and focus on
that limitation can you elaborate cuz you say
limitation can you elaborate cuz you say
that limitation is something we should
strive not to achieve limitation is
something you should strive not to
[Music] achieve that was
achieve that was
[Music]
beautiful simply in this way the
idea as we express
limitation in this SP is that what you
are yourself striving for in terms of
discipline and focus are the things that
come automatically when you simply do
what it is your vibration is all
about you automatically set up the
definition of what you are and therefore
cannot be anything else so you are
automatically focused but in a way that
is not a
struggle you follow me when you act upon
your excitement for what you know to be
true for you your reality can only bring
in
the situations and relationships that
are part of the idea you are being so
you don't have to focus yourself in a
concentrated way because nothing else
will be there to focus on other than the
idea you are
being does that make some sense to you
yeah it makes some sense I really sunk
in but all
right all you need to do is keep walking thank you one
moment while you are walking back
road yes it is all
right to stop once in a while and enjoy
the
scenery okay because when you feel so
inclined that is a part of what walking the road
that is a part of what walking the road
is all about not a deviation from
it be inclusive not
exclusive everything that is there is a
part of the road not an interruption in
it so
enjoy it is all right to enjoy it it is
not there to ract you it is there to let
you continue to walk the path you chose
to
read do not
forget that a path is not so much what
you are on a path is what you are you
can be off
yourself all right all right thank you
centu there is in your turn a few
moments remaining in this interaction
y I noticed that with some people you
um you come up with a pet name which
fits all right
Catalyst well that's the subject that my
I've had about four of them or five of
them since since we've been interacting
since the first time I'm wondering
um I don't believe it's because you
don't recognize it because I know that
you do recognize me but I'm wondering
why it is I keep changing my name
because you are all with a different
view well that's true for all of for
everybody though yes but you are
exemplifying the act of being a
switching station so it is
station so it is
apropos you follow me oh you're saying
uh the reference switching would you
prefer chameleon no I like switching all you're
chameleon no I like switching all you're
saying you're saying being a switcher is
um reflects around
the changing of the name you refer to me
as Zen
Sunny the switching of the name as you
become the different
modalities then you are that
vibration you simply have more of a
pensent to shift the modality in an
overall sense more often than
most and so in this way the overall
identity of switcher if you wish may
contain all the rest I see that's
interesting I just thought I was asking
different questions but as you ask different
questions but as you ask different
questions you have to be a different
person in order to conceive of that
concept and that vibration yeah it is
simply that we perceive that fundamental
with you is the actual Act of switching
itself many times more than the thing
you are switching
to mean you are the most learning out of
the switching action itself rather than
the things you are switching to that's
true than you swi
[Music] other yes
um and then it seems that apparently as
I've read uh a higher Consciousness is
achieved or experience you accelerate
your electromagnetic field align your
cellular structure and connect to all
all the different levels of yourself
that you call all the different types of
bodies that you have physical etheric
astral causal mental all these ideas you
align you super conduct yourself you
crystallize yourself so when all of
those are aligned that's when the
Kundalini energy what's referred to as
Kundalini energy is released yes because
now it can travel a straight path so to
speak we are doing that in going and
aligning ourselves with this idea all is
so you will find that you will exist in
Forth density in a constant state of
ecstatic
vibration you will beini he
precisely in s yoga the um
Guru I think is it one candle lighting
another than um what what is it about
the guru that has the well gives them or
that they possess the ability to
instantaneously uh light the fire in
another as it were they recognize that
the only individuals that come to them
are the ones that are ready to do it for
themselves that recognition lets you see
reflected from them your own life
light thus you become
illuminated fall yes thank you why is it
so difficult for someone to do it by
themselves once again it isn't no it is
simply your Habit to think that it is
consideration and that is the only thing
that makes it difficult because you
think it
is the sure yeah will arturus or neamon
be here next week one
moment different aspects of both
guys thank you very briefly
the idea of serious
energy mostly upon what you
call the seventh day of your seventh
month he but in this way some ideas and
identifications of
aspects of our daughter's
case briefly
in this way at this time therefore once
again allow us to thank you and extend
our appreciation for your willingness to
allow us to co-create and co- blend with
you and experience you as another facet
of all that is
and we thank you for allowing us along
with you to be the sharing that
continues forever in the now Eternal
moment excit dream life to you all we B
you a fond and
loving good [Music] morning everything [Applause]
[Applause]
go thank you all for being here me thank
you thank you for being here thank you
all for coming we have ret tapes tonight
it's going longer and longer and longer
it's
1131 what time was the yeah anyone who
wants just two tapes you're welcome to
have just the two
tapes almost
uh
9:00 9:30
9:30 so anyone who would like a uh two
or three tapes tonight uh we've already
got them started so you can have them
tonight very fast we got a highspeed
tape duplicator we also have video tapes
duplicator we also have video tapes
except for tonight for some reason the
machine went
Capo uh thank you all for coming what I
have part of the machine
went does the playback work I don't know
what it is I I it's first time it's
happened and crystals for sale