how are you all the even your time you
create time to
exist no in this way allow us to discuss
an
idea that of recent time in your terms
of time frame has come up with regard to
the idea of many psychological Endeavors
that are partaking in your Society upon
your planet at this time by many
individuals a new understanding of the
idea of your approach to the other
individuals in your Society who wish the
idea of Aid and
assistance recognize in this way that as
you co-create an interaction with us
there are many ideas that you have
suggested to me that you notice about
the idea of the methodologies of our
interaction that is co-created between
us in this way recognize simply that
many times you have been willing in this
way to create for
yourselves so-call solutions to your own
so-called Problems by creating an
interaction with us recognize we are not
doing anything for you you are doing it
for yourself but you are allowing us to
assist you by being a reflection of what
you already know in this way by allowing
you to know you contain all the answers
that you need for any question that you
might create in fact the idea that as we
have said that you can create a question
at all all is indicative of the fact
that you have the answer within you
otherwise the concept would never appear
in your
Consciousness now simply
recognize that the idea for why it seems
many times that these interactions between
times that these interactions between
yourselves and ourselves will allow you
in your own terms to open up in areas
where you may have felt you have not
been willing to open up the for is
simply because of one basic fact
understand that when you describe to me
the ideas that you have created in your
lives the situations that many of you
choose to label as a so-called problem
which to us is only a situation that you
are not willing to allow to change its
shape you find in this way that we do in
fact believe that you are in this way
believe that you are in this way
creating a scenario that is in every way
shape or form real to you and it is real
because you created to be real but
understand this
idea as we have said before in this way
our concept our approach to you is in a
sense alien and yours to us in this way
by your definition we are able to view
the situations you have created for
yourselves so to speak from a seemingly
exterior point of view not better just
different understand in this way
therefore that while we will interact
with you and many of the ideas you have
created for your reality to be real the
experiences that you have chosen to
experience which seem to be a reality
that you cannot change many times in
this way simply recognize that the
way simply recognize that the
foundational
difference between individuals in your
society when they hear of other
individuals telling of them the idea of
their problem so to speak and even those
individuals who are willing to assist
individuals with their problems so to
speak many times you will find that
there is still a basic belief that those
problems represent a
fundamentally real reality and are not
simply the product of what the
individual believes to be real therefore
understand many times that one of the
ideas that you are feeling that is a
difference from us is that when you tell
us your
problems when you define and describe
your situations that you wish to change
we do believe that for you they are in a
sense real but in a fundamental overall
sense we do not believe
you understand that our basic our basic
perception of you and every being in
creation is that you are
fundamentally positive do you follow
positive do you follow
me that is our perception of you as you
say from the
Geto therefore recognize that you can
sit if you choose all day and all night
long and describe all the different
problems you have chosen to create
fundamentally I will not believe you for
I understand that you have only chosen
to create the seeming problems to serve
yourself and if you are willing to know
that anything you have chosen to create
serves you in a positive way then you
will not believe you either except where
you are willing to recognize the idea as
it serves you in a positive way
connected to your basic foundational
creative ability your basic foundational
existence is in or as the idea of love
as the idea of Enlightenment as the idea
of Creator
Hood therefore in this way what you are
sensing from us in terms of our
willingness to interact with you is that
simply we do not carry within our belief
structure that you are so to speak
basically bad you follow me yes yes to
us you are like anything else basically
a Creator and in this way to our
perception and our point of view no
matter what you have chosen to create
you can always create something
else this is our basic approach with
you you follow me yes thank you very
much thank you
Shing you venue um
sun or last night I was uh had an
enlightened thought very similar to the
lines you were just describing and I
thought I'd share that and then I have a
question all right the analogy was that
love is the clay from which everything
is created and we create all the
scenarios that we see out of that clay
and we can perceive in any way we want
but it's still love yes every Act is an
act of Love correct in the ultimate
sense so to speak and that that was
exciting it sort of like drove home the
idea and I was enlightened but the the
question I had was when we perceive love
or hate or anger from another
individual I understand that it's our
own perception of Love of whatever the
emotion or feeling is but does it have
to be necessarily given off by the other
individual in other words are they if do
they have to be loving us for us to
perceive love and if we are perceiving
love and they are not loving us or is
that is that an you see what I'm driving
out of my just getting more confusing in
this way if you know you are love you
can always perceive love you follow me
yeah you can always understand that if
another individual chooses to express
themselves in what you call negative
ways you can still love the being that
they are it is the love you are willing
to share with them that can all allow
them to choose a positive way to
manifest the idea of their own love
rather than a negative way so in fact
Every Act is an act of love yes even if
it is the creation out of that love of a
situation that you do not prefer so that
you can give yourself the opportunity to
choose what you do prefer correct you
follow me yes every negative act is an
opportunity to decide whether or not you
really do wish to experience and live in
in that negative way mhm I I guess my
question is uh are we
is uh are we
perceiving without other individuals
would we perceive other individuals and
their love hate whatever their
emotions it is up to you mhm understand
you are the Creator you are your own
Universe you are creating your version
of every other individual that you
experience anyway therefore simply by defining that
anyway therefore simply by defining that
that is the type of a universe you want
to experientially partake
within that choice that tuning to that
vibration is what allows you to
experience this fragment of your
Consciousness in this universe in which
it seems there are many
individuals yes thank you yes yeah I
have two questions all right one is can
you mix silicon with fiber optic just
with telepath purposes and what else
could be mixed with it for that use
Fiber Optic D fiber optic dust well
that's what that's what
um no that's not the right one um that's
what Chris was saying can you mix with
um he said what can you mix with
death all right now the idea that we
have defined to that individual of the
use of the material you call the optic
fiber in this way will be of quite a
different nature than grinding them up
into dust they are wound and wrapped
many hundreds of times many thousands of
times in full length formation
that's understand in this way that the
energy at least from our perception that
will be channeled by grinding them to
dust will be just as dispersed and not
focused well then is there some way in
which so can can be
utilized there is an opportunity for a
type of interlayering in a sense with
the fibers fiber sheath silica sheath
fiber sheet silica sheath in this way
that can give rise to one particular
effect that may be of interest to that
individual with regard to the
transference of energy to different
levels of potentiality have oh
have oh
okay he was wondering
what type of I guess he wanted to make
some hment and he wanted to know if
there was any adhesive that would um get
in the way of reducing the receptivity
or adhesive that would enhance them
there are various forms of adhesive in
this way upon your planet that are as
you say electrically conductive but in
this sense the idea of embedding the
so-called dust in that adhesive may not
create the effect that he desires more
the idea of the
wrappings will be what creates the
effect that he
desires nice and my question is I'm interested
nice and my question is I'm interested
in taking town and using it in a way
that typed into earphones it would have
an immediate effect on the body by
having all their muscles vibrating at
all right
um is that so that sub subsonic sound
would be the there is one vibration in
this way that in a sense you may so to
speak play with the idea of your 7 and
1/2 cycle per second Earth
vibration this will set up a resonance
as you say sympathetic vibration
harmonic resonance frequency within your
material form which also partakes of its
existence alha that 7 and 1 half cycle
per second wave frequency that your
Earth gives off thus
you will then be able to create some
sort of
vibratory harmonic frequency within the
material body as
well thank you thank you sure you thank
you okay
um I have this coincidence here between
what Kirk was talking about oh very good
um okay first of all I just want to
preate this by or prate this by um just
clarifying some things that I've heard
from you and just kind of going that
over okay the ideas that I practic I've
been going here are that nothing is
really good or bad or right or wrong
either within ourselves or what we see
in our outer world it's just the way
we're perceiving it in a sense there is
positive manifestation there is negative
manifestation but in this way if you can
understand that everything serves the
purpose even as we have just said that
you may wish to create negative
manifestation to know you do not prefer
it then you could can understand that
even the creation of the negative
manifestation resulted in a positive
Choice therefore it is not so much that
everything is good or bad simply that
there is positive negative manifestation
in this way it is all equal follow me
all right so going along kind of with
Kirk was saying the idea of when you're
getting negative um input or um energy
from another um human being towards
yourself okay I understand that that's
one reflecting something in yourself I
understand that all right what about the
the idea of them experiencing that
negative energy towards you what is
their end of that we simply understand
that the same result can be for both of
you in this way the idea that you are in
let us say a state or an attitude
wherein you are certain enough within
your own convictions to be the being
that you are that you are willing to
reflect back to them that no matter how
Negative they get towards you you will
always reflect positive attitude towards
them so that they can understand in this
way that they also have the opportunity
to begin to question the idea of what it
is that allows you to feel so secure
within yourself that they lack within
themselves that allows them to choose to
negatively accost someone else be follow
me yes um what about oh gosh left my
mind um okay if somebody's having negative
um okay if somebody's having negative
energy towards you and you're looking at
it like what you said like they're
choosing to give up their security
within themselves and that you can also
choose to keep security within yourself
what about the idea of whether or not
what they're saying and what they feel
towards you may be valid in your own
mind also then you are judging yourself
in that way and you can also know that
if that is a reflection that you find in
your terms to be valid for yourself then
it simply could be an opportunity for
you to recognize through their
reflection to you that perhaps you have
not been functioning within the idea of
your own Integrity okay and when a
person doesn't function within the idea
of their own integrity and it's pointed
out with quote kind of negative
feelings we have the option to choose
not to think less of ourselves but it
that that that's still a tendency in
this you know Society wondering if you
could give some inputs as to how to
choose not to do that just because it
might be so in your eyes with this
person is feeling towards you simply the
willingness to allow yourself to have
the EXP experience of choosing to have
it another way in other words you change
things by changing them period choose to
adopt the idea that you do not have to
judge yourself and act as if that is now
the true feeling that you have of
yourself because you know that any
feeling you could choose to have of
yourself is equally valid to any other
choice you could make so if you find
that you do wish to look at how in input
is coming to you through a certain
perspective there is nothing to prevent
you from choosing to feel it in that way
to choose which way you wish to accept
that information since all choices are
equal you follow me so you're saying
that if it comes to you negatively that
you can choose to look at it but just
choose to look at it POS positively than
negative you may say all right this
individual in their terms is ACC costing
me but what is this approach doing to
serve me it maybe allowing me to see
just an example that I have not been
functioning for my Integrity now I know
that I do wish to function for my
Integrity so thank you for allowing me
individual to reflect to myself that now
I have the ability to positively see how
I can prefer to act in a way that I
really want to follow me very much okay
just a little bit further why is it it
seems that in this society that we are
so locking to the idea that it's our
place to judge others simply again what
we have called the habitual ritual the
idea that you have been doing it for so
many thousands of your years part of the
game you have been playing is to not
know that you are doing it so the idea
of your habits stem from the habit of
not knowing you are doing something
habitually follow me you are creating
your own cycle right okay what purpose
does it seem to serve to us why we do it
so much in this way the purpose of
experiencing separation the purpose of
experiencing the idea that you are
separate from the all that is in that
way is simply that that is one way you
can experience reality and your ultimate
desire as a Consciousness is to
experience everything that you can so
this has been one way simply the idea
that you chose to experience this idea
of separ ation brought with it in a
sense many ideas that allowed you to
completely forget that you made the
choice to begin with of your own free
will now you are changing your idea of
yourself you are not needing the tool of
experiencing that separation that
judgment any longer and so you are now
able to actually see that you are
judging you follow me otherwise in your
terms of past the idea of judging
another was not even questioned it was
simply the way things are this is the
way you should be and in that way once
you are in a system you never question
the idea of whether you can or cannot be
out of that system or habit now that you
are even questioning that you can have
another way of life that ability to be
able to transcend the idea of the
judgmental system lets you know know
that you are no longer in it you follow
me the ability to perceive a system
means you already have to be outside of
it do you follow
me no do you wish to share your Island
analogy sir oh right the idea being that
when you're on an island uh you think
you're you know on land but you have to
be to see it as an island you have to be
away from to see that it's surrounded by
water so if you're to realize that
you're in a problem or in or probably
sorry not problem in a situation you
have to be outside of it to realize that
you're in it correct therefore recognize
that if you can perceive you are in the
problem you are not having one
anymore so the idea is that your
perception of the fact that there is so
to speak a situation is not the
beginning of a process to get out of it
it is the end you're out of it because
you know you were in it what if you keep
following that action even though you're
aware of it so your
choice but it still means you're not in
it it just every time you understand the
idea that you have a so to speak problem
you are not in it you may now be in the
idea that you have a problem that you
cannot get out of but that is another
idea
totally yes every idea is its
own 100% Universe got
it simply that it is its own 100%
universe and is not connected to any
other idea except as you choose to make
an association so in other words you are
either doing a
you are either doing B but if you find
that there are elements of A and B in
what you are doing it is not that you
are doing half of a and half of B you
are doing the totally new third idea
AB which is not connected to a and not
connected to be except as you choose to
think that it is but it is its own
separate Universe with its own separate
rules so to
speak than
um I have created for myself the idea
that I would like to have a baby oh
right and this month I believe that I
had conceived a child physically I felt
that way and then I also had a very
lovely dream where in the dream myself
and my husband and this idea of a
Philip which I interpreted to be um a
soul of this child we're all kind of
intertwined and moving in a circular MO
and laughing and very happy and I
woke pardon lovely yeah and I woke up
the next morning I went oh boy we've
made our agreement and I really felt I
think I sort of rearranged my brain
waves and decided that I was pregnant
with this Philip idea and also I went to
um an acupuncturist who took my pulse
and said you know you have a lot of
signs of pregnancy but I also feel some
indecision all right in your p and then
it turned out that I wasn't pregnant in
this reality however I'd like to explore
the idea with you that possibly I'm
pregnant with this Philip idea in
another reality in a sense you can be
but also understand that being in
connection with the energy of the
so-called Consciousness Philip in this
way can mean that for the time you were
intertwined with that energy you were
pregnant with it in this physical
reality in that way for the purposes
that needed to be served just in that
way right you follow me yes now at this
time our perception is that this can
become a physiological pregnancy but
simply the way in which you experience
the interaction for now serves to allow
you to create yourself to be the being
that you would need to be to be the one
to have a
physiologically pregnant
agreement I I agree with you and I think
what I learned about being that being is
I learned about cocreation and I learned
about timing I learned about the idea of
timing and co-creation which allowed me
to sort of step back and take a deep
breath and let things happen in a nicer
smoother slowly way then you can also
understand in this way that with regard
to
Phillip you in this way are also
allowing through your agreement
interaction with the Consciousness
Phillip you are allowing in that way by
your own agreement you are allowing
philli to give birth to you as
well in the manner of the idea that you
need to be that Philip has actually made
the agreement with to be born unto
physically you follow me yes thank do so
there is gestation period for both of
you you may now consider yourself to be
in his womb as well and in this way
perhaps the idea of your 9 months time
may see within that time frame the idea
of a physiological birth
starting good that is how we perceive
the energy at this time that is not
chiseled in
stone before yes thank you thank you yes
um are you familiar with the well I'm
sure you are the AIDS crisis that's
crisis the aid situation we have
discussed this okay I'm I'm new here
it's my first time all right meeting
you um now briefly yes briefly yes
understand that to us it is on one level
fundamentally a symbol of the
idea that it is a
reaction arising from the preliminary
premise that your Society is not willing
to blend within
itself within each being in the society
the idea of its own male and female
energies there are individuals therefore
that have taken it upon themselves to be
born in your society that will exemplify
dichotomies or paradoxes regarding the
expression of male femaleness female
mess and all of these ideas to have
given your Society an opportunity to
give themselves a symbolic reflection of
what they were not willing to contain
within each and every being of
themselves but because several
individuals also chose even while they
were expressing that symbol to the
majority of your Society chose to accept
the Judgment of society upon them then
they in creating that reaction for
themselves judged themselves and created
for themselves what they were forced to
create the idea of a symbolic disase
that would break down the
barriers that filter different ideas in
other words that is the idea behind the
symbol of lack of immunity you are open
and vulnerable to
everything you follow me yes now to some
degree this idea is
already in a higher Consciousness sense
beginning to reverse itself for
individuals in your Society have now
begun more and more to integrate the
male femaleness within each and every
being to accept both sides ofs
themselves and to remove the need for
those individuals experiencing that
symbol to have to experience it to have
to reflect it to the society because the
society is now willing to accept certain
portions of themselves that they were
not willing to accept before which
created the need for such quote unquote
drastic measures you follow me got it
yes does answer your question yeah think
so yeah thank you thank you sure
sure on the health issue could you
enlighten me about diabetes and its
complications all right now there may be
again though it is being expressed as
what you perceive to be a single symbol
many different reasons behind that
idea in this way you may find
that the idea of energy is a
concern so to speak in other words there
are aspects let us say fundamentally of
many beings expressing what you call the
diseased diabetes with the idea that they do not
diabetes with the idea that they do not
lack or in this way create the idea of a
lack either one can cause this idea
the connection to their own
fundamental self-empowerment to bring forth into
self-empowerment to bring forth into
their physical
reality that which they desire to
express of their lives they are in a
sense feeling that they are running
without an engine that they must plug
into an alternate energy source to allow
themselves to feel connected to their
own fundamental Creator Hood creativity
they feel they have in this way created
a deprivation of their obvious and
immediate connection through the
fundamental natural Creator Hood ability
that they were born with in this way now
many of these diseases upon your planet
are also serving as an additional idea
your medical personnel to allow them to
understand why many of these symbols
have been created and there are many
opportunities for individuals in this
way to allow other individuals to come
to terms within themselves about certain
things they have not been willing to
face either in this life or in other
Lives Many of the socalled diseases
which Carry On from generation to
generation may be an exemplification
also of lack of willingness of forming
certain connections to the natural self
in many different lives in this way so
in that sense there are many so to speak
karmic diseases even though these are
all self-imposed and do not have to
persist you follow
me is there something more specific you
wish to delve into with regard to this
idea
I I'm just wondering
whether whether we will see um a cure or
a way for this disease the complications
of to see our perception of your
civilization is that every single idea
you now call a disease in your Society
will not exist within the idea of 50 of
your years for you will have made the
transformation that allows you to
recognize you no longer need those tools
to show yourself that you simply need to
be willing to make the connections to
all that you are the transformation from
your old to new age awareness from third
to Fourth density reality with will be
will be the recognition the cognition in
the presence of the willingness to know
that you are love and light and in this
way you are the creators of the reality
that you
experience so then one can really almost
believe that they don't have to have
these complications or the diabetes what
since this is the transformational life
this life carries with it by definition
the opportunity to realize that in this
life no you do not need to experience
those ideas if you are willing to make
the connections that allows it to be
able to be
changed that is why you are in this
transformational life in a very real
sense you do not even in your terms have
to physically die according to your
normal lifespan in this
life this is the transformational life
and by definition because of what it is
it allows you to recognize that
everything you have been experiencing
what you think is a part of a reality
that controls you is actually under your
own control and changeable that is one
of the definitions of why this is a
transformational light to recognize that
everything you have been experiencing is
only the product of what you believe you
should be experiencing they only tools
to reflect to you what you believe your
reality to be and that you can change
those tools you can change those beliefs
and as a result you can completely
absolutely totally without shadow of a
doubt change the physiological life to
reflect what you now believe it to be
you follow
me you you then
you um last week I created a situation
for myself and I'd like to describe it
to you see if if I'm really
understanding a lot of
things all right okay um I put my purse
down and walked away and left it you
know and I didn't know I was doing it
but I did it all right I figure
I you have all week I've been trying to
figure out why I created that situation
myself are you exploring the idea of
abundance uh well I've been exploring the idea
uh well I've been exploring the idea
that that someone else needed the money
that was in it my higher self want to
help them now could be for that reason
on the surface but understand that those
things are also created out of an
understanding that you are completely as
abundant as you need to be to begin with
and so attachments to certain things do
not need to be maintained as a focus to
allow you to experience the flow of
other things coming in which will
increase your sense of abundance
when you allow there to be let us say a
whole in your reality with regard to
what you have previously considered the
idea of abundance to be then something
else can fill that home which will
create a
flow abundance is not a static
experience it is a flow you follow me
yes so even though I think
that the money and the identification
and the important papers that were in
that even though I think I need those I
don't really there not a
question I think understand again if you
are simply willing to be a total idea if
those tools are necessary for you to
continue to be that idea they will be
there if they are not there you do not
need them you will find also that there is an
them you will find also that there is an
opportunity for certain of those things
in your terms to come back to you I've
been trying to believe all week that
there's no to try I've been having
feeling all week that it's all going to
come back all right then use the
opportunity as it exists right now to
explore all the different ideas that
this experience is showing you exist
within yourself that you did not know
existed there you follow me yes have a good time
there you follow me yes have a good time
thank
you you are
fundamentally fundamentally cared for by
all that
is you do not need need anything you
have everything you follow me this is an
everything you follow me this is an
opportunity for you to experience your
trust
knew I knew
[Music] you that is why you did
you that is why you did
it as I
said I am prone to not
believe that you do things for any other
reason other than the fact that you know
what you're
doing thank you guys Pasar I'd like to
uh I've been in imagination about your
physical organism this week and I'd like
to um if if I'm an organism does that
mean that you are a glandularis or
something all right if you wish to make
that definition is up to you well you
there's only a label do you have a heart
yes H how does the Android and how does
the glandular system if you are based on
gland how does your system work now
understand in this way that that is not
what I have said okay recognize that in
this way in the
ID speak 300 years ahead of you is not
all that great a period of time you
follow me
yes but that doesn't mean that I mean
right now in different parts of the
solar system or the universe there there
is more advanced civilization
organically too so so time period really
has nothing to do with it although you
are asking a question in a linear time
frame okay you say are you still
functioning that is a time question
therefore we give you a time answer got
um do you have blood that circulates so
it's the same phas okay do you bre do
you breathe oxygen nice okay now what
what I'm wondering is because we're in
physical bodies we seem to have a some
sort of reciprocal relationship inter
relationship with the universe by by
breathing that's one way that that we
have intercourse with the universe what
I'm wondering is do do our souls have an
intercourse with and what what sort of
relationship is
that now understand that this will vary
according to your definition of what the
idea of sess is in this way but you can
also understand that in a very real
sense all that you consider the physical
Universe to be is in a very real way on
one level made out of your soul self you
follow me
what about assist
you
um I there's still part of me that wants
to know what to give and take is give
and take right your terminology does not
translate this it seems like there is
some okay even though we are part of
everything that is there is still some
separate in that Unity that makes our
souls individual in in their unification
with everything that is and what I'm
wondering is what is that continual
osmosis um that that reciprocal
communion that is occurring is there is
it is
it can you fill me in a little
bit again allow me to say your concept
is not translating fully into our
Concepts but allow me to say
this everything in your terms as a
physical universe is the product of a
difference in the vibration of the
fundamental homogeneous energy patterns
that created you follow me even on the
idea of what you call the soul
level even the higher higher
Consciousness can choose to create a
differentiation in Soul structure by
simply altering the signature vibration
of what you perceive to be a collection
of many aspects or fragments of yourself
into one homogeneous
idea do you follow me yes does that
answer your question yes help thank you
thank you one moment yes uh for most of
my life I've had an association with
what's called The Church of Jesus Christ
of latterday saints the Mormons are you
familiar with them to some degree okay
and uh I'm in a bit of confusion at what
in that I really don't understand what
going on with them what their source is
whether they do have a sense of
channeling a type of channeling where it
comes from uh they seem to be to a point
in agreement with uh the new age and
after that point in a very heavy strong
disagreement with it all right can you
uh you know my questions as well as I do
simply in this way understand that one
of the reasons for what seems to be the
dichotomy is in the definition of the
idea you call religion upon your planet
to begin with which is a type of
structure that by definition allows
individuals let us say more than
actually living as an idea to follow an
idea and so in this way where the
experience the things that seem to be
the same they are experiencing in a
direct living manner the idea of their
own Creator Hood where there seems to be
the discrepancies they are experiencing
more in a removed manner the idea that
they are not creating that reality for
themselves is that clearing it to some
degree a bit all right now simply
recognize that with every idea on your
planet that you call a so-called
religion in this way every single one to
some degree has its basis its origin to
some degree in the idea of
channeling whether it is communication
with what may turn to be other
Consciousness or simply aspects of the
individual who created this idea's own
higher Consciousness the basic Primal
fundamental recognition of the basic
principles behind all religions upon
your planet are from the same overall
source and so in that way on that level
fundamentally all so-called religions
agree when you surround the fundamentals
with simply let us say rituals that are
reflective of each and every
individual's particular way that they
wish to go about relating to the
fundamentals that is where the
discrepancies come in you follow me yeah
for in this way it is simply that
because of the way your Society is as a
whole because of the separation you have
made from the all that is that you are
it has become a habit in the overall
society in which you live to think that
discrepancy means that there is not
being truth presented when in fact there
is the idea that your Society has chosen
to believe in is that there can only be
one way to recognize the fundamental
truth of existence and that by Obvious
definition is not the case for as we
have said if there is only one way there
would only be one person so recognize
that each and every individual is
actually their own way of forming a
relationship to creation Now there may
be groups of individuals in a sense that
seem to be sharing similar ideas but
even for those individuals there are
differences in what they think to be the
similarities between them in this way
and it is simply because of the fact
that every individual is a different
individual the fact that your reality
has been created in that way who Express
itself through individuality that is
what is creating the dichotomy it is not
so much that that is creating the
dichotomy but it is the belief the
belief that all individuals must only
function in one way that is creating the
dichotomy so because this is the
transformational era where you are
beginning to recognize that it is
integration that is happening in other
words that the unity any Unity that you
will experience on your planet is going
to be the product of granting validity
to the infinite diversity within your
civilization that is what is causing the dichotomy in
that is what is causing the dichotomy in
many of the religious organizations upon
your planet because they do not
understand that they can find the unity
they seek by granting equality to all of
the differences in your Society you follow
differences in your Society you follow
me yes does that clarify the idea to
some degree for you yes it helps it
helps a bit uh they as you say they do
seem to be going more in the direction
of
Separation uh from the others from the
rest of the the world then rather
towards embracing the idea of unity and
all encompassing this what will happen
to them will that change or they it can
everyone has their own way of
recognizing that they are all winding up
at the same
place they don't appear to believe so
all right again ultimately everyone
doesn't really come from anywhere and is
not really going to any place because
everything is right here and right now
so in an ultimate sense it does not
matter how they choose to get there you
follow me yes so in this way the way
they have chosen to learn what they are
learning is their way of learning and
for them it has validity should any
individuals choose to change their minds
those individuals will not partake of
that ritual any longer true that is all
there is to it okay thank you thank you
one moment yes yes I wanted to know
could you speak to us about male femal
and how we can best integrate them
all right to some you may simply begin
so to speak by recognizing that they are
already integrated you follow me there
is nothing that you have to do to
integrate them other than simply
allowing yourself to know that they are
already already integrated by
definition therefore allow me to ask you this do
therefore allow me to ask you this do
you have what you call an imagination oh
yeah all right can you right now now in
this moment allow yourself in whatever
way shape or form your imagination is
comfortable with to form let us say a
feeling or an image of the idea of this
so-called male energy and female energy
that you contain within yourself as a
being can you form this idea right as
one being in any way shape or form that
your imagination finds comfortable for
now you may allow them to in a sense let
us say be side by side if you wish or as
one being what is more comfortable for
you one being all right then you can now
one being all right then you can now
describe to me with your imagination
what are the qualities of this singular
[Music] being seems to be all knowing all
being seems to be all knowing all
together all joined all all all right
then that is all there is to
[Applause] it recognize in your formation of that
it recognize in your formation of that
creation right now you have allowed
yourself to know no they are integrated
they are married within you follow me
the reason why I ask the question is
because there's a lot of study now about
the differences between male and
femaleness with the idea of integration
so you're saying actually if you imagine
the integration to be so then it is
already happened yes and you can allow
yourself if you trust that it has
already happened to see it
experientially in your physical reality
to see the results of that now
understand that what you have said has
vality in terms of the experimentation
so to speak going on but recognize that
it is not only the differences but also
the similarities that are being looked
at so in this way you can simply note
that both ideas as they manifest the
polarity of your soul Consciousness into
physical reality both ideas both
polarities serve different purposes and
they simply work in tandem one being
more appropriate for a particular type
of situation and another being more
appropriate for another aspect of
another situation the idea of maleness and
situation the idea of maleness and
femaleness in that form of energy is
simply a definition in your physical
polarity terms of Simply one type of an
approach to a certain situation you have
created and another type of an approach
the idea more of an outward approach or
an inward approach you follow me yes
that is all there is to it the soul in
itself though it does contain both
energies does not experience them as
mess femaleness
you follow me yes it is in the soul one
harmonic idea thank you thank you yes yeah I've
idea thank you thank you yes yeah I've
been um playing with some of the ideas
that we talked about in the interview
about the psychology intention and I've
had some wonderful opportunities to uh
practice it with some of my clients to
be it to be it right thank you and what
I'm hoping you can help me what um no
excuse me
um hoping what
hoping what
I'm I am the idea okay what I've been
sensing is that this is an experiential
knowing and when I try and use what when
I using my analytical training I can't
really get close to the understanding of
what you're describing as psychology
intention all right however I really
knew what it was about
and I was experiencing it with clients
becoming the idea uh looking at the
probabilities and the event and knowing
that the difference was with no
expectation attached to these events and
what we have said this evening of your
time believing in their basic
abilities can you clarify that simply
what we said at the beginning of this
discussion not believing that they are
basically unable you follow me correct
unable you follow me correct
yeah um is it true that this is an
experiential [Music]
[Music]
knowing cuz I can't use my intellect to
to come to you may use your
reasoning however you may find in this
way that the reasoning you will create
will be an aftermath to your
experiential knowingness yes simply
allowing you to go through the paces in
physiological terms so that you can
allow it to be a physiological tool that
can be seen by other individuals not
oriented toward the idea of the
experiential knowingness but the reasoning and any
knowingness but the reasoning and any
analysis that you will apply to this
idea in your terms will come after the
experiential knowingness that creates
the
interaction you follow me yes cuz that
seems to be the only way that I can come
close to knowing what the difference is
between this kind of Science and the
science that we've had previous it is a
beginning in your Tes uhhuh you will as
you create yourself to continue to be
this idea as you change the idea of
yourself within this notion you
will discover more ways to express it
you follow me yeah and great that would
be
helpful thank you
you than
you you said we are not the result of
the past the present is not the result
of the past unless you choose to believe
that that is
so is it because that exist correct
because the only
experiential existence you ever perceive
is the present why do I remember the P
you are creating the memory in the
present and meaning it comes back
correct if you make it meaningful it
comes back
back
question know as much as the know
because you are as much as in a sense
let us say this even the idea you call
Spirit in that way allows itself to form
definitions of its identity in this way
we know what we know based upon the
interactions we create and in this way
we are also choosing within certain
degrees to limit ourselves in certain
ways similar in ways that you choose to
limit yourselves we have always said we
do not know expression everything in
this way in a sense neither does Spirit
in an overall sense because even the
definition spirit is a differentiation
from all all that is so in this sense we
have chosen to limit our knowledge in
certain ways and particularly when
dealing with your Society or any other
Society where the so-called knowledge we
may have access to will interfere with
the choices you have made then we will
not know it perhaps later we will when
we are not in contact with you but we
will not know it while we are in contact
with you if it would be something that
would not serve
you um
in our words there is no
future in a
sense
yes oh oh oh oh oh understand understand
yes there only seeming in the sense that
as we have said there really is quote
unquote no such thing as predicting the
future what is being sensed by anyone by
Spirit by higher Consciousness by your
own Consciousness is the situational energy
Consciousness is the situational energy
that exists in the present that has the
most energy behind it that is the most
likely to manifest into physical
reality but that is a present sensing if
the momentum of that energy does not
waver does not decrease does not
divert then it will in your terms come
to pass if it does change it will not
come to pass any prediction whether it
is made by so-called Spirit or not is
always only a sensing of the energy that
exists at the time the prediction is
made that has the most energy behind it
that has the highest degree of
probability of
maintaining that level of energy that is
why you will find that so-called
predictions of mass events are in your
terms more likely to come about than
individual predictions unless the
individual prediction has a great deal
of conviction behind the energy that is
being predicted in terms of what the
individual that is being predicted about
has created for themselves Now
understand that many times predictions
in and of themselves are there for the
purpose of having the individual about
whom the prediction is being made change
their mind simply because now they are
aware of the prediction you remember the
Island analogy if you are aware of the
situation you are then out of it so if
somebody gives you a so-called
prediction it might be an opportunity
for you to recognize that you can now
consciously make a choice between
maintaining the same level of energy
that the prediction sent and allowing
that to come to pass or changing the
energy if you do not prefer what the
prediction has
predicted but it is always only in the
present that those things occur
thank you
yes all
right now again what is your relative
idea of success for in this way again as
we have suggested if you are peace and
if you go as peace then the only results
will be those that connect to the idea
of yourself as peace
in other words it is not so much that it
is successful but it will always be
reflective of what you are um one
question is thank
you I have such trouble with the victim
now that is in itself its own belief you
know that stop right there for one
moment the phrase I have trouble with
victimhood is
one of the belief structures that goes
into reinforcing your experiencing of
victimhood it is not something that is a
law of nature that you have this trouble
it is your choice to believe you have
trouble with victimhood and that choice
to believe you have trouble reinforces
the experience of victimhood itself it
is its own vicious cycle the fact that
you even wish to maintain the idea that
you have trouble with victimhood May the
only thing giving you the experience of victimhood I
victimhood I
have but I
understand discuss I cannot believe that 11
discuss I cannot believe that 11
people oh oh oh one moment there is
simply some misunderstanding on your
part of the reasons in this way from
what we have said recognize that what we
are saying is not that all these people
woke up and said oh yes cheely
consciously I will now go out and be
killed by these other people I think
this is something I want to do no no no
no no understand that what we are saying
is that your physical reality is the
product of what you believe it will be
and in this sense recognize that what
activates these beliefs and what can
even cause many of these beliefs is your
creation of your
emotionality fear is one of the
strongest emotions that your Society has
chosen to give substance to on your
planet so understand that if you have an
overriding fear that something will
happen it is the same thing as
subconsciously saying you believe this
will occur so when we say those
individuals chose that reality we are
saying they chose to believe that such a
reality was the most likely reality that
could happen because they were fearful
that that was the most likely reality
and so that was the reality they
experienced it was their fear that
created the experience for them in that
way not a conscious willingness to
volunteer you follow me that is how they
made the choice to experience that
Reality by believing in their fear more
than their ability to Simply know that
that experience did not have to happen
for them and also also
recognize that intermixed within this
and valid because your Society has an
overall belief in the idea of karmic
reincarnation recognize that also many
of those individuals as a
society were also bringing forth from
other lives karmic fears of Retribution
for atrocities they had created by
themselves as a group many times
for for recognize in this way that many
of those individuals not to say that
they deserved it not to say it had to
happen but many of those individuals
unconsciously created that balance for
themselves in that way they did not have
to but many of them did because of past
life situations in which they as a
society took the lives of many
nations follow me it is now that idea
and that experience that they have now
allowed themselves to go through they
simply chose unconsciously to allow
themselves to go through it in that way
by actually physically experiencing the
same type of situation that they had
perpetuated on other individuals that
allow them now to form a balance wherein
that situation never has to occur in
your Society
again now understand that many
individuals who in your term so to speak
remember this Holocaust
are actually choosing to continue to
create the fear that can actually make
it plausible to experience that reality
again and it is only that fear that
makes it plausible if you understand
that the cycle has been completed
completed in that way and you take back
your empowerment knowing that there is
never any need anymore to create the
type of fear that would create that type
of reality ever again because you have
already exper all you need to with
regard to that type of fear and what can
create in your Society then you will
never experience that reality again so
let it be in the path let it be in the
path that does not control the
Pres thank you very much you all take a
short break right say thank
say thank
you uh Curious the VAR channelings
been have come mostly from the St
world and uh I'm wondering how you from
a civilization and in body 300
years in advance of ours can tell us
that the wealth of information and
wanted to know is that
information uh part of all of it of
course my civilization simply realizes
that and that is why [Music] one
one
moment I did not guarantee
anything all right simply in this way
what was said is
this a that dat in your Society
represents a time when there are let us
say more doorways open in your
Consciousness more will willness to
perceive other dimensionalities other
densities of experience in this way and
so the craft in aent that are always
round and about your planet may be
perceived if you are giving yourself
more of an opportunity to do so now the
area that has been described simply is
one of the energy vortices wherein many
craft find that they will enter your
dimensionality because it is in of
itself one of the energy doorways that makes
one of the energy doorways that makes
this
possible therefore in that area we have
said of your Malibu at the time we have
said of your March 15th we simply be
high degree of probable
justos to enable you the opportunity if
you are willing to be sensitive to it in
that way but not need to be wherein you
may have that experience maybe might I
add the the party that's planed is not a
c UFO party it's a celebration of the
idea correct that
way that attitude may actually enable
you more of an opportunity to see
something than going to see them to
begin with
thank spirit world when we all pass over
is it all the same spiritual we all end
up in the same place so to speak now
even in what you call the spirit world
there is some degree of differentiation
it is all the same place yet but in this
way you can still create the seeming n
that is not to some degree it will
depend upon in a sense what beliefs you
take with you so to speak What scenario
you choose to work out with yourself in
this way how quickly you realize it is
all one ey
all of these things can serve a purpose
for the soul that you still may
represent to be the individualized
portion of the over soul that has just
recently left the physical body but it
is just like this physical reality is in
essence the same
place as anything is for there is only
really here and now in an ultimate sense
all differentiations are in a sense
differentiations are in a sense
illusionary but you can create that
illusion even on some of what you may
call the lower levels of spirit
world follow
me
the the spirit of all of the souls from
every planetary group throughout the
universe end up in this
one no there is no space to
it you are outside the idea of physical
reality all that is is experience
and what illusionary space you wish to
create in order to have the experience
understand it is the same thing you are
to in here is physical space
crowded it is the same place as
non-physical space in an ultimate sense
it all takes place right here you simply
have different
phases of experience that allows you to
experience all that is how to face with
each other
so that everything can exist in between
seemingly in between everyone else's
moments you follow
me I wanted to ask you
about suicide oh right um
contemplating pardon me how am I contemp
are you am I contemplating it no I have
I have all right not uncommon in your
Society no and what I'm interested in
because someone very close to me my
mother did commit suicide I need I need
to know I feel I need to know what it is
that would make a human being someone
from this Society want to leave this
Society feeling they have no choice of
course no other choice no feeling of
self-empowerment complete and total
powerlessness the creation of the belief
that you are at the mercy of everything
you experience outside of you and that
you are not in control it is the one
last vestage that you give yourself to
know you are in control for it always
comes down to you now understand however
that usually the idea of what you call
physicalized suicide in this way usually
does not
fulfill the choices made by the soul in
being physical and usually you will find
that a physical Su aside once it is out
of the body will remember what the idea
was all about and reincarnate almost
immediately I wondered about that I also
uh thought that perhaps in that feeling
of powerlessness in the body in the
society at that time there is a decision
that this is not good I need another
place another time in order to that can
be one of the decisions but recognize in
this way that again the result or let us
say the reason for most suicide in this
way is usually not being willing to come
to terms with your own
self-empowerment which in various ways
was one of the ideas that the soul
created a physical life forward so you
will usually find that the soul in
reincarnating will actually choose
similar scenarios that cause the suicide
to begin with for in this way it is with
the knowingness that there is another
way to look at that situation that the
being reincarnates a more positive way
but it is also possible for that
incarnated being reincarnated being to
live that out again to another suicide
and come back again and is possible yes
okay um one
other comment or question or thought in
that when someone uh if someone knows
someone's committing suicide right and
they let them do
it um I suppose that also comes from a
choice there's no other choice that is
the choice that that person may is true
in that way yes but in this way you can
also understand that the idea of your
understand that the idea of your
knowledge of such an event is your
opportunity to share with that
individual opportunities to look at
their situation in another way now you
cannot ultimately prevent someone who
really really wishes to kill themselves
from doing so for they will find a way
if they are really dead set upon it in
that
sense stupid that the idea of your being
aware of that situation does give you
the opportunity to interact with them
recognize that if they did not choose to
find someone who was aware they would
not have attracted someone to be aware
of their situation so the fact that you
might be aware also is a reflection that
they chose to attract someone to them as
let us say maybe one more opportunity to
perhaps choose something else other than
the suicide so by all means interact
with them in this way now if you choose
to not interact with them in that way it
is then up to you to determine what that
action interaction or lack of it teaches
you is it the personality or the soul
the personality more often than
not how does one deal with
guilt how about not experiencing
it how does one go about not
experiencing when it's something thank
you first of all forgive yourself for
recognize that every experience in this
way is a valid
experience you have done it all you have
been it all you following yes now the
idea of guilt is simply judging the self
to not be valid for the experience you
created yourself to be all right you can
recognize that perhaps the experience
you created allowed you to know what it
is like to function without Integrity
but all right then the experience of
functioning without Integrity has now
taught you that perhaps you prefer to
function with it and so that experience
has served you so forgive yourself for
it has taught you something and it has
taught you that you can prefer a choice
between not experiencing integrity and
experiencing it you follow me yes thank
you I
do quite sure she
[Music] was I have two questions the first
was I have two questions the first
question I personally don't feel I need
a lot of expansion on um my cat
has been keeping me up at Night by
scratching at my door every 15 half an
hour whatever and if I do the things
that the veteran people recommended like
squirt her with water or chase her or
whatever
that's what if you allowed the animal to
reflect to you uhhuh a schedule that may
reflect more accurately the new person
you are
becoming well after talking to you about
the idea that I've the experienced of
insomnia and what you said I feel that
I've made great strives to not
experiencing that and I feel like my
cat's new schedule is bringing that idea
back in my life so that now you can use
it for what it is understand again the
idea of insomnia never occurs
if you allow yourself to recognize that
when you are awake you are supposed to
be it is only a judgment that you think
you should be asleep that creates the
socalled disease of insomnia is not a
disease it is a recognition of the
schedule that is more natural for you
well then I don't understand because
today from not getting sleep I lost a
job because I wasn't able to be there
good perform it good why it was an
office job with so what understand this
is the idea you are simply giving
yourself an opportunity to recognize
very boldly very unconventionally that
the majority of your Society is based
upon a structure that does not Grant
validity to what is called your natural
sleep cycle wherein you are actually more
cycle wherein you are actually more
highly active at 300 a.m. and lowkey at
300 p.m. not the way around why do you
think so many cultures on your planet
have what you call a
siesta recognize in this way that has
been your natural
flow well every half an hour doesn't
seem natural I mean she keeps coming
back like every half an hour that is not
the point what you simply will not get
up and P her attention what you're
saying so of course she is always going
to remind you so that's what I was going
to ask you what is she wanting and
that's what you're saying she reflecting
to you that you are creating a
recognition that you can be very
creative at a time you think you are
judging that you should be
asleep and that much of what you
actually want in life can be discovered
in those
hours and that you can rearrange the
idea that you need to have a normal job
schedule or you are now becoming
unnormal you are becoming
you are becoming
natural so my kitty cat is telling me
that I have the freedom to express
myself in ways that are more natural and
times are more natural yes and that any
so-called job that you require will be
attracted to you that will fit your new
schedule you do not have to to fit the
schedule of the job okay so let's say
tonight of my time yes that my cat
decides to you know to reflect to you
and I get up and I play with her and I
think okay well she's probably had
enough and I probably had enough this
time on probably probably you will know
feels like it all right I go back to
sleep what if it happens again do I get
do you what do you mean what if
that is not an
isness do what is if the cat so to speak
comes back get up okay in this way again
why are you creating what
ifs have it all right simply do what is
the capat is there play the capat is not
there please okay next question um I
just recently had an opportunity brought
to me for more massage work great
and I find that I would like this
opportunity but I'm having kind
of I don't know an easiness about it
it's with people that are older people
shedin and that um could be disabled in
different ways yes well I find in fact I
find I'm also kind of shamed of this but
I find that I'm uncomfortable with
certain aspects that might be with their
bodies different deformities or
abnormalities and I don't wish to choose
to shut that off because that because I
do wish to help people but I you can
simply understand that your discomfort
with the idea of your own abnormality so
to speak is what is causing discomfort
within you relative to the symbols you
are creating and attracting into your
life the idea that you are attempting to
refuse in this way to be abnormal
you follow me um
me um
yes understand your physical reality is
going to always contain every single
symbol that is creatively possible to
experience reflecting all the different
facets of the idea you are exploring now
one of the ideas you are exploring as we
have just discussed is the idea of what
is normal and what is
not so allow yourself to be natural
and you will not feel
uneasy about what you are being shown to
be in your previous definition and
abnormality which in another level is
actually quite
normal simply because it is a normal
expression of what they have chosen to
be it is a natural expression of what
they have chosen to
be allow your focus to shift to the idea
of naturalness rather than normality
see I understand that
idea what I what I would like to ask is
there some other idea that you can give
me while I process that to while I'm
working with these people because it
seems like that that's a very strong
thing with me and I I may choose to let
it take a while if you say so all right
one
moment h how's your imagination tonight
it's active as always all right will you
close your eyes for a
moment okay
now what do you perceive with your eyes
closed about all the individuals in the
room with
you I feel that it's very loving people
all right what
right what
else that they're unique very good anything
else that they are um also wishing to
clarify things about themselves all
right very good stop right there
now can you apply what you have just
felt to the individuals that you are
attracting into your life recognizing
that whether they manifest it
emotionally physiologically
mentally or not it is all reflection of
the same ideas that you have just
exemplified here tonight at your time
that they all are in a sense created
from love every situation they are
experiencing in this way is unique and
it is all for the purpose of their own
understanding of clarifying the idea
that they have chosen to be and if you
can see them with your inner
sight rather than fixate on them with
your outer sight than you can truly see
them you follow me and that can allow
you the opportunity when you look in a
mirror to truly see you as well for what
you really are and not what you think
you should be and not what you think
they should
be thank you very much for your loving willingness
willingness
yeah I I have um a couple of questions
in listening to you talk tonight about
um disease within the body um I I was
exposed to the idea the concept that we
can if Consciousness creates form is
that correct yes that we can um change
our B yes get rid of decease not get rid
of or be the idea idea that does not
contain disas yes yes um does that mean
that one can also physically choose to
change their body as well can be done
can be done now you will find that the
degree the degree to which it happens in
your Society will usually be reflective
of what degree will serve the overall
Society you follow me yes if you find
that a complete and total physiological
change will serve the mass Consciousness
then if you focus on that idea on being
that idea then that will occur to
whatever degree a change does occur that
is reflective of what best serves the
overall Mass Consciousness at this time
I see thank you thank you um my other
question has to do with um I was
listening to your response in the
question about suicide um I have a very
dear friend who is is um paid Assassin
by the government oh right um and he uh
has just left uh several weeks ago to
commit murder uh towards someone and I
was placed in the position of of having
to explore my own integrity and I let
him know how I felt about that and I
feel that it is wrong um and I I guess
that you know his his being in that
position I see now is served a purpose for me as
I see now is served a purpose for me as
well all right now you can understand
first of all that there is no need for
judgment upon it right wrong but allow
me to suggest an approach may
I you can allow the individual the
opportunity to
recognize that all murder is
suicide for all are one idea
and in this way to kill off even a
portion of yourself in this way is
invalidating yourself and creating the
type of reality that brings with it
those experiences all upon the self that
experiences all upon the self that
reflect that
invalidation all murder is
suicide all death ultimately in that way
is
suicide though there are differences in
the methodologies
but simply in your terms because you are
all one idea all murder is suicide now
you may ask the individual if he is
suicidal and allow the individual to accept on
and allow the individual to accept on
whatever terms his imagination can allow
him to accept the idea there's no need
to force an understanding for that
cannot be done yes I but you can offer
different perspectives that may allow that
perspectives that may allow that
individual to change their mind
and refocus on what they believe the
world to
be which then can change the world for
them and they can also recognize that
they are
self-empowered and they are
self-empowered enough as an individual
and you are self-empowered enough as a
group as a country as a world to have
any idea you wish to EXP experience
without needing to harm anyone else to
get it understand that when you feel you
it understand that when you feel you
must enforce your idea upon someone else
you don't really believe that idea has
Merit otherwise why would you have to
force something you know to be true on
someone else if you know it is a truth
then you know everyone ultimately will
eventually experience
it only when you do not believe in the
idea is you hold for yourself to be your
beliefs do you feel the need to force
them on someone
else you follow me yes you may discuss
that idea with that individual as well
thank you and that is one of the
commonality that what you call your
country has with all the other countries
that you think are your
enemies you all believe that you need to
force your beliefs on someone else and
that means that you don't believe what
you believe
in because what you really believe in
what you know for a fact to be
true you don't need to
force on
anyone you follow me yes I do share
these ideas and let the individual
choose for himself thank you thank you
very much sure
male energy post oh thank you you're
very receptive um need in What's called the
receptive um need in What's called the
Great Pyramid there's a place that we
call the king's chamber yes and uh in
the king's chamber is what was found to
be an empty Stone box without a lip yes
and the resting King when I saw it there
was a a break out a chunk taken out of
the uh the stone box I have a couple of
questions regarding that and then
another if I may uh what was that box
used for for the initiate to lie within
so they could project themselves out of
their body fantastic would you have any more
body fantastic would you have any more
comments You' care to share about that
is what the original pyramid was for
anyway as initiation for the expansion
of the understanding of the so
being interesting how how recently did
that was that used and why was the
pyramid closed off with the large St
block so that them had access to that
chamber in this way you will understand
that there was a recognition of the
ending of a timing of knowledge that was
brought from what you call
Atlantis and when there were the
recognition that the initiates were no
longer in existence within the society
than the chamber was
sealed I ask another question of course
um I played for a symphony orchestra and
we have a conductor who is very good and
who I would like to uh understand and
interact with more than I do I have a
difficulty understanding the way he
relates one
moment tonight's discussion is about
believing in
beliefs now you can have a
belief and you can also believe that you
have a
belief and in this way many of what you
hold to be your initial beliefs are
found founded on nothing more than
belief in another belief to support
it I have difficulty in
interacting again that is not a law of
nature it is not chiseled in steel it is
a
belief if you can choose to understand
that you already are an interaction no
matter what definition the interaction
takes you already are an interaction
with that
individual then you can simply know that
if you already are an interaction with
that individual and if you do not prefer
the definition of the interaction then
you can rewrite the definition of what
that interaction
is you follow me yes now how does your
imagination choose to rewrite the
definition of the interaction that you
already are with that other
individual okay thank you what I would
like to do is understand more I am
I beg you pardon repeat after me I am I
am the interaction the interaction of
understanding of
understanding Like That Tune
iy I shall learn to sing it you are
singing it right now understand again
that if you can even conceive of an idea
you are
it you can only perceive what you
contain you are equal to the vibration
of that which you perceive to be
real it say once more all right in other
it say once more all right in other
words as you create an idea whether
vocalize it or imagine it you are in
synchronous harmony with it or you would
never hit that
note when you
are giving a note you are that note and
you are what that note
represents therefore as you say I am the
interaction of understanding that is the
note that you are it is the symphony
that you are and and that is what will
play itself out if you truly know that
you have chosen to believe but that is
equally as true as any other thing you
could believe and you simply make a
preferential choice you follow me yes my main
choice you follow me yes my main
question is I do not wish to impose upon
him you won't understand again if you
simply allow the idea of your integrity
to have created your new belief of
yourself then you will know that the
timing is also perfect and that they
will interact with you and you will
interact with them you will create you
will co-create situations in which it is
obviously all right to interact and then
when you see those opportunities you
will ask upon them thereby granting
yourself the validity and the conviction
of actually being the idea you are now
assuming that you are to reinforce that
Reality by acting upon the opportunities
you give yourself to act upon when you
create those opportunities by being by
trusting by knowing that you are that
reality perfect thank you oh thank
you thank you I have a deep desire to
express myself desire I do as an actress
and an Entertainer more than I do more
than you do I keep seemingly for
yearsing the [Music]
[Music]
surface I'm not
um um can you give me some some way to
see this clear what what surface are you
scratching Define the
surface where is it is an arbitrary
point in my
estimation all right Define it all right
what is the service I don't I'm not
working as much as I want to
work and I I don't seem to contact the
right people right people the people
that you put me to work are you an actor
yes are you sure yes really sure then
why not act like
one you are acting like allow me to put
it this way here is the idea I perceive
you to be I am an actress that contains
the idea of not being able to act
that is the whole idea that you are
exploring now if you are willing to
prefer that you are an actress who
contains the idea of being able to act
in perfect timing then that will be the
manifestation of the reality you will
experience you follow me well how has it
served you to be the idea of an
actress who does not
ask how has it turned you what have you
learned by being the being you are
being TR myself all right it also has
shown you what you prefer
yet all right now how in your terms can
you trust yourself more than you already
do understand that even what you are
experiencing has been the result of your
trust because you showed yourself what
you needed to show yourself you can
certainly trust that
therefore let what you have shown
yourself serve you then by not judging
the reality that you have you can create
another reality
Margo would you care to read that
idea all right now is the perfect
timing we have all co-created
it and now this can be an example for
you as well of the perfect timing in
which you are always functioning so pay
attention to the reflection of yourself
that you have
co-created when you allow yourself the
opportunity to not judge yourself for
the ideas you are experiencing and the
way you are experiencing them and allow
the way it happens to you to be the way
that serves you then it will not matter
to you that it's happened that way and
when it does not matter to you that it
happens that way you are giving another
way an opportunity to come in you are
not focused on the one way that you have
experience got to sing
him thank you for your loving
act for understanding his way in
aent in this life this physical life
you're always
acting the part you show to play to
serve
you follow me thank you very
much one moment you want [Music]
what the time
frame
aty thank you you will find one
combination at least the pyramids you
are familiar with early Egyptian
civilization with late atlanteans with
some some what you call extraterrestrial
intermixing that is the earliest in that
Way St H in this way another remnant of
atlantian civilization which we call the
druidic fashion that in this way created
that as a Remnant as a symbol of what
they believe they had lost in their
relationship to Nature by destroying
themselves in Atlantis in this way you
will find that at the island chain there
were several ideas of Destruction in
this way over a long period of time
stretching to what you understand in
your time frame all the way let us say
intrinsically as the existence of the
land mass itself as the beginning of the
civilization from approximately the idea
anywhere from 100,000 of your years to
50,000 of your years ago in this way and
also up to the ending point of what you
would recognize to be approximately
11,500 of your years ago to what you
call the final subance in this way the
idea is not Atomic as you understand it
but vibratory the transformation of
light directly into vibratory energy
more akin to what you would understand
to be through Crystal and energy the
laser that you have now created in your
Society but slightly different it was
the vibratory resonance pitched too high
that activated synchronous harmonic
vibration in Subterranean volcanic
chambers that caused the collapse of the
island chain follow me thank you
chain follow me thank you
are desend
yes is it true that the Easter Island um
the statues that were were brought from
orine like a scare code to SC the native
away because the space cracks were
Landing now there is some connection
some to that idea but again there's not
that anything was brought
recognize simply that in that idea you
call Thea in your Pacific Ocean in that way
Thea in your Pacific Ocean in that way
you will find there was some initial
interaction initial
identification with the idea of the
Orion Energy in this
way and there was some recognition of
some of that but not in the way you
think it was more in archetypal
recognition of energy that now existed
upon the planet and it was let us say an
instinctual representational expression
by the natives who existed in theoria to
represent the aspect of what had now
become blended with the entire idea of
your Earth
civilization that is all we will say at
this time some
some
yes again also the idea what you call
atlantian influence some lorian
influence some lorian
influence also some idea of other
densities other density venusian
influence in this way for you will find
in that area you call the wco the idea
of what you call your vuan
calendar representing a year that is not
what you call your Earth year to
be upon what you
call the inscriptions upon the stone you
call the gate of the sun
thank um two questions one uh is about
the idea earlier Express of uh complying
with the mass Consciousness on this time
you uhand that I are
uh nothing much needs to be expanded
except that the ideas that you can
experience as a physiological being will
not extend beyond the limit that serves
the mass Consciousness however you are
finding that your entire idea of
yourself is changing and therefore that
is why more and more quote unquote is
allowed to be experienced that's
seemingly is opposed to what was
previously able to be experienced upon
your planet as you stretch this
definition of yourself so the mass
Consciousness will agree to more and
more leeway so to speak as to what is or
is not possible to serve itself as a
reflection to what it can or cannot do
in this physical reality it's part of
the agreement then of experiencing this
reality as to at this timing and
everything else as to what you will or
will not do within that
basically this does not mean you cannot
identify with the probability for in
this way it is the ability to even as we
have said conceive that such a thing
might be possible that is your first
indication of a change within the mass
Consciousness the other question was
about cats you mentioned earlier that
when was talking about her cat but it
was a guide is that all animal
Consciousness is very willing very
lovingly reflecting to you many
different aspects of your Consciousness
that you have created to be outside
yourselves animals are guides for many
different portions of the Consciousness
you are only beginning to
remember and also in earlier sessions
you said that they don't karmically
reincarnate as we do they reincarnate
but not with the sense of karma except
the karma that you choose to create for
yourselves to which they may lovingly
attach themselves I see for the purposes
of serving you again they come back to
us they can yes they um
reincarnate uh into a third and then
fourth density as I
mean as you shall so shall they okay
thank
you to experience yourself as separate
from the universe in this way whereas in
fourth density you will see through
through the Illusion for you will know
more of yourself and see from in a sense
a higher point of
view you follow me yes I do so the
density finin can continue to move
forward as our understanding of the
higher Consciousness moves forward and
you will then see through that
perspective yes is it truth that the
exper are connected through underground
uh corridors or
no not all of them there are a few that
are here and there but not all of them
know sure now there will be a few of
your minutes
remaining for this
interaction yes yes would you address
the um idea of animals on this planet
and with respect to what what's
happening to our so-called endangered
species how is this going to
I don't know all right now simply again
understand that animals are always
willing to reflect to you the state of
your own
beingness and as you create that idea
you have created the belief that you
yourselves are endangered in that way of
becoming extinct for recognize they will always
extinct for recognize they will always
be willing if that is what you require
of them to lay down their lives for you
to reflect the idea of the state in
which you find yourselves to be creating
your civilization also recognize in this
way that the animals upon your planet
exhibit the idea of being territorial
because you do animals upon my Planet
are not
territorial simply in this way you will
find that the idea of territory is what
you stake out to be your own in terms of
possession in that way possessing an
area of land that is not to be
interacted with with other animals with
other beings in this way you will find
that in our civilization all animal life
can be found based basically in all
portions of our planet at different
times there is no defined territory that
anyone needs to defend for there is no
sense of
Defense there is some remnant of this
idea in our civilization still to this
date but in this way you will find that
the majority at this time of our animal
forms are more in the term
symbiotic and rely upon each other for
their existence and are all Al more now
in this time frame reference of our
civilization also energy
absorbent so as we move into the fourth
density then
um we will create the idea of abundant
animal life and and yes so this isn't
the problem is a situation like any other
problem is a situation like any other
situation that you can redefine
you follow me yeah
again when you allow yourselves to
understand that all killing is
suicide then you will bring the idea
home and you will not want to destroy
your home follow me yes I do you have
par there is some remnant idea of this
and yet again once again those that are
attached in that way to the idea of the
physiological construct that we are will
all be of a positively serving nature in
that way even as you yourself have in
that sense created some that are in that
way positively
so not in that way
no there will be
be one in this
sense that you will find that will be a
remnant of that
idea that in this way does perform this
service at this
time where there will be closer to what
you would understand to
be our perception is your terminology
you call the slope you follow me in this
way this
animal upon creating co-creating the
opportunity to be upon the skin of any
individual be it our human form being or
another animal has the
animal has the
ability to act as a
living in aent solar Crystal and in this
sense can imbue a filtering from the
sunlight through its body into the skin
and form a
re-energization or a rearrangement of
the crystalline structure of our
cellular being and in that rearrangement
deriv for itself a sustenance in the
energy that is released in the
rearrangement the rearrangement serves
those that are rearranged and the
rearrangement serves that which does the
rearranging you follow me for it is the
energy that comes out of the
rearrangement that is the sustenance
energy upon which that animal lives not
the Direct Energy that it transfers to
do the
rearranging you follow me
so in that way you may say yes parasite
symbiotic in that sense but
beneficial for the rearrangement is
always a reflection of positive
Evolution foll me sounds like a turbo
slug if you
wish don't see me
just we don't know how that like for in
that way
exactly I have a question you just said
before that um all murder suicide is all
killing ourselves yes is this true also
of abortion our concept of abortion all
right now in this sense
recognize that even while we are
defining that all killing in this way is
suicide we are not judging the idea for
all is learned from everything that is
done now we are not saying that you need
what you call to be abortion but in this
way it is not intrinsically negative in
and of itself for you are understanding
that since your Society has created the
idea that such a thing can occur within
its needs and its wants are only
attracting individuals that only need to
experience that much of physical reality
to fulfill their needs so you are not
depriving anyone of anything in that
ultimate sense you will simply find
however that when you allow yourself to
be in communication with all
consciousness you will not necessarily
then find yourself being pregnant when
you do not need to
be and that is how that symbol will
transform you are not intrinsically in
that way doing anything
wrong but in this way you may understand
that there is another way that may be in
your terms more
efficient and in this sense again in
terms of what you recognize to actually
be the personality
Consciousness that personality
Consciousness in your terms does not
actually so to speak enter the body
until just prior to physical birth you
follow me yeah whatever energy Essence
is experienced in the time that was
experienced in the womb to the time of
what you call the abortion was all that
that entity needed to extend of one of
its tiny fragments into physical reality
let us say to test the waters of
physicality for itself to experience
just that much of physicality and and
the purpose has been
served to some degree it is not exactly
the same as the idea of in your terms
the killing of a fully formed
Consciousness that is fixed into
physical reality though in this way
again it is a symbol you do not
necessarily need for it does bring up
within you the concerns of the negative
idea and in this way you can simply
understand that if you are in touch with
the idea of all Consciousness then you
will know in this way as we have chosen
to create in our civilization the
interaction with the Consciousness to be
born will then simply recognize that
when the purpose is served to be born it
will be born when the purpose is not
served there will never be even the
beginning of the creation of a birth you
follow me yes does the idea of suicide
enter into abortion at all when you said
that murder was a form of
suicide does that apply to AB at all now
that is what this being has just asked
yeah but I didn't understand where
suicide could
or simply what was being said is that
all killing is suicide since in killing
you are killing a portion of yourself
you follow me now the idea is not
exactly the same idea because in this
way what you call the physiological
Consciousness personality is not
actually instilled within what you call
the fetus until just prior to bir
but in this way it is not necessarily
saying that this is a symbol that you
must continue for what it is a
reflection of is the fact that you are
not in touch with all levels of your
Consciousness and that if you know that
the idea of having a birth serves that
being to be born then it will simply be
born or it will not even be created as a
pus to begin with there will not be the
question of abortion in the sense that
when you are in communication with other
aspects of yourself and are fully
cognizant of the purposes for which you
create and co-create other beings to be
physically in your life then you will be
in touch with the being wishing to be
born and you will simply consciously
clearly cocreate either a birth or not a
birth there will be no in between thank
you but miscarriage then is miscarriage
a choice to yes to not continue with
that process yes okay and in this way
understand it is not even so much the
choice to not continue it is the result
of the choice that has already been
determined to experience just that time
frame and no longer you follow me yes I
do that is the reflection of the
agreement that was made you may come
into my physical body in that way and
partake of physicalness exactly as you
need to up to a certain point then not
needing to experience that any longer my
physiological reaction be to miscarry to
allow you the opportunity in this way to
pull back the idea of your energy that
you have instilled in the physical form
that you are experiencing yourselves to
be for that short period of time all
right all right all right all
right for in this way understand
this there are many many many Souls
being born upon your planet at this time
that are a reflection of the idea of the
transformation and in this way they are
carrying within them the opportunity to
when they are physically born to
remember who they are and in this way
many of these Souls have chosen as we
have said as a symbol to stick perhaps
one of their little fingers in the water
to get used to the idea so that they can
choose individuals to make the
agreements with that will allow them to
create the
remembrance so that that will serve the
fourth density
transformation understand that many of
the children being born now this way
they will remind you what the agreement
was all
about follow me for they are now for
density individuals
individuals
briefly I'd like to know if my brother
reincarnated in December into the body
of a female child Nam Shan why and why
do you have that
understanding it's an idea I have all
right what does it do for you
and how did your brother in your terms
die canc all right why
December um what does that represent for you Reb
um what does that represent for you Reb
well I no it's just that I know someone
who had a child inber and that person
this is very connected to you in this
lifetime all right and you saw the
opportunity for that Consciousness to
express itself in that
way do you find that you feel the
identity in that way to be a connection
for yourself are you attracted to that
child in that way I haven't seen her
yet but I then at this time allow
yourself the opportunity to view the
child and when you view the child
understand that there is a
connection literal or not as you are
choosing to understand it for now we
will not say for there are many
understandings that you have yet to
create for yourself within this idea of
why you are forming a connection it is
more more than just the idea of
exploring the literalness of whether it
is a direct
reincarnation when you have gotten a
little further in understanding why the
connection is being formed there may be
more opportunity on your behalf to
understand whether it is in your terms
literal or not but for now it is our
perception that one way or another to
say yes or no would not serve
you there is a process going on and it
is a process of forming a relationship
and it is the essence of that
relationship that is the important thing
of this interaction not the specifics at
this time the feelings the connections
you follow
me then extend your love in that way to
the child and
listen listen with your imagination to
the energy that child may send all right
thank you no thank you now it is well
we will extend to each and every one of
you at this
time the
recognition that your
beliefs as you choose to believe
them are the methodologies that serve
you and as you allow them to serve you
you give yourselves the opportunity to
try so to speak other beliefs to live
other ideas to expand the idea that you
are and to experience directly the new
understanding of
yourself it is the willingness to
recognize yourself as the experience of
your life as the event of your life
rather than experience yourself apart
from it outside from it it is the
willingness to know that you are the
experience of your light that will allow
you to see yourselves as the fourth
density transformation itself you are
the experience of the fourth density
transformation and together we are the
co-creation of that idea both in your
terms and in our own we thank you for
the gift of allowing us to experience
each and every one of you individually
and the collectivity of the
Consciousness that you are to us this is
unconditional love in our sharing we are
the sharing that continues forever enjoy
your dream lives and we B you good night