All right, I'll say how are you all this
evening of your time my alien
friend right we will begin the idea of
this interaction this evening of your
time once again and further of all with
the idea as we have been discussing
ecstasy in this way allow us to remind
you for in this way it is always a joy
to be allowed to remind you that it is
your birthright to live in ecstasy you
are created from ecstasy Y created from
love. It is the fabric and the essence
of all that is the
very material if you wish out of which
the idea of a universe is created within
all that
is ecstasy. Your willingness to
recognize your
right to exist
as the
fundamental being. You were created to
be your zero rest
point. A place in a sense within
yourself, an attitude, a demeanor, a
state of
being in which you find that all
situations are created from you and that
all situations are created fundamentally
equal and
neutral. And that you can
apply the
knowingness to each and every
situation. The knowingness out of which
you created each and every
situation. Simply allowing each and
every fundamentally neutral situation to
be a reflection of your knowingness.
Trusting that every situation that
occurs, every event that occurs is an
opportunity to recognize within yourself
the primal creative essence out of which
the situation was fashioned, was
fabricated. Knowingness is ecstasy.
Ecstasy is knowingness both our trust.
The idea of simply exercising the faith
to know that everything in your life is
by definition something that belongs
there. Thus that gives you the
opportunity to operate in a knowing
condition in a controlled
condition. Knowing that everything is an
opportunity to be viewed, to be of
service in a positive way. If you but
know and have the attitude and trust
that it is so, then that is the only
type of manifestation that can occur in
connection to any given situation. A
positive one. As we have said, the idea
of every situation being fundamentally
neutral gives you the opportunity to
give it whatever meaning you desire,
positive and or
negative. Giving an idea a negative
meaning will create it to have a
negative effect. giving it a positive
positive effect. It is in your terms that simple.
effect. It is in your terms that simple.
Ecstasy is also the allowance not the
making not the forcing but the allowance
of life to be that simple to know that
you by the simple fact that you exist
deserve anything you can imagine
anything you can
desire. It is your
birthright, your creation
right to allow that which you can
imagine to be realized for
you. In this way, recognize on other
levels of your existence. The
imagination is the reality. You can
allow it to be the case in physical
reality as well. And this is what part
of the transformation at this time is
all about. The blending of your physical
reality with all the other levels that
you are in a way that allows you to know
that your physical reality is just as
much an imaginary choice as anything and
that you can replace the ideas, the
events and the situations of your
physical reality with any choice at all.
Since what you are experiencing is the
product of a choice to begin
with. Only you
decide what
versions, what beliefs about reality,
about the idea of reality will be the
ones to be
realized, solidified in your experience.
You are therefore going to find as you
blend your physical reality and your
dream reality, your imagination reality
together that you may find until let us
say you get used to living in that state
that your physical reality from time to
time as you create time to exist may
take on disassociated disconnected and/or
on disassociated disconnected and/or
dreamlike qualities. A sense of un or
sir realness in which you seem to be
realness in which you seem to be
floating through the
event. Not really so much a part of it
and yet connected to every level of it.
In which physical reality may seem all
of a sudden to take on a
dimensionlessness, a
flatness, an
insubstantialness. These are only your
conscious recognitions of the blending.
You can always continue to exist in that
state in an ecstatic way by simply
knowing that life is something in your
terms you can flow through and that can
flow through
you. For life is what you are. Life is
what you are made of. You are yourselves
the pulse and the heartbeat of the idea
of time and space. You determine how
much of either you
experience. Integration gives you the opportunity to
Integration gives you the opportunity to
experience all the events you have
chosen to experience in less
time. Separation and judgment creates
the opportunity to create more
time and need more room in which to
experience the ideas.
Therefore, recognize that even within
what you call your language, once again,
it is quite literal in this instance,
that when you are blended, when you are
when you are blended, when you are
flowing, when you are totally within the
ecstasy of the act, it takes less
time. Literally, it is not that time is
the same and it is only sped up. It
seems to be sped up because there is not
as much of it. You are creating less
time in which to have an experience. Sharing
Sharing
uh my daughter was at a service station
yesterday and left her car door open
briefly and when she came back a little
dog was on the back seat. very small
little very tiny little dog about this
big
and she asked around that nobody knew it
so she brought it home and she has a
very strong feeling that this little dog
should be with her and she would like to
know what you think about it and my
question is was the little dog abandoned
or are her previous owners looking for
her in this way once Again, do not
forget that the animal always knows
exactly where it needs to be at any
given moment. And in this way, you will
find that if anyone truly in that sense
needs to have that animal back, they
will recognize that you can simply do
recognize that you can simply do
whatever is within your power to
advertise the idea that the animal is
with your daughter in that way. And simply
your daughter in that way. And simply
recognize that for whatever time the
animal is with her, that will be the
time that the animal needs to be with
her. And once again, remember the idea
in your civilization of what you call
the symbol of the dog is the symbol of
service, uh, a companionship and service. Well,
uh, a companionship and service. Well,
does does the dog's consciousness have
uh a special relationship to my
daughters? Obviously. Otherwise the dog
would not be there. Obviously any
interaction is obviously by definition
the product of a relationship
in those terms as they need to be
experienced and in your terms therefore
special in that way otherwise it would
not happen. Once again allow me to
remind you
nothing nothing in the universe happens
extraneously. Nothing happens for no reason. Sorry.
Nothing happens for no reason. Sorry.
Yes. Oh, do not be sorry. Simply allow
me to remind you once again that you are
very capable of allowing yourself to
recognize that these situations, at
least in the terms upon which you are
asking them, are all quite obvious.
That's true. In those terms, well, the
little dog is walks in a a strange way.
Is something wrong with her back legs?
How does your daughter walk through
life? Au life. Okay.
Yes. Up and down. All right. Sideways.
Then allow your daughter to attract to
her whatever reflections are necessary
and allow her to take onto heart the
idea that communication is going on
quite consciously on the surface if she
is but willing to see.
Okay. All right. Thank you very much.
You you me.
All right. You then
I waited 10 months to to 10 months.
I couldn't come come here 10 months ago.
Anyway, um about last April, I
experienced about 3 months of what you
described at the beginning of this
session. Um you experienced three months
last April. Yes, I did. All right. All
in one moment. All right. Um it was
um I was absolutely fascinated with
every moment and every moment was was
almost like jumping off a cliff and it
was okay living in the now. It was
lovely was and then yes was why was well
you'll see
then a strange thing started happening
strange strange um I these very morbid
horrible thoughts started coming in one
by one in other words I could I could
look at the news prior to this time and
it all looked good even the starving
faces in Ethiopia were brilliant
reminders to everyone to open their
hearts and all that
Yes. Then then then it started all
looking ugly and it all started looking
malevolent as if as if this thing that I
had experienced was all a joke and as if
it was all an illusion, which I know
that it is and I know I've created all
of it. All right. Um how does seeing it
in that way serve you now? Well, that's
what I'd like to know. U then then the
next thing that happened was a uh an
experience one night all of a sudden all
these dichotoies which had melted. I
swear every single dichotomy in the
universe came rolling in on me and it
was not it seemed to not be in my
control and my heart started Yes. And my
heart was beating a mile a minute. I
actually thought I was dying and I was
having a heart attack and I almost went
unconscious and parts of my body
disappeared and I was just terrified and
I even had the paramedics come up and um
they did nothing but um but I had
company.
3 in the morning.
3 in the morning. Very appropriate. Yes.
So, and also I was quite lonely during
this time and then I got these but
anyway I thought that was quite funny
that night but then after this I went to
hospital uh very slightly. All right. Um
then I I took myself to the hospital and
I I I was not having a heart attack but
everything looked very strange to me.
Ace Yes. and disorientation very much
so. So I continued I couldn't even go
out of my house. I actually uh cringed
from the sun and the moon even it was
too much and I thought well and um I
think I know I'm creating this but I
don't want to be creating this at the
same time. It was almost a dichotomy of
the original thing that I experienced.
Okay. Then on and on and on. Um I tried
various ways of dealing with this. I do
have to function in life. Tried pride.
Yes. Yes. I know we know about tri. So,
so then recently I've been experiencing
again uh driving in my car and I my my
heart will beat a mile a minute and I
will start to faint and uh uh I feel
very very disoriented from life. It's
boring to me and uh but not really
boring but am I ill? I want to know if
I'm ill. E yes, you have symptoms of
transformation sickness. That's what I
You are experiencing the idea of fourth
density disease. That's what I thought.
Well, what is the remedy?
To live. That's how I thought you were
going to and cease to judge what is
happening to you as something negative.
Yeah, there's less fear now about it.
Yes. Make a friend of your fear. It is
there to show you something. accept the
message it delivers and integrate that
message within you as a part of you.
Well, it's pretty humbling. Recognize in
this way that may have been the
point so that you will also know that in
your ecstasy you will also at the same
time remain grounded enough to assist
others. You follow me?
You follow me?
Yes, kind of. I'm sorry I don't quite
go. All right, just take it in a general
sense. Okay. The idea that when you
accelerate to infinite speeds, many
times you will create within you from
your belief systems that you will lose
sight of the ideas you wish to exemplify
in choosing this physical life upon your
planet. So you give yourself the
opportunity to experience the polarity
of the ecstasy in that way so that you
now will be able to blend the two
dichotoies as you say and form a
balanced state of being that will allow
you to exist in the fourth density state
with equal ease. Now I get it. Thank
you. Thank you. Thank you.
All right. You
are now one. Yes. [Music]
How are your dreams? Oh, I've had uh
interesting dreams where I have actually
identified someone several thousand
miles away that I never heard of and had
someone call me on that a week later and
and tell me what I had dreamt. All
right. Very good. And I Yes, I forgot to
mention that. Thank you very much for
allowing me to mention it for you.
My pleasure.
And for allowing yourself to begin to
remember who and what you are.
Pay attention. Messages will come from
farther away than that.
All right.
Thank you, Crystal.
Yes. It's strawberry.
Strawberry. Crystal is sitting next to
Strawberry. Like Crystal, life ain't been that
Like Crystal, life ain't been that
sweet.
You are not being strawberry.
Right. Lately, I've been experiencing
absence of ecstasy.
What makes you think so? Perhaps you are
simply not recognizing the guise in
which it is appearing in your life and
judging it to not be ecstasy. Perhaps.
Perhaps you are. Okay, that's that's a
good thought. This a suggestion. I like
it. No. Right. I also have been
experiencing apparent automatic
disbelief that I'm causing this crap.
What are you labeling as crap?
Uh this this choice to experience the
dichotomy of ecstasy,
which I don't see. All right, let me put
it another way. All right. What is it
that allows you to continue to label it
as the opposite?
Uh what allows me to label it as what
makes you think it is the opposite of
ecstasy that you are experiencing?
Um by what definition does it seem to
be? So um I guess I've assigned pressure
um uh the absence of certain feelings.
Um these various conditions I call
miserable heavy. All right. First of
all, pressure from where is this
pressure coming?
It seems to be coming from the whole
universe. The whole universe. The whole
universe seems to be laying on my body.
Oh, right. Perhaps in a sense it is.
Yeah. So that you will have the creative
pressure to be motivated in the
direction it is pushing you in. It
doesn't seem to motivate. It seems to
contract contract contraction and
immobility more
than you know it seems. That is because
all realities are equally probable. And
until you make a decision to move in a
certain direction, you will feel
pressure equally from all sides because
all realities have the equal potential
to be realized. They are all vying at
the same time for realization.
You must decide which one to allow
through and therefore which valve to
open so that you can move in that
direction. That's very nice. Thank you.
Oh, thank you. Now, you're welcome. What
about these ideas of absence of
feelings? How do you know if you cannot
feel them that they are absent? Oh, I
can I can feel I have a tactile
sensation of an absence. A tactile
sensation of an absence. Yes. An absence
of what?
um an absence of a particular sensation
which I can mock up and remember. Why is
mocking up and remembering not the same
thing as being in that state? because I
have it separate from why
that one I'm not I don't know I need
some to us the idea of mocking up and
remembering is the creation of the state
in the present but you can ex you can be
sitting apparently in the dichotomy of
it and have the the positive creation
quote unquote or the preference separate
you can keep it unreal
Yes.
Or you can allow it to be real. Okay.
And how do I go about allowing I'll go I
allow this to be real and it go you
fully trust that it is
which obviously you do not. No. No. I go
I go to fully trust and I get automatic.
Oh, you're full of crapola. Nope. Nope.
No. You are making a connection where
none exists. You cannot by definition
fully trust one reality and get any
effect other than what is by definition
a part of that reality. If you get
another effect, that is the reality you
fully trust. That is correct. And that's
the one I'm trusting. I'm trusting the
crap. Yes, I seem to be good at trusting
crap. Nice. Perhaps it is simply your
way to experience that to the utmost so
that you can truly have pride in being a
master of limitation.
Oh yeah, I have a crap master student.
When you when you find that it has
served you enough and you are in your
terms finally good and tired of it, then
you will change. I seem tired. I I
invented a crap eating dragon who died
from an overdose of crap.
Why did it not survive?
Uh it seemed to get overdose. It had a
limit of nothing seems in that way
without your creating it. You seem so I
created it with a limit. It was a funny
story. All right. We are laughing.
Very good. But simply we are pointing
out that all the definitions that you
are basing these things on are quite
conscious choices in terms of how you
wish to look at things. Even the
conscious choice that is not a conscious
choice. But it is. Right. Of course.
Okay. This is very nice reflection. I'm
enjoying this song. Well, thank you.
Okay. Number two. Uh oh, that was all
number one.
Actually, it wasn't all of number one.
I didn't want to give you all the number
one. Okay. Anyway, that's more funny. I know
Okay. Anyway, that's more funny. I know
you're laughing up there, but you don't
want to express it because you'll center
and break the connection. Okay. Why are
[Music]
wonder as much as we can give you?
I just looking at my notebook. Okay,
that's I'll have the videos. Okay, good.
Okay, good.
Why are wondrous moments in times
apparently followed by rotten moments?
Because you create that belief that
something is too good to last. No, I
don't I don't recall creating that and I
recall but you are creating it right now
because you are conscious of it. That's
right. But I've also had the experience
where I was creating the continuousness
of wonderfulness and then crap appeared
and then I went but you are judging it
to be crap and that is what makes it so
instead of trusting that whatever comes
to you is there for a reason that is a
part of the ecstatic path and let
yourself see how it is. You keep telling
me that and you write all it back. It is
simply that you are so much more quick
with the judgment than you are with the
trust. Ooh, nice.
Because you have had so very much more
practice. That's right. I'm going to
develop a new beingness called quick
trust. Yes.
I am sure that will earn your interest.
Thank you, Bashar. Thank you very much.
Our pleasure.
One moment.
I would like to share a very touching
experience that happened to me. All
right. And I don't understand it, but it
obviously you understand it how you need
to proceed. I I understand it how I need
to understand it and I have a strong
desire to share it to this group
tonight. Then you understand it
perfectly. Continue.
I have a um creation that I'm in the
midst of creating an institute called
consciousness institute for
consciousness in the media.
And today at work, I teach in a school.
I'm still teaching. Today at work, one
of the teachers came up to me and said,
"What are you going to do this summer?"
And I said, "Oh, I'm going to just sort
of uh create my business. I'm starting a
new business." She said, "What is it?"
And I told her and she said, "That is
incredible. Um what do you need?" And I
said, "Well, I'm looking." I will
assume, of course, she meant it was
quite credible. Yes. All right. And
also, the school where I'm teaching is a
very religious, Orthodox Jewish school,
and most of the people do not allow
their children to watch TV because
they're very anti- images, media images.
They're very selective on what their
children watch. All right. She had a
very, very positive reaction. And um I
said I was looking for financing. and
she said, "Well, let me be the first one
to give you money." Been not only a
positive reaction, but a positive
action. Now, this woman is raising her
children alone as I am. She's one of the
few women that's uh divorced in this
particular group. Most of the Orthodox
people are very tight with families and
have a lot of children. She doesn't have
a lot of money. She said, "I can't
afford much. All I can give you is $46.
Would that be
okay?" I started crying. I was totally I
mean you can you can imagine how I felt.
We walked into the office.
We walked into the office. She writes me
out a check and I said to her, "When you
get this check back, would you give it
to me? I want a Xerox and I would like
to put it in a plaque and you are my
first contributor. You don't know what
what wonderful things you have just
done." She says, "Yes, I do. I really I
understand." Now, I come home. The
minute I walk home into into my house,
my daughter is crying hysterically.
She's 11 years old. At the very I found
this out after questioning her. The
minute that this woman was signing the
check, my daughter was almost hit by a
car walking across the street. Uh she
was crossing on a green light, a car
went through and she said she felt it
touch her legs. That's how close it got.
And there were witnesses and it really
shook her up. Okay. We questioned each
other and the time that it happened is
exactly when this woman was signing the
check. St. Now, my reaction, which I
mean when when something like that
happens, you never know what kind of a
reaction you're going to have. Oh, yes,
you do. My shock. Okay. My reaction was
of course I I I started crying. I was so
grateful that she was okay. And I said
to her, "That is an incredible thing
that happened. This proves that there
are guardian angels watching over us at
this point in time." in a sense in a
sense and that we were very fortunate
and the synchronicity of the two events
became very significant and I wanted to
share that. Thank you very much for your
willingness to open doorways
simultaneously. You will now find that
there will be much acceleration in both
of your lives.
Well, I have nothing to do with
it. Thank you for your sharing. for your
sharing has also made a difference and
will open more doorways simply because
of the action.
I understand
you are both now not who you used to be.
That's right. True. Thank you. That's
true. Sharon,
Sharon,
in what sense are the their guardian
angels? In the sense that there are in
your terms non-physical beings that are
associated with you in this way that are
constantly sending you unconditional
love that you can make a decision to
associate with and thus in this way form
the idea of the type of path that allows
you to sense the reflection of the idea
that it is not so much that you need
protection but that simply the path that
you are on does not contain the idea of
attack.
Did you follow that? That last one I got
didn't follow. The idea of guardian
angel is simply one that reminds you
that you have the opportunity to agree
with the vibration of that being of that
spirit that you do not need protection
and that to use your term is what
protects you.
Very good. You identify with that
portion of your own creatorhood,
with your own spirit.
One moment. Um, I have a young friend
who uh just turned 12, but was 11 years
old when this happened to him. Another
one? Yes, another 11year-old. And uh I
hadn't heard from him quite for quite a
while. And when I went back to
Australia, I found out from his mother
that he had a brain
tumor. And he was a very good artist.
And I think he was probably a star
person because he was always telling
stories about outer space. He drew
pictures of uh starships of all
different kinds. Now he's lost all his ability in
kinds. Now he's lost all his ability in
his right hand. He has to learn how to
speak again. He has to learn how to draw
again. I just wonder what was the
lesson for him.
To some degree karmic but not so much
more the idea of service to others. For
in this way what he shall relearn will
be what needs to be communicated to
others in the process of his
relearning. For it is to others that
this information is now going. And what
others will learn about how to extend
their senses to communicate with this
individual will serve them in life. And
what they will now learn will allow them
also to recognize their own artistry in
life. as well as the loving act of
limitation that this child has chosen
for himself so as to be an example in
this way to many individuals and to
recognize the strength of that
choice. It is also part and parcel of
the opportunity of many individuals to
be in touch with the idea of what
communication and channeling through the
idea of the brain is all about. So that
you can blend and homogenize all of the
ideas of mentality upon your planet and
recognize in this way that you are
always in communication with all aspects
of any particular being and you do not
necessarily have to rely upon the
physiological manifestation of mentality
through the brain to achieve that
connection.
This will play out in our perception
over the next three of your
years and will blossom into many
flowers. We thank you for bringing to
our attention the sharing of that facet of
attention the sharing of that facet of
the multi-dimensional crystal in your
world. Sure.
Lashar, on um television the other
night, I saw um a newscast about three
dozen or so pilot whales that have been
trying to beach themselves on the north
of California along the coast. And
despite attempts by people to guide them
back out to sea, they keep coming back
in. And I wonder what is that to some
degree the idea of magnetic fluctuations
within your electromagnetic field. And
in this way the idea of the confusion of
the directions that you as a
civilization as the land humans may be
traveling in with regard to your
relationship to them the water humans.
So but it's it is opportunity for
communication opportunity for the
recognition of getting in touch with
what it is that guides you through life
and in this way allowing yourself in
that sense to determine your own course
and to share with them this opportunity
to
recognize that you do not ever have to
go
astray. Is that in the sense that
they're pilot whales in that sense?
That's very interesting because it's a
suicidal kind of attempt really. Not
really. Not really. It is more the idea
of confusion in your terms. For in this
way, the idea is their navigation along
the electromagnetic fields because of
the shifting of the planet does not
necessarily in that way physiologically
allow them to understand where they are.
[Music] and they enter your
and they enter your
realm as you are also attempting to
enter theirs.
Can we help redirect them? Yes,
you can surround them with the idea of
the electromagnetic navigational field
that will point the direction away from
the land and thus give yourselves an
opportunity to recognize what you are
capable of in terms of directing the
electromagnetic energies of your planet
and channeling them through yourselves.
and that will have been their service to
you. Was that true when Humphrey got
Yes. for recognize the idea of the
response of that being was first and
foremost when they brought in a land
human that attempted what you call
telepathic contact. Then there was a
response not complete in your terms
simply because the whale was making a
point and in your terms was let us say
and in your terms was let us say
lobbying. recognize
recognize
us. We are here to help you. Yes. Was a
tremendous amount of people turned out.
I could sense that there was something
happening there because people Yes.
Those connections will strengthen as you
go into fourth density with what you
call your whale and dolphin brothers,
sisters, and cousins.
Thank you, Michelle. Thank you,
Michelle. For sure. Yes. Um, I want to
go back to guardian angels or higher
self for a second. Um, all right. Have a
good time. Okay.
Why does the higher self send down the
lower self to learn a lesson that the
higher self already knows? I don't What
is my misperception? Oh, thank you. The
higher self does not send down a lower
self. The idea is that the self creates
an idea and the idea automatically
determines that it will be split into
components that can experience what it
wants to experience. Only in a universe
of limitation of forgetfulness can you
experience many ideas. You cannot
experience in a universe in which you do
not forget who you are. Thus to
experience certain ideas of limitation
you must create a portion of your
consciousness to extend itself into a
universe in which you can forget who you
are. Thus the idea of a lower self is
created instantaneously upon the desire
to have a certain type of experience. It
is not that the higher self sends a
lower self. It is simply by definition
according to the experience that is
desired that these ideas of separations
are created.
You follow me? So I'm now within a realm
of limitation and I've cut myself off
from the true knowingness because I'm
limiting myself so that I can
experience. But you are still within
true knowingness for what you want to
learn. You are learning. Yeah. And in
this way you have not cut yourself off
for the conduit is always there. Now
this is the transformational life. In
your terms you are at the ending of a
multi,000ear cycle in which you have
been forgetting and now you are
remembering. So you are reintegrating
and becoming aware that you even have
such a thing as a higher self. Do we use
human aberration to learn these lessons?
Yes. So is it pointless to try and get
rid of human aberration? You cannot get
rid of it by accepting and learning the
lesson. You simply no longer need that
tool and then it will integrate and
smooth out.
It is all of the fighting against what
you have chosen to learn that continues
what you are calling aberration. The
acceptance of it will be the integration
of it, the learning of it and the
smoothing out of it. What does
acceptance actually mean though? Let's
say I have something that would be um
socially unacceptable socially and
embarrassing to me. Then in this way you
are learning the idea of
judgment. And that if it is something in
this way that you can still learn from,
then it is a lesson just as valuable and
equal to any other lesson that you could
learn. And you can also learn and have
the opportunity from that in terms of
knowing how to express yourself in terms
that you prefer
to. But do not judge any portion of
yourself. For to judge it is to create
it to remain. I understand the judgment.
But but does one practically just go
with the flow and just do whatever one
feels like doing within your integrity.
Yes. Recognize the idea of flowing
within your integrity is simply
recognizing that you are as powerful as
you need to be to learn and create and
do and be anything you want without
having to hurt anyone else to do
it. So there is no need for
forcing. Going with your flow does not
mean the violation of others rights.
But what if my mother wouldn't like me
climbing trees all day long because it's
socially unacceptable, but I feel like
climbing trees. You then climb them. But
how how does that not spread on her
toes? In this way, you simply recognize
the opportunity to share with her the
idea of what you are learning from it in
that way and offer her the
opportunity to recognize that it is not
interfering in your terms. It is not
forcing an idea upon someone. It is
simply her choice to judge that the idea
is something that she does not want to
experience in that way. But obviously
she has chosen to be with you. And if
you are the type of being that wants to
do that, then by definition it is
something she wants to be shown.
Okay? You follow me? You can work it out
to an equality by granting each other
self-empowerment and validity in each
other's points of view. Then you may
simply find that you may not always want
to climb a tree as often as you think
you do if it is simply out of
spite. You follow me? When you come to
equal terms, you will climb your tree
when it is exactly all right from her
point of view for you to do so. And that
is the only time you will feel like
climbing it. And vice versa.
Whenever you choose to climb it will be
the time that she feels it is all right
for you to do so.
You follow me? Yes.
Thank you. That is the synchronous
harmony that your entire civilization
can become. Thank you. Sure.
Yes. Um, this year I've become involved
in the Native American church and I'm
going to TV meetings and um, their all
night peyote ceremonies and I've been
using peyote and seems to be a very
powerful teacher and I'm wondering what
is you are a powerful teacher. Thus,
when you choose a symbol that reflects
the level of power you are comfortable
in dealing with, you will receive the
power on that
level. But it is only a symbol. You are
creating what you are experiencing. And
the peyote is only there to remind you
that you are creating it. You are using
it as a symbol. It is not that you need
it. It is simply showing you what is
possible within yourself because you are
removing your responsibility from having
created it and placing it on a symbol
that lets it be all right for you to
have that level of experience because I
am not doing it. Something else is
responsible. But you are doing
But you are doing
it. Um,
are you enjoying yourself? Yeah, thank
you. How come we seem to need those symbols?
How come we seem to need those symbols?
If I if I Because once again, in your
choice to experience separation,
limitation, and forgetfulness, you tend
to forget that you are the source of all
you experience and simply assume out of
habit that it is other things outside
yourself seemingly that cause these
experiences. So in continuing that
habit, you will assume that the drug is
causing the experience when it is in
fact you. For sure. But would it be easy
to say for me to go on an LSD trip
without taking LSD? Yes.
Have a good time.
In your language, do not many
individuals tell you from time to time
that they think you are tripping anyway?
All right, let that be your sign.
Yes, go do it. Um, in these ceremonies,
um, it it's it's real accelerated in the
it it's it's real accelerated in the
ceremonies for me. I learn a lot and,
um, you know, it's like channels are
opening up
and it was all because of your level of
willingness. And it seems like outside of the
And it seems like outside of the
ceremony, the ceremony is accelerating.
When you allow there to be no difference
between your symbols and the life, it
will all accelerate at the same pace.
Okay. All right. What can can you say
anything about the Native American?
There seems like there's a lot of
spiritual it is simply that they have
not so much forgotten that they exist on
more than one level at the same time and
to them all those different levels are
real. So they can consciously move in
and out of them more easily than many of
the other societies upon our planet that
have forgotten that they can do so.
Thank you. Thank you. Nice.
Nice. Um, my friend Allan has cancer and
he's worried about it. Is there
something I can do to help him or
something he can do to help himself?
Since he created it, of course he can do
anything he wants to with it. Mhm. What
does he want to do with it? Well, he'd
like to get rid of it.
What is it
serving? What is he being forced to look
at at this time because of the creation
of this idea?
I don't know. Then you will have to ask.
Ask him how it serves him. What he is
forcing himself to look at what is
coming up. What portions of himself he
has not seen before. Allow him to simply
know that the idea of the cancer is only
a symbol. It is a symbol to allow him to
know that he simply did not believe
there was any other way that he would be
able to look at these portions of
himself. So he created something that
forced him to. If he is willing to
accept what the symbol is showing him,
he can then choose another way for those
ideas to manifest and he does not have
to choose in your terms such a drastic
measure to force himself to look at
portions of himself he has been denying.
Will he will he in fact live after that
is up to him completely. There is no way
to predict such an idea. It is up to the
individual every single moment.
You follow me? Yeah. We sense that his
energy could go either way. We sense
that there is a bit more of the momentum
that he can learn in your terms to
alleviate it. But it will depend again
upon his willingness to take it as
something that he can learn from and to
not wallow in victimhood or
self-pity but to learn to live, expend
and share and
reconnect. The ideas he has separated so
that the ideas symbolically of the cells
within his body can also reconnect and
not become part. continue.
continue.
What's hard for me to understand is that
he seems to be so full of life and so
excited about his work and so warm and
responsible for the people around him.
Yes. You are making a connection that he
is being punished. You are making a
connection and you are making the
assumption that this does not serve a
positive purpose. Well, how can a good
person like him get something so
terrible as that? Obviously by
definition he can. So take it as a sign
that what is happening is a
service. Treat it as such and you will
allow yourself to see how it is
such. Follow
me. Yes. No. Maybe.
Maybe. The idea is simple. Once again,
it is up to you to define what events
occur in your life. Every event is
fundamentally neutral. Uhhuh. If you
know that the being is a loving being
and is being of service in that way,
then recognize what is being created is
also an extension of that love, an
extension of that service. For it will
also serve others to get in touch with
portions of themselves such as you in
terms of dealing with what you normally
call your fear.
Recognize that because of the way you
have created your civilization, there
are many ideas that in your terms lay
deeply buried within you that it takes
situations like this to bring out
because you will not allow them to
happen more easily. Once you allow them
to happen more easily, then you do not
need such drastic
symbols. That is what you are learning.
Thank you. Yes.
Um, last week when I was here, one
moment. He can also avail himself of the many
He can also avail himself of the many
opportunities of individuals that will
allow him to get in touch with his
mentality, with his spirit, and in your
terms learn in your terms to
visualize himself into a reality that
does not contain the idea of cancer.
Okay? But he will still have to come to
terms with why it is there in terms of
allowing it to serve a purpose and then
allow those purposes to be served in
other ways. All right.
Would that same principle go for a
79year-old person who anyone age is not
a factor unless you choose to make it
so. Great. Thank continue.
Um last week you told me to
um think about or imagine the crystal
domes. Yes. And when I was
um
and who is within it,
right? Um when I did that this week, I went to
Um when I did that this week, I went to
um your planet at Kani and I was in a
crystal dome, guys. And was there anyone
with you? Yes, there was this the the
entity, this man. I still don't know his
name. We do not have names. Oh, well,
Bashar is not my name. It is a
convenience for you, and it is more of a
title than a name. Uhhuh. Well, in any
event, um I the the dome was like this. It was
um I the the dome was like this. It was
like a liquid crystal. case. Yeah. It
almost felt as if there was like the
membrane itself was also a liquid in a
sense. It is malleable,
formable, transmutable.
Then um a strange thing happened when I
was inside this crystal dome. Not
strange for the crystal. No, not strange
for the crystal, but strange for me. All
right. When I was inside this crystal
When I was inside this crystal
dome, there was like an instantaneous
shift over to a dome that was made of
like raw crystal rock.
Continue. And um I saw myself within
that raw crystal
dome also wearing a crystal headpiece.
Yay. And
And
um I it seemed like I was preparing for
some kind of dance performance or
something. Oh, in a sense a connection
to more of all that is. Very good. You
were in what we will refer to as the
primmaa which in this way is simply a
place in which to connect to all that is
and is left more in what you would call
a natural state.
Oh, so that was that was something on
your planet. Yes, it was. Oh, I was
wondering, you know, like in that what
you call a Prima, there was like wooden
seats that reminded me very much of a
church. They were they looked real
uncomfortable. And I you would think of
the idea as a chapel, but it is not. And
those seats are not there. That is
simply your projection because of the
association you made. I figured that's
what it was. It is a place for
connecting to more of all that is. And
hence you would make the association
that it is in your terms a church but it
is not really. Um and the crystal
headpiece was that just um an
interpretation of mine or
um in a
sense it is something that is
manifestable. Mhm.
Mhm.
It is an interpretation but it is also
real as you imagine it to be. In other
words, in those terms, the wooden chairs
as you imagine them also become real,
but they do not exist there without your
imagination. Right? The headpiece does
also not exist without your imagination,
but once you imagine it, it becomes
real. That is the idea behind the
primer. Okay.
Okay.
I have a sense. Do you understand that
there is an entire now we shall call it a
is an entire now we shall call it a
planet, but it is not in the strictest
sense in that way. There is an entire
planet that functions in this way, a
crystal world in which all of your
imagination is instantaneously
materialized. Many beings partake of
that experience.
Well, the reason I asked the question
about the crystal headpiece is I've seen
crystal headpieces in some of my
meditations before. It is also a
reference to the idea of what you call
Atlantis. Okay.
Okay.
Um, and I've also collected some large
crystal pieces and there's a sense that
the crystal headpiece has very large
crystals in them. So much so that for
for on this planet it would be very
heavy. I mean like too heavy to wear but
it's as if to some degree although again
that is in your terms an interpretation.
Okay. An exaggeration a sensing of the
power. Okay. Because what I sensed is it
at least I visualized them large. Nice.
But it's as if they didn't have that
kind of weight on my head, you know.
Okay. All right. Thank you. Oh, thank
you. Nice.
I'm interested in the difference between
uh old age and youth. Uh what is the
actual definition of old age? state of
mind, state of being. So, is it because
they're failing to learn the lessons and
they sort of slowing down and cogitating
on these things? Not so much. It is
simply more that you have an overall
mass conscious belief that as time
flows, you age in that way that you
think you become more
infeebled. It is only a
belief. It is a product of your beliefs
of limitation.
And how do we disconnect ourselves from
that belief? In this way, by simply
knowing that all is now. And by living
in the moment, you will no longer count
your
years. Then you will never know how old
you are. For you are eternal, and you
will simply have a life that is defined
by the purposes within it. And when you
are done, you will leave. Not because
you are infirm, simply because you are
done.
Thank you. Do you in general not count
your years on your planet? In general,
you do give it give us a birth. It is a
correlation. Okay. For you. Thank you.
Sure. Yes. Sure. Continue. Thank you.
We've chatted in the past about the
crystal skull known as the neutral
hedges skull. Nice. And
um reports from people who have studied
it indicate that it changes color and
clarity. Dice. And I'm wondering if this
is if it changes the color of the light
of light that is passing through it.
Yes. Is it is it light that's projected
from the bottom of the skull or light
that's entering the skull from all
angles and all angles and also it is in
your terms an atmospheric phenomena and
also an energy phenomena.
Okay. They and it is also a perceptual
phenomena. Does that mean that some people would
Does that mean that some people would
not perceive it while others would? Yes.
I see. Is there a
physiological change in the crystal that
occurs to to allow this color change?
case something that it is more of the idea of
something that it is more of the idea of
a densifying or the manifesting of other
dimensions to which it is
connected. So there is a densified
energy and opakeness. Okay. Okay. Now,
for the changes in color,
different frequencies,
that's clear, but I'm wondering what
kind of physiological measurable
physiological change takes place in the
crystal to allow this
um apparently some kind of a very
minute degree in the vibration of the
crystallin structure, the atomic
structure. Very minute shifts. You may
or may not be able to measure it in that
way simply because we don't have fine
enough tools to also because the shifts
take place within the crystal and not
necessarily do they always extend to the
outer surface. I see. Now, however,
magnetic fluctuations might be recorded
by you.
Okay. So, measuring the magnetic flux or
magnetic field around this skull would
Yes. Okay. Now, I haven't I haven't seen
this myself because I haven't actually
seen the
crystal. In your perception, are these
manifestations dramatic? Are they
extreme? Or are they just nuances of
color shift? They can be in your terms
extreme. Sometimes they can be subtle.
Uh-huh. Sometimes they can actually be what you
Sometimes they can actually be what you
would recognize and even in your terms
photographed to be substantial pictures.
Would you elaborate on that please?
Simply as I said you will find that you
are able to see images within the skull
of people, locations, things like that
and photograph them too. Yes, it has
been done. I see. And uh are the color
changes and clarity changes also
photographable? No. Yes, some of them.
Yeah. Uh let's see. There's also
phenomenon of um chimes
and again different frequencies,
different vibrations as they affect the
idea of your own clar audience for the
most part. Sometimes there will actually
be a physiological manifestation as well
again within the electromagnetic field.
Okay. We we normally trace our sound to
We we normally trace our sound to
vibrations in the air emanating from
some physical. Yes. So therefore the
idea of the new frequency of resonance
in the electromagnetic field around the
skull can create aberrations in the air
molecules to give off sound. Okay. Okay.
But if we were to actually if we were to
measure vibrations, physical vibration
of the skull during this um these sound
manifestations, we wouldn't necessarily
pick up vibrations as we know them in
sound emanating uh equipment.
In some cases, you could Okay. Although
again, our perception is that the
majority of them will be more
perceptible than electromagnetic
readings which then could tend to
confuse somebody who is meas who is
hearing. Yes. Okay.
because some of the readings do not
always correlate with the physiological
phenomena but only with the clar audient
phenomena. Yes. However, if someone had a a device
Yes. However, if someone had a a device
to measure the electromagnetic radiation
shifts, then they may be able to
correlate what they're hearing with a
physiological at times. Yes.
Although again the clar audience
phenomena does not always require an
electromagnetic or let us say a
perceivably electromagnetic shift.
Certainly it would just be a
transmission from another
dimension. Okay. Thank you. for you.
Yes. Um venue.
Um this last I guess it was Friday, we
were driving up to uh San Francisco and
south of Monterey on Highway 101, we saw
some craft that looked very much they
were like hovering as if they were a
helicopter copter but much too high to
be a helicopter. And I was wondering if
those were um UFOs.
Obviously by your definition they were
unidentified.
We assume you mean were they spacecraft?
Were they? Yes.
What color if any were the lights? Green
and red and white.
No. However,
in your extension of your
senses, there was connection to
energy. That is what gave you the
feedback that allowed you to project the
idea upon one of your own crowd. forward. Yeah.
Yes. Um Bashar, I have two questions.
One is that
um I've been aware at particularly at
night of waking up well waking up in the
morning with a great deal of my head
like vibrating very very quickly. But
also at the same time a like it's almost
like a band around particularly the back
of my head at the top of the spine. And
I've tried different kinds of
experiments to in a sense let that go,
including um having uh someone like
bounce my head around and move my head
around in the sense of just kind of
letting go of the energy. A lot of
different kinds of things in terms of of
what about channeling it?
I feel like I'm blocking it and I don't
know in a sense how to unblock it to Are
you doing what you want to do in life?
No, not necessarily. What do you want to
do that you are not doing?
Um, be able to ch channel my higher
self. Then do so.
Form the connection and you will not
feel the constraints.
How in your imagination do you imagine
you can be doing this? What services can
you be providing? What can you allow
yourself to learn that will give you the
opportunity to be comfortable in doing
so? Well, I've been trying to work
Well, I've been trying to work
what um working with dreams the dream
channel. All right. Um not judging
differences between All right. But how
can you apply in your physical life this
idea? How can you channel it through not
just back into yourself in a closed
loop?
I mean by projecting projecting the
dreams out.
What can you do to act them out? Yes.
Can you act one out right now?
Act out right now. That is what I said.
Um I can't think of anything. Oh, come
now.
Um you are among friends. Mhm.
I feel fear like a knot in my stomach.
So I blank. You're excited but you are
judging it. So is anxiety instead.
You feel the vibration of your path, the
vibration of your being. Excitement
resonating within you. But you judge it.
So it becomes fear.
But you are feeling it. Yes. So trust
that you are in touch with it. You are
in touch with your higher self.
For to have that energy to begin with,
you have to be. The fact that you choose
to judge it does not mean it is not
there. The fact that you have something
to judge means it is.
Yes. So trust that the connection is
there. Trust
it. Trust
it. From time to time, as often as you
wish, be a little silly.
All right. All right. Allow
yourself to look a little foolish
as long as you are having a good time.
All right. All right. Now, what else do
you wish to do? Oh,
in terms of the dreams, anything at all
in life that you feel you are not doing?
Um, that you are waiting to do instead
of doing I see. Why?
What is accessible to you now in terms
of making film that you can be acting
upon now that will then create an
acceleration to the rest of it.
What opportunities are open to you now
that are every bit just as equally valid
a part of film making as anything well
well one of the things I'm doing is
actually you know I am taking actions on
my dreams and intuitions that I have um
as quickly as they occur as opposed to
waiting, planning, scripting, writing,
um you know going through the the
process of film film making which seems
very long then you do not enjoy film
making I don't enjoy waiting do you enjoy film
I don't enjoy waiting do you enjoy film
making? Yes. Is scripting not a part of
film making? Yes. Why do you not enjoy
it?
It seems to take a long time. That is
because you do not enjoy
it. You are considering it is not a part
of film making. You think you are not
film making but you
making but you
are. If that is a part of film making
then writing a script is film making. So
you are doing it in whatever way at this
point it is open for you to do. When you
begin to trust that you are doing it
that is what will allow the rest of it
to fall into place. You are the one
that's holding it back by assuming that
what you are doing is not part of film
making. So how can you get the rest of
it if you are disconnecting what you are
doing from
it and creating yourself to be an
island?
Well, does that make some sense? It
makes some sense. It seems that I am
taking a lot of actions but not um
there I have again some frustration
about a sense of a sense again that is
judgment. All frustration is judgment.
You are assuming that what you are doing
is not something that is a part of what
you want to do.
You are assuming that what is available
to you to do is not what is going to get
you where you want to be when it is
where you want to be all the
time. You are putting expectations and
judgments on the different portions of
the film making and not considering them
to be a part of the
whole. So the rest of the whole is not
there.
Does that clarify to some degree? Yes.
Have you
communicated with all the individuals
that you can communicate with that if
you were in your estimation truly making
a film, you would automatically go ahead
and be in contact with? Or are you
waiting until it is more real?
Or are you acting as if you truly are
making a film?
Or are you acting as if you are waiting
to make a film? I got it. Thank you.
That makes all the difference in the
reality. Yeah. And each is its own
definition and therefore each is its own
reality. I see it is that simple.
Thank you. I got it. Dice.
Um I don't find the
u I don't know how to
say I I seem to go back and forth on the
same idea for months now and I just
don't get out of it. It is not the same
idea. You are never the same person. You
are never looking at it exactly from the
same point of view. You're only making
an assumption that you are repeating but
you can never repeat. You are always a
new you. Allow yourself the
understanding that many times an
individual in becoming all the new you
they become may choose a similar idea
and look at it from many different
points of view so they can integrate the
entire idea. But you are not repeating
idea. But you are not repeating
anything.
It is only that the idea is you are
judging that makes it seem as if you are
repeating. So you do not pay attention
to the new things you are getting out of
the new perspective.
because you think it is the same old
thing. So you don't pay attention.
Yes, there are differences. They may be
in your terms subtle. They may not be
subtle. But you will never let them be
anything more than remote if you
continue to assume it is the same event
all over again, which it never is. And
what would create the impatience to
like finally integrate the whole thing?
You don't want to hear by
the idea of impatience comes from the
need for
patience. If you are enjoying living in
the moment, you do not need
patience. Patience is the assumption
that what you are doing now is not as
good as something that's going to come
next. So you are focused on the future and not
So you are focused on the future and not
on the present. And that is the only
reason you need patience. And that is
the only reason you have impatience
because you are not enjoying what you
are doing now because you are judging
that you're doing the same thing all
over again. And it is not the same
thing. Well, it's just you know ideas. I
understand what you mean. Ideas are
reality, right?
It's just it just open up your
imagination as you have already begun to
do by doing things that are in your
terms new to you.
This will then create new perspectives
within you that will give you a new
background to look at the situation when
it occurs again and you will understand
that from your new perspective in the
new being you have created yourself to
be the situation is not occurring again.
You will see it as a new situation
because you will now be more recognizing
yourself as a new you because you have
been willing to extend yourself in
things that you have never done before
such as your martial art.
You follow me? I do. It will give you
new insights and then the situations
will not seem like the same old ones
because you will be a new consciousness
looking at it for the first time.
Yes. Oh, thank you.
Oh, thank you.
Um, but how about this somewhat
analogous situation you're describing
there? What happens if you find yourself
talking to a person
who you find boring? You have a
preference to be somewhere else. That
can be described in many ways. The
person's uh speed of particle flow,
level of acceleration is not something
that the term boring is a judgment. I
understand the recognition that what
they are sharing may not be indicative
of the reality you prefer does not mean
you cannot learn something from it and
be fascinated. Right? And so what I'm
trying to grasp better is the difference
between having a preference. Yes. In
other words, if if I find myself in a
situation and I decide that I prefer to
be someplace else, what's wrong with
that? or how does that compare with
being in a situ in other words if I'm
pref what's the difference between
preferring a different situation and
finding the present situation boring in
this way the difference is in
recognizing first of all that if you are
not invalidating what you do not prefer you
invalidating what you do not prefer you
will not find it boring the idea of a
preference is to simply recognize that
there may be things that are going on
that you would wish to do and you can in
your integrity, in your openness, in
your honesty of communication. Simply
let the other person know
that and simply then be on your way
without in your terms finding that what
they had to say was not a help to you,
was not fascinating to you for some
reason, was not something you could
learn from. You can say I thank you for
the fascinating sharing that the idea
you are expressing in this way allows me
more recognition of what I prefer. So at
this time I will be on my way.
So it's I understand that. So it's
possible to have a preference. You're
saying prefer what you prefer. Yes. And
don't in addition to that judge what it
is that you're not preferring. Correct.
But clearly you have decided that you
prefer it less than something else. I
mean not less just different.
Well, is preference not a com something
which has amount attached to it. I
prefer this more than that. No, it is
simply a state of being. It is only a
definition of who and what you offer.
Well, at a at the at now at this moment
in of now whenever we're discussing
I will have a state of being which is
defined in many ways. One of which is a
preference to be engaged in an activity.
Yes. Now when you find simply that your
reality no longer contains that
preference, you will not be engaged in
that activity automatically. That is the
other planet we want. One moment. Sorry.
That is the other plank. And do not be
sorry. There's no need for it. The idea
is simply again look at it
synchronistically. If you are a
particular idea, you cannot
attract someone that will in your terms
have something to say that you can't
learn from, that does not fit in with
something you want to
know. You will only attract those that
you will recognize the reflection
within. I I agree with you. We've we've
shared that idea often and nevertheless
I am there is no nevertheless. If you
find that you are engaging with someone
you find boring in your terms then you
are attracting someone to show you that
on that level you are still
judging and that is the reality you are
defining yourself to be otherwise you
could not attract them.
Okay. Is a definition of preference that
which you are experiencing
in a sense? Yes. So whereas on this
planet we we tend to say well let's see
I'm sitting here talking to somebody
who's boring and I'm preferring
something else. But in that in in a way
that's kind of a misconstruction of
what's really occurring in that you are
preferring talking to the boring person
again. Yes. But paradoxically once again
the acceptance of the situation as it is
happening negates the need for that
situation to continue or occur again.
True. So if you have faith as soon as
you become fascinated by what a boring
person is saying, it is no longer
boring and you go on your way. You learn
something from it and never again will
you encounter a person that is boring.
dwell not with dissatisfaction on the
way things are. Ace. Yes. But we on this
planet. You said that if it were true.
What do you mean? But we on this planet.
Is that some sort of a foundation that
is supposed to explain something? No.
No. I I you let me back up. You're
right. You said that if you prefer
You said that if you prefer
if you're clear about what you prefer
that that will be the experience that
you're experiencing. The idea is this.
If you are engaged with someone and you
find yourself judging that they are
boring. Then recognize within yourself,
well, wait a minute. Obviously, I am
co-creating this. I attracted it.
Therefore, for some reason, it must be
what I preferred.
How is it that I preferred this? You
see, automatically you are absorbed in a
fascinating dichotomy within yourself
and perhaps you do not even hear what
the person is saying
anymore. And then you will get something
out of it and automatically the boring
situation will not be
boring and before you know it, it will
be
over. I understand that. I'm still
fascinated by the
the experience it is all a paradox and
all you are doing is delineating a very
fine line of one particular paradoxical
case. The idea once again is that when
you are in the middle of a situation you
find you do not prefer it. The idea is
to recognize that it is serving you by
letting you recognize that in that way
and the second you recognize that the
situation will conform to what you
prefer.
automatically but there is a span of
time in which that process is evolving.
Oh, are you so impatient you cannot wait
a few seconds? No, I No, no, you
misunderstand the intent behind my
Right. Clarify. I am observing merely
observing without judging that in the
process that you
describe, you're describing a manner in
which to approach a circumstance that
many people on this planet perhaps find
themselves in. I wonder if people on
your planet ever find themselves in a
situation and therefore need to go
through the process in time that you
just described. Every situation we find
ourselves within, we assume is supposed
to be there. So we enjoy going through
it. So boredom is not an experience that
people on your planet experience. No.
Never. We are far too fascinated by why
everything is happening.
[Music]
Interesting. Thank you.
Yes. Thank you.
Do people on your planet get suntans?
Not really. Okay. The reason I'm asking
this question is there seems to be a lot
of attention at least in the media
regarding the danger. I will use these
terms. Yes, that the sun uh presents to
us in getting sunburn with with regard
to skin cancer and other you know immune
system deficiencies. Since the idea of
what you call your environment, your
atmosphere, your weather is the product
of your mass conscious emotionality, let
that be your guide.
If you feel so raw and exposed, it is no
wonder. In this way, we are always
nurtured by our environment. Therefore,
never harmed. Does that mean to say if
someone in your society goes out in the
sun, they will not have some kind of
effect as you know as a result of the
radiation from your the only effect will
be the energizing that is the result.
Okay. There will be nothing negative.
Okay. Now,
um it seems to me that there's something
significant to this fact that we've
chosen to allow our
sun well this create the idea that our
sun is damaging to our bodies. Can you
elaborate on that? Can you
Well, to me it ties into this entire
cycle that we've been experiencing for
the last 15,000 years. Yes. Is it
something that we are seeing an end to
and therefore we're putting attention on
the phenomenon that we have created to
some degree it is also a symbolic
representation to some degree of the
idea of how shall I put it I don't know being
of how shall I put it I don't know being
burned by your brightness
okay well it's not simply the fact of
sunburn it's the
resultant cancer and immune suppression
Take it all symbolically. Okay. Not
being able to withstand your own power.
Okay. Judging it.
All right. Well, there seems to be this
mass conscious agreement that this is the
conscious agreement that this is the
case. However, I particularly would like
to be able to be out in the sun without
contracting some kind of then create and
open a conduit and a relationship to it.
be connected in that way to all of
nature and allow your naturehood to
create the type of atmospheric bubble
that will only channel the energy in
positive ways.
Okay. The approach there would be to use
my imagination that is and your trust
and your love. Well, it takes a lot of
trust to if you say so.
Okay. Trust does not come in quantities.
It is there or it is not.
quite well
taken. The reality that we that I and
people that I associate with find
ourselves in is that we are bombarded by
the media saying, "Well, you'll get
cancer if you get sunburned too much,
etc., etc." Reflections are all around
you. Uhhuh. Choose which ones you
prefer. But the reflection seems to say you're
But the reflection seems to say you're
going to get cancer if you get sun.
Reflections are all around you. Choose
which ones you prefer. Why don't you
elaborate on that for me? If you are
able to see such a reflection in your
society and create within your
imagination that that reflection does
not have to be true to you, choose which
one you wish to listen to.
In other words, just by seeing seeing it
as a a reflection in your society that
you think is negative is an opportunity
to choose the one in you that you
prefer. Yeah.
Just because it is all around you does
not mean you have to believe it.
Yeah. All right then. Yeah. It is that simple.
All right then. Yeah. It is that simple.
Yeah. Then it comes back to it. It comes
back to nothing. It is that simple.
Well, I create the idea that it comes
back to to this choice. Yes. that we've
had before about how we
can create a
belief other than what the mass
consciousness believes and therefore
apparently go against apparently I say
go against simply stand out. Yeah.
Shy. [Music]
Okay. Thank you. Thank you Sammy.
I used to be
Zen for sure. You Thank you.
In a recent private channeling, I was
given the names of two people that I was
to meet. One was a space brother and one
was on the earth plane. I've easily
tracked down the person on the earth and
I'm I had this meeting set up for Sunday
evening. Nice. And is there anything
that I can do to make the most of this
experience? Should I go by myself? My
work is completed here now. What do you
feel? Well, I feel I should go by
myself. Then trust your instincts. That
is how to make the most of any
experience. And will I be able to
communicate um in the way that you
communicate through this channel?
Do you think you would enjoy that?
I feel blocked sir at the moment.
Let me know when you think you would
enjoy it. I would enjoy it. I would
enjoy it right now. Then you are not
blocked.
Okay. Do you have any suggestions as to
how I could um
um make the most of this? The most?
How do you imagine it will occur?
I do not know. If it were to, how do you
imagine it would? Telepathically.
Describe the scenario.
What do you do then? What happens?
Put myself in a receptive frame of mind.
Yes. Then what? Um clear myself to put
my personality aside. All right. Then
what? And then um trust. Is that all
there is to it? I think so. As easy as
all that? Well, well, well, you'll have
no problem.
Mhm. Do you believe it is that easy?
Yes, I do. Well, then why are you asking
me these questions? because so far I
haven't been able
to to channel. Then allow yourself to
recognize first of all that you are
always channeling whatever you need to
be channeling whatever you are
comfortable with and also whatever fits
the timing that is best for all
concerned. You are not alone in this.
You know, therefore, the rate at which you
know, therefore, the rate at which you
allow yourself to be comfortable with
the idea will be the rate that is
comfortable for everyone you are
connected with that will in your terms
benefit also from your service. Mhm. And
could the service continue in the area
that I've been working in a direct
children's theater? Why
not? Why do you think any idea that
attaches itself to you in that way would
not be able to participate in what you
have defined yourself to be? What
purpose will that serve?
Well, my my work so far has come to an
end in the next three days. It's
finished. And it is never finished.
It only
transforms. Maybe that is something you can allow
Maybe that is something you can allow
yourself to recognize and allow the idea
to be easier. Everything only
transforms. It does not
end. Everything you are doing now in a
sense is the same energy of everything
you have ever done. It only
changes its definition.
You follow me? Yes, I do.
Does that assist you? It does. Thank you
very much. Briefly,
Briefly,
I wanted to explore the idea that you
said at the beginning of the imagination
being able to bring anything that's in
your imagination into physical reality.
That idea is compared to you can have
anything you want. In this way, it is
not so much perhaps in your terms the
confusion that dichotomy is that in
thinking you must bring something from
your imagination into physical reality
rather than simply allowing yourself to
exist in your imagination.
Can I give an example that? Of course.
Um, okay. I I get excited about the idea
of winning contests. Yes. And excited
about the idea of winning a lot of money
in contests. Yes. For two reasons. One
is because I have a lot of projects that
I'd like to fund, but also because of
this whatever contests mean to me. You
may or may not be missing the point, but
go on. Okay, so the idea simply is this.
When you are excited and all consumed
simply by the idea of winning contests,
you will win contests if that is the
total reality.
When you make an attachment that you
need to do so for something else that
you are actually more excited about,
then the energy does not go to what you
are really excited about.
[Laughter] So is there no reality? Like I have a
So is there no reality? Like I have a
dichotomy
between wanting money. I also want the
projects, but I also want the money. I
Why do you want the money
to do the projects? Yes. And because I
haven't allowed myself yet to you to
experience that vehicle. So what? So I
have the desire to. All right. But
recognize in your so-called process to
experience it. Again, it will depend
upon where you are actually putting the
most energy and if the projects are
actually
I I have explored that route and I still
find myself being drawn back to that
other desire. All right, then perhaps
you will become very excited about
making money. But if you do, do not
expect yourself to be able necessarily.
Not saying that you can't, but do not
expect yourself to be able to use that
money for the projects. Because the idea
you are putting all the excitement
behind is simply having money. And if
having money is what excites you, you
won't be able to use the money. You will
only continue to have it.
So then you're saying if I want to use
it for the project, that's a whole
separate I have to hold a separate.
The idea is to do and act upon where the
highest level of energy and excitement
is
and not to connect things that do not
necessarily need to be connected to get
from here to there to there to there.
Each is its own separate equal
experiential idea.
Recognize therefore that is why there
have been certain individuals in your
society who have been excited about
nothing as so much as simply having
money. They had all the money they
wanted and in your terms died poorer
because they did not do anything with
it. They simply hoarded
it. They never knew how to do anything
with it because having the money was all
that ever excited them. So they had it
and they died not using it. If I have
both ideas, it feels to me like I have
both ideas. All right. And you can again
all I am saying is that you can do
whatever you want. Do not necessarily
expect that one will connect to
another. You follow me? They may, but
they may not. You may have the money and
you may have the projects and the money
may not fund the project.
Something else might or money from
somewhere else might. It may be kept
separate. It may not.
Even if the excitement is the excitement
to me is getting the money and funding
the project. I understand what you are
saying as a single idea. But recognize
that you are also dealing with the idea
of what your beliefs actually are within
the mass consciousness. And all I am
saying is that it is not that you cannot
have that as one idea. But simply
recognize that if it does not occur that
way, then the stronger beliefs within
you are the ones that are contained
within the mass consciousness that these
things are in that way two separate
ideas. And the energy directed to each
of them is its own separate energy. Not
that you cannot have the idea of making
the money and using the money to do the
project if that is what excites you. It
is simply up to you to determine whether
or not that actually is one idea within
your belief systems or two.
You will find out obviously. Mhm. So you
can just like want to have a lot of
money just to spend it.
[Music] You can want to have a lot of money. You
You can want to have a lot of money. You
can want to spend a lot of money.
That can be two ideas as well for
recognize that spending money is not
having money.
And what you call millionaires many
times are millionaires because of the
amount of cash flowing,
not staying.
Right? [Music]
[Music]
You may all take a short break
and upon
recommencement there will
be not only for you
Steve but also for many of you in this
way an ancient message. Yes.
All right, I'll
say. Are you all gathered? Yes.
Then allow me in this way to begin
facilitation for
another one
moment. As I have been instructed to do,
I will send you greetings.
Greetings. Greetings. Greetings.
Allow first of
all for there to
be the
indication that the
perception of what I have just
experienced is something that is strange
for me and I am not entirely
sure that what I have been told is
occurring is in fact
occurring. But in this way I find
that though it seems I am speaking to
the one I must
trust in who I have
met who has referred to himself as the
commander that such an interaction is
going on.
Therefore, I will assume that I am
speaking, that you are hearing,
hearing,
receiving you for me is subtle. I was
told by the self-same individual the
commander that it would be yet it is in
this way not something still that
is
more than enough to be in your terms
sure that the idea of the interaction is
taking place yet again I will place my
trust as I have been told to
do and assume that the message is
getting
through. I have been told therefore
things which again are strange to me.
Yet I have chosen to be party to this
idea. Therefore, I must assume again
Therefore, I must assume again
reliability upon the information I have
received in that the information does
come from what I have come to recognize
as a source in that way inexplicable
within the system with which I am
familiar. And in this way, the being
does represent, as he says, the idea of
something through time from a time
closer to, I will assume your own, the
beings that are supposed to be receiving
this
communication. In this way, I have been
told that I will be communicating to
those I have known, though I have been
told things I do not understand, such as
the like that those individuals, as you
call yourselves in this way, who I
assume to be receiving this
information, will then at this
time be not the individuals I have
known, as I have known them, nor are
you, as I have been told, supposed to
remember who you
are. Thus, in this way, even for you,
this contact, if it is indeed taking
place, without my feeling too
foolish, I will still assume that there
is some content within the conversations
you have been having with the commander
that perhaps will enlighten you to a
certain extent, perhaps even more than I
have been enlightened.
I will therefore simply make the
assumption once again the idea is
occurring as I have been told that it is
across what you would call the idea of
175,000 years of
time and I will assume as I have also
been told that the idea of this
communication though it be going on in
what I consider to be my present is
reaching 175,000 years ahead of time as I count
175,000 years ahead of time as I count
as you count I assume something similar
in that way and that the message is
being delivered and received not in my
present time since you are not there but
in a time when you are regardless of the
idea of where I should be now and where
you should be
now in this
way. Allow me then should this truly be
occurring for it brings me joy to think
that it might.
the idea that I send you the greetings
once again and the dearest wishes in the
hopes that your endeavor has been
successful as you have created it. For
in this way you will find that I have
been told you refer to the idea of where
I find myself and where I know you once
existed in your terminologies of
something I have been told to refer to
as Orion.
In this way, you will find that much has
transpired since your
leaving. And in this way, you will find
that only a few recognize that you have
left at this
time. Though again, not to be confusing,
I will assume that much time has passed
by your reckoning, and that there will
be many more individuals who will be
aware of what I am speaking of now,
though I find myself to be quite alone
in this understanding with all whom I
talk to.
The idea shall be in that
way. I have been told that there are
several among you in this way in your
society as you call yourselves whatever
society by whatever name at this time
who are now recognizing and remembering
the idea of connections to many places
here among
them. And in this way, what I used to
refer to as my
colleagues shall no longer be those that
even remember themselves. But I will
still entrust that you are the same
colleagues who left. And I will talk to
you as such, for that is the only way
surely that I can make sense of the
conversation. Therefore, once again to
begin without the preamble, I send you
greetings and you may in this way refer
to me by reckoning as
Naamon in this
sense. I am told that you would
understand in your present reckoning the
idea of what I am best by referring to
the idea something akin to priesthood.
Although I am told to clarify that this
is not literally the case in your terms,
but it will
do. I am told I may share with you the
idea of the sending of this information.
Now to express
that the idea of your leaving the Orion
systems, as you call it, will be
representative of your willingness to
continue the idea of reaching beyond
what you have recognized as a great deal
of suppression within the systems. And
in this way again I can only hope that
you are
successful that you have arrived where
you have deemed yourself to be. That
will do you the most good in the
completion of your journey wherever it
should be. Although once again though I
am not unfamiliar with the ideas that
are referred to by this commander as
afterlife. Some of the ideas again of
reincarnation that he has described to
me by that terminology are in terms I do
not understand nor am I familiar with.
But I will assume once again that you
have lived many lives by the time you
receive this message. And that in the
living of this many lives, you have in
some sense, according to the
understanding I have, worked through the
ideas that you attempted to work through
by relocating
yourselves to a point at least enough to
receive this communication. Should this
communication be any measure of anything
at all, I am not certain, but perhaps it
will make more sense to you. I have
simply been told in this way that in the
position I shared with you all at that
time, it will have some bearing on the
idea of forming connections for
yourself. And so I willingly grant in my
hopes, in my desires for your
success, that what small part I may play
may reach you across the span of ages
and bolster and support your cause. For in
bolster and support your cause. For in
this way many of you again were
colleagues either that I have known as
contemporaries or in this way the idea
of individuals who are known to
me what I have been instructed to share
at this
time and there seems to be that there
are certain individuals to whom this may
or may not relegate more sense but to
all of you it does apply all who are
supposedly present and listening to this
communication that there is within the
idea of what you are referring to as the
Orion systems and the idea of the
presence of what will
be. I am told your recognition of
creation now from our point of view to
remind you of your heritage what is
referred to as three primes. I have been
told that in your vernacular it will
translate into the terms Shadrach,
Mishak, Abednego. In this way, it will represent
Abednego. In this way, it will represent
to you something that is referred to as
sorcery. In this sense, it is recognized in this
In this sense, it is recognized in this
way as simply the action of the three
primes as the fundamental triad
consciousness, as we recognize all
symbols within the Orion system in that
way to be representative of our heritage
within this fundamental understanding of
what you would call religion.
In this sense, I have been told that you
have taken much of this baggage with
you, but you have applied it in ways
that are more in reference to the system
you now find yourselves within. And so
it has not been understood for what it
was. The actual interaction of your
mentality, personality, consciousness
upon the primal energy in this way,
exemplified in what the commander has
termed an archetypal energy flow of your
subconscious stream.
The idea therefore simply being, if I
may assume that I am simplifying
anything since this and some of the
terminology again is outside of my
experience, that the
idea of the
formation of what you call polarities
within yourself, positive, negative,
when blended into a third persona that
is neither and both, all three together
will form the interaction in mentality
that will actually create an effect in
the electromagnetic field of the planet
in which you now
reside. And in this way, this
effect I am told in what you refer to as
your history will have been referred to
as magic.
This is simply again I am told to relate
the idea of the interaction of your
mentality individually with the primal
field of mentality that represents the
idea of your entire
civilization. It is a
personification of the mass
consciousness through an
individual. I am told to repeat this.
Magic is the personification of the mass
consciousness through an
individual. In this way, you will find
therefore that each individual by
blending the polarities and becoming the
third identity becomes a reservoir and a
wealth of all that is possible within
any particular system or universal
tangent that you find yourself. Now
Now
I in my priestly endeavors have sought
to have some measure of understanding of
these ideas within our systems, our home
systems. I understand the idea that you
have reached
out to form scenarios that will allow
you the recognition of not necessarily
needing the suppression this time to go
along with the utilization of these
abilities. In this way, therefore, you
have removed yourself from a universal
time track system. And this removal has
allowed you to experience the pure
nature of this interaction without the
idea of the burden of the mass
consciousness of domination and
suppression that has been within our
systems for so
long. Again, I can only
assume that what I am perceiving in
terms of the idea that you are hearing
any of this is real, even though it is
most subtle within my imagination.
But once again I must rely
upon the information from the commander
as he calls
himself. In this
way I am
instructed that I am to hold some sort
of paternal image for
you. Not that this is a calling that I
have asked for in that way, but simply
that I would treat you as the friends I
have known and in this way have formed
for you
simply through my love for you, my
willingness for your success, the idea
of an anchor for you in the home system.
So that again, this message as it is
being delivered is something that can be
allowed into your system as a reflection
to allow you to know that you are
forming the connections you need to be
forming. Again, I can only hope that
this has been of some service and that I
have played my part for you in this
way. I have been told that I may
continue to send from time to time these
interactions. I have been told that you
will receive them. And it is this
belief, it is this trust, and it is this
hope that you will that gives me even
the shred, the shred of
willingness to act in this
manner so unlike that of our
society. to assume in this way that
mentality can be bridged, can be linked
up in ways that are not in your
terms. The
property of the
mass that are not in this way privy to
our communication.
For there would be in this way, should I
even believe for a second, had I not
been patronized enough and convinced
enough by your so-called friend that
such was the case that I would fear for
my
life. But my love for you in this way
will transcend this to some extent. And
I must only trust that the idea of this
love is in and of itself a conduit that
in your terms is pure
enough to remove all doubt, to remove
all of what you would call
easedropping, and that there will be for
you a clearness of communication.
I am told therefore at this
time to simply extend to you my thoughts
and my wishes for your
well-being. And I am told
that I will in some
form have the opportunity to meet you
all again on some other stage. I will
take this to
heart as I bid you my leave. Message received. Message received.
Yes. [Music]
[Music]
We thank you for the opportunity in this
way of the completion of a cycle and the
beginning of many new interactions and
doorways that shall be opening to allow
there to be the further acceleration. so
that you may blend the idea of the past
you are creating in the present with the
present and create again the future you
desire in the
now. We thank you for your
release. We thank you for your
willingness to allow there to be the
reflections in your life that you have
all chosen to place within you.
Sure. Sure. You
the connection
um went through many areas
um in this life
through Mach and
Abednego strangely enough at Disneyland
with the war gospel singers and then
earlier
through dozens of beingnesses of magic
and the connection ction
was the
cleanest that I have yet
experienced. Thank you. We thank you.
Sure. For sure. You how are you able to
be in communication with uh that
beingness? How do you communicate with
him? In much the same way that I
communicate with you, but in this way it
took a little more. There was the
allowance in this way of a physical
visit. You physically manifested beforehand.
You physically manifested beforehand.
Yes.
I see. Was that a surprise to him? Oh,
yes. Because it doesn't occur in his system.
Because it doesn't occur in his system.
Not so much. No. Uh-huh. He said that he
would fear for his life if as I
understood it, if anybody knew that what
he was doing, he would be
um he would be in jeopardy of his life.
Yes. Because however, that did not
occur. Good.
I found the experience fascinating and
wonderful. Aside from the message that
was delivered in the
reflection of how some of us have
uncertainty when we communicate with
others telepathically we're going gee
now I'm putting this in my imagination
and I'm trusting that it's happening but
geez I don't know if it's being received
and this experience was us being on the
opposite end of our communications when
we it was our imagination to transmit
fascinating reflection. Thank you for
the allowance of the co-creation.
Certainly. Sure. Sorry.
Men and female. Is that me over here?
Um, was the entity who spoke to
us connected to you in a similar way
that you and Daryl are connected?
A different way, a different route, a
different track altogether. Not an
earlier self, a past self, but not
exactly so much in the same way. Not
such a strong connection, more of a
generalized one. Thank you. Thank you.
Sure. Yes. Um, it sounded like the fact
that he was afraid for his life that he
was involved still in the old energy of
the dominant
that we all came away from. Yes. He is
in your
terms still there. He's still there in
terms of 175,000 years ago from whence
the message came. Not now. Is he still
there? But from whence the message came,
he is still there. Right. So what we are
doing then is the the transformation
from that type of energy. Yes. Does he
understand what we're doing? Not
clearly. But his wishes are with you.
And in this way, what you have done has
made a
difference back there.
Right? And in this way, at this time,
that individual in the life in which
that individual lives now back
there is part and parcel of a dramatic
change within those systems. For there
is now, as there was not then, life in
those systems. Mhm. Which planet will it
come from? In this way, you will find it
will be the general idea of the Orion
systems, not particular planet. In that
way, for there will have been travel
from planet to planet.
I have a a planet. There was in this sense a
sense a
transliteration at the time the message
was delivered for there to be the origin
point of the message from a planet
within the systems that would translate
into your vibrations as kova.
Ha. What is the relation of huba to
mimak? [Music]
[Music]
In this way you will find out Maka will
be the star close to which was the
idea of the dark crystal moon that was
utilized by the
resistance to the suppression.
And did we come from Naka?
Many are from the resistance and strong
connections abound. Bashar.
Bashar.
Will that have served you? Yes. Thank
you. Yes. One moment. The individual was
there then, has left in the intervening
175,000 years. As I have said, the
individual is now in a new life still
within the system and is partaking of
the interactions of beings that are now
within light within those systems.
[Music] So he did not leave as we do.
So he did not leave as we do.
No, he stayed to form an anchor and a
foundation in many lives paralleling
your own so that there would be someone
to receive the communication that you
had learned that you are sending back
there so that there can be growth
paralleling your growth within the Orion
systems. Got it. Michelle, what did he
mean? One moment for you. Yes. Um, I'm
very excited about this because my
little girl has been singing a song in
another language that has the words
Mishak. Um, in
ways and
[Music] and uh and she's been collecting rocks
and uh and she's been collecting rocks
and just changing all over the place.
And I personally um channeled a picture
that has a triad at the top. Okay. And
there are three small circles that go
from the top to the bottom. There is a
circle at the bottom with a star in the
middle. Um I'm supposed to be standing
on the
star. There is a um below this circle
with a star on it, there is a like a
zigzag semiircle. And I finally got a little
semiircle. And I finally got a little
bit of what this is about. But I'm
wondering if you could shed some more
light because I feel like there's still
more. What did you get? There is much
more but what did you get? Um what I got
was well actually the communication that
occurred tonight. Um, also what I got
originally with what what he brought up
with the
[Music] um with the individual
um with the individual
[Music]
um on on this on this kind of force or
on this plane actually changing things
in kind of a metaphysical manner. not
like in a physical universe but like
through you know his like a mass
realization you know and that's what he
brought up too I mean that I did get
that all right um there are many other
connections that you can share with many
individuals that you are surrounded with
this night of your time when you have
the opportunity interact update yourself
and we will discuss this at another time
okay thank you for what's density was uh
were the individuals entertained 5,000
years ago in the Orion systems and what
density third and what density are they
in now again third transitional for so
they're actually parallel
yes what did he technically mean by lose
his life what's the technical
explanation for that technical well well
what's the what practical I should say
the idea simply that communic ification
outside of that which is recognized
within the mass consciousness of those
systems is not allowed and is punishable
by death. But death to what? His body.
Is that was that a great consequence
to him?
Can you can you practically describe
what you mean by no light within the
system? What what would how the idea of
systems suppressing its
populace? Governments of
Governments of
suppression. All interaction being that
which dominates and seeks only to
dominate others. Is that similar to our
communist system? No. What is different?
It is more akin to what you would call
fascism. There's more light in a fascist system
There's more light in a fascist system
than there is in a communist system.
Sure. Why? Well, fascism is
authoritarian. Communism is
totalitarian. In this way, recognize the
ideas are not so pat and there are many
versions of the idea of communism and
fascism. But simply in this way you will
find that the idea is that there is only
contained within the hierarchy that is set up the
within the hierarchy that is set up the
only authority that has any say of
anything within those systems. But how
is that different from a communist
system? For in this way you will find
that the idea is not even remotely there
of attempting to assume that working
together will achieve anything. The idea
is only that there are a few under which
all shall work only for their
gratification. You following? Well, I follow you, but I
You following? Well, I follow you, but I
see that the communist system is that
system. It just doesn't state that it's
not exactly and not entirely as you
understand it. Again, there is within
the individuals within the system the
belief that the idea of the way in which
they are working together whether it is
in your terms idealized or not is still
representative of the ideal that they
hold. May I offer a clarification? Yes.
Communism actually is an economic system
which uh is grounded in the idea of
communal support and working together.
Totalitarianism is a political system
which does relate to um one group or
person suppressing the others or
controlling the others beneath. So
communism that we experience isn't
exactly the total totalitarianism that
goes along with it in the Soviet Union,
but it has a worse record compared with
fascism. Well, yeah. In fact, uh what's
what the totalitarianism that we
experienced with in uh the Soviet
Union, communism gets a bad name because
of the totalitarianism that's going
along with it. It's not the communism
that's really um in other words, we are
simply in this way responding that the
primary definition as has been pointed
out of what you are referring to as
communism is not what is going on. say
our communism in this way. Again, there
are many forms of communism even upon
your planet.
But communism has such an atrocious
record as far as killing people and
controlling them. It's far far worse
than the fascist record. And what about
democracy? Uh democracy doesn't even come close to
Uh democracy doesn't even come close to
communism in the last 40 years. They
wiped out 40 or 50 million people.
Democracy has not done that. is in your
terms the death of 40 worse than the
death of one. Um
well I'm trying to clarify that. I don't
know. All right. I'm trying to see what
in this way it is much all the same. All
we are saying in your terms is that
without becoming confused in labels, the
idea we are defining of the majority of
the Orion systems is simply that the
individuals that are being suppressed do
not even have within them the belief
that they are being suppressed for any
particular reason that is going to
benefit them. I see. Okay. So I did the
slides. I shot. Hey Sure. Was he talking
as a since he was third
density and he was talking as a
priest? Was was he
uh conscious of what he was doing or was
he was he
dreaming? Conscious
again allow an assistant to be put into
a trlike state, a daydream state, but
still very aware of what was going on.
Okay. So he had somebody with him.
Yay. Me
I am to whom he was referring as the
commander. Oh, I know that. Yes, I
realize that. I didn't know that you
were there specifically at the time he was
there specifically at the time he was
transmitting the message. I thought you
had gone there and
then left and then he he transmitted the
message. I would not do that to him. No.
All right. Well, I'm sorry. I didn't do
not be sorry. Okay. And and now at this
time is he aware of what he did then?
Yes. Okay. Thank you. For sure. For
sure. Yes.
Yes.
Um would it be uh in danger
his current existence that parallels
ours right now for me to or anyone to
communicate with him at this time? No.
No problem. For he is within the light.
Very good. Thank you. And this is now an
opportunity that is open.
Thank you. Thank you.
Um yes, I would like to ask a few that
are probably fairly
uh Hey, Eve Quudge.
Okay, I won't. Uh the first one is I uh
well I perhaps you can clarify for me
um said if he's existing in present time
now why not the one in the form you
receive the communication from right
right but uh but I don't understand why
or how
uh where for what
peripa as there was a communication from
175,000 years ago. It is simply because
you are not connected to that series of
events as some other individuals are.
Okay. Okay. Like I said, it was probably
a naive question. Um and
um you know you know you know and
perhaps you could sort of explain or
just put a in some kind of
understandable framework for me why this
came through. Now I mean Now is the
timing for the recognition and the
opening of areas and doorways within
certain individuals. It is the receiving
of a message they had sent to themselves
so very long ago. I see. Thank you.
Yes. Can
you communicate with this being and
thank him and acknowledge that we did
receive his communication and have I
have told him that you did receive it
and that you were very grateful. But yet
again, it is his choice to doubt whether
or not you truly have gotten it. I would
like to communicate the gratitude and
understanding of the profoundity of his
love to agree to do what you said. I
have already done so. Thank you.
Um I did not have any conscious
recognition of this message, but I had a
sense that on other levels this was
really powerful. And I'm not certain how
would I know.
You simply have recognized it according
to whatever level you are functioning
within for now. As you have recognized
it, that is as far as you need to
recognize it for now. For we do not want
it to interfere in the path you have
chosen to be, nor stop you from doing
what you are more natural at doing.
Okay. Thank you. Sure. Peace. I am
excited by the idea of helping
responding to this being in the way that
he appealed to us. Just wanted to share
that with you. Like you again recognize
that the idea is that that being turned
out just fine.
Yep.
Your willingness to be who and what you
are and where and when you are has been
what has assisted him. And now he knows
that [Music] shar
shar
last week uh we chatted about my
relationship with the 10-year-old
youngster.
And when I saw her the next time after
speaking with you, there had been what I
perceived to be a dramatic
shift after my um understanding of our
relationship of the past had been
broadened. And uh it was quite uh I'll
say miraculous. All right. And quite
enjoyable. I haven't done the thing with
the gloves and the uh the lace
handkerchief yet, but it's all right.
That's to come. But it was a dramatic
shift and it was just quite obvious.
Thank you very much. Thank you for
making the shift within yourself so that
your reality could reflect it. You're
very welcome. Oh, thank you.
You're welcome.
I have a couple questions. Good. One uh
having to do with the prim. Hey, uh when
you were talking about that, I just got
an interesting thought about that and
using that as a tool to contact
intelligent infinity.
Hey, okay. Thank you. The other thing
was a few weeks ago um Leia mentioned
that our physicist um ran across some
discovery or some information some sort
having to do with the golden nebula
which shocked them I suppose or had had
them realize that their ideas about the
universe were really not exactly the way
the universe is. Can you elaborate on
that because I don't really understand
what she meant by that. Simply they are
beginning to discover that there is a
primal doorway let us say a grand primma around
doorway let us say a grand primma around
which the entire universe that you are
familiar with revolves.
Okay. And how how did they happen to
discover this? Were they monitoring
this? They were in your terms making
measurements and the readings surprised
them and they could only conclude
certain ideas from those readings and
those conclusions were unlike anything
they had ever expected.
Can you can you um elaborate on maybe
what one of those conclusions might have
been that they came to
that
they know nothing of what they thought
they knew?
What do they believe that they
discovered? They are not
They are not
sure. But it is something that allows
them to know that it is time once again
to rewrite all the equations. [Music]
[Music]
For it simply is not so much that they
know what it is they have discovered,
but they recognize that whatever it is
does not fit.
Okay. Where is what they discovered in
our old relational terms?
This in your terms is not clear, nor is
it clear to them. Though that may sound
funny to you, they have discovered
something and in a sense they do not
really know where it is.
But not in our galaxy. No, not in any
galaxy. But that all galaxies revolve around it.
But that all galaxies revolve around it.
all
galaxies. That is how big it is.
[Music] To some degree, guys. Is what they've
To some degree, guys. Is what they've
touched on will will what they've
touched on eventually lead in the
direction of their recognition of the
necessity of including the concept of
consciousness and mathematical
equations? It can. But is that the
doorway they've opened up? It is one
opportunity. It is a very strong
opportunity. I was trying to be more particular about
I was trying to be more particular about
that which they contacted. Is it It has
many probable applications because of
what it is being a doorway to the
infinite.
Whatever sense they choose to make of it
will be how they choose to recognize it.
But then then specifically what it was
was a doorway to infinite intelligence.
Yes. The one let us say the
valve to infinite intelligence and from
infinite intelligence that manifests
what you call your particular universe.
Got it.
Um, we had an experience a week and a
half ago where we went through a time
warp. And when this happened,
um, time basically stood still. Ace and
we we were explained afterwards
that the blue star Cachina was stalking
us
and we stalking it. In a sense that is
an analogy for the relationship you had
formed to the concept of the
universe which allowed you to experience
the idea of the sessation of time.
Your discovery of that portion or that
connection of yourself to your greater
infinite intelligence will always take
place in the twinkling of an eye. And
you are in that sense stalking yourself,
discovering yourself and allowing
yourself to be discovered by all that is
sure. Are you true? Well, this
particular um cacina has been explained
to us to be a cachina that
um only has appears very seldom but has
appeared before each of the world wars
and is now dancing in the plazas again.
It is a black cachina with a a thunder
symbol on it, lightning symbol and is
symbolizing our use of
power and that um we have choices at the
point that it dances in the plaza. Yes.
And there is also always the blue white
vagina which can be the polarity. It is
your choice.
That is the one that is related to it.
the name of it. There's the other one
that the is that the star chasing cach
star chasing cachina that's in
combination
why when they said that it is appears in
dreams and and other occurrences with
certain people it has something to do
with being um
um Harold Jace are we associated with it
as heralds
case hardening of the momentum of your mass
hardening of the momentum of your mass
consciousness, the directions in which
it flows, so that you can choose what
you prefer. Associate with what you
prefer. Associate with what you
will, that will be the reality and the
dimension that you will experience. For
the kacina energy also
specifically is the type of energy that
actually associates with you and you
associate with to actually
form actually form. The cacas in a sense
are the mechanism embodied in
consciousness that actually forms the
parallel universe after your choice.
They are lively beings. We enjoy them
very much. They represent a specific degree
much. They represent a specific degree
of quasi planar consciousness and our
civilization has yet to understand them
fully. But enjoy them we do.
They
are in a
sense, not to be
flippant, a very specific type of
extraterrestrial. A very specific type.
Thank you. Thank you.
Allow yourselves to
yourselves to
be thunder dreamers
and follow the star
follow the star
Sirius in your
chasing. All right. There's a
suggestion. Use it as you will. Thank
you. Stay away.
Stay away.
Um, I recently had an ex experience of
of uh of what I would feel to be
channeling. I it's never come about in
my life before and I I was wondering if
that was uh my self or or was
that someone trying to come through me?
I I I didn't allow it to. I I felt I
didn't want to be simply this. Nothing
happens without your agreement. First of
all, remember
that. Secondly, it will always only
happen at a rate you are comfortable
with. Otherwise, it would serve no
purpose. You follow me?
Therefore, recognize it is both a
portion of your consciousness and other
consciousness, but it is all
one. And in this way be comfortable with
it on whatever level you choose to be
comfortable with it. You always are
channeling yourself anyway. Be
comfortable with that. Do what excites
you. Be of service, live and love. And
that will
all go into all that is necessary for
you to channel how and what you need to
channel. You do not even have to make it a
You do not even have to make it a
channeling scenario, but simply life
itself is channeling.
Okay? Relax within
Relax within
yourself. Love yourself for who and what
you are and the way you are. And then
however you choose to be will also be
all right.
All that you can possibly
discover within your fear is more of
yourself to love.
All right. Thank you very much for your
willingness to share. For that
willingness already has made a
difference and opened the door. Pleasant
dreams. Yes. Um this is my first visit with you
Yes. Um this is my first visit with you
and I don't really know exactly what I'm
looking for except a little inner peace.
a little in
just a little. All right, time's up.
Um I've had quite an experience um this
past week um while I was away on
vacation. I came back and found out that
my brother was on a vacation himself.
Oh, right. And went river rafting and
fell into the river and he hasn't been
seen or heard of since. Um I don't
necessarily want to accept the fact
that he may be gone away from me
anymore. No matter what definition, no matter
No matter what definition, no matter
what transformation from his but from
his um
um
personal, you know, why not? Um maybe
it's a little selfishness that I really
do want to be able to communicate with
him. You can,
but on the same level as we've always
been be been able to communicate.
How and what level is that?
I I don't know. Just I really May I ask
you a question? Yes. In your terms, am I
being too hard on you? No. I just
um I just really don't know which way to
confront this because I feel like I'm
going through a lot of sorrow right now.
Yeah. It's releasing. Yeah. And um it is
not that you need a confrontation but
the allowance of the release.
Yeah. Exactly. Well, I have I have been
releasing from I think the reason why I
don't want to release is because I feel
as though when I release
um I'm
feeling that maybe
he's that he's already gone from me in a
physical God I don't even know how to
explain. All right, we understand. In
this way, may I ask you another
question? Yeah. Can you allow within
your imagination yourself to
perceive that
that
non-physicality on his part might be the
fulfillment of the agreement you have
with him?
Quite possibly so that what it is you
now wish to communicate about can be
communicated from him to you.
But I don't even know if he is. I feel
like I'm just floating. I don't know if
for some reason he has, you know,
drowned, you know, if he if he is
drowning or has drowned, if he went
through any kind of pain. I mean, I
don't know if if
What is your time frame for what you
call the disappearance? It has been
since last Saturday, which has been a
week and a half.
Then give it 1 and 1/2 weeks more.
Okay. And so so I still stay in the same
frame for a week and a half more. That
frame, that limbo
state is what will disconnect you from
certain realities and allow you to
connect up to other realities later.
What you are experiencing now is
necessary so that you will have the
opportunity to experience forms of
communication you had not allowed
yourself to experience previously.
Love all that you are and love all that
he
is. All that he
is. All that he is.
All that he
is is is is
okay.
I understand. May I tell you something
else? Yes.
We love you very
much and you are loved very much. Thank you.
Allow that love to become tangible. Mold
tangible. Mold
it. Use it. Breathe
it. Create with
it. Expand with
it. Give
it. Send it out. Extend
it. and receive
it in whatever way it
comes. You also have an opportunity to
some degree because this is not primarily our
degree because this is not primarily our
place nor our
purpose. But you have an opportunity to
some degree to
discuss with either what you would call
another entity or another individual
upon your planet according to their
sensitivities about the
situation. What you need to
know. You will find them if you haven't
already within the next few days.
All right. All right. There may be
recommendations. Trust your
instincts. Trust your
instincts. Feel upon hearing
recommendations of perhaps who to
acquire information
from. Feel the vibration of your brother
and apply your understanding and your
intuition and your instincts of which
one your brother would choose.
All right. All right.
And trust that that reliance is actually
trust that that reliance is actually
communicationally.
All right. All right. Thank you. Thank
you.
You have danced this dance many times
before.
If I have, it's never been to
this as fast the song.
This is the transformational life. The
temple is accelerated.
But you have done it before together
many times.
Such is the extent of your trust and
your love that you truly have no fear of
any outcome.
There will also be the discovery of
connections to consciousness that abides
in water.
For sure. Yes. trace or reflect with me
the experience with the word gospel
singers at the uh Disneyland the the
phrase uh the Lord come down and he say
no Mach Shadrach and
Abednego this there's a a point of
integration there where many factors
came together where did they pick up
that uh that what was the historical
origin of that phrase connected to that
crew. Again, in this way, a strong
exemplification of the remembrance,
although only subconsciously, of Orion
understandings, Orion connections in
what you call your Middle East.
Okay, I see the connection now. We got a
black group there reflect doing a
reflection on that energy in a sense.
Yes. Uhhuh.
But it is in your terms very ancient.
Good. Where did they pick it up
biblically? What's the biblical trace
line that came through this
culture on that phrase? The Lord come
down. Let me see. Again, simply
connections to some degree with the
original Orion energy. In that way, a
direct connection and a recognition in
whatever way was
translatable recognizing this way there
is even within what you
call the
idea commandments some Orion influence. Of
commandments some Orion influence. Of
course, for no idea of all that is in a
positive manifestation ever translates
out to thou shalt not.
Thus, it was the introduction of an idea
so that there would be dichotomy in the
idea that was presented.
Thank you. I'm picking pick up all the
reflections. Thank you. Thank you.
you. Um I have a question about um
computers. Um I've been a computer programmer for a
Um I've been a computer programmer for a
couple years and I've not been
um I didn't choose computers to go into
it because I loved it. I chose it
because it would provide me with um
security. Do you love security?
Um, no, but it was a value of my parents and
no, but it was a value of my parents and
I was a necessity. Who are you now and
what are your values? Um, and what do
you love? What I love now is my dreaming
and my writing. Yes. And your own
computing. Yes, my own computer. What
I'm curious about
is what the reflection of the
computers whether they should be
incorporated into my life. They can be.
It is up to you. They are reflections to
us of a symbolic embodiment of
communication with your higher
consciousness in a form you will allow
to be real.
So in other words, the
multiaceting of it. Yes. And when
literally you develop the idea as we
have said of artificial intelligence,
you will find you are talking to
yourself as we discover.
Um that brings up another issue.
Um the
um there's another entity Lazarus and
the group that surrounds Lazarus is at
the moment trying to quote unquote break
the system which would allow them to
have rather than fewer people speaking
to Lazarus individually now that more
people are interested to have more
people satisfied and happy and and I was
wondering if there's any way to use
computers in the way you use computers
to communicate with Lazarus and increase
the in order in other words to break the
system. You are a
computer. You can use whatever symbolic
extension of yourself you wish to
according to how your imagination
creates it. But you are the computer and
you are as accelerated as you need to be
to achieve that.
Well, I'm not sure that I understand how
that applies.
Define your specific intention.
Well, um, for example, the way you communicate
um, for example, the way you communicate
to us through your um, use of the what
I've heard you describe as a computer.
Yes. Using the imagination. Yes. Would
it be possible for us to create
something like that here in order to
communicate with Lazaro? Yes. It would
be possible to do that. Yes. However,
your technology has not been applied in
that area.
So, it's a matter of somebody interested
enough and excited enough to apply that
technology. Okay. Now,
Okay. Now,
have you asked Lazarus?
No, I haven't asked for Lazarus. Then
since you thought of it, you go ask.
Perhaps Lazarus will be able to tell
you. Thank you. All
Thank you. All
right. Say hi. I
heard you. Um I've been hearing about
the the beings that are in the inner
earth. Excuse me. And
um I I was wonder and supposedly our
government knows about them and they
they this is all I will say for now.
They exist but they exist in another
dimensionality that is not exactly your
dimensionality. So they are there and
they are not there.
You have to change the frequency of your
vibration in order to experience them.
The inner earth you will be in then is
not exactly the inner earth of your own
earth in the same frequency as you are
in now. Mhm.
That is all. But you are. Yes. Um uh I
have and so have a few of my friends
been experiencing what seems to be the
uh perception of an earthquake. Very
subtle tremors. And um I was just
wondering what that was. And yet you
don't hear on the news that we had a uh
an earthquake.
Understand in this way there may be in
your terms localized tremors in that
sense that are not announced. There may
also simply be the recognition of
vibrational shiftings within you.
equilibrium shifts that may feel like
quakes or other vibrations going on that
simply only translate locally.
Or it could be a perception of what
Steve and I have been going through for
the last week.
Define the tremors. I'm preparing to
duplicate this energy. All right, that
is also plausible.
Yes. Um, you were talking before about
how the Bible states things in a
negative sense. Is there any way you can
state in a positive sense the highest
truth by which we shall live?
Very simply, the truth is composed of
all truths.
So is the acceptance of non-resistance.
Yes. And unconditional love, trust and
faith is all there is. How's that?
How's that?
That's pretty good. I want to ask it
leaves me confused in a practical sense.
All right. How's that? Well, I went to
England and I had a fantastic time
socially, but it's like a spiritual
desert. I come back here and it's like
a This is where it's happening, but I
don't have quite as good a time. So
yes, what you are saying is that since
you cannot find what you want, you now
have a sparkling opportunity to create
it. By which should I just should should
By which should I just should should
Yes.
Fill your desert with lifegiving water.
All right. It rains a lot now.
Then soak it up.
Thank you. There will be in your terms a
few moments remaining
for this interaction.
For sure. Yes.
Um I just wanted to share one thing.
When the Orion person came through, I
right immediately knew him. It was kind
of a neat experience. And I also was the
channel to the space you were in was
very real to me. And then I've been on a
whole thing on it since then. And um a
whole thing all that that gives me too.
No, just it it opened a lot of windows
for me. Oh, thank you for opening them
up and letting the sunshine in. Okay.
And um one little quick question. Um
there seems to be the experience. I'm
gonna be delivering my third baby next
week. And there seems to be the
[Laughter]
to my mother.
[Music] But you know it doesn't I don't
But you know it doesn't I don't
understand why there should be pain in
the there does not have to be. All pain,
physical, mental, emotional, spiritual,
is the product of judgment and
separation of a portion of yourself from
the rest of all that you are. An
avoidance of the experience on many
different levels and simply the product
of many things you have been ingrained
to
believe. Get in touch with the
consciousness to be born. Cocreate the
birth with the consciousness and you
will be absorbed in communication. So
absorb, you will not notice. The birth
will be over before you know it. Wow.
Oh, no. Wait.
Really? No, I am kidding. Stink slippery. In other
In other
words, let the baby help.
Oh. With its own delivery. Okay.
Thank you. Yeah. Thanks. Good.
Okay. Oh, can I ask one little question?
I'm waiting.
This baby um where's he from?
You I mean the being
everywhere and nowhere. No labels.
Okay. Not for now. Yeah. Now let it be
born whole
labels. Right. Oh, okay. Well, that clarifies a
Right. Oh, okay. Well, that clarifies a
lot. Thank you. Thank you. Name him all
that is
[Music] nothing polarity.
Thank you, Strawberry.
[Laughter] Briefly, very briefly. I heard in the
Briefly, very briefly. I heard in the
tape you were talking about cats over
the last few weeks and um the on t what
evening was it? Tuesday evening I went
to um a home of uh two medicine women
that live out in La Cresenta and they
they were complaining because their cats
keep disappearing like five or six cats
kept um walking away or maybe getting
eaten by coyotes or this and that and
the other. And they said, "Does anybody
have any idea why their cats are
disappearing so quickly?"
More cats the oil and the people eat
them. Also,
now you have said they are medicine
women. What does that mean to them?
What does that mean to them?
the the disappearance of the cat. I What
does being medicine women mean to them?
Um,
what it means also that they have a
special relationship to animals. All
right. So, I think it's very disturbing
to them that they're then why are they
co-creating it?
I was wondering the same thing.
Do they feel that their connection to
animals is more special than their
connection to people?
No, I wouldn't say that. Do they feel
that being medicine
woman means that they must
deal only with fragments of other
people? Or do they perceive that they
are dealing with whole individuals?
Do they feel themselves in dealing with
other individuals to be fractionated?
Do you know any of this?
[Laughter] I'm trying to just
I think there's some fractionation on
their part. Oh, no.
You never did TR3, did you, Busher?
I do not drive cars.
Or is that a drill? No, it's a drill
that teaches you always to get an answer
to the question you ask before you ask a
second one.
I see. That was a joke.
Did you take it? I loved it. Yeah, I
did. I didn't I didn't learn it either. [Laughter]
My suggestion for your medicine women.
One of them, by the way. Yes. Closer.
The one that was complaining, I think,
is closer to her dog than two people.
All right. She has two wonderful black
dogs. At any rate, why are you concerned
about the cats? The
idea, allow them to
become feline. Follow the trail. Use
their instincts. When they discover where they
instincts. When they discover where they
have gone by being feline, they will
know why. Because they will find
themselves in the same place. And if
they are willing to face the fear that
they will generate by being in that
state of being, they will break through
to another side and another
aspect of their
power. Follow in a sense follow the
disappearances by disappearing down the
same hole and reemerging in another
portion of the self.
relate to the idea of the
transformational power of nature
as only a cat
would. That is what I can share at this
time. Thank you.
We will extend.
The title is connections. Thank you to
each and every one of you this evening
of your
time. Our joy and ecstasy in your
willingness to co-create this
interaction for the gift that you have
given to us by your willingness to
interact is beyond measure. We thank
you. We bid you exciting dream lives and
great accelerations.
Fun and loving life to you all.
Good night. Wonderful.
Wonderful.
Thank you, Daryl. Thank you very much.
Thank you all for coming. Thank you.
[Music]