we will begin this interaction the
seeming of your time the idea of pulling
together some of what you may call the
loose and dangling ends everyone no
matter in what configuration you are in
right now allow yourself to become as
comfortable as you
can Center
yourselves if you wish close your eyes
keep them open it does not matter but
allow yourselves to
center after this time allow us to
gather together the energy of your
individuality the energy of your
beingness and focus and consolidate and
synchronize and harmonize this energy
each and every division each and every
level within you now allow yourself to
begin to bring together these ideas so
that you can begin to feel the
acceleration of your energy this day of
your time
bre deep and relaxing breath that's your
own pace that's your own
gra as you do so simply allow yourself
to understand that in whatever
configuration whatever pose whatever
stance you are in allow yourself to
Simply take the aptitude that it is
exactly for now the correct pose the
correct stance the correct position to
be in to allow yourself to to Avail
yourself of whatever it is you need to
get out of this idea this technique this
exercise that is about to commence do
not judge or invalidate yourself in this
way and allow yourself to recognize that
as we begin each and every idea each and
every noise each and every thought each
and every feeling no longer needs to be
considered a
distraction allow all of it to become a
part of the
exercise invite it all in nothing will
interrupt you nothing can interrupt you
invite it all in as a part of the
exercise as a part of the centering of
your energy of the collectivity of the
total you at this time therefore in
whatever way shape or form your
imagination so desires allow yourself to
float to drift to go inward to Center to
meditate to relax and recognize that the
ideas that we may suggest the
visualizations that we may describe
throughout this exercise once again in
no way shape or form have to be exactly
what you envision exactly what you
imagine simply use them as guides and
recognize that if you find your
imagination giving you something
slightly different an alteration of the
idea then that is an indication that
that is is precisely what you need allow
yourself the opportunity to recognize
that your imagination is the tool that
works for you supplying you with exactly
the idea the methodology that you
require to be in touch with all those
different levels of yourself that you
desire to become in touch with and that
there is no right way and no wrong way
to experience this
exercise so now simply
relax and above and beyond all on
whatever level and in whatever way you
choose to create it enjoy
enjoy
imagine yourself now drifting and
floating within the very core the very
center of the dimension of your
imagination floating in space and
time allow yourself now the
opportunity to
stretch your senses outward from you in
all directions Front back left right up
down
360° outward in an expanding
bubble a sort of energy shock wave that
you will send out from the very center
of your being be it your heart be it
your solar plexus be it your mind it
does not matter where it originates at
this point simply send it out in thought
in image in feeling in whatever way you
wish to in whatever way you imagine it
allow it to
expand ever outward infinitely
outward and recognize that as you do so
as the very surface of this bubble
expands it creates
it creates as it interacts with the time
and space with the void you imagine
yourself to be in it creates the
solidification of what you consider to
be physical reality around you as it
expands it is as if physical reality
unfolds from the interaction of the edge
of the bubble with the edge of the Void
with the substance of the space time
Contin allow it to continue to expand
infinitely outward and as you begin to
allow it to go beyond what you perceive
to be the immediate
Horizon then allow yourself to know you
are at the center of this
creation and by being at the center of
this creation you can begin to realize that
creation you can begin to realize that
you are completely and totally
immerse in the
energy that you have sent out that is
creating the reality around you you are
completely a part of you are that energy
it is your
pulse it is your pace it is your thought
it is your emotion it is your
belief allow yourself to know therefore
that all that you perceive to be the
physiological reality around you is
intimately intimately not only attached
to you but intimately a part of you it
comes from you feel that with every
slight motion that you may make with
every slight shift that occurs within
you you sense a ripple going outward
from the center again Rippling through
the physiological reality through the
medium of energy which is within the
infinite bubble that you have sent out
to begin with every move you make sends
a ripple through this fluid through this
energy through the atmosphere within the
bubble within all
reality that the bubble has created that
the bubble
touches allow yourself to know therefore
that you truly in your terms pull the
strings of the reality you perceive
around you the reality you perceive is
but an exension of
you allow yourself to drift breathing in
this fluid breathing it in breathing in
the raw material of Creation The Raw
space-time energy and breathing
out the
specific realities of your desire the
specific realities of your belief the
specific realities that represent your
emotionality your energy motion
emotion as you
drift silently
smoothly lovingly effortlessly warmly
powerfully within this fluid within this
medium within this energy within this
atmosphere as you
drift allow yourself to begin to let
something sink deeply within
you understand the illusion of physical
re
reality understands the projection that
you have always considered to be so
solidly outside of yourself so solidly
more real than your imagination so
solidly more real than your dreams now
begin to understand it all as one
reality that simply shares different
definitions different
applications different projections but
all being the same one reality created
within the same one bubble
and allow this knowledge allow this
allow this knowledge allow this
understanding to become
inherently and consciously From This
Moment forward if you so
choose for a very long time in your
accounting you have considered the idea
of your spiritual quests still from a
differentiated point of view you are
beginning to see the so-called
connections within everything but you
still consider that it is connections of
separate things as we have already shared with
things as we have already shared with
you many times everything you perceive
is the same one thing manifesting in
multi-dimensional simultaneous aspects
all the aspects that the one infinite
all that is can manifest within so you
already have absorbed to some degree the
notion in your exploration of
spirituality that everything everything
is the same one thing manifesting in all
the multi-dimensional ways that it can
but beyond that and more emotionally to
the center of your being and your
home you can now take it to
heart to recognize the difference in
thought modality the difference in
perception that comes when you realize
this for a very long period of time you
have thought
Consciousness is what exists within the
body allow yourself to begin to
understand and allow yourself to begin
to know and allow yourself to begin to
truly feel it is not
feel it is not
Consciousness which exists within the
body the body exists within
Consciousness all is
all is
consciousness it is not that
Consciousness exists within all all
exists within
Consciousness Consciousness is all that
is and it is everywhere and
everything everything therefore is the
same Consciousness everything is within
the same Consciousness and that is why
you have the
ability to affect seemingly any portion
of the universe space or time because
everything is the same within the one
Consciousness all the
[Music] differentiations are
differentiations are
illusionary they serve a purpose but
they are still all the same one Consciousness allow
Consciousness allow
yourself to take to heart the
understandings of the
changes the profound and Powerful
changes of s
synchronicity that can occur in your
life when you truly understand truly
know and truly
Express the reality that Consciousness
is not in the body the body is within
Consciousness three deep
breath as you take these breaths allow
yourself to rise as you say to the
surface of your reality the reality you
consider your day-to-day
experiences allow yourself to awaken
into this projected illusion once again
for it does serve you and it is your
playground it is your tool it is your
etic expression of creation but allow
yourself to know that you are changed
you are refreshed
you are clearer you are connected you
are your expression your unique
expression of all that is of the
infinite with a capital
i how do you all feel
great thank you for your sharing thank
you for your co-creation thank you for
your willingness and your unconditional
love right
right
sure yes I woke up this morning um I
remembered an image speak up I I
remembered an image in my dream of
seeing my profile and coming out of my
eyes was the um projecting projecting reality
was the um projecting projecting reality
like the eyeballs were the
projection uh I noticed that one time I
playing around with a black light they
One Moment by I interrupt you for one
moment please thank you allow me to
remind now each and every one of you
that if you now truly understand that
everything is one thing then you
understand that everything that happens
can be utilized by everything else thus
recognize that everything that anyone
has to share is an opportunity for you
to apply what is being shared to your
own situation
remember the following idea very
clearly there are no boring moments only
bored Minds there are no boring moments
Minds there are no boring moments
everything is something that can be
learned from everything is something you
can explore with excitement and ecstasy
and learn more about the ideas that are
being reflected to you about yourselves
so that you panic and and accelerate in
synchronicity with all that is thank you
please continue projected from your
eyes oh yeah
what okay okay anyway so I was wondering
um okay so so is this reality do have we
set it up so it's being projected out of
the eyes the Visions are being projected
out the eyes not really but in a sense
yes because you use the idea of your
eyes to represent what you think you
receive as visual
imagery in this sense there is no need
to break it down as far as that no need
to be that specific in that way you
create your reality with your mind in a
sense with your Consciousness do not
forget you do not see with your eyes you
see with your
brain okay you see with your mind
mind you create your mind your
Consciousness the Consciousness that you
are creates mind out of the
physiological electromagnetic
field thus you create your physical
reality as a series of electromagnetic
vibrations of varying rates thus the
quote unquote organ or tool that you
therefore symbolically create to receive
the imagery of physical reality is the
tool that is sensitive to shifts in
vibrational elect magnetic wavelength
what you call your eyes all right do the
chakras such as the solar plexus the
heart and all those do those are those
projecting or they feeling or how would
you explain that it is all as you say a
two-way street everything is projecting
and everything is receiving
simultaneously but it is even further
than that for you are still thinking
linearly so that's it is all one
simultaneous event it is not really
actually coming or going anywhere so
that's more or less a a Minds a mind is
designed to make it appear it appears
that way to a mind yes and the idea like
Lazar speaks of
projecting um through the body through
the brain yes on a curve and and all
that and that's still just part of our
our logic programming of how it is the
terminology necessary to allow certain
Concepts to become clear to C certain
individuals still functioning within the
Illusions and the symbology of the
physiological reality okay and finally thank you and
reality okay and finally thank you and
finally when a black light is held up to
the eyes and looking in a mirror I see
these little golden discs in front of
the eye what would that be those little
golden little yellow dots fine you you
are simply creating what you call the
counterpart vibration in your
Consciousness to represent the complete
idea of any event you are seeing the
opposite quote unquote complimentary
color you follow me um I might get it
later but I haven't gotten it yet when
you allow yourself to perceive we shall
be colloquial to perceive the vibration
of any particular electromagnetic
wavelength that you call visible light
you will always create the opportunity
to also perceive the complimentary color
which is the opposing vibration so to
speak so that you have the complete
event both polarities of the vibration
you are
sensing and it appears to float right in
front of the eyeball there right in the
eyeball yes because you still are
creating the idea that you are receiving
it from the same Source you received the
original vibration if one were to look
right inside that little area there um
I'm just picking this up as a as a guess
or knowingness but but would one could
one would that could could one see all
of one's reality reflected right in that
little spot there yes
okay the universe is holographic and the
ability of the universe the entire
universe to exist exists within every
point in the
universe you can use and create whatever
symbology you wish to represent that
point and once you focus upon it you can
allow yourself to tap into the totality
of the universal
holog right thank
you you you I would is uh noting that
down here with all the baseball games
that have been being played in the past
week or so culminating with two very
intense games today uh one that lasted I
don't know 16 Innings or something 17
Innings whatever that there seemed to me
to be an
archetypical uh element of the energies
focused energies of struggle and
competition and and sort of the nation
channels its emotional energy into these
events and they're acted out by the
players and um it it's just an
observation really just the the
interesting intensity by which we
process as a national group our emotions
through these events oh yes thank you
for your observation and recognition
that all that occurs within your Society
is a symbolic reflection of the ideas
you carry within yourselves to be true
and express themselves on every single
level of your Society in many different
ways some that you would call quote
unquote constructive and some that you
would call destructive right I I had one
other thing that asked actually it was
two in the form of Dreams uh after I
left here last week as I was falling
asleep I heard my own name mentioned in
my head and I couldn't get anything more
out of it than that if you have any call
into yourself in a sense taking a
reflection from a guide some assistance
to lure you into more of yourself the
recognition of your own vibration so
that you can in a sense follow it to
become the future youth the higher youth
ah good thank you and last but not least
I also experienced in the dream the
other night the reading in detail of a
book I was walking around reading uh
quite extensively in the book and I was
uh very boyed up by this experience with
the exception that it seemed like all
the chapters had to do with sexual
perversion and I was wondering to myself
if this was my own way of reading Bad
Karma from the past or some other
interpretation that would uh perhaps
come from an angle other than my own
immediate there is some connection to
that idea but we find that it may be
representative of old shall we say old
ideas old ways of representing
connections to things old ways of
thinking about why you experience energy
coming through in your physiological
reality in the way you do thinking that
it is attached to ideas of what you call
now not so much quote unquote sexually
but the perversion of energy in that way
what you perceive or what you used to
think of as the perversion of energy
seeing it arise now in your Society
being able to in a sense read your
Society like a book in that way
recognizing that all that has been quote
unquote the reason for the manifestation
of the struggle in your Society has been
because of the quote unquote not in the
judgmental way do I mean this but in
your colloquial terminology because of
the perversion of energy this is from
your own thought forms your own way of
looking at it you follow me yes the idea
is to Simply recognize that you have now
read the scope of the way you used to
think what you scanned was your old
mentality your old point of
view the idea that used to allow you to
think of all the manifestations of
negativity in your society as
perversions of all that is now you can
simply understand them as choices now
you can simply allow them to be equal to
the idea of being able to choose
Positive Choices and thus be able to
choose Positive Choices because the idea
of the old way the quote unquote
perversion of positivity no longer has
any more power than the idea of choosing
what you feel to be harmonious
presentations or examples or expressions
of the same energy it is an exploration
of the idea of knowing that you are and
every individual in your Society is as
powerful as they need to be to have
anything they want without having to
hurt anyone else or themselves in order
to get it they do not have have to in
your terms debase themselves pervert
themselves in that way all of those
ideas come from beliefs in one's own
powerlessness rather than one's own
powerfulness you follow me yes
certainly does this assist you yeah
quite a bit and especially the answer on
the name because that sounded to me to
be the same frequency as I had heard
about 15 years ago relative yourself
thank you for answering your own call
yeah yeah guys yeah this has to do with
the the idea that we are becoming more
aware of how we actually can create our
reality as and um how you actually do
how create your reality and also related
to the mass Consciousness I I was
wondering um I'll just give you the
example that triggered all this thinking
all right uh I planted a Pim last year I
guess it takes a few years to start
bearing food and I've had some successes
using the 33 second technique when you
when you create things on the CLE plane
I and this morning I thought oh I wonder
what it would happen if I created fruit
for this year when it's not due yet and
then I said well the mass Consciousness
you know doesn't permit that but since
I'm becoming more yes powerful there is
one way if you will remember in that
technique to now this is in colloquial
terms to sneak around through the back
door of the mass Consciousness agreement
and the way to do that as if you will
remember in the technique that was given
is to say well all right if this in your
understanding of linear time takes such
and such amount of time to happen then
in your imagination go back such and
such amount of time and start the
process then right let say I do that then they
then right let say I do that then they
can appear
tomorrow well wouldn't that be a little
too much for most of us ex that that is
up to you to decide whether that means
anything to you or not whether you care
whether it means too much for someone
else and whether you will allow yourself
to understand that if it truly is too
much for someone else they don't have to
come wandering around to see
it and that they won't if it is too much
for someone they will never Place
themselves in an area where something
would be perceived by them that would be
too much for them to handle so you don't
have to worry about them perceiving it
if someone does come along and perceive
it then it is not by definition too much
for them to handle if it is not too much
for you go ahead and do it okay as long
as long as it remains in my backyard I I
can see doing it but aren't there things
that we might start doing that would
affect other people too I do not hear
what I said yeah I did hear what you
said yeah I did it affects only the
other people who feel they are willing
to participate in that idea so whether
it is in your backyard or not all the
individuals that need to see it will be
there the more willing and more bold you
are willing to be then the more
opportunity there will be for many more
individuals to perceive it when they are
also ready I guess one of the questions
was in this case you know it's it's it's
something fun that would be great
but um answer there some questions of
Ethics involved sometimes are you doing
this within your integrity are you
forcing this on anyone no then you are
not breaking any ethics you are simply
doing what excites you in the privacy of
your own Universe your own backyard and
those that come along synchronistically
coincidentally will be those that you have invited and
will be those that you have invited and
have accepted the invitation there is no
need to force this idea on
anyone okay it's it's really a very
exciting idea that simply understand
that if you know you are going to do
this idea within Integrity then simply
don't worry about the idea of going
beyond your ethics for you will simply
find that if you are out in quote
unquote public and you do this thing if
it does manifest
then that is a sign it is all right if
it doesn't manifest then that is a sign
that it wasn't all right okay great
simply trust that if it does or doesn't
manifest it will do so automatically
according to keeping in step with your
integrity since you know that's why you
are doing this to begin with and it's
really I don't have to consider the mass
Consciousness then you are considering
the mass Consciousness you are saying
that you go along with the mass
consciousness's comfort zone and are
willing to accept that when it does
happen it fits and when it doesn't
happen it fits you follow me yes thank
you very much
you you um this week from what from your
you um this week from what from your
talk to me last week it really helped me
in what you gave me advice I had the
experience of another gentleman of when
the bed got kicked you know when he said
that last week I and woke up I had the
same thing happen to me exciting it was
great it was great because I I knew I I
remember last week I didn't know where I
was in reality because I was Greening
ahead and things like that now I'm not
worried about it at all I feel great F
you things are really good in fact I
went to this Tao drum show and uh the
drums that the Japanese Doo played made
me feel all these different things that
I knew where I was and now I know why I
am where I'm at because of what I saw
through the drum oh than you but I have
these friends who
I I talk to them about these experiences
that I have that are so real and so true
for me for you that is the underlying
phrase for you for me they are and I
have spoken to them about purpose and
synchronicity and how I see now how
everything is perfect in the universe Y
and they are very confused as they don't
see Jesus and the whole biblical
scriptural thing fitting into the whole
program oh it is very simple and it fits
quite nicely
so where does uh you may find that there
may be
interpretations of the idea that do not
seem to allow it to fit but obviously
since the idea does exist it obviously
fits that is the foundation to start
from since the Christ Consciousness does
exist and since all these other things
exist they obviously
fit that is the point to start from then
discovering how they fit is the journey
the Ecstasy The Joy yeah because they
tell me there's nothing in the
scriptures about going and listening to
Drums let me tell you I know what it did
for me because you told me that I'd
lived many many many many times everyone
here you've told that and I I shut my
eyes and through the beat of those drums
I knew I knew what I saw I saw myself in
five six seven different situations and
I I realize why I'm where I'm at now but
they look at me like well hey buddy you
know may I ask you a question you do
your friends Drive
automobiles yeah is there anything in
the scriptures about
automobiles no I'm not very well versed
in the scriptures but I I mean I don't
not that I've why does that have to be
anything in the scriptures about drums
in order for someone to recognize it as
a reflection of the idea of the intent
of the essence of what is being said in
your literature why does it why does it have
literature why does it why does it have
to be why does the symbol have to be
something literally represented rather
than ENT yeah that's what I I said hey
the Bible's written by man inspired by
God it's written by the hand of man like
this girl here last week she was saying
I you know she felt very very disturbed
over the story of Isaac right because we
said she was
well that's what I was telling them you
know hey it's only a book written by man
and you can't take it completely
literally because oh they can if they
wish to now do understand one thing
since each and every individual is their
own Universe if they truly truly
literally believe every single word of
that literature in their Universe it is
literally true so they don't need
anything in their Universe right they
don't need anything else they have it
all for now for now for their I like
coming here listening that is your
Universe okay recognize that the idea
the foundational idea that perhaps they
are not understanding is that all truths
are true right now the truth is composed
of all truths there is no one background
reality against which to measure other
reality for their way to go reality
factor for their validity there is only
one thing that exists in common for
everything in the universe and that is
only that everything exists period that
is the only common factor to everything
in the universe everything else is a
manifestation of the Primal existence of
the infinite for as many reasons as
there are Creations within
it that I mean I I tried to delay that
to them oh oh oh there is no need to try
they do not in any way shape or form
need to believe what you believe that's
why I said they go at their own pace I
just hey that's okay it's all right you
do whatever you want it's the way it's
supposed to be it's all perfect yes
don't sweat it
but recognize at the same time that you
will understand that there are many many
ways to recognize that much of what
individuals think of as seeming
discrepancies really are not and it is
only semantics that make it seem so well
I was kind of confused about this
perversion thing you know before what
you just said the sexual perversion I
mean I mean to me there's my idea of
perversion is a lot different than what
other people think it's perverted of
course and I want to know is there
perverted behavior in your Society no no
there's not in a sense there isn't in
yours the idea is that every type of
behavior is completely in sync with the
idea that it is expressing now we
understand and what we were saying is
that what you think of what you label
what you judge to be perversion made
usually be a representation of an
expression of negative energy but it
does not have to be this is why we say
the ideas you call Good and Evil right
and wrong in and of themselves are not
really very quote unquote accurately
descriptive of anything they are value
judgments all the time the idea is that
there is either an expression of
positive energy which is totally
integrative or negative energy which is
segregative someone may look at a
positively integrating energy situation
and say that it is wrong or evil someone
may look at a negative segregative
situation and say it is good or right
these things are value judgments someone
may think that a very strong and loving
positive situation is
perversion and we will know this through
ourselves as in truth cuz I know what
truth is for me and know one's going to
change it the way I'll go that is true
for you is the only truth you can ever
know thank
you all right all
[Laughter] [Music]
[Music]
right yeah I I wanted to share a dream
that I had last week all right then
speak up and it was wonderful it just
dropped that evening of the last
channeling right into it I was um I was
on a large open Park area and there was
a crowd Gathering because an event uh a
conference of some friendship Conference
of some kind was about to take place and
all of a sudden a student was in front
of us it seemed very much like the 60s
and he was
addressing some faculty or some
administrative head behind us and he
said if this if we are not allowed into
this conference it's not going to take
place and all of a sudden everybody felt
that there was going to be some trouble
uh oh trouble trouble trouble and I said
wait a minute don't panic a Don't Panic
there's no problem and then I realized
it was my dream I these are all my
feelings but the guards in quotes who
said this is not going to take place had
little cloth armbands people started to
run and I said don't panic and I walked
up to the gate that was closing I said
wait a minute I have to go to work so
they let me out
and then I realized that I was in a very
enclosed room and it started to get
intimidating I said wait a minute I
don't like this and I woke up and I I
got up very good right I heard you say
you can take control of your dreams they
are your dreams I I wrote The Dream down
I went to turn off the line I thought
wait a minute I don't like the ending of
this so I'm going to change it I laid
the book down I laid back down within 10
seconds I was back into this dream and I
said I said I don't like this all of a
sudden the room opened up
I was in a field everyone was laughing
and having a wonderful time there were
unicorns
rainbows and then I started to have a
child and I looked her and it was it was
becoming painful and I looked around for
Connie because my feeling was well this
is yours but I thought
wait I thought no this is my child too
and then I heard you again say it does
not have to be painful
talk to the child something else that we
talked about that night and I had an
underwater birth and it was so smooth
and so wonderful and it was I was giving
birth to my
Enlightenment and we were walking over
the hill and then I heard you say we
will come to you in your dreams and I
saw your spacecraft come over the hill I
mean I saw it I felt it it was not a
dream picture I saw the condensation I
heard it I felt
it was it it I had transformed myself
there in front of the ship it was
wonderful happy birthday thank
you thank you very much doctor of
Dreams by the way doctor of drum yes yes
the ideas also of what an individual
believes in their physiolog olical
reality in their own
universe may be literally what they
experience upon physiological death for
a while because what it is you strongly
believe in to be true will carry over
when you become a thought form in a
world of thought
form yeah so an
individual that truly believes that they
are going to see precisely a certain
type of afterlife
will see that because their thoughts in
that level create instantly create the
reality they proceed with no time lag
well that's a relief cuz I have already
perceived myself this week of where I'll
be and that's right where I want to be I
and end up
there now recognize that again you will
not remain in any particular
Locus because you will understand that
it is all all reflective of Simply what
beliefs you carried with you you will
change you will acclimate and you will
move on than on than
you
you okay um I'm go I'm coming to the
channeling about 3 months and all kinds
of things been accelerating in my life
lots of Enlightenment what a surprise
what a surprise it feels hasn't feeling
terrific and wonderful thank you for
feeling terrific and wonderful thank you
for creating all the changes that have
been taking place thank you cuz there
there really are hundreds of changes
thanks and then in the last week um all
kinds of strange things have happened
all strange where I was having vivid dreams
strange where I was having vivid dreams
I started having none that I could
remember and then all of a sudden I had
a couple of Dreams in a row um one was
all I heard was a buzzing sound in my
left ear oh very good
guys unless of course you persist in
insisting that when things change they
are for a negative reason no no all
right and then another dream was that I
was going down a sort of a swirling
Vortex all right all right you are
beginning to have outof body experiences
consciously what you call the buzzing
the clicking the popping bright light
swirling swaying acceler ated motions
spinning motions vibrating motions all
of these are many of the different ways
that you have a physiologically
interpreting the separation of what you
think of as your mentality your
Consciousness from your body I see
because then even during the day I'm
dizzy Li headed okay well I was
coinciding with this I was on a
medically supervised protein F guys I
lost about 30 lbs in about 33 days but
because I was complaining of dizziness
and headiness the doctor started
increasing this detaching all right and
the next thing I know this week I ended
up breaking out this incredible rash all
over my body and I am not prone to
rashes blemishes and Ang the first time
that it happened to me and the
chiropractor that I see that I trust
more than the doctor um said to me today
you're overdose on potassium so we have
to get you off the potassium get you
even off the protein for about a week
all right and have a
detoxification of your body all right
and he recommended some uh abuse fast
for 24 hours and then a light died for 6
days and
then uh well we both agreed that there
would be no way I could convince the
medical establishment as to what
happened next week to go back on the F
very complicated because the medical
situations in our society well my
feeling about most doctors is they
they're not that enlightened and so I
find it they are completely and totally
enlightened in their own in their own
way um okay my my thing this week now is
some dreams have continued right um and
one dream the other night was that I was
standing in front of a Black Kettle that
was swaying back and forth when it
swayed one way the kettle was empty when
it swayed another filled with silver and
money and um and then all of a sudden
the person front of the it was like a
gpsy was in front of the kettle yes and
she moved over to a very hot outdoor
stove and began making pancakes right
with all kinds of things in them a
little boy that I'm I know I'm very fond
of 5 years old came by in the dream and
he wanted pancakes with chocolate in it
and when I woke up I remembered that I I
had had a past life uh regression
recently they said that I had had a
lifetime in the m civilization all right
also as a gypsy later on and then I was
a powerful sorceress and afraid of my
own power in this life and I had read
something in a book about the Mind
civilization that the Mind women may be
spat with all day long and that seems
symbolic of well not all day
long the feeling I had I thought was
actually the new and I go boy I'm glad I
was one powerful women and I didn't have
to stand around making the Tor all day
that crazy um so any I felt that was
symbol some kind of symbol
pan but um and then much of what you are
experiencing with regard to the idea of
waste has to do with the fear of your
own power because you think you need
extra grounding uhhuh in order to be
able to handle it m but you can handle
it
fine okay this is the first time in my
life I believe that um that is perfect
timing what I am concerned with right
right now oh
and I you told one of the master that
she could grow the fruit by tomorrow my
feel is I want the rest gone by tomorrow
I don't want this all right then allow
yourself to accept the fact that it is
there for a reason allow yourself to
realize what it is you are showing
yourself then accept the message without
needing the symbol that brought it
anymore and it won't need to stick
around okay um and is there something
you can recommend in terms of the kind
of detox F that I can you are in good
hands with the chiropr juice fast and
then starting back on the protein to
some degree some of the idea of your
vegetables will be of great assistance
to you as well
uhhuh um purifying
water okay um but you are in as you say
takeable hand okay see because if I if I
remain under the care of the chiropra
he's weary of that protein F and he
wants me to see a holistic nutritionist
all right you may explore the idea if
you already have told yourself that your
trust is not within what you call the
medical profession then why remain
attached to something you do not trust
I was
25 we are hanging on but we are noticing
that you said was was yes oh yes I gave
it it look last year especially in the
last couple months I just walked away
from nursing and medical and you walked
into another variation of the same
idea uh it is not that you have given it
up you have simply transformed it into
another method that represents the idea
you now know yourself to be that's true
because recently lots of people come to
me that I that I really appreciate and
want me to do a lot of the healing
workshops that I used to do guys let the
energy flow through you let yourself
clear yourself out in that way become
that conduit then the energy will be moving
conduit then the energy will be moving
will be being used you will be doing
what you need to be doing with that
energy you will not be waiting to do you
will not be allowing the energy to turn
into Mass because you are not using it
and that will clarify and balance
everything within
you use that energy to heal to assist
and you will automatically be healing
and assisting yourself so then it was
perfect timing to set up a workshop me
to teach a workshop starting inek on
healing healers is the name of the
workshop healing the healers you can
trust your instincts in this matter and
do not have to have the old carryover
belief that what you are doing is [Music] [Music]
rash thank
you one moment one I just want to send
you a kiss thank
kiss thank
you you in the past you have shared with
us some of the things you learned from
our civilization would you share with us
some of the things you've learned in
your own civilization recently thank you I you I
have
become the
idea of
vibrational Gates that I have not been
Gates that I have not been
before I have become the
idea of interaction with Consciousness I have
of interaction with Consciousness I have
not interacted with
before I have become the idea of being
cognizant that this interaction reflects
a level of Consciousness within me that
is a
gate an
atmosphere I conduit
it that represents my ability now to
begin to
explore other dimensionality to
dimensionality to
chart courses if you will into those new
dimensional real ity that you have heard
us referred to as quasi plar
reality there is more
opportunity within this discovery as you
would call it to begin to
interact with more directly with the
energy that has manifested itself upon
your world in the form you call Capas
we have open more
dialog explored the idea of their
existence as in our perception that
existence is in a sense in
between different universes in its own
idea of universe its own quasi plar
reality universe and thus become the
idea of the excitement of exploring a
whole new understanding of
dimensionality and interaction with
Consciousness thank you were you just
channeling your entire
civilization there was some connection
with the association momentarily oh okay
have you subjectively um experien this
what you just shared with us I okay
another question uh I guess about 3
weeks ago on the cruising tape uh you
were talking about uh the desert and you
said something like um many of us on
this planet uh Earth don't recognize
upon our own world that the ideas we
surround ourselves with all the time
have many more levels of meanings than
we allow ourselves to be aware of
because we consider them mundane guys
will you sure uh give us some examples
of such such some of these ideas and the
different levels there many different
levels as we don't recognize that it can
the idea has been recognized to some
degree by certain individuals in your
society that are willing to remember one
of the ideas we shared with you earlier
this evening of your time there are no
boring situations only bored Minds the
idea is that if you are in any situation
you will be able to recognize the
interaction and interplay of your own
Consciousness what you think of as
higher Consciousness the interactions of
other consciousnesses the mass
Consciousness archetypal substream
consciousnesses other ideas of other
Consciousness connected to your world
but in non-physical ways beyond your
dimension alog together that interact
you'll be able to see the interes of
interaction the holographic nature of
everything how one thing one interaction
may lead off to another interaction
you'll begin to see that the symbology
changes from Individual to individual
you can begin to see through other
individual's eyes through other
perspectives through the idea of higher
ideas of understanding through the ideas
of animal Consciousness through the
ideas of the Consciousness within what
you call the minerals and so forth the
entire stage on which you walk at any
given moment has an infinite number of
points of view I'm an example Bashar all
right the other day I was having
breakfast and I heard barking and I
looked out and here is my neighbor's dog
on the roof and I thought that was great
I've seen a lot of cats on the roof but
never a dog before and I started
laughing and it occurred to me this is a
wonderful symbol of service to mankind
having achieved a
higher on that same note
Could you um I wrote this down so I
wouldn't forget it thank you very much
could you come comment on the mentality
and Sensibility of uh seeing ey guide
dogs as they relate to us in service to
the blind in what way does it not appear
blind in what way does it not appear
obvious to you well I'm interested in
getting into their mind I I don't know
that I have fully understood their
mentality or their their Sensi
sensibility or sensitivity I'd like you
to share what insights you have all
right now recognize foundationally once
again that what you call animal
Consciousness refers to
itself any individual animal is
cognizant of its individuality by being
aware of everything else it is connected
to it sees itself as an individual in
Connection in relation to everything
else that is how it knows knows it is an
individual by seeing the grander picture
first and simply understanding its place
within it and acting upon that
understanding instinctively you follow me uh yes I do
instinctively you follow me uh yes I do
that is how to get into the mentality of
an animal beginning to understand your
individuality as a product of the inter
relationship of everything within all
that is and then seeing how all the
threads as they inter con lead to you
okay so let's say that I started to get
into the mentality of an animal in that
way and I want to explore further with
the Seeing Eye guide dog and uh I
observed an animal who has
specific intelligence with respect to
our society so that they can guide a
blind person and I'm wondering can you
help me uh get deeper into this
mentality with this particular kind of
animal one moment
I have a suggestion
okay perhaps you could do what they
do that's that's a very interesting
suggestion now the difference is that I
view myself I mean I have thoughts specific
myself I mean I have thoughts specific
thoughts and um sensitivities emotions
knowing as beliefs that I understand
they don't distinguish among to some
degree that is correct but what we are
suggesting is that you can gain a very
close approximation by falling into the same
approximation by falling into the same
modality that they are in and
functioning like them okay I can do that
in my imagination and I've just done it
and uh perhaps you can help me pick
out what I've just done and compare it
with what they do and see the see the
similarities in this case we find that
the dimension that may be in your terms
missing that would allow you more direct
understanding of the experience is the
dimension that requires that you
actually put it into physiological
action and explore that dimension of
your imagination as well okay all right
one more question to do like is to be
like yeah yeah I I do recognize that
there will have to be differences
because oh yeah but you will have your
insights from the point of view you
desire to have I understand that and you
may find that you will gain a more
complete instinctive understanding than
you may believe is possible okay all
right one more question uh the other day
I I spotted a lizard outside of my
doorstep and this in the middle of a
city lizards don't frequent very often
and not that you
think well I've seen them I do that I do
know that they exist okay um
nevertheless I have not seen one on very
good very good very good how very
exciting recognize that they do exist in
your city but they usually exist in what
you call the substream
substratum the
underworld connotation that let them
exist underneath the foundations of what
you generally think of as the only
reality that exist the concrete reality
the solid reality seeing one come to the
surface on your level means that many
different levels of unconscious
knowingness and unconscious wisdom are
now breaking through to the surface what
the symbology of the lizard is okay
let's take it a step further ancient
knowledge wisdom similar to the ID you
call snakes and more grandly dragons
yeah okay well I did something that I
found very interesting uh it was kind of
a Zen experience in that I um I wanted
to see how close I could get to this
lizard okay and I knew that on the
physical level I could spook him if I
move too quickly so I very very he was
moving very very slowly almost as though
he was in a different time uh different
measure of time counting and so I
thought well I will match this mov very
slowly observed the whole process while
I was doing it and he was observing me
too and I got to the point where I was
actually able to touch his back hey
which is pretty unusual uh one lizard to
[Music] another that is why we say identify
another that is why we say identify
identify identify if you wish to
understand about the seeing eye dog hang
out as one of them if you wish to
understand as lizard hang out as you
have done as one of them I'm going down
and get myself inste of knee
pad well that's very good so I came I
became the symbol of I became my own
symbol of Wis
yes you
identified as that is the expression of
wisdom because it means you are totally
going with the flow and not fighting to
gain your knowledge yeah identifying as
is
wisdom thank you thank you very
much you
you
um okay um this weekend I experienced a
a big acceleration and a lot of changes
and I not you
too not you too oh um no a lot of people
I know are experiencing on the planet
and I think that's really neat um I was
with a group of people from our Center
that we took to facilitate a a
promotional growth
weekend um a lot of these people that were there
um a lot of these people that were there
we've been working with them in
therapy and many of them have been
sexually abused
but it even goes farther than that
they've been satanically sexually
abused um some of them by their parents
some of them by people that lived in
their neighborhood nice they were forced
to do really abated things kill
humans um what happened Saturday evening around
um what happened Saturday evening around
3: 4 in the morning was I began to bring
forth information that I wrote down and
then I I did not judge it at the time
that that it was coming
through when I began to judge it it was
whenever it became evident and very
clear that I was supposed to share this
with with everyone there and it felt a
little bit
uncomfortable and I
um when I thought of judging it I knew
that the minute that I started judging
it the creative fla would be cut off all
right um
so I did share in the beginning of the
sharing I explained it and that this was
very high for and that I didn't want any
of their
judgments um and in sharing it in
sharing the information that was given
to me with them it really served as an
acceleration in all of their processes
during the weekend and we really went
through a lot of stuff with them because
of it and they got to a new phase a
thank you for expressing that degree of
willingness and the
convic um
you can continue in the same light
shining as a beacon a beacon that can
allow them to allow all
expressions of negative energy in their
lives to wash
away to allow them to regain their
understanding of their own
self-empowerment to allow them to
know there is no need for the
continuance of the cycle of refres
Retribution revenge and all the ideas that they have
revenge and all the ideas that they have
been experiencing in that way all the
ideas of powerlessness that were
expressed by the individuals that they
interacted with yes there was a lot of that and
with yes there was a lot of that and
this these events took place in their
childhood and they
are you know I don't want to put
judgment on this but in a way they are
dysfunctioning adults because they
caught up in that process that you can
begin to teach them the magic seed if
you will of recognizing that while all
of that is a valid portion of their soul
while it is all a valid portion of their
being in in no way shape or form needs
to be cut off they can begin to
understand that their present does not
have to be a result of the past they can
allow themselves to create their
childhood a new in the present with the
new understandings that they are now
um will you assist me before we stop
talking about what I seem to be bringing through
about what I seem to be bringing through
it was I feel real weird and and it's
because I'm I'm holding back and judging
and I don't want to the um what I seem
to to Define and express
as the Council of you
are will you um
I guess what it is is I want to Define
it a little
bit let us say you are gaining some
assistance from a reflection of
different levels of consciousness that
have to do with the
polarity positive side
of factions that have had physiological
counterparts in times past in your
history specifically with regard to
ideas you call within Atlantis within
Atlantean time
they are now relatively
discarnate but in this way carry on the
idea of reflecting the continuance of
the transformation of the expression of
these old Earth empowerment ideas from
negativity to positivity the idea of
what is usually referred to as the
ancient negativity expressed in your
terms as the satanic witchcraft to the
understanding of the idea of natural
magic the idea of the positive of light
the idea of knowing that the Earth's
vibration the soul Spirit and the
inspirited the embod idea of the light
vibration is something which is a
counterpart to what you are perceiving
to be the negative vibration of that
same connection they are in a sense the IDE
connection they are in a sense the IDE
Cally represented by the council that
oversees the
transformation of those type of
expressive energies from negative into
positive you follow me yes I do it is
the modulating vow that is composed of
many different degrees and perspectives
of
Consciousness these degrees and
perspectives and beings of Consciousness
from time to time will change so to
speak their identity but in general it
is the regulating vow that oversees any
such Transformations they are in a sense
in a sense symbolically colloquially
Angelic guides okay that was what came through
guides okay that was what came through
and I guess what it was is I really
wanted to validate that because they
said that that it was an angel an
Angelic counsil yes so that that helps a
lot one more thing um I want to continue
the creative process because I'm seeing
how it can accelerate growth with the
therapy that we're doing at the center
and so um I'm really feeling good about
that and that it will continue oh yes
all you need to do to allow it to
continue is to continue to shine and to
share okay um one more thing guys
give me a minute all right go ahead
release release shine and
share you are positively
[Music] glowing
glowing
um thank you for your flow dreamer
flow dreamer
yes you wish to speak
um I wasn't there Monday
but Frank came
home and told me what happened and when
he said the name
dreamer my throat chakra there was
something opening up in a CH throat
chakra and some sort of activation that
took place
yay and I was really happy about it um
did you feel like
singing I just felt just
ecstatic love PL thing
okay um you may have after your break
this night of your time the opportunity
for a brief communication with
K all right okay um another thing too
and this is the end and I'll pass on oh
the end it is just the beginning well I
I want others to share tonight right I
um I have made the decision to go to
Hawaii I'm in a place of this cner where
I don't even have to ask I just walked
in and say I won't be here for 2 weeks
in December we have to organized so that
I can be gone what I want to do is
to assist myself in every way possible
so that I can have wonderful
communication with dreamer and with any
other dolphin Consciousness out there in
Maui okay is there anything that I
realize that something will come like um
all things will come ideas will come all
things that you need will come but again
briefly you may discuss this with
dreamer all right okay is a lot of that
in a dream state like um some of it yes
there can be physiological interactions
that can also take
place at at the beach hey okay thank you
you may all take a short break
break
oh right I see
fale that wish to speak to
dreamer yeah stand ready stand up no seat but be
yeah stand ready stand up no seat but be
ready okay give us a moment
recognize that the
idea of what you may perceive to be the
translation of the speech into your
language make from time to time sound as
if you are
being told
something when many times if you are
paying attention you will understand
that you are being given something that
indicates it is time for you to
respond simp we pay attention to the
difference in the patterns and you will
recognize when you are being given
something that indicates that you can in
fact share what you have to
share all
right ask question you said you wish to
communicate yes this means you may share
you may ask whatever you will are we
doing it verbally it will come through
vertually okay but simply we are saying
that the patterns you may recognize as
speech may be different than what you
recognize as the pattern that are
created with my Consciousness and in
this way it may be at times not
recognizable in a way you are familiar
with and you may not realize when you
are being given an opportunity to talk
okay simply feel with your heart and
respond instinctively all right all
right one
more sing you song song
away your
EO six dolphins that I had a dream with
that I swam with in a lagoon was was
that like a vision of seeing Maui at a
future time [Music] [Music]
rep
presentent also symbolically symbol
six density communication communication
Sy
represent many
many
area your world our world which we
share m Al Al
sou
sh area you call New
Zeal oh so point
oh so point
of area you
call M M
also area in Great
in Great
Wall Northern
wall you call jop
and Three Points along
Three Points along
with
area Coast you call
Coast you call
per
[Music] also a yeah you yeah you
call
Central America America
Six
Points of
six dreamers to represent six
dreamers to represent six
[Music] Danity
Danity
dreamers ah are grouping
Gathering our
Consciousness we
[Music] present understanding dream
present understanding dream
[Applause]
sharing understanding dream living understanding
living understanding
same that you do Dreamer
do Dreamer
what was activated when I heard your
name in the throat area just exact well
in a way explain more of what happens
and how that will
help intera share
dream M
[Music] Recreation Recreation
memor
creation you live now you live then and
[Music] at this you remember
at this you remember
communication
sharing you share dream asleep now you share
you share dream asleep now you share
dream awake you speak you
Echo you share you
communicate now dreams true your throut
dream become
physical awake and Open
Door awaken open
instrument awake and open ability sing
with
us you me
what the connection between the star
serus and the Dolphins is is
Danity
Consciousness dreamers in
dreamers in
communication sing with
serious hundreds of
years Serious Sign of dream service
serious beings live in energy
sea we live in energy
SE we together share many same dreams
dreams
you when receive Echo serious energy
many times past you
think energy
energy
mean serious is water
beings amibian not live in water SE live in
amibian not live in water SE live in
energy
see you mind translate as water
amphibious I energy
I energy
dreamer energy Earth counterpart to
Serious
energy will you tell me please I've
never fully
understood the integration a couple of
years ago
of
sensing myself as dolphin and giving
birth as a dolphin
share dream non physical share dream
physical money from
at
Incarnation as dreamers dreamers
Incarnation as
[Music] human
human
exchange interchange incarnate
human dreamer dreamer
human share non physical energies of
birth we share gateways of opening in
dream assist gateways of opening in
dream we assist gateways of opening in
birth also connection
communication Aris Aris
arist
assistant Gateway opening of birth in
Earth
planet do you feel my
communication when I Feel
Love feel
dream feel song
feel light warm light fun
light happy
light love
light um I'm going to have I decided to
have the water bir with my
child whenever my husband and I
agree within water share our energy w
ass um is there a particular name of the
um is there a particular name of the
dolphin that's been coming to me in my
dreams is it you dreamer or oh now oh
dolphin dreamers
dreamers
you name dream dreamer name all of us
name one of us
dreamer
I you will be there
now energy be body be new
and other
dreamer Maui
Spirit be everywhere body be New
Zealand well who who will be there to
interact with me in Maui Maui
dreamers so dreamer one dreamer two
dreamer three and on like
that okay oh be sa
Dreamer speak us all dream be
same okay uh Lori and I are going to
Malibu next
Friday um is there would is there
something that you would like to to give
to us to assist us in communicating with
you right now
share dream swim dream play Dream be as
dreamers in water
absorb Energy share
mentality through
water okay so are you saying to get in
the water with you
hey well
okay I'm just thinking it was cold um
dream be
warm okay I like that a lot are we going
to be able to
hug dream hug
dream hug
okay touch be
brief why why why would it be breath
more must be in
[Music] dream more must play in dream okay
dream okay
um what I'd like to do right now is just
open and let others ask questions to you
dreamer dreamer
dreamer receive or
Echo I have a poem that I wrote for you
last Thursday when I woke and I I was so
aware of your love and
energy and I felt that it was flowing
from me like a co-creation so I wrote it
down and I would like to share it with
you and all the dolphins and all the
humans too and I call it dolphin
dream the dolphins swim the Seas of my
Consciousness do I walk the land of
their Consciousness we are moving closer to
Consciousness we are moving closer to
each other thoughts and feelings
blending into one flow of love until the
bonds between us link our separate
worlds into one ecstatic waking
dream thank you very
much than your
song Thank for sharing
[Music] song thank
you wece your
Echo dreamer I had a Dre speak up please I
dreamer I had a Dre speak up please I
had a also
uh last week
order be very playful in dream
reality we swim through dream reality of
you all you swim through dream reality of us
all you swim through dream reality of us
all
your interpretation of interpretation of
Interac
had you receive my
echo I yes I received your Echo I don't
the question no question be sharing
be sharing
dream you
remember I
remember just the the flow of uh of the
water SE and the water and speak up
please I remember the flow of the water
SE and
the flow be flow of consciousness
it was it was a lot of fun it was
something that I wanted to do as water
ski and I always thought that it would
look really meat at um at b or wherever
I've been I seen that but I didn't know
if that
would I always was concerned whether
that was hurting the Dolphins when
they is that painful to have them
pulling on strings and
being Guided by
no physical
pain oh some mental pain in
oh some mental pain in
captivity no physical pain joy in
interaction not all
dolphin dreamers not all
dreamers not all
dolphin understand and all
empathize all find
Joy but
manal pain for some captivity all captivity all
[Music]
Freedom W interact we share you play
Come seea ocean we
seea ocean we
play no physical pain no mental pain no
Spirit pain in
Ocean to fly in
oan not let you
drown will you keep the Sharks
away shark polarity polarity
dolin Soul
yes shark
polarity dolin
Soul reflection reflection
reflection
do past
[Music]
do you interact
now sh blending
polarity see here
see here
Fe need for
shark [Music]
[Music]
words not go
inside as much
now avoid voidance of either to each
each
few cases where dolphins not dreamers
some
interaction not much
now more dolphin become
dreamer more human become Dreamer in
in
dream no more
Hunters no more teeth in
darkness dream warm dream
bright see here
everywhere everyone no hiding place no nothing to
everyone no hiding place no nothing to
hide no [Music] [Music]
need
love we
play we
share dreams
dreams
together night of dream is world of
dream now forever sing your
song sand our
Echo all right
Cherry ni B I would like to know what
the cause is of my current health
problem and how I may read it health
what problem Health
what recognize I am becoming selectively
third density
death and I no longer hear the words
that represent or reflect an idea that
means or implies that you have not got
the ability to change this idea I I
don't disregard the fact that I I have
the ability we understand semantically a
problem in your Society is something you
think is a situation that will not
change it is in its own definition something
it is in its own definition something
that is repetitious in a negative cycle
a problem it seems to be a wall seems to
be something that cannot transform it is
not that you will get rid of it it is
that you can learn to transform it what
is the situation that you prefer to
transform I'm currently going through
allergy hives
allergy allergy
allergy
yes in this way for how long have you
experienced this idea
three [Music]
months are you doing in your life
something very new within the same time
period that you feel unsure about in
your foing yes job new job all
right you may simply be creating a
rejection symbol that allows you to feel
as if your environment is rejecting you
and so you symbolize the idea that you
form a rejection in that way it is
simply the idea of needing to allow
yourself more trust with your ability
more trust with your intuition more
trust in the ideas that you create for
yourself may I ask you a question yes is
your new job something that excites you
or is there something more exciting to
you in
life both both what is it that is more
exciting is what is more exciting
something that if you did what was more
exciting would mean you wouldn't be
doing the job you are doing
now probably probably all right why is
it that you would prefer to do the job
you have as opposed to what it would be
that would truly excite you
more I think La is probably self self
assurance self assurance all right
that's a very good reason for
maintaining something that you do not
really enjoy and perhaps time to get
there oh time that's another good
reason you are very creative all of you
are very creative and can create more
than enough reasons to not do what it is
you truly know represents
you what is it you are more excited
about doing
well many things but including healing
all right in what way do you imagine
right in what way do you imagine
yourself
healing is it through the hands
yes all right are there areas are there
facilities are there in your
institutions are there Gatherings
wherein you could be of service in this
way yes I'm doing that all
right as you allow yourself more and
more opportunity to recognize that that
is how you truly wish to function you
can allow yourself more and more
opportunity to recognize that you will
be completely
supported completely
supportive you will attract the
situations to you in the connections
that you make that will give you more
situations and more situations in which
you can apply yourself in this manner
and you will find that you will be able
to create a type of momentum that will
balance nicely with the idea of what it
is you wish to do and that balance will
create exactly the support the amount of
support you require in
life do you believe this can happen yes
if you truly believe this can happen
then all you need to do is live as if
you believe this can happen and it will
happen thank you that is all there is to
it it is simple mechanics and simple
physics understand that you are always a
100% idea but you may find that the
idea but you may find that the
definition of where you
are directing that 100% may be
fractionated in many different multiple
percentages so let us say your job you
have now is job a the job you wish to be
the healer is job B you
follow the idea is that you are now
perhaps 100% the idea of job a and job B and so
100% the idea of job a and job B and so
because you are the idea of both of them
then you still require both of them to
have support in your life as soon as you
are willing to shift the percentage
toward what you truly find exciting in
this way then that will be allowed to
support you 100% because that is where
your 100% will be as long do you
maintain let us say for example 80% in
the idea of what it is that excites you
the most and 20% still in the job that
doesn't then the job that excites you
the most can only support you 80%
because that is all you are giving to it
when you give 100% to that idea then it
will support you 100% just as giving
100% now to the idea of being both job A
and B is what supports you
100% you follow me yes is this
clarifying some ideas for you and
allowing the idea of making decisions to
not be a struggle but simply something
you can allow to be obvious very much oh
thank you very much you are then also
willing to allow yourself to be here yes
you sure one
moment all right you may yes thank you
for sure
um I have
speak up I have a relationship with a
girlfriend of mine that um I find to
be well it's it's on a it's on a
different plane than any relationship
that I have with any of my other friends
yes um and we have a lot of psychic
abilities going through us like she'll
she'll say something that I was just
thinking or I'll say something she was
just thinking or I'll say something
before she finishes it how synchronous
you are vibrating in a similar
wavelength and interpreting the overall
Consciousness similarly yeah I don't know um my sense
similarly yeah I don't know um my sense
is that there this occurs because there
is deep affection and love in the relationship relationship
telepathy is
love telepathy is
communication inspired by love it is you
willing and your friend willing to
operate on the same type of wavelength
that allows you to translate the
infinite in a similar manner so you are
expressing each other's synchronicity
you are in step with each
other I I see that and I I find it um
humorous to a lot of points that
sometimes do laugh a lot of time but
she's also been feeling some concern why
I wish she was here I would had hoped
that she would be here so she could
express herself but um she
is she is scared of of this just sort of
spooked by it and I I that is simply
because she does not understand what it
is she has no definition for
it it is in her terms a mystery and she
is simply creating the idea of a habit
of fearing what she does not understand
because she thinks that it is something
that is happening outside of her and not
fully within her and therefore fully
under her control she thinks it is
something that can get out of control
she thinks it represents something that
represents being able to be out of
control something Beyond something above
her it isn't yeah
um is there a past life or many past
many many
with could you no
[Music] I was hoping to
I was hoping to
hoping
wishing why
why
uh for I guess curiosity sake to see
what the connections there's no such
thing as Idle curiosity use your
curiosity and discover what connections
you need to discover use your
imagination use your feelings use the
relationship let the relationship
reflect to you what is very obvious
between you let yourselves explore
together and discover any connections
you have had before then that exercise
that sharing is what will allow both of
you to come to more easy terms with the
ability well she has a sense that it's
that it's a negative connection and I
want to be able to um
why because she choose to perceive that
it has to be negative everything has the
ability to be perceived as negative and
positive if she chooses to believe it is
negative then that is her choice and
that is why there may be negative
manifestation to reinforce the negative
belief I've been trying to explain no
trying I have her path is her
own she will discover what she needs to
discover when she needs to discover it
you can be of assistance by simply
reflecting that you believe it is
positive if that is the case and let her
pick up from you when she's good and
ready the idea that well if you are
involved in the same relationship and
obviously if it is working for you
positively there's really no reason why
it can't work for her in the same way
and that if it can used to work for her
in a negative way then that is obviously
the way she chooses to relate to it and
therefore the negative effect she gets
is completely and totally under her
control I if you can both go through the
same idea and you can experience it
positively then that is an indication to
her that she can
too you follow me yeah I or are you
experiencing it negatively as
well um speak up okay one one of the
things that I had a sense about about
her past life of hers was guys um of
being a witch all right and um that is
not in of itself a negative description
right well I don't see it as being I
don't see it as being negative I see
that she got
um all right all right all right that
was this is now that's what I've been
this is now that's what I've been
explaining to her that that she's
allowing herself to still be punished
for being a witch in a past life by
fearing it in this life all right very
good and I've been explaining that she's
continuing to allow herself to be um
punished and limited by that
experience however that
um that doesn't seem to be assisting her
and I feel well then I ask her what she
gets out of experiencing the continuance
of
punishment I've just been feeling so
frustrated CU I'm one with you are
assisting her by fully being yourself
there is no need for frustration you are
doing brilliantly the more you are willing to
brilliantly the more you are willing to
Simply Be Yourself and funnel the
positive idea through yourself as an
example then you are being of assistance
you cannot force anything upon them you
cannot rescue her no one needs to be
rescued follow
follow
me if you are coming at her with that
attitude then you are reinforcing the
scenario in which she is very very
easily able to create a situation in
which she believes she needs to be
rescued and you are going right along
with her saying yes you do need to be
rescued you are in a very bad
situation thank you I'll throw you a
rope but it may not be long enough
add the reinforcement of the negative
belief and if it is long enough it will
probably be covered with something
slippery do not play into her
reality be your reality and let her see
your reality so that if if if she
chooses to she can share
yours the indications and the sharings
that you have psychically are very
strong indication that she can if you
are but willing to function as the
positive reflection then you give her
something to have a handhold
on I I totally agree and I love what
you're saying and I intend to the tape
so she can hear this all right um the
other thing that um that I wanted to um
to get some Enlightenment on is I had um
a dream of a butterfly
and transformational
symbol okay th caterpillar cocoon butterfly
okay th caterpillar cocoon butterfly
metamorphosis transformation Freedom
relief flight higher awareness overview
oversold okay um that the dream
manifested the next day with a butterfly
landing on my notebook in in a classroom
in school I mean it was just so strange
to see a butterfly in the building but
it landed there not
anymore um it landed there was not
afraid I picked it up and I let it go um
because my coworkers threatened to kill
it and
I um vicious butterfly
[Music] yes I was real upset by to many
yes I was real upset by to many
individuals that symbol may be extremely
vicious for it may allow feeling to come
up within them that they in no way shape
or form are ready to look at right
exactly a butterfly is always been a
symbol of freedom to me well thank you
for physicalizing and manifesting the
idea of your causal and dream realities
into physical manifestation so easily
utilize the same degree of manifestation
and trust with your friend you and she
are both butterflies all
all
right yes no maybe yes yes yes it's up
to you you can say no no no you can say
maybe maybe maybe I don't care no I I I
want to say yes I'm just I'm I don't see
how I can Preposterous you are a
butterfly you have a wonderful overview
you can see just fine okay what where
I'm coming from Bashar is is that I can
see that I can manifest anything I want
in my own life I just don't see that I
have power over anybody else you
don't okay so if I wish if I trying to
create something in my mind what I was
gathering is what I would like to have
as a Rel the idea is to be in your own
Universe the fullest reflection of what
you know to be true for you so that you
can shine into other universes and let
them know that there are other ways to
be again if you are shining forth with
that self-empowerment you will love her no
self-empowerment you will love her no
matter what she chooses and so you will
always feel as if the relationship is
exactly the way you need it to
be no matter what she is going through
you will love her just the thing oh I
do I do then that is it m there is no
need to continue the expectation of the
way you think she should act to make you
feel better about the relationship if
you are complete with the idea that you
are are learning with each other then it
won't matter to you what she does you
will love her just the same and so to
you from your point of view from your
end of things the relationship is now
and will be just
fine because you are willing to let her
do what she needs to do and that is a
part of the
relationship and that allowance is what
will paradoxically allow her the
quickest opportunity to make the
transformation and represent herself in
your reality in the way you are now
assuming you would like to see
her you follow me yes if you enjoy being
a butterfly then Let Her Fly where she
needs to as
well she will land on the flowers she
needs to land
upon when I had um I have been doing
channeling of and what I I had channeled
in her presence
guys um she got
very when I was coming out of it
something she said went through her she
was very frightened by that that is all
right she has opened up a doorway
individuals that have the habit of
fearing what they think is unknown
within them will generally then create
that reaction anytime they allow
themselves to experience ing anything
new about themselves it will pass there
wasn't any Spirit or anything that did
actually go through that was just an
experience of a heart Fe manifesting
itself yes okay that's what I that's what I
yes okay that's what I that's what I
thought I just I know that the spirits
that have been coming through me have
been very positive and I could imagine
if they did go through and and departing
from me that they could be anything but
positive so so I I just guess I needed
to have that validated remind her that
in her habit of
invalidation she will usually then
render an experience that could be taken
as exciting into one of anxiety because
excitement and anxiety are the same
energy one from a positive point of view
and one from a negative point of view
she is only experiencing more and more
of her own ecstasy more and more of her
own excitement but because of her habit
of invalidation she is experiencing ing
that energy as anxiety and fear rather
than ecstasy and excitement it is the
same energy her attitude and her point
of view will totally and utterly
determine the effect she gets out of it
whether it will be the rush of anxiety
or the warm Rush of
[Music] knowingness you follow yes I do thank
knowingness you follow yes I do thank
you very
much uh two question all right number
one I know we have many lives past
future present alternate i' like to know
about the one approximately about 2400
years ago from
now till 2500 why uh I just want to know
if I existed at that time I could tell
you why
afterwards one moment we
we
sense what you might call a few
manifestations what you might call
counterpart consciousness of the overs
soul that you are one as a
warrior one as an artist
planter we sent the agricultural idea
being connected with what you would call
American Indian cultures of some sort we
sent the others being connected to what
you would call the
euroasian areas Mediterranean areas
[Music]
we also sense a few female incarnations
in that time one
time one
at a courier of
Swords there is some manifestation both
male and female in this time frame of
the idea of priests and priestesses
there is manifestation in this time of
Egyptian Heritage as
well there is also some degree of
understanding of an individual portion
of your soul expressing itself in the
terms you would call architect
one approximately what you would call
also 3,000 of your years ago in a
shamanistic
sense this is what we are perceiving at
this time there may be more connected and
time there may be more connected and
convective flow to this
idea before we continue you allow us to
remind you that the idea of the
connections to past lives are being
created from the
present you create the past and the
future from the present because the now
is the only time in which you ever
exist therefore recognize that our
perception of your flow and your
perception of your flow come from two
totally different Universal perspectives
of what is being created now now in the
present and the idea many times as to
why we hesitate to delineate and label
the idea you call past lives is because
many times it takes you out of the
present power and allows you to believe that the
power and allows you to believe that the
power for understanding yourself in the
present comes from your past which it
does not now with these ideas and with with
not now with these ideas and with with
what we perceive that we can also
continue to share with you to some
degree has this to any degree already
been of some service or assistance very
much what I like to know is about the
I'm really concerned about the warrior
why are you so
concerned uh
well mostly because he you said euro
Asians right some place around
Mediterranean that's when the country
I'm presently from was formed around
that area 2500 to 2400 years
ago and it was by the by the hands of a
warrior who gathered the people and made
the first civilization which was called
the Persian Empire which are you
speaking of Saron Saron yeah exactly I
speak of Saron and from the Aryan race
that he was from and he formed the
people together which we called in our
own language the mod
people you have many strong connections
as a warrior in that regime but not
Sargon itself
itself
Sargon is a collective
Consciousness you
share a part of it with many other
individuals one of the individuals you
share a part of that Consciousness with
is the physiological
Channel wow it is also a very strong
Orion connection very strong Orion in
con and follow
me some ways the constellation you call
Orion in your sky is very strongly
represented Incarnation into that particular
Incarnation into that particular
civilization that particular culture
particularly at that time particularly
through the being you know as
Sargon right I
follow there are many cycles now
completing many cycles of this Warrior
aspect this curved sword aspect and the
horns of the Moon aspect all coming
together now in balance in blending and
in light for now it is being Blended
together and recognized that no longer
are civilizations created from
conquering but from
nurturing in this way you are now
beginning to assimilate this energy and
you are beginning to balance the old
negativity with the Positive light do
not worry all of these Cycles are now
coming into
fruition there is no need to feel that
there is a remaining negativity holding
on holding over from this idea from this
aspect you can now use the strength of
the warrior in peaceful
ways you can gather the same Force
fortitude the same resolve and the same
conviction but your sword is now a sword
of reason of light of love it will cut
through anything and allow there to be
anything and allow there to be
balance the balance represented by the
edge of the sword Harmony light
peace creativity growth and a new type
creativity growth and a new type
of Empire
building we follow me yes you will now
begin to find perhaps many more
connections to this
area and much that is
associated with some of the original AR
ideas particularly where it
involves symbols such as the sand such
as Dark Crystal such as Emerald Stones
such as as lapis blue
[Music] stones such as the archetypal
stones such as the archetypal
representation of the subscreen
consciousness of your planet represented
in the form you call gin or
Genies all of these ideas now are coming
back because you recognize the magic of
the times for sardon was in a sense a
magician a sorcerer M as well as a
military individual you follow me yes all of
individual you follow me yes all of
these ideas now can be put forth after
having come through very ancient
Atlantean times for Saron is also a
Reincarnation of an ancient Atlantean
King and therefore represent the idea of
the building of
Empires but now that things are being
built in positive ways all of that
energy is being funneled and F focused
Into The keenest Cutting Edge but a
cutting edge of brilliant
light and reasoning loving
power thank you
Warrior thank you
sage has this assisted you very much
thank you one more question one more
uh uh ever since I was a kid about like
years I could never go to a sleep by
myself uh I always have various
creatures in the spirits yes foll me and
want to cut me down and gra me it is
again the
archetypal surfacing of the energy you
call gin or genies
demonic representations but it is only
the old negative energy cloaking itself
in forms that are projections of your
own fears your own past fears your own
Consciousness all of these ideas are
simply representations of the power you
know you wield but can recognize that
now that you are in touch with it you
have always been able to be in touch
with that level of power even on the
negative side and now you simply
recognize that because you do contain
the power on the negative side just as
strong is on the positive side there is
nothing nothing nothing nothing there is
nothing no manifestation no
consciousness no Spirit no form in any
way to perform no matter how negative
that has any more power than you do it
is equal equal equal and thus you don't
have to buy into it you don't have to
fear it you are on equal
it you are on equal
terms for you have been just as powerful
a warrior in that way as they
are and now you can get on with what you
prefer in a positive life and when you
shed that positive light they will all
transform into the projections of your
Consciousness that are more
representative of
nature beings the spirit of the Earth
beings the spirit of the Earth
itself in trust and love and
support Pleasant Dre
you are opening many gates and into
those Gates and through those Gates
shall pour The Fragrant oils and Waters
of cleansing from earn jars shimmering
jars shimmering
gold and enlightening
silver are now the foundations of the
kingdoms you will build within your you sleep in
Joy sleep in
peace your blanket of stars your bed of
Earth are all you need
Warrior you have your sword the king
Cutting Edge of trust and conviction thank conviction thank
you
B I have no questions B but I wish to
share some do share Strawberry
yes I have been on a trip as you know to
Washington and Tennessee and so many of
the truths that I have had an
opportunity to share with people have
really share loudly loud sh um I've
really take on a lot of depth I I did a
couple of seminars I worked with a
number of individuals and the most
marvelous experience of of recognizing
in incredible depth that every single
thing that each individual was creating
was totally
true um was 100% their creation I had a
woman in one of my seminars who was
um creating the consideration that she
was having tremendous difficulty guiding
her husband to discover things that she
thought he should
discover and asked me to assist her with
that and I and I said uh I I said write
down this program it was done very
dramatically she took out the paper and
the pen and we all prepared it and I
said the first step is for you to
discover that everything that your
husband has been telling you is totally
100% true and correct
had to develop the willingness to
discover that and she said but he's been
yelling and arguing against this yes
totally correct 100% And I invited her
to discover that all of his truth was
100% correct using references that uh
that were of value to her and then
inviting her uh instead of resisting the
flow simply sharing one's own Viewpoint
as you have been sharing with us so many
times but not evaluating the other
person's being judgment that this is
right or wrong or that they must follow
this path but that everything that they
are creating always is
100% and perfect creation yes and
and and how immense was her Joy
oh she got so um keed out she us an old
terminology kept walking into walls you
know so and so did everyone else and you know
so and so did everyone else and you know
the the the feedback of what had
happened throughout the Washington area
that I got from people one after the
other after the other was immense joy
that the whole area had changed and was
changing constantly because there was a
progression of these concepts of truth
that were now going all throughout the
Washington area to the embassies and to
the to the different people that they
were you are now beginning to equalize
you are now beginning to communicate
you're now beginning to realize that you
are your government yes and that you can
share the same dream yes and allow all
to be of service
service
yes thank you for being a crystal
feed oh my pleasure thank you for being
a Crystal Seed watermelon SE strawberry
SE strawberry
okay that's part of it you get the whole
Ecstasy of this thing there Rippling
waves going all over the place even
Reagan was sitting there in a telepathic
mode laughing and coming up with
Concepts that he hadn't uh he hadn't
created in a long time so was nice shall
enjoy watching you all plant your
ecstasies one other sharing before I go
on um I felt a tremendous um love and
Affinity uh with uh dreamer as you can
imagine that's I've been a dreamer
myself for a long time I and uh I just
wanted to express um the desire to
articulate that uh love and Affinity
with with that being um I have it
telepathically and yet there seems to be
um a a a design to articulate it in a
physical sense I know I know as I'm
saying that discover of course because
that is the sharing that the dolphin is
offering on that plane yes oh very nice
that's good so um next time he
physically comes through I would like to
have the opportunity to share that love
with with thank you you may also
interact with the dolphins that are
available in your ocean oh I will do
that I'm I'm good on this weekend thank
you
enjoy speak up I live in Mal I wanted to
tell you all that I now that I live
there I find I dream all the time and I
always dream but it's even clearer so
guys I don't think you have to go in the
water just to get in touch with oh you
do not have to no but it is an
invitation to become more familiar with
their world on all levels intimacy
yes wonderful stuff and I wanted to ask
you some questions about our tourist and
about um could you speak up so we can
hear are some astronomical questions
about the symbols that will be going on
um in the near future with your planet
we have a planet that's going to make a
contact to your planet Uranus will be at
21 s soon what are some of the symbols
that might come through for us and you
how will it affect you how will we
affect you you l m you this thank you
now first of all realize in this way
that we are slightly out of phase with
your dimensionality and though
connections can be inferred lines can be
drawn we are not specifically in your
dimensionality in your physical
perception in this way therefore the
ideas that can connect will have to do
with the opening the funneling
the opening of gates of the unconscious
the opening of the gates of the
subconscious and allowing yourself to
recognize that what we represent to you
are the mental workings of your
subconscious of your
unconscious that is our place so to
speak in your representational
charts you follow me yeah consciousness
that is represented by your planet our
planet and Sirus
conjunctions that may be of assistance
to
you may come when you draw lines of
[Music] inference
inference
between your planet of
Uranus and the third star are in the
belt of Orion that you call
Mina it will be in your
hemisphere the right star of the belt
rather than the left there are all
so individuals that are surrounding you
this night of your
time that may be of assistance with the
terminologies the conjunctions and the
symbologies that that you are referring
to for the terminology for translation
does not exist within the physical
channel for us to
utilize you follow me yeah do they have
a
name the terminology is in your language
for what you are asking of us the
terminology does not exist within the
physiological channel to translate the
concept well I understood that you mean
that there are um manifestations of
people who have the terminology near me
okay and so I asked you if those people
you have put out your idea this night of
your time those that have heard you and
can be of assistance in determining the
conjunctions you seek may be able to
Simply communicate with you after this
interaction this night of your time if
there is anyone present now who knows
that this is the case with themselves
you may simply indicate by raising your
hand
do you find any response yeah then you
may enjoy yourselves in working out the
scenario in the symbolic terminology
that you understand and priming the tool
and the machine that will give you the
precise understanding in your own
terminology okay there is enough
awareness of our vibrational frequency
in some of the individuals and in
connection with the Orion idea to be
able to glean for you some of the
meanings that can be extrapolated from
our connection with
you thank you and I think what about the
connection with our I think it's
Saturday when we have a lunar eclipse your
eclipse your
moon to some degree also represents the
subconscious but in this way you will
find that this alignment in and of itself
that this alignment in and of itself
will function as the opening of a valve
that will allow more accelerated
awareness to come into your planetary
sphere regarding New Birth one
moment I see all
right there are other
individuals who can give
you because you have a stronger
connection to them in this particular
Avenue who can give you more precise
information along the lines of the last
two questions you have asked we are a
referring not only to individual in your
physiological reality but also what you
would refer to as other channeled
consciousness
one of them may be
found in what you call the Malibu
area you will find that you will attract
what you
need you will run
into the information that will lead you
to this channeled
Consciousness in whatever form it may
appear that will allow you to understand
the questions you are asking this
evening of your time there is a momentum
in this and there is a connection a
necessary Connection in
this we find that we are able to say
that Frameworks are being set up or laid
down if you
wish Frameworks upon which you will find
much Clarity and much awareness in the
months to come as you call
it particularly in the first three
months of your New
Year between that time and the six
month will come much clarification with
these ideas much clarification with the
idea of conjunction much clarification
with the idea of reinforcements and
overlaps much more raw understanding if
you will but there are
others who have been designed to give it
to
you more than
we we thank
you thank you sure one
more there will be but a few moments
remaining for the timing of this
interaction this evening of your one
moment there are adjustments
what you each
choose to
believe is utterly up to
you what you choose to
believe is utterly the reality you
experience what any
individual including myself
has to say about anything in your
lives is pragmatically
inconsequential compared to what you
have to say about
yourself do not
forget that we are here as a reflection
of what you already are
and do not
forget that what you experience in your
life emotionally physically spiritually
mentally is your
responsibility and therefore within your
power to change as you desire to change
it this time of
transforming is a time once again of
conviction a time of willingness a time
of doing a time of living the idea of
living the dream that you
are it calls for
boldness it calls for
conviction it calls for
ecstasy it calls for
doing it calls for being
analysis is all well and good and has
its
place the equivocation of this and that
the comparison of these and
those the meanings of
that the inferences of this the
inflections of something
else all of these ideas have their place
and are valid in your Storehouse of
tools but they are all expressions of mentality and
mentality and
mentality is not the seed of what you
are it is an
echo but a reflection in physical
reality in physical terms in physical
dreams of the
of the
Consciousness that all mentality is
within it is but one
band One wavelength one
frequency you can allow it to remain
filled to the
brim with chatter
which again in its time can serve a purpose purpose
and
and you can also
choose to allow
all bans of Consciousness to flow as
clear and pure as
streams as clear light
with action with conviction with doing
anytime you are so
moved to truly believe and trust that
you can do what excites you you
you you
will be supported by the universe by the
infinite
many of you are discovering that that is
how life
Works many are choosing not to but that
is their choice but life still works
that way
forther if you choose to
believe in Failure if you choose to
believe in struggle if you choose to
believe in
negativity the universe will always back
you up and say if that's the way you want
up and say if that's the way you want
it here it
is and so
remember that in
choosing positive idea in choosing
integration in choosing to understand
that everything
is there for a reason for growth and
expansion and
awareness it is not that you are
learning to do something you don't
already do you are simply doing it in a
do you are simply doing it in a
different fashion than you have been
doing it and as you apply this positive
understanding then the universe will say
in no uncertain terms 100% guaranteed if
that's the way you want it so be it it
is
automatic it is
instantaneous regardless of the linear
time framework the change happens
instantly it is your opportunity to
allow the symbols that represent the
change to transform in a
representational way within the highing
framework by knowing that you have
changed and therefore imbu yet all the
old symbols with new meanings that will
allow them to become new
symbols once again no symbol has built
in meaning no symbol means anything they
are all blank the meaning you fill them
with is the effect you get out of
them you are
Divinity you are the
infinite the infinite is all within
it the infinite knows
itself as its
own idea and also knows itself as all of the
idea and also knows itself as all of the
ideas it is within the Consciousness
that it is you are all
infinite with a capital
I use that eye and let yourselves see
what is
clearly clearly
the idea that you are then live
it live
it as soon as you
do you will then experience yourself in
the now
moment as the expression of the
infinite and ecstasy
will make it seem as
if you have never experienced anything else our
love the love of the
dreamers and the sharing of energy is
with you
always all levels all
Consciousness allow yourselves to swim
in the sea that once
again is the
idea that Consciousness is not in the
body the body is in
Consciousness excitement and
ecstasy and action to you
all good
night [Music] [Applause]
[Applause]
good for here