All this evening of your time as you
create time to exist.
We will begin this
interaction. This evening of your time
with
the This evening of your time with the
idea of what you call in your
society habits. In this way do recognize that
habits. In this way do recognize that
many times when you are creating the
exploration
of the ideas that you desire to
experience in your life. Many times as
you create that
create that
exploration, you will also create along
with it the idea of so-called
blockages, socal
impasses, so-called stumbling
blocks and
Many times whether it is from a recognition,
times whether it is from a recognition,
a cognition, a
creation of something having to do with
the present life or another
life, you will usually hinge it upon the
idea you call habit. the idea that you
have been taught to do something a
certain way, have believed that that is
a representation of the only real
reality and thus find yourself
exemplifying that methodology over and
over again. Even when you are dealing
with things that no longer need that
particular methodology as a tool of
relating to the new idea you are being
or becoming.
Now, in no way, shape or
form are we saying that your experience
of this idea is invalid? No.
But do
recognize that the idea that something
is the result of what you call a
habit is still only yet another way to
believe that your reality is rather than
a representation of the way it actually
is. Regardless of what you
believe, the idea of something being a
habit only has manifestable reality in
your physical experience when you
believe that your definition of a habit
is something that is difficult to
change. The habit is only a concept like
any other
concept. It is not a fundamental law of
existence. You may allow it to attain that status
You may allow it to attain that status
when you
choose to view that the situations that
occur in your life are the result of
something that you deem to be difficult
to
change. But in this way, do recognize
that the idea of a habit is a
construction, an artificial construct
just like anything else. And that basing
a situation in your
life, the reason for its occurrence upon
what you call a habit is only basing one
illusion upon
another. You are not basing it upon
anything that has any more substance,
any more
foundation than any of the situations
you are attempting to change.
You all follow along so far.
Simply in this
way would
suggest that when you are creating your
own cognitions of your relationship to the
cognitions of your relationship to the
realities you are
experiencing. For you are the realities
you are experiencing.
You are the reality you are
experiencing. It is not something
outside you. And in this
you. And in this
way, we would suggest that you pay
attention to yourself. Pay
attention to
how you construct your conscious
you construct your conscious
relationship to the idea you are
experiencing. Listen to yourselves. Many
times you will hear in your own words,
in your own patterns of thought. You
will hear how you are consciously
choosing to believe that the situation
is difficult to
change. Listen to
yourselves. Listen to how you phrase
ideas. Listen to what you say. for many
more times than you
think. It is a consciously aware choice
that you are making to have the
experiences you are having simply based
upon what you hear yourself saying you
believe in. Listen to yourselves and
recognize that so-called
habits are only created by you to be
habits because of the way you choose to
think about the
concept. That is the only thing that
makes a habit a
habit. The way you choose to think about
it. The way you choose to create such a
concept to exist in your reality.
There is nothing built in as a mechanism
that makes a habit work regardless of
your belief system.
Nothing. It is all a product of your
belief system. All of it.
There is nothing that you experience in
physical reality that is not a product
of your conscious belief system except
for the
generalized themes that you experience
in life. But these are very very
general. All of the
specifics are the result of your belief
system as a physical consciousness.
And if you are simply willing to pay
more attention to yourselves, give
yourselves the respect you are due and
love yourselves unconditionally enough
to
listen. Then you will hear yourselves
creating the very realities you are
struggling to change. And then you will
simply recognize you do not have to
struggle to change them. All you need to
do is to say something else. And to know
that that is just as true as anything
you have ever said.
Following.
Yes. Something like what we call the
real strong habits like heroin that
stronger drug addictions. Is that really
because the people that have chosen to
use that as a tool are such strong
creators that they have done an
excellent job of creating
dependency in a sense. Yes, they could
walk away from that still. Oh yes. Do
recognize that the usual connection to
that particular idea is the creation of
the removal of taking responsibility for
your creations from yourself and putting
it on something
else. But you are still creating
that. That is how powerful you are. Is
that the same thing as spiritual
anything? Everything in physical reality
is only a symbol of the idea you are
being. Nothing in physical
reality comes with its own innate
existence until you give it life and
meaning. You are all of the physical
reality you are
experiencing. One more time.
You are all of the physical reality you
are experiencing. Follow me. Therefore, any
experiencing. Follow me. Therefore, any
physiological symbol is only a
representation, a reflection, a
mirroring of the idea you are being. in
a form that says you are still creating
the idea of your reality to be something
outside of you rather than what you are.
That is the only reason you need a
physiological reflection because you
believe that as a physical being reality
must be reflected outside of you.
Does that mean you can change your body
to pretty much basically now there will
be to some extent some limitations
according to once again the generalized
overall agreement you have with the mass
consciousness as to what it is that will
serve the mass consciousness. Anything
beyond that in your terms, you will not
find yourself able to change into. Or
let us put it this way. It is not that
you cannot change into it. But if you do
change into something that does not
serve this mass consciousness, then you
will change out of the mass
consciousness at the same time you
change into the other idea. You will
disappear from this reality.
You follow me? Yes, I do. But you can
change into a variety of ideas. in this
mass consciousness. Do recognize that because
consciousness. Do recognize that because
this is the transformational life, this
is that particular transformational era
in your history, so to speak, that there
are many more things that are possible
now than used to be because you are at
the end of the cycle of limitation. And
thus, your mass consciousness is
allowing for more things to be possible
to reflect to itself that it can and
does in fact create all of the reality
it experiences. So there is more, as you
would say, leeway now than there used to
be. However, again, recognize that if it
does not serve any of the purposes
within your entire civilization to all
of a sudden become blue and have six
arms, then you will have chosen to agree
to not make that kind of a change.
But if you do make that kind of a
change, you will not be in this reality.
You will be in the one that making that
kind of a change or being that way is of
service to
what are the general themes that
you birth, death, that idea experiences,
let us say of your ability to recognize
to become cognizant of the fact that you
do create your reality. That is a
general theme. Ideas of recognizing your own
theme. Ideas of recognizing your own
deservability of abundance. That is a
general theme. You follow me? Yes. There
are many ways to explore these
ideas. Deservability, inherent birthright of
Deservability, inherent birthright of
ecstasy, the fact that you create your
own reality. These are all general
themes. Everything else that is more
Everything else that is more
specific you are choosing as a physical
consciousness to simply create that way
to explore the general
theme. In other words, let us say the
general theme is recognizing that since
you are connected to all that is you are
as abundant as you need to be. The idea
of exploring abundance can be explored
through the physiological specifics of
quote unquote being rich or being poor.
You are still exploring the idea of
abundance as a general
theme. And all of the ideas in between
all are still the specifics that explore
the general theme of
abundance. You follow me? It is up to
you to decide which you prefer. The
higher consciousness that you are that
made the choice of the general theme
does not care what you prefer.
Everything to the higher consciousness
is learning
everything. Therefore, that is why it is
left up to your free will to decide
which way you prefer to explore the
general theme. You are
certainly more than allowed to explore
it in
ecstasy. It is up to you.
Does that assist you? Yes, it does.
Thank you. Sharing.
Yes. All right. If you feel such a
All right. If you feel such a
connection, then obviously it is
something that rings true within your
vibration. Can you tell me anything about Can you
Can you tell me anything about Can you
We just connection after all this time.
Yes. Then that is in and of itself a
sign of the timing and lets you know
that there is as much information there
as you wish.
What do you think?
All right. That does not mean you have
not had past connections. But do
remember that you are creating the past
and the future from the present always.
The present is the only time you ever
exist within. Ever.
Therefore, whether you have a cognition
of a so-called past connection or a
cognition of a so-called future
connection, a recognition or a
precognition, it is
only that that is where your focus lies
with reference to the life you are
living now that you are making that
connection.
Everything, every level, every
interaction that there is to have with
that individual, you have had and will
have. The ones you quote unquote
remember, the ones you find yourself
focusing upon are the ones that may be
of service to you to symbolically
reflect the ideas you are choosing to be
in this life. From this point of view,
different lives may connect into
different other lives for their
reference points if they need to.
Therefore, as you are creating your life
now, how is it, as you have already
expressed to some degree with the idea
of the notation of a future life, how is
it that you
feel that knowing about this connection
of energy, knowing about this
interaction, this blending of your
consciousness with your friend's
consciousness, how does that allow
you to make a cognition of your life
right now?
What does it do for you? I like magic
and I like to Oh, create that. All
right. Well, everything in your life is
magic. Everything. When I just today I
shared a friend's baby and I was just
thinking, do I create that or is that
picking up? Well, I could be playing
with. All right. All right. Now, in a
sense, recognize this.
Let us put it this way. If we were
talking to you, oh, let us
say 20 of your years ago, I simply would
have said, yes, you are picking up on a
past life. Today, however, I will say you are
life. Today, however, I will say you are
picking up on a past life that you are
creating from the present in order to
fulfill the needs to recognize who you
are now. It is both true. I do enjoy it.
Yes. All you need to do is recognize
that your imagination will always supply
you with whatever connections are valid
to the idea you are being. Do not look
for accuracy. That is a relative term. The
accuracy. That is a relative term. The
truth is composed of all truths.
Therefore somewhere. Oh yes. Therefore,
however your imagination attracts you to
symbolize a connection is the way you
need to symbolize it to understand it.
That is all there is to it. Okay.
Oh, by all means. Curious. Follow your
curiosity. which leads me to believe I'm
probably on the buzz after of course
can never be off your own button
I saw like a a
honeycomb or cubicle like a vast space
and there was like seemed like all the
way around the wall or whatever
keep going like it
going like it
was there was no lit
I don't
self luminescent. Keep going. Feelings,
impressions, sounds, thoughts. Keep
going. I guess that's that's as far as I
learned at that point. Keep going. Okay.
Well, probably the belly of the mother
ship. Thank you.
It looks like
we understand the idea.
Thank you. Thank
you. How's that
assistant? Find it.
Sure. A shark. Nice. Could you tell me why the
A shark. Nice. Could you tell me why the
dinosaurs died out in this planet? In
this way, you will find that there have
been transmutations of many of those
animal types into many others. And there
are still variations that exist in
different planar dimensions and a few
that exist even in your own dimension.
Some of them have also transformed into
the life forms that you understand and
recognize to be what you call the
lizards and also the birds. In this way,
however, the overall idea you are
referring to, you are now as a
civilization beginning to be aware to
some degree of the idea of what you call
the meteoric commentary bombardment that
altered and shifted the electromagnetic
field of your planet and caused there to
be a cessation of a certain type of life
form that beat at a certain pulse and
could no longer be sustained.
Recognize that the idea now proposed by
your civilization of recent times of the
recognition that this cometary or
meteoric bombardment could have been
caused by the idea of what you call a
dark star orbiting your system is in
fact the case. You do have a dark star
orbiting your system.
Thank you. Thank you. Is that a third
density dark star? Yes.
Otherwise it would not affect the idea
and pull the meteors to your planet. I
heard that it was Malbeck. Malbeck.
Malbeck. Well, that is the idea of what
you are referring to now as the remnants
of your asteroid belt. Well, was it the
radioactive sensation or whatever that
word was that
actually have the scientists traces of
radioactivity or just mostly again the
idea is meteoric bombardment and what is
not yet understood by your scientists
electromagnetic shifting of your planetary vibration.
shifting of your planetary vibration.
What kind of effect does that dark have?
The idea again is that you will find
there will be reversals of magnetic and
electromagnetic and gravitic fields in
your solar system as the star passes
through from time to time.
It will also pull with it the idea of
meteoric debris which causes much of the
bombardment.
In your terms of time frame,
11.2 million years.
It is not light years away. It is
connected to your system but outside the
orbits of all of your inner planets.
A dark star. What is
the cycle that passes through?
As you have already ascertained between
the idea of what you call 25 to 33
million years. It is in that sense
halfway through the cycle.
Last time being the the dinosaurs.
Nice. Is the dark star anything to do with the
Is the dark star anything to do with the
black hole? It is compacted mass but not
as compacted as that. It is simply not
luminous because in your terms it is compacted
because in your terms it is compacted
mass and does not radiate the idea of
illumination except what you would call the infrared.
except what you would call the infrared.
What effect does it have on the physical
and emotional bodies of man?
In this way recognize again it will have
to do with connections of the gravitic
fields the tensor dynamics of your
system and can to some degree represent
the idea of the patterns and the cycles
that you have allowed yourself to create
upon your planet to begin
with. The idea of
cyclical extinction or transformation
itself is connected with that idea.
Well, that since we're on a duality
planet here where there is good and
evil. No, not good and evil. What is
there? Positive and negative expression.
Good and evil are your own labels and
are judgments.
What do you then how do you define
positive and negative? Thank you.
Positive is recognizing that you are a
part of all that is. It is integration,
integrity in that way. Knowing that you
are a part of all that is negative is
separation, limitation and judgment.
Separation of yourself from all that is.
Thank you.
Therefore, the idea in and of itself of
the labeling of positive and negative
energy as good and evil is in itself a
negative expression because it is a
judgment and a
separation for me. Yes, I do. Thank you.
for sure. Is there another star that our
solar system including our sun revolves
around an orbit of around once every
25,000 years. There are cycles in that
way. Yes. But recognize it is mostly the
idea of what you call black holes that
creates the massive revolutions of
systems. So our sun is revolving around the
So our sun is revolving around the
center of this particular galaxy. And
this particular galaxy is revolving
around a center point.
And clusters of galaxies revolve around
their center points and on and on and
on. Universes revolve around their
center points and on and on and on.
Does our consciousness shift, our mass
consciousness shift as we evolve affect
the electromagnetic field. Oh yes. For
understand mentality is created in the
mentality is created in the
electromagnetic field by your
consciousness. You affect it all the
time anyway. What you call
weather is a direct result of your
emotional mass conscious effect upon the
electromagnetic field of your life.
You follow? Does that answer your
question? Yes. You sure? Yes, somebody
may have asked this, but I wasn't
present. The um there's supposedly a
hole in our ozone layer as what it is
the product of a cyclical magnetic lens.
In this way, you will find that it
fluctuates in what you call annual
terminology once per orbit of your
planet. Many planets have them. It is
simply a type of magnetic lens that
causes a dispersion of certain gases
within your atmosphere to allow for the
crystallization of the gases in that
area temporarily. Oh, so it's really
nothing to be alarmed about then. Not
really. Great.
In this way, you will find however that
there is a change of the balance in the
idea of the gases in your atmosphere and
that is the idea that many of you are
connected to with concern. But those
gases are then should be escaping
through that hole, right? Not so much in
this way. Escaping for your terms of
gravity will pull them back for the most
part. But recognize that this idea, this
recognition of the magnetic lens cycle
will tell you a few things about the
idea of what your planet is as a
generator, as a dynamo, so to
speak. And in this way, you can avail
yourself of the information that it
provides you.
To once again, as certain individuals
upon your planet already have discovered
many times, to avail yourself of the
pulse of electromagnetic power that your
entire planet can provide for you,
rather than the generation of power in
the ways you are doing it now.
The planet itself can provide you with
all the energy you need for anything.
in a sense.
Will we be tapping into that power?
Excuse me. Why not?
It is up to you. It has already been
attempted many times. That knowledge
that we have the knowledge. You have had
so for quite some time. But again, the
idea of the way you have structured your
society says that you do not want that
to happen.
So you create structures within your
society that suppress the information
because the way you have set them up,
they are protecting you, so to speak,
from certain kinds of ideas that you
allow them to protect you from because
you are not taking responsibility for
your own self-empowerment and
recognizing that you are your
governments. coming out.
As all you need to understand is that
when you change the idea that power is
not power over others but
selfmpowerment then those structures of
society you have created will recognize
that they do not need to suppress
anything. For the release of the
information and the sharing of the
information will not be a loss of power.
It will be a gaining of selfmpowerment.
But because of the way you think of
power and because you think that
vulnerability is weakness then that is
the type of society and the type of
effects you create and so much of the
information that you have available to
you is not dispersed
is Tesla's work some of this information
you're talking about a great deal of
it understand that that individual knew
exactly the relationship of the
understanding of the electromagnetic and
gravitic dynamic tensor fields of your
world knew exactly how to utilize them
in that way. But once again, the
structure of your society at that time
as a mass consciousness, let us say,
voted against
it. But that available
technology is yours any time you decide
it is yours, some of it. But do
understand that because of the degree of
suppression that has existed, much of
the information is not known even to
those who have
suppressed. It will be
understood that the way to recognize the
rest of the information will be when
they are willing to share it with
everyone. Because only then will you be
the unification that will have access to
all of the information instead of
pieces. As long as you decide they will.
As long as you decide they will.
It is up to all of you to become
self-empowered and recognize that you
are not chastising them for what they
have been for you have made them that
way. You are your governments. How much
power is there? As much as you believe
there is the idea to us of what you call
is the idea to us of what you call
prayer and light work are once again
simply symbols of knowing what is true
for you and acting like it. And yes, we
believe that works
always. Thank you. Yes. 222. Thank
222. Thank
you. And you woke up just before. Yes, I
did. And I had a sensing, but I didn't
know. I woke up and I sat up and I said,
"Why am I awake?" And then the bed
started jolting all around. Frank slept
all through it. But I was wondering
about this this young lady's question
that she asked you um previously about
the earthquakes and stuff. What um what
was the synchronicity with that event
and some of our our our transformation
in our social consciousness? Was there
something taking place last night?
That's again the passage through of a
gateway and in this way on the cusp of
something that perhaps not to you
specifically but to other individuals. A
week ago of your time we mentioned that
there would be a gateway on what you
call 77.
I missed that.
What do you mean seven? What you call
July? What do you mean by gateway? The idea of
What do you mean by gateway? The idea of
a shift in the electromagnetic field
that represents a shift in your mass
consciousness and therefore a release
and an absorption and a channeling of
that energy. In that
way you are making
adjustments and you are seeing them
reflected in your planet.
Thank you. It has to do with many old
connections of Harvard negativity. As
you already know,
you remember
what do you mean by that? The idea is
that that area that you call Palm
Springs, many of your years ago, was a
recipient to what you would call
extraterrestrial civilizations that arrived upon your
civilizations that arrived upon your
planet to begin a new cycle of life and
rebirth to allow there to be the
blending of positive and negativity so
that there would not be the domination
of negativity that they had within their
own systems. Thus for you it is a local
systems. Thus for you it is a local
focal point of the idea of having
absorbed and blended and integrated old
and ancient ideas of negativity which
you no longer need. That is why the
energy in that place has now been
crystallized and so that you have made a
step towards fourth density
as a group all at once.
For sure. One moment
Oh, not sorry. You are next. Yes. Yes.
Can you possible to use the law of
universal ratios in probabilities
to some extent? But again recognize that
because this is the
transformation, such things as odds tend
to begin to lose their meaning. For
everything at any given moment is
exactly at zero. No matter what has gone
before, there are ratios. Yes. Are they
constant to some degree in general
terms, but again, portions of them are
beginning to
fluctuate. What is it you wish to apply
this idea
to probabilities?
This way there is some recognition of
cycles but do also remember that in a
sense you are at the end of many of
those cycles and will not experience
them again.
Yes, but they will not last as long. The
idea of all of your experiencing of
limitation and judgment has occupied let
us say tens hundreds of thousands of
your years millions of years.
The beginning of the cycle of
integration only requires two to three
thousand years and then you will no
longer be
physical. So the idea is that any cycles
you are now going to begin to recognize
through the ratios you are familiar with
will take on new
meanings will begin to create polar
inversions of a sort. There will always
be two sides, so to speak, to any cycle.
And you can begin to recognize that the
cycles are not so much ideas of
predictability, but recognitions of
opportunity and
change. Does that assist you?
Thank you. Yes. Do you know Rona to some
degree? Do you communicate on one level?
Can you uh
the idea of a communication? Yeah. And
knowing knowing that entity simply you
will find that all consciousness now
associated in assisting your
civilization forms some level of their
awareness, some level of their existence
to be in communication constantly with
all other consciousnesses being of
assistance to you. On that level there
is communication. Not so much within
what you would call the specifics of my
personality consciousness with that
consciousness directly but on the level
of the association of the overall idea
that we are reflecting to you as a
society. There is communication. There
is the recognition of timing. There is
interaction. So that all of course
of course
that is why we are both
recognize that any so-called
discrepancies or disagreements come from
your recognition and interpretation of
the information you are getting.
I had a question about I uh watched a
videoape and he said to a man that he
smoked marijuana that he was going to
die before he was ready and I can't die
before you're ready. Oh, thank
you. Recognize once again that what is
said to certain individuals is said
because that is what that individual may
believe they need to hear to make a
change. nice
nice
um I know he seems to be the one that I
found that I have no discre
again understand this all consciousness
being channeled upon your planet at this time
channeled upon your planet at this time
will find different avenues of
expression different vehicles and
different levels of relationship
symbolically because there are many
different levels of relationship and
many symbolic understandings upon your
planet. Therefore, the information in
general is the same but will be clothed
in specific symbols in order to reach
those who come from those symbolic
understandings. Otherwise, they wouldn't
understand it at all. There are
only only in some cases individuals upon
your planet that will only begin to
understand that they are creating their
reality when at first they are told that
someone else will do something for them.
Then they will believe that there is
power to make a change. Then slowly,
subtly and surely the power is given
back to that
individual. Recognize that there is always within
Recognize that there is always within
any
interaction a myriad number of
opportunities to recognize what is in
fact true for you. Now, if I told
you that your doing something would
allow you to die quote unquote before
you were ready, and you simply
recognized, as you have done so, that
that is not possible, then it is your
duty to say so. To recognize that I am
giving you an opportunity to stand up
for what you believe in. Well, you do.
But the idea we are simply illustrating
is that many times many of the
consciousness ends will say things in
certain ways that you interpret in one
way but are being done for a reason that
you do not consciously perceive at the
moment because you do not understand the
idea of the relationship going on
between the entity and that being on
your planet and what it is that the
entity sees will trigger something in
that being.
A lot of uh souls that are like kind of
say waiting in line but I would like to
communicate to people and that when
we're ready they'll just like somebody
will be ready for you. Yes. Is the Ouija
board a good way of it is a way if you
enjoy it more than anything else as a
symbol then it is your perfect way.
Everything is a tool. Everything is a
symbol. If you are attracted to it then
obviously for you it rings true. If you
change your mind so be it.
that bow tie symbol. No.
No.
What is the difference between you and
ascended master?
That's a good one.
May I answer the question with a
question? Yes. What is the difference
between an ascended master and you?
An ascended master speaks.
Well, we're not physical. I figured
that. Well, so what?
I don't know. I'm wondering what this,
you know, this the idea in generalized
terms are simply a reference point to
individual consciousnesses that are
willing to recognize that they do in
fact create their reality, no matter
what level they are on. Okay? Ascended
simply refers to the idea of a
transformational consciousness
connection and assimilation to all the
levels upon which you exist for whatever
effect that creates in whatever level
you happen to be projecting through.
Is that then have to do with this the
white brotherhood? Oh, in a sense. But
again, that is your third density
[Music] symbological reference point for another
symbological reference point for another
idea of an extension of your own
consciousnesses.
You follow me? Yes. Not that it is not
congruent with other consciousnesses as
well, but they are simply no more
powerful than you are. They simply know
that they are
self-empowered, and they assist you to
remember that you are. Do remember that
a master is the first one to remind you
that you are a master.
Thank you. So look in the mirror
and you will see a master
is there any correlation in a sense?
Yes. Again, an event of timing, a
recognition that certain foundations and
groundwork had been laid down, and thus
another doorway could be moved through a
new level of understanding and
relay. Thank you. Did you like the light
show? I was not scanning at that time.
I was not scanning at that time.
Can you scare all your [\h__\h]
from time to time when we are in your
neighborhood? Were you busy doing something else? Yes.
Were you busy doing something else? Yes.
Of course. Do you remember what it was?
Yes. Would you share it with us? Yes.
Is there any other time was
time was
interacting with other
civilization and was interacting with
different levels of consciousness
regarding some of the changes going on
between your civilization and another
civilization that is experiencing some
ideas of parallelity.
with regard to the
expression of
borders and such that you create.
Where is the civilization
in another density of the star you call
Kenopus? Star. Hey, I'm doing uh some
Star. Hey, I'm doing uh some
uh adventures. Uh I'm just uh
discovering stones. I'm going to be
working making jewelry and I'm going to
try to not try. I'm going Oh, thank you.
I'm going to be uh using the vibrational
qualities. Going to Well, I haven't done
it yet, but you haven't. You haven't.
You haven't. You are doing it right now
as you discuss it. Okay. Is that not a
part of the idea? Yeah, I'm exploring.
All right, then. You are doing it right
now. You will be doing it in many
different ways but you are doing it
right now. Okay. I'd like to explore an
aspect of that with you. All right. Uh
today I bought a lot of just samples of
different stones that I found in the
book that mystic minerals is the title
of it and uh mystic.
Yeah. I didn't judge the cover
information. All right.
Pretty good. I was wondering if you
could tell me if there was like any
general way to get the best quality out
of the stones. Like I'm sure meditating
will help, but in regards to using it
for other people too. Again, you will
only always attract those individuals
that you need to interact with to create
and co-create whatever effect you need
to represent the path you are being.
Okay. Thank you.
Thank you.
Yay. I wanted to share with you
something that you taught me many many
months ago. Something that you taught
yourself. Okay. Um, someone had asked
you how you communicated and you said
that it was through vibrations. Your
mental telepathic understanding was
through vibration in a sense. Yes. And I
left here and several months went by and
a very dear friend of mine that also
comes here, her mother was very sick
with Alzheimer's disease and no one
could talk to her because she made no
sense at all. And I started to
communicate with her for three and four
hours at a time and have conversation
after conversation while people sat in
the room laughing because they couldn't
believe that we understood each other.
And I finally understood that she wanted
to pass on and go to the other side. and
I helped her and her daughter to
communicate through those last few weeks
that they were here and she um had
something she wanted to teach her
daughter and I helped them to
communicate as well as myself with her
and shortly after that she died and it
was a wonderful awakening for all of us
to be able to communicate with her on
that level. Thank you. Thank you for
having made a difference.
One individual makes a difference in the
total consciousness.
Thank you. For sure.
A lady I was involved with a while back
as ago was was was was was involved with
was on another level continues. Ah thank
on another level continues. Ah thank
you.
She was involved in a very bad
automobile accident about a month ago.
Memorial Day is from what I understand.
She's been in the hospital for a month.
She'll probably be there for a lot
longer. Probably. Here we go with
probabilities again. Probably.
Is that what you perceive to be her
reality? Is that what you are saying?
Yes. All right.
She was supposed to uh get married a
couple days I think after that happened.
Obviously that hasn't happened. I have
uh visited the hospital twice. All
right. We've spent a great deal of time
together. She uh she comes and goes, but
she knew who I was.
Actually, we spent about eight hours
together on the two. The total for the
two walked over the phone.
The family I met her folks for the first
time. They don't know me. Uh because of
the impending marriage, they're very
uncomfortable when I'm there. I've
talked with her fiance several times and
uh he is exceptionally uncomfortable. Continue.
Continue.
Uh he has asked me not to come back, not
to contact
her. I'm part of me feels as though I'm
abandoning her if I don't contact her.
At least to allow her to know what's
happening. Does a part of you feel like
you're abandoning yourself if you don't?
Yes. Yes. I'm torn between going back and not
Yes. I'm torn between going back and not
going back and not worrying about
hassling with it and everybody else. I
mean, the family's had enough with
everything that's happened. God knows
I've had enough happen in the past. No
one wants any hassles, but there's
there's this other feeling.
U she's happy when she sees me. All
right. I know she enjoys that
now. I really I don't know what to do.
I'm I'm really torn about it. Can you
would you comment on it? Well, simply
you can recognize first and foremost
that you are no matter what the
definition of your physical proximity
always interacting always.
Now if you find that the idea of the
physical proximity attracts a creation
on your parts of the idea of displeasure
from others, it may simply be the idea
that you can know you are interacting
anyway and not necessarily choose to
continue to create the idea of
dissension from them. But in this way
also do recognize it may be an
opportunity for you to recognize that if
you both wish to continue to co-create
the idea of the interaction in the
manner that you most enjoy then in that
sense it does not matter what they
think. Does she enjoy it?
Yes. To my knowledge she does. And do
you? Yes. Then what does anyone else
have to say about it? I that has been my
thought process for a long time. But I
the other part of me that plays the
devil's advocates as the devil's
advocate. Well,
I'm trying to be fair about situation.
Why do you have to try to be fair?
Why do you not know that you are a fair
being that you are functioning within
integrity? So what what has that got to
do with what he knows to be true for
himself?
Do you know you are a fair being? Oh
yes. Do you know you are functioning
within integrity? Yes. Then why not
allow yourself to simply understand that
once again you can know that there is an
interaction going on right now no matter
what your physical proximity and you can
be just as powerful being not physically
present as you can be physically
present. And at the same time you can
recognize that if that individual wishes
to co-create with you physical proximity
and you wish to co-create that with her
then it is your opportunity in this way
to do so. If that is what excites you
the most, if that is what excites her
the most. if you are functioning within
integrity with each other in that way.
And also simply recognize that both of
you together may be allowing all those
others who are giving you all of the
judgment to come to some terms about
themselves by seeing something reflected
in the two of
you. For what reason should they judge
you? Perhaps you can be a reflection for
them to come to terms and cease judging
themselves. Is that possible without the situation
Is that possible without the situation
really taking off and blowing up and
escalating into something it shouldn't
be? It is possible. Yes. But again,
recognize that if you simply know what
is true for you, even if it quote
unquote does go that way, you will never
feel it.
But again do recognize that you are able
to do anything you want from anywhere
and anywhere. So again it is up to you
and if you feel that within your
integrity and your conscious choice that
you would prefer in this way to simply
know you are interacting with her as you
need to no matter where you are. Then
physical proximity is not necessarily
something you have to insist
upon. But then again, it is up to you to
feel out the situation for yourself and
simply function through the integrity
you know you are utilizing.
Seeing the situation from your vantage
point right
now, do not necessarily assume that I
have a greater vantage point than you
do, for it is your personal
life. And it is not always the
case that
ideas are more apparent to us than they
are to you. And right now, such is the
case. There is nothing that I have an
overview of that you are not privy
to. Since you are dealing with such an
intensification of focus of the energy,
you are very well aware of all the
factors involved. As many as I
am, as many as I allow myself to be
aware of based upon the idea of not
interfering with your
choices. Thus, it is totally in your
hands. Overview notwithstanding,
if you were in my situation, if
if what parallel reality are we talking
about?
That if has nothing to do with what
is. What is is that's correct. But
you've said you you've just said that
you see the same things I see. No more,
no less. Guys, knowing that
what would you feel would
be the best possible choice at this
time? All right. All right. All right. One
right. One
hint and that is it. All
right. Yes. No. Maybe an indepth an
inepth one hint of my definition.
one. All right. All right. Take it or
leave it. In that case, I'll take it. I would.
I would.
Oh, this is fun. I
would if if I were in your shoes which would
if if I were in your shoes which would
not fit me very
well. I would open complete and total
communication with everyone as to why
they feel the way they choose to feel. I
would talk with everyone and explore in
depth what everyone is choosing to feel
and why they think they are feeling what
they are feeling so
that I can function with my integrity
and integrate the entire interaction
within me by talking to every portion of
the interaction.
If you're aware of the situation as I
am, you know that I have attempted that.
Attempted? Well, you know that I have
done that with at least one of the
individuals involved. At least
one. I said
everyone. Who knows what talking to one
will do for another? before me.
before me.
Yes, you do not sound too happy.
Do you think it will be a great deal of
trouble to talk to all of It's not so
much that I think it will be a great
deal of trouble. It's it's the idea that
I can I can uh
reasonably project [Laughter]
[Laughter]
stopping before you start. Are you
planning the outcome in advance?
The outcome that I was thinking about
was certainly one of the options of an
outcome. Well, yes, but you do not have
to prefer it, do you? You do not have to
act like that is the most expected
outcome that could happen,
do you? That's correct. Where is your
faith? By my mind comes and goes. Where
does it go? There is nowhere for it to
go to. Where does it come from?
You your opening statements this
evening, you were talking about habits.
Yes. Yes. I mean I saw I suppose a lot
of parallels with that in this situation
I see
but I I can't for the life of me for the
life understand in this particular situation
understand in this particular situation
yes it's
why I would agree to I shouldn't say
that why I would cocreate all right
cocreate an additional negative
situation on top of ah negative
situation that's already taken placeh a
but why are you defining what has taken
place as a negative
situation and why are you defining
everything else that occurs from that
point forward as additional negativity
if you are functioning within a positive
vibration how can anything that you are
associated with in that way and
interacting with have anything but a
positive reason for its creation
That's fine for someone to see on
another level, but
that's fine for another level. As if it
was not all one
level. Again, the habit of separation.
Oh yes, I understand it intellectually,
but emotionally I choose to make a
difference that there is an intellectual
and an emotional understanding and
therefore I refuse to blend the two and
therefore I refuse to understand it.
What makes you think there is another
level? Oh god,
there is only another level to
understand it upon when you create
another level to understand it upon. Do
not forget unconscious knowingness is
the same thing as conscious
unknowingness which is saying you
consciously choose to not
know and relegate it to your unconscious
self which does
know. But it is all one
thing. It is all one consciousness.
There is no other level.
only the illusion that there
is. Now if you wish to understand then
simply once again allow yourself to
understand that
every. Now if I were to suggest to you
that you would underline the word every
as many times as you could. How many
times do you think you would underline
it before you would get tired?
until you would understand that I mean
every when I say every. All right. How
many times could you underline it?
All right. that many times underlying
the word every to understand that when I
say every I mean
every every
situation is fundamentally
neutral until you give it meaning
positive or negative. No situation has
builtin meaning.
No
circumstances, no scenario is inherently
negative or positive. It just
is until you decide to choose how you
wish to look at it. Then looking at it
as a positive idea creates a positive
cognition and a positive effect in your
reality as you relate and interact with
that situation. Choosing to think that
it is a negative situation to begin with
creates for you more reinforcement of
negative experience because then that is
all you allow yourself to see in a
fundamentally neutral situation is the
negative side. Based upon what you've
said, I find a grave contradiction. All
right. When I first approached the
situation, there wasn't a thought in my
mind that the situation was negative. I
was not looking at the accident as a
negative situation. What has then got to
do with
now? Again, understand no matter who you
used to be when you first approached it,
you obviously the moment you chose to
experience negativity chose to be
someone
else to whom it was possible to have a
negative experience. What happened? Why
did you choose to become someone who
would only experience the idea in a
negative way rather than the continuence
of the positive idea? You have two
individuals that are experiencing a
situation from a positive stance no
matter what it is. And you have another
individual or or additional individuals
enter the same situation. Yes. You still
have the two that are looking at it
positively. The others are not looking
at it positively. But that is their
reality. It does not have to be yours.
Why should you be attached judgmentally
to the way they choose to look at the
situation? Why should that change your
positive outlook? Well,
outlook? Well,
all right. Let me see if I can answer
that. It does not change my positive
outlook with regard to the accident
itself. Uhuh. You are making a differentiation.
Uhuh. You are making a differentiation.
Yes, because there is a differentiation.
You are making a differentiation. There
is no differentiation until you make
one. If you are completely the idea,
this idea, this interaction completely
positively, then no matter how many
other individuals appear within it that
choose to be negative, you will still
love them the same. You will still feel
that they are there for a positive
reason. You will not allow yourself to
create an effect of negativity in your
life with regard to anything in that
situation. Anything because their reality is not
Anything because their reality is not
yours. Just because they are interacting
with you does not mean that for you they
are not there for a positive reason.
Maybe for them you are there for a
negative reason or a positive reason or
for themselves they are there for a
negative reason or a positive reason.
But the idea for you no matter who or
what they are can still be positive. You
could for example say well now here we
are interacting in this relationship. We
are having a positively good time. Here
comes someone to interact with us. They
are choosing to be
negative. What a wonderful
opportunity for their negativity may
allow us to choose to continue to prefer
our positive reality and let us know we
are just as strong and can be even more
strengthened because we have a negative
reality to look at and know that we
don't prefer it. So that negativity may
be exactly what you, my friend, in your
state, need to strengthen yourself
according to what you believe in. So you
can stand up for yourself so that you
can then truly physically stand
up. You follow me? Yes. Yes, I do. Use
your imagination and trust.
That is all. Thank you very much. Thank
you. I have an additional question. All
right. Okay. It has to do with where
emotion comes in with this. Yes. Okay.
Because listening to him talk, it sounds
like the judgment of negativity
uh came when it didn't feel good.
Your emotions are the result of what you
already believe to be true.
believe to be true.
You follow me. Okay. I was wondering if
I had had it backwards.
comment. This is just my All right.
Your reality of the situation. My
reality.
Yes. Your what? Go ahead. Um Keith was
feeling since he's you know vulnerable
how you say that and he's very
strong how you interpret. Yes.
Vulnerability is infinite strength. Yes.
To me that makes a lot of sense.
that um he feels the negative effect of
the the parents and he feels this and he
doesn't want to create for them a
painful experience. But again understand
the idea is that if you know you are
functioning within your integrity and
you are fulfilling all of your end of
the idea in terms of what you feel to be
true for you then the idea of feeling
someone else's negativity is creating it
for yourself. If you simply recognize they
yourself. If you simply recognize they
are choosing to be negative, then you
can assist them by giving them a
positive reflection that will then allow
them to see in you a reflected
opportunity to also become positive if
they decide to.
If you know what you are and who you are
and find yourself in a situation with
other negative individuals in that way
around you, then simply recognize that
if you know you are functioning within
your integrity, then perhaps you are
there for the purpose of reflecting some
positivity to
them. Perhaps they need you more than
they are willing to admit.
Bishar, I'll find you. I understand that
and it makes a lot of sense to me. And
there's also this reality that we've all
been conditioned with to not make waves
for other people. All right. Again, we
are not saying that you should
intentionally force yourself on anyone.
That is why we also say that you can
recognize that you are having an
interaction regardless of whether you
are physically in contact with that
individual or not.
However, if you also understand that in
your terms there really is no harm truly
being perpetuated maliciously by you by
being physically in contact with that
individual, then all of the ideas that
are being told to you by these negative
individuals, it is their choice to feel
that way and you are not responsible for
that.
Even even not being responsible for that
though and listening to everything
you've said. Yes. I know that a negative
and I'm using that word again. Another
negative situation on top of all the
other crap that's happened is
being but whose negative situation? So
it's theirs. They are choosing it. What
do you have to do with its creation?
It is their creation. You are
responsible to them to be yourself. You
are not responsible for them or their
choices.
Now do you
again change. Oh another habit saying it
is a big habit to change. Habit built
upon habit built upon conditioning built
upon habit built upon that's the way it
always has been built upon another
belief another scenario another creation
third density that is no
density that is no
excuse telling you where we're coming
from [Music]
we as a civilization
I am laughing with you
at your wonderful
joke. Yes, I know.
Oh, thank you. You may all take a short
break.
All right, I'll say sharing.
Bashar, my friend Sydney and I were out
by the pool and um we were discussing
the difference between emotion and
intuition and um we were sharing with
each other what our realities were on
that. Right. And I sort of felt for me
that my emotion and my intuition were
the same thing and I was wondering if
you could sort of comment on that as far
as if there is a distinction. Um there
is in a sense a distinction since you
have made one in that way. There is a
differentiation but recognize in this
sense the idea of intuition is more the
idea of knowingness whereas
emotion energy motion is one of the
three parts of the artificial construct
you call your personality that you have
created to remind you that you do in
fact know what you know.
So emotion is more a reflection of
intuition expressed through the
personality. Although everything is of
course one and the same thing in
different manifestations of itself. But
in this way the differentiation is
simply that intuition is simply
knowing recognizing or being cognizant
of the relationship of you and the thing
you are interacting with.
Emotion is emotion energy motion. It is
more an activation idea. It is the
recognition of the intuition in action.
In that sense, it is more the idea of
giving yourself a
barometer by which you can then see or
feel within yourself the reflection of
your degree of acknowledgment of your
degree of acknowledgment of your
knowingness.
you forward. Yes.
Can you give some sort of assistance regarding how
regarding how
to work out if if you are letting your
emotions hang you uph
uph
emotions do not hang you up.
Judgments hang you up.
There is no such thing as once again an
intrinsically negative
emotion. Judgment creates the
polarity that you experience as a
seemingly negative
emotion. The emotions themselves do not
hang you up. They are simply put once
again emotion energy in motion.
Are you sure? One moment.
You follow? Yeah, I do.
So, in releasing yourself from from
judgment and judging situations,
if that is such a habit for people to
judge things, it is a belief that it is
a habit. Okay. Can you give assistance
on releasing judgment?
There are many ways we have reflected
and assisted with this idea. Different
individuals will experience different
portions of this reflection according to
what they feel they need to understand
the idea. Now you can put it on this
level very simple understanding if you
wish. The
idea is to recognize what you prefer and
what you do not. But what you do not
prefer does not have to be invalidated
as something less than what you do
prefer. You follow me? Mhm. Therefore,
to simply recognize what you
prefer and act that way allows you to
experience your
preference. Judging what you do not
prefer creates you to be the vibration
of judgment, the vibration of what you
are judging. You form through your
judgment an attachment to what you don't
prefer. So why would you want to judge
if the idea is to become something else?
Judging is what keeps you focused on
what you don't prefer.
You follow it? Yes, I do. So, why would
you want to do bad?
Don't for when we look at a situation
and we view it as being perfect and we
have this phrase of oh that's perfect.
Nice. Is that a judgment? It is a
recognition. The idea is that everything
is perfect.
everything. The idea that you need to
achieve perfection is a
judgment because you're saying that you
are not already everything that you can
be to express the idea you are being at
that given
moment. Are always perfect always. You
will never achieve perfection. You are
perfect now. You are always a perfect
manifestation of the idea you are being.
If you are being another idea later on,
then you are simply being another
perfectly manifested different idea, not
a better one, a different one. Perfect
on its own terms unto itself. Just as
perfect as any other idea you have ever
been or will ever be, but different.
So perfect is just a word, a label that
we put on something for just existing as
it is. Yes.
Thank you. Full cognition of what
something is is the cognition of its
perfection.
Okay. And we have brought about the
distinction of whether it's
perfect and not perfect as being a
judgment of being good or bad. Yes.
Okay. Thank you very much. [\h__\h] you.
Yes. I was going to ask you what role
does instinct play in emotions.
Again, the idea is that many times you
may find that when you are functioning
upon your instinct with conscious
awareness, when you are trusting your
instinct, there may be in your terms
less need to experience the so-called
range of emotionality other than simple
unconditional love.
Thank you. All emotions are derivations
of love. Love is the only emotion there
is really. Everything else is either a
judgment of that or some sort of
differentiation of that.
That would apply to angers and
resentments. Oh yes. Oh yes. Oh yes. Oh
yes. And do remember once again that
hate is not the opposite of love. Guilt
is. For love is complete worthiness and
guilt is the belief that it is
worthlessness. Hate is only the polarity
of the idea a polarized expression of
love attachment after having passed through
attachment after having passed through
the filter of the judgment of
guilt. But it is simply another
manifestation of attachment. Hate still
believes itself to be worthy of
something. Guilt doesn't
so everything is as far as emotions go a
derivation of love for love is what you
are made of. Love is all that is.
Thank you.
Um, I was wondering if you would like to
reflect about the archetypal symbol of
the
crow. In this way, as you may already
know, it is an expression to some extent
for many individuals in different ways,
but generally speaking of
curiosity, investigation also to some extent the
investigation also to some extent the
idea of alarm
the idea of the marking
idea of the marking
out of territory.
to some degree. In some cases, some of
the polarities also will be the
idea both in a positive and a negative
way of unseen
actions and subconsciously delivered
information like a messenger.
Thank you. Thank you. Sure. For sure.
Yes. While we're on the symbology, would
you comment on our mythological cyclops?
Thank you. In this way, to some extent,
do
recognize that it is partly the idea of
what you call the archetypal mythology
and partly a physicalized
interpretation out of the archetypal
energy substream of consciousness of a
manifestation of a portion of your own
consciousness that represents itself as
what you would call second density
civilizations of existence, second
density worlds. The idea that for you
there is no third dimension of
sight, no parallax, no reference
point. Everything is flatly perceived
with one eye.
Rather than dimensionally perceived with
two. Mhm. So it is a symbolic
interpretation of a
manifestation of your subconscious
archetypal mass conscious energy of the
second density ties that you may still
have to that level.
Is there a connection between um that
idea and what I have heard referred to
as the elves or the elders? To some
extent there is that mixed in with it.
Yes. as that will have been a bridge, a link,
as that will have been a bridge, a link,
a tunnel, a doorway from the second to
the third density
experience and represent therefore an
expansion of consciousness that you call
the elders.
What geographical area did did they
exist on here on on this planet?
There were some scatterings in this way.
Not exactly completely one arrival point
so to speak, but in this way the old
connections of what you would call now
though not then Asia as it was also
connected to the idea of what came to be
called Leoria in your
Pacific to some extent ranging
throughout that area.
All right. Mhm.
Yes. Uh some realistic artists have
believed that their art should stem from
their dreams. Uh basically because they
felt that uh it was their only pure
source of of
imagination. Uh I was just curious as to
how you did that coincide with your
philosophy in a sense although recognize
that your physical reality also stems
from your
dreams. Simply what they are recognizing
is
that dream
reality physical reality being one type
of dream
reality both are products and extensions
of the dimension of imagination which is
what you are all potential ideas of
existence. It is within the idea of
existing consciously within your
dimension of imagination that you do
recognize that all is possible. All is
possible. And they are simply recognizing that
And they are simply recognizing that
portion of themselves.
Uh from your physical reality though
your does your imagination become
subject to outside influences? Is that
there is no outside?
You may imagine there is but then you
have created that with your imagination
and so physical reality is still subject
to your
imagination. You follow me? Yeah.
Are you sure?
Um, yeah, I do. The only thing that I'm
confused about, I guess, is if
it's imagination from your strictly from
your dream state, which I I understand
is part of your physical reality.
Um are you able to more in your dream
state more finetune to uh to yourself
without that is as you believe it to be
and so it is so but your physical
reality is also a part of your dream
reality. Your dream reality is also a
part of your physical reality. So when
you understand that they are one reality
and not two realities then the same
ideas will be just as possible in both.
Thank you. Thank you. Sharing
I heard that the Labor Day weekend is
going to be a good weekend for viewing
UFOs. Did you know? I did. I see. And
I'd like to know what you call the idea.
September. What you call the idea?
October highly active. Okay. Both months
in in their entirety
generally. Okay. There may be what you
call peak points but follow your
instinct. Okay. Um in terms of where to
go. Would you suggest that I follow my
instinct? Yes. For there are many
variables now. Many variables. And you
may find that a recommendation now will
not be a recommendation then.
Thank you. Sh. Yay. I Yay. I
[Music]
have I have noticed that oh over the
last several years that probably 95 98%
of the women I know that have had
children have had cacaians. A what is
this all about? Instead of natural child
birth, why are they being cut open? In
this way in many cases it is because
there is still a belief within your
society that natural child birth is too
painful has to be painful. Thus in this
way for the
child in a sense it is not.
And it is one way to open up the ideas
within yourselves about coming to terms
with many of the different projections
and different types of ways of giving
birth in this sense. To allow you to
know there is not just one way and to
allow you to know that these children
are very multi-dimensional and will
enter through unexpected doorways.
Hence all the
um test tube babies and things that are
starting to happen. block.
I heard someone saying something about
that the other day and that there is
some legal thing that the doctors for
some reason are afraid of getting sued
or something like that. I don't remember
all the details but that was part of the
reason. It does not matter what
physiological symbol you attach to give
yourselves a reason for it. The ideas in
this way is simply an exemplification
that there are now many doorways to come
through and that many of them are
attached to the idea that you have the
belief that you have that the so-called
old ways are still attached to pain.
Isn't it easier for the child to be
lifted out of the womb rather than to
have to go through? That is what you
believe and so it is so as we are
saying. So it's just a belief. It's not
real. I
Nothing about the idea of child birth
has to be painful. Nothing.
Bashar, what kind of experience would a child
what kind of experience would a child
have um being being the process of being
born through the integration of using um
like a a water birth with dolphins and
stuff? What would your experience be?
What would your experience be?
What you might call less forgetting of
who they are. I was just going to ask.
So, so the birthing process as we know it is
so the birthing process as we know it is
is a little bit traumatic and and we
forget things. So you're saying that
they would um
they would be allowed to transfer from
one dimension of experience into another
and still take with them a lot of what
they are familiar
with. They do not have to be
purged of their
experiences by pain.
And and what would the dolphins
experience at that time? Oh, joy. Lots
of communication. Yes. And do not forget
that they are assisting you in that way
now. Okay. And well this is something that I
Okay. And well this is something that I
was thinking about doing and
um if I want I do understand if you
simply follow your intuition in this
way that you will create a scenario you
will create an atmosphere and you will
create a condition that will allow the
child along with you to co-create and
choose whatever methodology is best for
both of you whether it may be the one
you think you are going to do or not.
Mhm. But follow your instincts and you
will create an opportunity to create
whatever is needed.
Okay? In other words, there have been
individuals who have imagined that they
would give birth that way and once again
wound up in the idea of what you call
cesarian. But simply they did create an
atmosphere that allowed there to be the
recognition or the cognition of whatever
scenario was of best benefit for all
concerned.
Okay. So, what what you're saying is
prior to the
birth, the child and the mother both
agree. Oh, yes. Always.
Well, is there any way I can communicate
with my child or to say that this is
what I want? Let's work it out.
This is what we want.
Keep it equal. Now explore it as one
possible method. One possible method.
But understand the child comes from an
experience of feeling not thought. And
in this way what feels correct is what
will happen. You follow me?
happen. You follow me?
But you can talk with the child. Yes. Do
remember that before
birth you are not talking to a child.
Thank you. I needed to be reminded of
that. Thank you.
Yes. Um just as we have uh agreed upon
this physical reality that we all exist
on here in these bodies. Do we also have
an agreed upon reality where we exist
when we leave? between lifetimes or
what? Yes.
What happens? There are many different
levels you have co-created within that
existence as well. And this is shared by
the mass consciousness of many different
consciousnesses within the universe.
There are many different things that can
occur according once again to the belief
system that you have and to what you
need to experience.
You can experience everything from
having a complete overview and
understanding of all the ideas you have
ever been in physical reality and know
that you do not need to incarnate ever
again and can go on to other levels. You
can go from that level all the way to
the experience of not even knowing you
have yet
died and become what is called in your
vernacular a haunting. A
A
haunting. The idea of what you call
spirits or hauntings are simply
individuals who have transcended to the
non-physical realm but don't know it
because of their belief system. It does
not allow them to have the recognition
that they have in fact died because they
did not know what to expect. Don't they
find it frustrating trying to
communicate with us? Sometimes
that sometimes is what can clue them in
if they are open enough to listen.
But the original idea of what you call
your so-called
exorcist was for the purpose of
functioning as a spirit psychologist to
let them know they had died. They are
fine. They could go on.
They are not originally for the purpose
of banishing evil spirits.
Yes. Aren't suicides to some degree also
in that realm? Yes. For in this way,
what you call conscious
suicide is to a point the only method
open to you to negate the contract you
originally made. But in this way, do
understand that once you usually arrive
back at the point where you originally
made the contract, you reestablish that
contract once again and many times
experience similar circumstances in the
next life so that you will allow
yourself to explore the original idea of
knowing you create your own reality and
taking responsibility for that in that
next life that you perhaps refused to
explore in the previous one in which you
took your own
Do recognize therefore that there is a
difference between the idea of the
consciously recognized suicide and what
you would term regular death because
every death is in fact suicide
since you do create your own reality.
But consciously recognized suicide is
usually the lack of willingness to take
responsibility for what you have created
for yourself to
experience. Your lack of willingness to
believe that you are in control of it.
So the majority of the idea of what you
call conscious suicides usually are
reborn almost immediately.
Oh yeah
question. One moment. One moment.
I remember a comment Seth made about
suicides. He said if that happens you
are required to live out that particular
time span that you had originally set
for yourself. Oh in a sense. But do
recognize that what Seth has also
referred to is the understanding that
time spans differ when you are
non-physical and when you are physical.
Now to the physical being still alive
the time span may seem to be long for
how long the ghost hangs around but to
the ghost it doesn't necessarily have to
feel like that same amount of time.
Thank you. Nice. Um on the suicide
subject uh what about people who who
don't want to be on life support systems
and would rather die who are but
critically ill. In this way again that
may be different for it may be an
opportunity to be of service to allow
individuals to recognize the degree of
self-empowerment that individuals have
and to explore the idea that there is a
point at which you are in fact then
interfering with someone else's choice
of reality.
So the idea may be in your terms a fine
line but a line there is. I see.
And back
to this also relates again back to what
you had started with in habits. If
somebody has a habit that eventually
takes their life um is
that u is that okay with the higher self? It
u is that okay with the higher self? It
will depend once again upon many of the
reasons for such an event and the degree
of conscious awareness of what is going
on because there are opportunities for
the higher to experience such an idea
what may seem to be a quote unquote
accidental so to speak suicide and not
necessarily have the same inonation as a
consciously aware suicide. However, do
understand that again more often than
not those individuals have also almost
immediately reincarnated and also do understand that
reincarnated and also do understand that
an individual in the situation the
so-called life support situation
question have also co-created themselves
to linger to be of service in that way
to allow other individuals to come to
terms with their own understandings of
life and death. Do understand that if an
individual in that situation truly
created the timing for their death to be
that they would not linger, then they
would not linger.
So they are being of service in many
different ways whether they may think so
or not.
For sure. Thanks. Uh cataracts, what's
the cause? and uh short of an
operation. How can they be? There may be
many ways. There are certain ways that
are available in your society. And also
there can be the recognition of the idea
for certain individuals of simply
reflecting for themselves or to other
individuals a lack of willingness to see
what is going on in their lives to cloud
over the issues.
Now, full cognizance and
alignment with the crystal clarity of
existence within the dimension of your
imagination can allow any idea that has
been created physically to be quote
unquote cleared
up, but it may take that recognition.
Short of that is there is there an
additional way recognizing that that do
understand that no matter what way it is
cleared up it is all a
reflection of the taking of that
responsibility and the creation of that
alignment. No matter what symbol you use
or allow someone else to use to clear it
up with. If you are not ready to have it
cleared up nothing will clear it up.
When you are ready to clear it up,
nothing will stop it from clearing.
Follow me. Very much so. Thank you.
There may be some other exploration of
this idea at a later time.
Fourth density is calling.
My uh my dog has cataracts. Is he
reflecting to me? Animals will usually
do that. Now in this way again do
understand that we are not saying that
in every case this has to be reflection
taken negatively. In that sense it may
also be the recognition that you may be
shutting down your sensory awareness of
one reality so that you can open your
eyes and be born into a new world.
Why shut down my sensory awareness of of
one reality and open your sensory
awareness to another. The idea of
cataracts can also be what you have
referred to in your society as the
passing through of a
veil. Osmosis through a membrane.
How can I? It's interesting because I
had a uh you can in this way always send
the animals unconditional love and
acknowledgement that if they are
performing a service for you that you
are willing to take full responsibility
for the service they are performing and
know that taking full responsibility
means that it does not have to affect
you negatively. Then they do not have to
continue to take upon themselves the
effect in a negative way that you might
have created for
yourself because of your belief that the
only way it could manifest was
negatively. But them taking it for you
gives you the opportunity to continue to
do what you are doing without being
impeded. If you simply know you are
willing to take back responsibility for
the symbolic creation of that idea and
allow it to transform for you in
whatever way is necessary to be
represented in a positive way, then they
will not have to have the cataracts. You
will rechan the energy in a positive way
and both of you will be clearsighted
about that. Become
that. Become
clairvoyant about your own life. That is
clear seeing,
clairvoyance. Allow your life to become
transparent and there will not be a need
for a symbolic darkening or
darkening or
fogging of the senses. You follow me?
I do for sure. Nice. Um, at different
times I It seems like there's a lot of
beings that want to communicate with me.
A lot of them. And I kind of get
confused on who to Well, lots of times I
used to get scared, but I don't know
which one to communicate with first. It
seems like a lot of them are around at
the same Then what difference does it
make? Cuz I' I'd like to explore it, but
I Go ahead.
Just take one at a time. Why not?
But it seems like they're all none of
them are going to be impatient.
Okay. You do not have to be impatient either.
You do not have to be impatient either.
Okay. Good. Recognize that you will also
simply be blending with many different
portions of your own personality as
well. Okay. Thank you.
Okay. Thank you.
Lovely. And I
I am not aware of any of my dreams. That
is all right. Once again, as we have
shared with you, the idea of not
remembering your dreams can be a
reflection that you are blending the
dream and physical reality into one
thing. Right. And so, not creating the
necessary bridge to represent a
connection between things that seem to
be separate, right? Okay, that makes
sense to me. Thank you. Yes. Do you have
entities from your planet that want to
be born in our bodies and come through
and live here in human form
in a sense? Well, a few have. That's
that's what I want to ask next. One, if
you wish to make a reference in this way
in your symbolic terms, one of my past
lives is the physiological being sitting
before you
follow me. Wow.
And didn't have life. Wait a minute.
I just I thought I heard somewhere that
there are many levels of
consciousness and there are many
alternate forms of physiological
consciousness in the
universe. Now we are fourth density not
third density but that does not mean we
do not have a physiological
representation. You will find that one
of the myths that your society may have
been creating in its metaphysical
understanding is that all
extraterrestrials have to be spirit.
But you're saying that's your past life.
Yes. What about right now? I am in my
fourth density physical representation.
But people people or entities or what
are is everybody from your planet fourth
density? Yes.
Then would they ever want to be born at
this very moment now into a woman
carrying a new baby? Obviously I
did. Again, the understanding that you
may be missing is that
time past, present, future is all one.
The idea of being of assistance to you
by allowing a portion of my
consciousness to be born upon your world
happens in whatever timing is
appropriate regardless of where I am in
time. Your confusion is that it's born
into Daryl as opposed to a woman. Right?
Is that what
No, no, no. I'm just saying for instance
um if if anybody in this room got went
home tonight and got pregnant and was
going to conceive a baby is there a
possibility that an entity from your
planet would walk in and become that
spirit of that child and be born in 9
months in a sense yes but you are making
the idea of the misunderstanding by
saying it the way you are saying it
because of the way the time track in
your mentality
runs. It can be looked upon as if an
entity from my world became physical in
yours. Also, however, if you wish to fit
into your linear understanding, you
would simply say that an entity became
physical in your world, lived its life,
died, and then became physical in
mine. You follow me?
In other words, the idea of being born
in any particular place and
time has not really so much to do with
the idea of going back to somewhere or
up to somewhere. It is more the idea of
going over to
somewhere. So that simply if at any
point in my life in my overall total
consciousness awareness there became a
need for such a light it would occur
regardless of whether it is before I
exist as a personality or after I exist
as a personality does not
matter. It simply occurs in whatever
timing is appropriate. If that fits into
what you then call a time frame, then
you will tend to see it linearly before,
now after. But that is not necessarily
the way that the life manifests. So it
is not necessarily so much that it would
be the idea that one of us would decide
to be born in your society, but simply
that you may look at it for simplicity
purposes in your linear time frame that
perhaps many of the individuals in my
society have already experienced lives
in yours and are now in
ours. Even if that decision were to be
made in our society in what we call our
present time, it would still already
have happened in your time frame
already because by
definition you are creating us to be
something so to speak more accelerated
in your
future. By definition we are creating
you to be in a sense. What are you
creating yourself to be? the idea of
simply who and what we are. As we relate
to different other consciousnesses, we
can recognize the reflection that they
may have of us and simply relate to them
by that perspective since that is the
way it is easiest for them to understand
the communication going on. But that is
the reason for the so-called confusion
now because you are beginning to
equalize yourselves with our vibratory
level. And in this way there is not so
much of a differentiation in the idea of
our relative time
flows. I'll put it
simply. Yes.
But it is not always exactly as it seems
in terms of when the decision was made
and when the decision is activated.
Well, no, but you say now is the only
thing we have. I'm asking you now. Yes.
Not past or or my future. I mean then as
of now there are individuals that have
attachments and representational
consciousness in my society that are now
being born into yours. Is that to help
us as you're channeling through Daryl?
Yes, of course. That's what I needed to
know. Thank you. Thank you, Mr. Simply
in this way thought it would be
interesting to explain some of the idea
of the temporal physics. Thank you.
Thank you, Mr. Um there's a situation
that somebody told me about and I trust
them as being um truth. We trust you.
Okay. in terms of the idea that
everything you attract will have
validity for what you need to hear
regardless of what you choose to prefer
to create from it.
Okay. Now,
um, this situation of these women that
are being impregnated in their sleep and
carrying the entity, the child for a
couple of months or a couple of weeks
and taken from their body during their
sleep, what's going on there?
There are many types of, as I said,
doorways that a birth can occur in.
One of them, many of
them, they do not have to open into your
dimension.
You mean it's a pit
stop, right? We understand the
terminology to some extent. Yes. Does
that mean it's the pits?
In this way, recognize that there are
many different types of connections now
being formed, many different
associations of consciousness. In this
way, some degree of association to your
physiological reality may be appropriate
for those consciousnesses to experience
temporarily.
So that's the purpose of that one of
them. Okay. What's another?
It has to do with the choices that are
being made by the physiological entities
in your civilization to recognize
certain portions of themselves that they
then come to terms with after having
experienced such an interchange.
Is this well is it also a situation of
of um cooperating with um another
civilization where where are these
entities? Yes, in a sense. Yes. Again,
many different levels. All for the
purpose of allowing there to be a
blending on a different level that will
allow the changes that you wish to occur
in your civilization to be able to
occur. Does that mean they're
immaculately conceived? I mean just kind
of stepping in without any
Thank you. Thank you. Yeah.
Well, in a sense, but not really. What
you are calling the idea immaculate
conception still involves an
interchange. Perhaps not as you are understanding one
Perhaps not as you are understanding one
that we're talking about. Correct.
Although there is a physiological
activation of the cellular structure to
allow the cells to multiply into a
certain type of physiological being
which is not the way we know it. What's
the process they use
more rather than let us say immaculate
conception spontaneous activation of an
idea. It is giving energy to an idea
that then can transmute that energy into
a material
expression because the raw material is
there. That's how you have birth on your
planet. Right? More the idea it's more
although again we have been sharing the
understanding that it is of a sexual
nature so that you will have something
to relate to because there is an
interchange of physiological beings in
that way. But again there are many
differences and in a sense our
differences are more akin to that idea
than to what you are used to
different along the idea of thought
creating from idea energy energy
emotion energy. Are the physicalities
different between you and the females on
your planet? Do you mean would you
recognize a female to be a female and a
male to be a male? Yeah. Yes. For again
we are simply reflecting ourselves as
those polar expressions in order for the
interchange to take place in some
physiological level. But sure what are
the polar expressions of male and
female? I mean I know active passive but
is there more to that than than uh I
mean not so much not really obvious. It
is simply the idea that both
together
exemplify generally all the different
viewpoints that you can be within all
that is in
this particular universe. All that is
all that is in in this particular
universe is yes for there are other
universes where there is something other
than the idea you call male female.
Really? What other what? Oh, there are
triary arrangements
and again you cannot refer to them as
well what are they male or female? It
does not express itself that way. Well,
we have male, female and uh uh
right in that way that is still an
in that way that is still an
exemplification for you of an idea
expressing a blending of maleness and
femaleness. A so-called hermaphrodite in
a triad expressive universe would still
be a hermathrodite but not exemplifying
maleness or femaleness but the
personification of the triad.
So there are also different types of
hermaphrodite sure seems like it would make cruising
difficult. Okay. All right then. I don't
I don't really That is all right. That
is all right. Okay. Um
Okay. Thank you. Thank you for you.
Can we take this a hypothetical idea?
You can't take it anywhere you wish.
That a doctor. Okay. His wife had five
of these so-called other dimensional
children. Nice.
In the last about eight years. Okay.
Where have
these children are these children being
brought up somewhere else in a sense and
some of them may return? That's what I
think I'm asking you. You just said many
there are many connections being made
right now to help us with our
transformation. This is one of the ways
one of the connections that are being
made. These children are being
schooled in some way.
so to speak on our tourists. That is one
place on our what will they ever ar tourists?
on our what will they ever ar tourists?
Will these children ever be a will this
woman for example ever know her
children? Yes, she will. Yes. Perhaps
not as you think but yes but there will
be a connection if a connection because
she did allow herself to be yes. Are you
talking about also babies that that
boarded? What about babies? Some. Yes, some. Oh,
What about babies? Some. Yes, some. Oh,
I wasn't talking about. But aren't
babies that have been aborted in a sense
the same thing as uh to some degree? Not
always is that the case, but to some
degree? What? What's the question? The
idea that there are simply recognition
that certain consciousnesses only need
to experience a very short extension of
their consciousness into physical
materiality. So they will make an
agreement with one of your physiological
beings that does not desire a fullterm
birth. Sure. Thank you.
Sure. Thank you.
I was wondering if you could uh share
about uh arms. The back of arms. Is there any
uh arms. The back of arms. Is there any
symbolic uh back of arms? Yeah, back of
arms. Well, there's a front and there's a back
Well, there's a front and there's a back
and there's a side.
Well, maybe you could just tell me
generally arms. Arms.
How do they serve you?
Do they allow you to reach out and hold
things? Well, do they allow you a sense of
extension? A sense of remote
manipulation, remote
control, dexterity, creativity.
dexterity, creativity.
Do they not extend your
reach? Do they not form a type of
communication with what they
touch? Do they not also define quote
unquote your space?
Yeah. My question
uh came from a friend of mine told me
she had like some spots, not bumps, but
just spots that just appear in her arms.
And she said they don't bug her. Her
husband bugs her to go to the doctor. I
said maybe she'd go to the doctor. But
then today my arms are like I feel them
buzzing or some little things in the
back of my arms and I'm just like that.
You know the connection. We
he has no perception of the body or he
has the same perception of the body that
one has in sleep.
The next run down that takes about two
hours. The next one down.
The connection as we can perceive it at
this time seems to have something to do with
time seems to have something to do with
the idea of exploring a belief that says
you can have gaps in your
electromagnetic field. which is the same
thing in a way as
saying that you may feel or
believe that there are missing
components within your ability to
communicate to reach out me her or both
of us.
You may be empathizing. Okay.
Thank you. Yes. Um, would you tell me
why would you explain to me um when I
asked you about communicating with these
beings, why they'd be reflecting or why
my doing that would reflect a lot of my
personality? Because you are your own universe and
Because you are your own universe and
when you communicate with anything else,
you have to create your own version out
of what you are in order to experience
that interchange. So many spirit guides
and other levels of consciousness are
constantly doing their job by luring you
to more of yourself.
Because to interact with anything else
means you have to interact with your
self-created version of that something
else and that brings up more and more of
yourself to discover. And they're trying
to help me discover more of myself. They
are not trying. They are doing it. Oh,
thank you. like you the along that same
line. This one
this is a nice one. Spirit guide are
they not simply an extension of
ourselves? Yes and no.
They again do their job
unobtrusively. They can be represented
as other consciousness as other beings.
But the idea more often than not, not
that it cannot happen in more direct
aware communicative ways or
methodologies, the idea more often than
not will simply be that they lead you to
more of your own recognition of yourself
rather than direct experience of them.
Okay. I was just uh considering the
possibility that all our ownelves. Well, everything
that all our ownelves. Well, everything
is all of these other individuals
sitting with you in this room are you.
But you also recognize that they are
other consciousness as well. Spirit
guides have the same degree of reality.
They are their own beings and at the
same time they are all you and you are
them. Do they appear in the form that we
need to see them? Yes. More often than
not
you use I I think I've used the term
unless I'm mistaken. Unfoldment. We are
unfolding in a sense.
That's is that the same as evolving?
Yes. Can be also the same as remembering
more of who and what you are.
Remembering more. Okay. All right.
Peeling back the layers you have built,
the limitations, the levels
unfolding in vulnerability to all that
is
invol. Okay. It's beautiful.
So you a being essentially then just
keeps unfolding and unfolding and
unfolding. Creation is active, never
ends.
Well, it's difficult for me to get away
from the idea of they learn more than in
a sense, right? If you say so.
Well, isn't that something linear about
that or as like Well, that is simply
because you are doing it in a linear
universe. Learning more is simply
remembering more of all the different
levels upon which you already exist.
So, you essentially become more
expansive. You take in more of you
become more consciously.
You become more consciously. Yes.
Since you have decided to explore the
idea of limitation,
then you had to create the ability to
forget that you chose to limit yourself.
Otherwise, how could you experience
limitation, right? So the idea of now
integration rather than limitation is to
stop forgetting. I see.
So in a sense you you're a part of all
that is but in the unfoldment process
you become more a part of all that is in
a sense more aware of yourself as all
that is. Same thing. Yes. In a sense larger
is. Same thing. Yes. In a sense larger
too. In a sense. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
Yes. Yes. In a sense.
All of these symbols are valid. Act upon
them. If they inspire you, act upon
them. Thank you. Oh, thank you very much.
Thank you. Oh, thank you very much.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Um, could you talk to us
about multiple births in particular
identical twins? Many of them have had
many lives together. Many of them may be
counterparts of the same soul. There are
many different ideas that can be
exemplified by that idea. can be one
soul splitting itself in a sense into
counterpart selves for the experience of having a
selves for the experience of having a
direct and immediate reflection.
Could I have twin boys? Um, do you feel
so inclined?
Do I feel so inclined? He said he has.
He said, "Could I?" No, no, no. I do.
All right. And uh there seems to be a very
right. And uh there seems to be a very
close connection I have between myself
and one of these boys that exist. Are
you asking if you have been twins before
yourself? I don't even know what the
question is I'm going to ask now. Well,
that was one.
The answer is yes. Okay. You have taken
turns being each other's twins many
times. Triplets, too.
Triplets, too.
is is can you tell me why I seem to have
this psychic connection, this ability to
be able to communicate with why one
child of mine? Um I mean it's not
verbal, it's not over the telephone or
letters or anything. It just happens
because you are in love.
Understand that the idea of telepathy is
to
love. Telepathy is emotionally
activated. To love them is to know them.
Now it also simply represents a specific
connection that is being played out from
a last life with that particular
consciousness. It will equalize with the
other child as well when the timing
comes when you will all be
equalized when the idea is played out.
Thank you. Well, thank
you. Bashar you said that telepathy
is you say that again telepathy is while
in a
sense mentally let us say
mentally let us say
realized it is emotionally activated.
Many of you think oh telepathy oh cool
intellectual consciousness no
emotion but telepathy is actually
empathy in a sense. So the more we allow
ourselves to be open to feeling, the
more likely we are to be. Yes. To love
them is to know them. That is why you
know that people in love often share
each other's
thoughts because they vibrate with
integration, congruency on the same
wavelength, so to speak, and that comes
from unconditional love.
That is why our society for itself is
telepathic because we love each other
equally and
unconditionally. Not because we are
mental giants.
Sure. Why do people fall out of love
then when when they're they do not have
to. All they are doing is not allowing
themselves to recognize that perhaps to
begin with they simply did not allow
themselves to know what the relationship
was for rather than what they expected
it to be. Any relationship that changes
changes for the same reasons it was
created to allow you to experience what
you have chosen to experience in this
life. Therefore, when the relationship
changes, that does not mean you have to
fall out of love. You can recognize that
the relationship changes because of love
as
well. You follow me? Yes, I do. Thank
you. It simply may be that since your
society has quote unquote in the past
usually made a quote unquote
habit of putting expectations upon
relationships for what they think they
should be rather than allowing them to
be what they are. Then perhaps when the
relationship changes as it was going to
do according to the path you chose to be
then you simply in this way think you
have lost something so you imagine you
have fallen out of love. It is all
created from love. When you allow
yourself to know that, then the changes
that go on in relationships will all be
reflective of that love and not a loss
of it.
I see. That is simply the idea of
allowing everyone to be who and what
they are, not what you want them to be.
Thank you. Thank you.
Yes. Um I remember you speaking once about uh
Um I remember you speaking once about uh
appetite and making a distinction
between what the mind wanted to eat and
what the body wanted to eat. Hey, could
you clarify how to uh personally
recognize the difference?
It does not have to be so very complex
in that way. And you can also recognize
that if you are listening to your
so-called body consciousness section of
you section the idea will simply be a
recognition a cognition that the
vibrational food that represents the
vibration you are on will be what you
have the urge
for and the things that do not represent
your vibration you will not have an urge
for in that sense a natural urge so to
speak. If you find yourself with the
idea of going through the expression of
your negative ego, well, I want this, I
want that, regardless of how I know my
body feels about that idea. Then you are
not listening to your body
consciousness. You will recognize once
again, as we have said before, that if
you simply pay attention to yourself and
listen to yourself, treat yourself with
respect and unconditional love, you'll
know the difference automatically.
Okay, thanks. Are you better off to
listen to your body consciousness rather
than Again, it is not being better off.
If you find that what you want to
explore is the idea of struggling, then
in your terms, you are better off
listening to your negative ego. However,
if that is not what you prefer, then
listen to your body.
I want to
know. Remember that there is no need to
force yourselves to be
spiritual. You are
spirit. You are spirit. If you find that
your body
consciousness says that your body does
in fact need something to support the
belief system that you are, eat it. Do
not say, "Oh no, I cannot eat that meat.
I will not be spiritual."
If you truly are simply of a vibration
wherein you do not need the meat, you
will not have the urge for it. It is as
simple as that. It will not be a matter
of having to make a tough
decision. Relax into
yourselves. Love yourselves as
unconditionally as all that is does.
Why should you treat yourselves any less
than all that
is treats
you? You
exist. You always will. You are
eternal. Relax. You have all the time in
Relax. You have all the time in
creation. You create all the time in
creation that you need to be any idea
you want to be within a time
frame. At this timing, we will extend to
you our unconditional love and
energy. We thank you for your sharing of
the gift of your particular point of
view of all that is so that we may see
that many more ways that all that is has
of expressing itself within creation.
We thank you for teaching
us and we thank you for allowing us to
reflect to you that which you are in our
eyes. You are beautiful and we love you.
We are the sharing together that
continues forever. We bid you exciting
dream lives and life
lives and life
dreams. We bid you a fun and loving.
What do you think?